<Blog>

<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Friday    My dear wife was walking on her graduation day! Although the dude did not pronounce her name correctly, she managed to shake the older dude's hand and then raised her arms to show victory to her parents sitting among the crowd! As you know, no other students would even dare to do that. The would only bow to the guests and that's it! Yes, my wife is always full of life and joy. It was the day that marked another beginning of her life: a professional life as an Urban Designer! I recalled the day when she first came to NUS when we were living at the HDB flat. It was a bit hard for her to adjust to life in Singapore as compared to Hawaii, but after we managed to  urlLink get a place for ourselves  her energy skyrocketed. It's amazing how much she has improved in her professionalism. ConGRADUATION to you, dear MicroWife!   PS: The commencement ceremony at NUS did not seem sacred. In fact, it looked very mechanical and different from most ceremonies. Rani's dad was annoyed when he heard Majulah Singapura only played halfway! He said, "It was a big day for students, why not just play it until it finished, rather than sampling it?"      Saturday    We took a bus trip to Melaka with  urlLink Hasry Delima Express Bus  from Lavender-Kallang intersection. It costs SGD11 one way per head, relatively cheap knowing that it will take us halfway between Singapore and Kuala Lumpur. We arrived at 13:00 at the Melaka bus terminal and hired a taxi for RM10 to take us to  urlLink Baba House on Tun Tan Cheng Lock Street . Baba House is a historical shop house with 60 rooms inside a 200-year old structure. We managed to get one deluxe room for Rani's parents and one standard room for us lovebirds. I really have so much to say about Melaka so why don't you just  urlLink click here  or  urlLink here  to get a gist of it!    There will always be festival market going on Jalan Hang Jebat on Friday, Saturday and Sunday nights. You could get putu, grilled dried sotong, sugar cane juice, at half the cost you would have to pay in Singapore (while the taste quality will be doubled on every food you eat here!).       Sunday    We woke up around 0800 and ate breakfast at the Baba House hotel, free breakfast if you danced Macarena just before you checked-in. After we checked-out, we took a river boat tour (private boat tour, that is, at RM 50 for one hour!). Oh, you gotta see it to believe it! The government of Melaka has done an excellent job revitalizing the riverfront as well as the preservation of the key landmarks. After boat tour, we hired a taxi to eat at  urlLink Bibik Neo , an original peranakan restaurant with an excellent array of "asam pedas". Make sure you come here and order the kangkong belacan as well as three orders to Kerapu Asam Pedas. It ended up only costing us less than RM9 per person for such a friendly service. Oh by the way, we asked the Indian taxi driver to eat with us but he was full already and sat down to watch us eat the delicacies while having a modest lime juice.   We then took Metrobus Ekspres bus to Kuala Lumpur, leaving at 1230 and arriving at Hentian Pudu around 1600 (the last 1/2 kilometer took us about 30 minutes to finish because the parking arrangement inside the basement was awkward, not allowing our 45 seater bus to zip in through quickly!). We then took a taxi for RM20 (what a rip off!) to get to KLCC where Danny and Sisca Tobing had been waiting for us the outdoor terrace of Dome cafe. For your information, Danny and Sisca just got married in May 2003 and now Sisca is 2 month pregnant. I have known Sisca for over 15 years - went to the same middle and high schools). Danny was a charter pilot who took over a business from his father dealing in marine and offshore drilling services. They both just moved to KL from Indonesia/Singapore and have loved every minute of it! Rani and I felt that they made an excellent choice of making a nice home in Ampang, on top a hill overlooking the Petronas tower from about 5 km away. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I had lunch with Azlin in NUS Arts Canteen. As usual, I was having Japanese Salmon Teriyaki. I personally think that the Japanese Food Stall is the best in NUS! Azlin gave me a pack of  urlLink Aroma Coffee  that Henry brought from Bandung. This is a very unique coffee that is stored and aged for 8 years to eliminate the acidity and increase the robustness / body. Even now, Mr. Widya is still using firewood to roast the coffee for two hours to full perfection, without any additive or chemicals. We gave some sampler to our neighbours. Even Mike Willie who has espresso machine complimented this Coffee. I think Kopi Aroma is the best coffee in the world!  I also met with Prima after lunch and we ended up having some coffee with JW in Engineering Canteen.   Later in the evening, while Mas Indi was having dinner with Minister Jayakumar, Minister Susilo Bambang Yudhoyono and the whole US-Asean guys in Shangri-La Hotel, I was struggling in CASA Lab in NUS trying to make ArcGIS Editing works without crashing. On the other corner Simon was playing WarCraft in his SGI Computer!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      To answer Fay's question:   "And Rani, your sudden craving for nJ ice cream kebetulan ke or because you baru baca pasal BnJ on my website? Hehe. Hope to see you guys next week. :)"   No, Fay, I did not tell Mas Indi about my desire for Ice Cream. In fact, I was expecting Movenpick! Somehow miracle does happen. After we chatted about BnJ, Mas Indi later came home bringing a pint of Cherry Garcia without me asking for it. And by now one pint has already run thin.  This morning, while Mas Indi was doing putting and driving in Raffles Country Club with the big bosses, I was having breakfast with my former boss (my present foster dad),  urlLink Mr. Jeremy Wagstaff  in Borders Bistro Orchard Road. He was bragging about his new Palm Tungsten with bright screen nice resolution and all wi-fi capability (which he could not manage to make it work in Borders Bistro). I also introduce myself to  urlLink Ms. Sari Sudarsono , a very kind petite young lady who works for LA Times Indonesia. I ended up buying books on learning chinese characters and chinese dictionary with hanyu pinyin.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday night Mas Indi brought me one pint of  urlLink Ben and Jerry’s Ice Cream Cherry Garcia ! He just knows what and when to give pleasant surprise for me. I think Ben and Jerry’s have a bolder taste, a funkier type of ice cream, whereas  urlLink Movenpick ice cream  (my favorite is Maple Walnut) has a smoother taste, a classier type.   urlLink Indonesia is mentioned in Ben and Jerry's website . Is this an example of fair trade? Do the vanilla farmers in Indonesia receive appropriate reward?  This morning I accompanied Mas Indi practicing golf in  urlLink Temasek Club  driving range. Too bad he just realized now how comfortable it is to practice near our house. Now it is too late because the driving range is going to be demolished pretty soon to build a new road connecting Queensway to AYE, right in front of our estate.  After breakfast we went to Shangri-La hotel and met up with Fanny Bahar and David Hutagalung.  Askar and I continued to walk to Plaza Singapore to get Pizza for brunch. I have been longing for pizza for quite a long time. The Pizza at Pasta Mania has great cheese and seafood topping but I don’t like the crust. I think the crust is too crispy like crackers. I don’t like  urlLink Pizza Hut  crust either, because it is too bread like. I prefer the pizza crust in  urlLink Papa John’s ,  urlLink California Pizza Kitchen , or  urlLink Domino’s  which has rubbery crust and tasty.  We continued to walk to  urlLink Sonata Dance Supplies  where I inquired about the price of ballet equipment. I would need to spend at least $80 to buy those equipments. Then we went to Times bookshop where I bought “ urlLink Stupid White Men ” by Michael Moore and “ urlLink Why Do People Hate America ” by Sardar and Davies.  Then I went to Specialist Shopping Center to find out the cost for Adult Ballet class, which turned out to be cheaper then YMCA. I think I will enroll to this class in August. Having class once a week will be enough.  I went home after that and Askar followed to Hang Jebat to seek shelter from the rain. I ended up cooking chicken porridge for him. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      As mentioned right below, we want to accompany Karyn to fulfill her desire of Thai Food at  urlLink Lotus Thai Restaurant  which we consider the best Thai restaurant in Singapore. It is located in Tanjong Pagar Murray Terrace and has the authentic Thai taste and great spiciness. The Sea Food Tom Yam is to die for. We also recommend the Lemongrass Salad and Mango Salad. Chicken With Basil and Pad Thai are also our favorites. Don't forget to order Sweet Tapioca for dessert!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday Uman showed me the website of his son,  urlLink Aidan Prasojo , who was born June 10th, 2003.  The name Aidan originated from Celtic word which means  the little fire that gives warmth to the family . Such a beautiful name! Indi and I will consider that name for our future son.   We have several other choices for names. For girls:  Lalita  (to be natural),  Lani  (Hawaiian -  the sky or heaven),  Aina  (Hawaiian - the earth or motherland),  Moana  (Hawaiian). For boys:  Kamma  (as in Kamma Sutra),  Neruda  (from the Poet in the movie Il Postino),  Keoni  (Hawaiian),  Vidhya  (Indian of Widya). Any suggestion for other names, please do not hesitate to post us some advice by  urlLink writing in our guestbook .  It is nice to know that we have such a great neighbour! I bumped into Karyn this morning (and Sacha the dog!) and she complimented my mutton tongseng curry! We will arrange a cookout sometime this week to cook mutton tongseng, spinach masala, and chapatti in my place. Karyn as a pregnant lady desires to go to Lotus Thai restaurant next week. I think Indi and I should take care of it.  I had lunch in NUS Engineering Canteen with  urlLink Simon Zhuang , Freddy, and  urlLink Antonio Ismael  who happened to be in Singapore all the way from Bali. Too bad JW couldn't join us. We had a great discussion on Architecture for the Poor. We hope we all can develop some kind of cooperation in the future for the sake of Indonesian urban poors. Now, I am going to cook Spinach Masala with Brown Rice for dinner. Mas Indi is working overtime tonight for  urlLink US-ASEAN Busines Council  Board Meeting and I want to surprise him with masala. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Rani has been feeling very guilty for the past several days after watching Japan Hour on ChannelNews Asia: re: SUSHI. Last night in the quiet moment just before we fell asleep she suddenly woke up and said, "Doggone it! I should have dipped the fish topping first into the soy souce! Head first!". I was surprised by her attention to details especially in dealing with delicacies. PS: For those of you who'd seen her eat Sushi would know that she'll chow down on the fish first!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      We all received an email from Yodhi, marking the beginning of his adventure in the youngest country in the world, Timor Leste. Here's what he wrote:   Halo semua, Saya sudah tiba di Dili, Timor Leste, jam 12 WIT dg selamat. Trus langsung kerja setengah hari. Sementara (2-3 hari) menginap di kamar no. XX di Hotel Turismo (hotel antik & "rustic" gaya Portugal) yg menghadap laut biru bersih di  pantai pesisir utara dekat rumah Uskup Belo (Av dos Direitos Humanos, Lecidere, Dili). Yg paling asik, sempat mampir Taman Makam Santa Cruz. FYI Hotel Turismo Telpon: +670 390 323 180 dag, Yodhi 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      masindi tes..
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This all happened on Sunday 3 August 2003   Our highly nutty and extremely amateur groovy music group just got a quasi-funky name. After contemplating all morning when I stunk up the toilet and meandering around the house driving Rani's lovely cousins (Nana and Ria) confused during their 4-day long visit, I chose to name our group as "Kelompok KARIB Gembira"; well, take it or leave it, we don't have much ideas other than utilizing the spirit our Indonesian bureaucratic abbreviation euphoria and that's how the name came into existence. The name makes a good sense because we have Jeng Kiki on saxophone, Askar on vocal, Rani on piano, me on conga/trumpet and Budiman on djembe. During the audition session at Indonesian Embassy for a  urlLink Panggung Gembira in Singapore , we managed to "express" our apparent "spontaneity" to a board of jury, mainly comprised of NTU and NUS students who are highly capable of organizing this marvelous event. Our composition is based on a common people's music, a famous latin American song titled Moliendo Cafe (also became famous in Indonesia as Kopi Dangdut) and we created this musical performance with a nice blend of salsa/mambo rhythm transitioning into semi-dangdut ambiance. The music began with a potent "call of the hand-drums" followed by a solid foundation on salsa/mambo rhythm based on sax and piano harmony with hand-drums in the background, which then opened up a new aura with a tacet by Askar's tenor voice driving encompassing his love of the latin and dangdut grooves. In the middle we inserted a solo drumming by Budiman on djembe followed by a crisp and quick harmony of sax and trumpet (it was a hard transition from slapping the skin to kissing the mouthpiece with an embouchre). If you were there, you would have danced just like those girls in jilbab/hijab who suddenly became crazy of Askar's Sundanese-Latino charm. Kiki, as usual, was very calm and  capable of delivering such a rich and melodious output on her Selmer sax! Honestly, not only did we smoke it big time but we also made the jury believe that we should be givent he best points among other groups of highly capable Indonesian musicians in town. Without further ado, let me present "Kelompok KARIB Gembira"on 9 September 2003 at Victoria Theatre!  urlLink See you there  ! 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Lebaran to everybody!  Bapak and Ibu Hindro came to visit us to celebrate hari raya.  Yesterday we took them to Geylang Night Market along with Askar. We had Otak Otak, Pulot Bakar (a kind of Lemper with shrimp filling), Dendeng, Chicken Shawarma (a really good one), Peanut cake (but I like better Cheese-Chocolate Martabak Manis from Bandung), Halal lasagna, and of course TURKISH ICE CREAM! It was totally crowded there, and it was difficult to move around! People spilled over to the road. We met Dewi and Yusoff who were used to be in Bumi Band. I have never seen them in Traditional Malay attire before. They mentioned to us that they were no longer in Bumi Band.  As for today, friends kept coming to our place to greet and celebrate Lebaran. Mak Tuti prepared chicken opor and meatball sambal, accompanied with beef-lung rendang that she brought from Padang. As dessert, we all shared big basket of Sumatran Durian which was brought from the forest in Anai Valley.  We played music all day long and jamming, and we never stop eating. Daniel brought his guitar and played everything from jazz to blues. Kiki joined the jam session with her saxophone, while Ramses watched her in admiration. Adi could not stop singing. Later, Leonard joined and hit the piano playing blues and jazz. Geraldine helped Adi sang Chinese songs. Later that day, Askar and Feca also visited us and helped us finish the meal.  BTW have you checked out our new personal name card? We made one using a hand-carved chinese seal of our family name as the logo, made in Melaka during our last trip with Kiki, Dimas and Yati. here it is!    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Mas Indi and I, along with Dimas, Adi, Jay broke the fast in Geylang Night Market at S-11 Food Court. I had Nasi Goreng Ikan Asin with Baby Sotong Asam Manis. Later we regretted having dinner, because we found a wide variety of foodstalls along the way to Joo Chiat.  We closed our trip with a big scoop of  urlLink Turkish Ice Cream , vanilla and chocolate flavour, made from goat milk and all natural ingredients. The ice cream has a very unique sticky texture and does not have aftertaste like other ice creams with preservatives.  I was so happy to find Fresh Melinjo in  urlLink Geylang Serai Night Market , now that I will be able to cook real Sayur Asam with Melinjo. I was surprised that they also sell Fresh Jengkol, but I wouldnt buy it! I don't want my husband to avoid me if I have bad "Jengkol" breath. Mas Indi is not a kind of guy who likes smelly food. He does not even like durian! That is why I haven't eaten Durian ever since I got married :>  On our way home in MRT, we met Andi and Fahmi, our two architect friends.  Yesterday Mas Indi and I had dinner with Leonard and Melissa in our favorite restaurant:  urlLink Lotus Thai . We had a great discussion about things, from volunteerism to Melissa's initiative in countering child trafficking and to work on Palestinian-Israeli peace workshop simulation. It intrigued us to start to get ourselves involved in NGO activities in Singapore. I have never known any NGO in Singapore that deals with developing countries, which is one of my main interest, until now I know what  urlLink UNIFEM  does.  Leonard parked his car right in front of the Himalayan restaurant. On our way home, the chef of Himalaya persuaded us to visit his restaurant. I asked him if he cooks things with saffron, and I particularly was interested in Saffron Ice Cream. He then offered me to make a special Saffron Ice Cream if I come and eat at his restaurant. He gave me his phone number so that I could call him before coming to his restaurant and he would make sure that my order would be ready. How sweet! The menu looked good too. We plan to try Himalaya North Indian and Nepali restaurant next time!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yep yep yep we have been absent from blognews since AUGUST! man, it has been 4 months since the last time we've updated this page!  A lot of things has been going on in four months!  ---  1. Rani got a new job at  urlLink JTC Corporation   urlLink one-north  department.  2. We and KARIB Gembira (Happy Friendship) performed successfully in  urlLink Indonesia Arts Festival  in Victoria Theater in front of 1000 people.  3. We, Kiki, Dimas and Yati went to Malacca for Deepavali Holiday and we indulged ourselves with peranakan food just before Ramadan Month started. You can see Malacca  urlLink our photo album here !  4. Our dearest friend Micky Goh passed away last month :  ---  Today we went for audition for Detrash event in orchard for next month. After practising for only one night, we finally settled with two songs: - A Waltz-Bossa Overjoyed - An A-Capella  urlLink Soleram (DOWNLOADABLE!)  and Kroncong Kemayoran We think it's more important that we are having fun while singing these songs, with whatever audition result comes out later!  Wish us luck!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Okay okay, we have been so busy and unable to update this news.  First, we will be performing in orchard, again, this wednesday. Here's the flyer            Last sunday's performance hasn't been so successful, partly because of the rain. We sincerely hope that this week performance will be better than before.  This morning Mas Indi saved a snail from the pathway and into the grass, to prevent the snail being stepped on to his death. I was touched by his simple yet cute action!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I meant to show you the Stone Seal which we got from Malaka. Here it is:   It writes: su ma quan, a transliteration of our family name Soemardjan, and it means "A Powerful Horse". It took the carver one hour to get to the appropriate chinese characters.  We both have been addicted to  urlLink fotografer.net  lately. It is a website where we can upload our photographic works and have other members comment on it. Please check out  urlLink Indi's fotografer gallery  and  urlLink Rani's fotografer gallery .
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is Rani speaking. I really love and appreciate the time staying at home and being together with my husband. We just stayed at home for two straight days during chinese new year. Partly because of the rain, partly because we want to do our spring cleaning, and partly because we want to finish up our DVD collection (including all the special features). Time seemed to stop moving, it is really cool to be able to detach ourselves from the fast-life in Singapore.   We went to visit Mike and Karyn Willie who were supposed to have their daughter born on that day. We haven't seen them for a long time because we were really busy! I wish I have more spare time to visit our close friends and pay more attention to them.  We went to Jaggi's on Saturday, our favorite Indian Restaurant. I had the best and the freshest Gulab Jamun I've ever had!  On Sunday we met Aaron on the bus stop, when we were coming home from Tanglin Halt Market. We were thinking of having a trip to Vietnam together, to get ourselves exposed to Vietnamese people and culture, and to take pictures of the people!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today I felt that Indi and I can use a new nickname "The Most Misunderstood Couple".. Why? Because I observe that both of us had experienced many times being misunderstood by people. For example, people think I am arrogant, whereas in reality I am shy and timid!  As for Indi, he is the man with sincere curiousity and is inquisitive in nature. He loves to question things and never take things for granted. But people misunderstood him as somebody who craves attention, because he ask a lot of questions!   Perhaps here's where the cultural clash came about. Having lived in the US for a long time made him a man who is not afraid to ask questions. I guess Indonesians find this really weird and in many cases, feel offended. To be honest I feel angry at the people who misunderstand Indi. But I'd rather put my energy into somewhere more fruitful rather than channeling my anger.   Anyway, we take it as a lesson to be more careful in communicating our ideas. But we will never let other people judge us! :> 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yodhi told me that I was on TV, RCTI News to be exact, when they were covering Inul's concert in Singapore! Viva Inul!
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today... hmm what did we do today? Oh yes, at  9:00am we went to have fish congee and cakwe for breakfast at Alexandra Village and then went to get economy haircuts for only 10 SGD per head at  urlLink QB  inside IKEA building. We walked back home soon after and I did my weekly chores: Ironing our work clothes, while Rani worked on her application for UK Urban Design Scholarship that she's been wanting to submit.  Later in the afternoon at 3:00pm we went to my colleague Fauzia's party to celebrate her sister's 60th birthday. Her sister, Sharifah Noor, is now a resident of Den Haag and works for the UN International Crime Court (?). It was kinda big family reunion for them and we were very privileged to be a part of them. After all, Fauzia is a great person to work with and she does have a heart of gold. She is like family to us!  She lives in the Marine Parade town area where PM Goh Chok Tong's political strength is based out of. The area is just so lively and you could find every single detail virtually spotless.  At 6:00pm we left the party and walked toward  urlLink Marine Parade Community Centre  and guess who we saw at the lobby surrounded by hysterical folks? INUL DARATISTA! :) Yes sireee.... Inul had just had a small concert with about 700 people and it was indeed her first time shaking her bon-bon in Temasek. Rani soon handed her camera to me and started getting closer to Inul. Inul was indeed very radiant in her red tight outfit showing her typical energetic gestures. After the public photo sessions, Inul was escorted to the van and was surprised to see a young woman already waiting for her in the van. She was crying and begging to come with Inul in the van but the bodyguards wasn't able to persuade her to come out of the van until Inul approached her and gave her a hug. The young woman was crying and Inul comforted her like a mother to a child. Inul really knows how to show her love to all. She has been mystified as a Hero in the eyes of every young woman in Indonesia. Inul symbolizes success and pure modesty in every way (although her outfit does not always seem to say so). It was a heart-breaking moment to witness it as Rani kept telling me to take journalistic photographs of them but I was just unable to do so. I just snapped the camera but my mind just couldn't capture that moment. It seemed so unreal that a person like Inul was so open and forgiving to that young woman. We thought she was perhaps a maid working in Singapore and if so, then she must have been the luckiest person among all fans to experience such a warm hug from the Heroine.  Enough said... here is Rani's picture with Inul and the heart-breaking moment with a fan:             Written by Indi
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Various interesting psychological test you can find in   urlLink BBC - Science Human Body - Psychology Tests Website !! I just did "What Sex is Your Brain?" It says that my brain is a Male Brain... o my god!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My old monitor finally rested in peace and now I am using AOC, a Taiwan made, 17" CRT non-flat. The LCD ones are too narrow/thin for my big desk. It won't look good at all so I decided to stay with CRT technology instead.  My wife has kindly reminded me to write daily and I think this can be quite fun! See you tomorrow...
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday night we had a great big family dinner at  urlLink Jumbo Seafood Restaurant  in Riverside Point! Attendees are: Indradi Soemardjan and me, Gita Wirjawan, Yasmin Wiryawan, Gian Wirjawan, Bu Iik, Pak Maman, Mbak Yuni and Mas Ricky, Prita Delia, and My Mum. we had Chili Crab and Black Pepper Crab!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After being resigtered in Friendster.com for quite some time I finally managed to have 60 names on my list of friends. If you are a member of Friendster.com and view it, you can click  urlLink Friendster - Indi's Friends . Alternatively, you may also ask me to invite you to be my friend.   My wife is coaching me on blogging although I think I am already an expert on snogging.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last saturday (31 January) we held a lunch gathering at home inviting the members of fotografer.net Singapore Chapter. Full coverage can be found  urlLink here  (in indonesian language). We made Tongseng (Javanese Mutton Curry) and Gado Gado (boiled vegetable salad with peanut sauce). Earlier that morning, I found a green caterpillar munching my lime tree away. Initially I wanted to just kill this little monster. But, the little animal was so cute, that all the photographers who came for the lunch started to take out their camera and tried to take macro shot of that poor little guy. At the end of the day, I decided to adopt this little caterpillar in order to save my lime tree, and fed the little guy with lime leaves from Pierre's lime tree.  At 6pm we all continued to walk through the abandoned HDB land to take the bus to orchard road. We intended to take pictures of  urlLink Chingay parade .  Indi and I arrived just before seven and found a nice spot in front of Mandarin hotel where we met Adi (he brought us a bottle of Bailey's from airport). It is a nice spot because our view was not blocked by the chair stage (those chair stages were intended for people who pay for the seat). We waited, and waited, and the parade which was supposed to start at 7pm did not start until 8pm. And later we found out that the parade participants were only performing in front of the chair stages! When the parade participants passed in front of us, they were only, well, walking by and waving at us. But they did not perform their full stunt for us. This is disappointing. As Masindi told me, even the parade in NYC does not treat non-paying-member-of-audience differently. I guess I wouldn't want to go to Chingay parade anymore. At 9pm we gave up and continued to take MRT to City Hall and had dinner with Adi's Sri Lankan friends in Chinese-Thai Restaurant at the Capitol Building.  In the morning, I checked out Cattie, our little caterpillar. She's so cute when she is eating, she eats the lime leaf just like eating pop corn. And after finishing one leaf, she took a break and poo. Her poo is in the shape of small balls with 1.5 milimeter diameter. I can't believe that this little thing manages to eat leaf that is about her body size.  On Sunday we invited some friends to enjoy Mutton Curry, Sambal Telur, and Salad. We plan to put the pictures and story here, but I haven't figured out where I should store the picture to link back to this blog. And it is late, we are going to sleep now. Tomorrow is not public holiday anymore (I wish it is still holiday!)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Our third day started with a drive to Bukit Tinggi to do shopping! We went to Aisha Craft Shop near Pasar where the ladies were excited to buy traditional fabrics and some clothes. The owner, Tante Nacha, was really hospitable. She served us all her home made peanut cake and capuccino. Sure enough we ended up doing a massive shopping.  We continued to go to Pasar, where Ibu Wies went to buy Dadiah (traditional yogurt made from Ox Milk and stored in bamboo) and Ampyang (traditional cereal made from rice pounded flat). Mas Indi had a chance to tried Pisang Bakar (flatten roasted banana with sugar coated shredded coconut). On the way to the car, we visited General Election Committee Center to see the preparation for the upcoming election. People there seems to be very busy folding the gigantic ballot sheets.  We had lunch in Kedai Nasi Kapau recommended by Tante Nacha. She promise that she will pay the lunch if we were able to prove that the Nasi Kapau served there is not up to our taste. Well, it turned out to be really good that we did not mind paying the lunch ourselves. I personally enjoyed the Jengko Curry most.  We continued to drive northward to Harau Valley which is as beautiful as the Grand Canyon or the Yosemite Valley. Natural ponds were formed by the water streams that falls from the top of the valley. Here's one picture that we took in one of the ponds.         There is one spot in the valley which was called "Echo" where we can stand there and scream out and echo will be repeated on the other end of the valley.  We took a break in Echo Lodge located in between two high canyon. The scenery is simply amazing, and this lodge highly respects its environment. A lot of european artists rent a room there for few weeks simply to enjoy the scenery and to do their artistic works such as painting.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The second day in Minang starts with a stroll along the Anai golf course, which is located in a very unique setting : in the middle of tropical jungle. The scenery was breathtaking - there are layers and layers of mountains and valleys! There are a lot of monkeys that will throw back the out-of-bound golf balls. Wild boars dig holes along the fairway to look for worm. The fairway constantly needs repair and maintenance due to wild boar attack. We end our walk with a great breakfast in the clubhouse: Fried Noodle, Noodle Soup, and the most delicious oxtail soup (needs a pinch more salt).  We drove northward to Paya Kumbuh to Minang Cultural Museum, which is a replica of traditional Minang Village with its traditional carving and grass covered roof. The museum had a great collection of old photos, in which we were able to find my Incik (great grandmother) and my Oma (grandma) when they were very young. The museum also rented out traditional minang dress which we can wear and take pictures with. Finally, under the pressure of Pak Hindro, Bu Tuti, and Bu Wies, Mas Indi and I rented traditional minang wedding dress. Since we have done our Javanese wedding rites, now is our chance to fulfil my Minang origin by wearing traditional Minang dress.         We then continued to Pak Datuk Restaurant where we had lunch and I had a great Jengkol Curry!  The lunch made all of us very sleepy and we slept in our car while the ladies (Bu Tuti, Bu Wies, and Tante Paula) went shopping and buying some Minang craftwork. We took a break in Novotel coffee shop and I had Kopi Talua, which is a glass of black coffee mixed with raw eggs. The result is like Capuccinno, with froth on top and creamy texture from the beaten egg. Too bad it was raining heavily and we could not make our way to Jam Gadang.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We arrived in the land of Minangkabau this morning from Batam. The whole family picked us up from the airport and we drove 60km southward to get to Jembatan Akar. On the way we stopped at Restoran Keluarga and had a great Minang lunch. Fish Head Curry, and I managed to eat the curry fish eyeballs!  Jembatan Akar, as the name suggested, is basically a bridge made from the root of Banyan Tree. Two banyan trees are located across the river in front of each other, and a bridge is made by tying the root of those trees. After one-hundred years, the bridge become like this:         The river below the bridge is really clean and a lot of people swim there, jumping right from the bridge.  Later that night we arrived in the villa in Anai and had a great dinner of green duck curry. It's really spicy and I am sure the cook was using a dash of marijuana to make all of us addicted to the curry!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mas Indi, Leonard, and I had breakfast in Little India in a South Indian restaurant with Melissa Kwee. We were introduced to David Cohen, from  urlLink Berkeley War Crimes Studies Center  who is in charge for East Timor Human Rights tribunal. For this special breakfast occassion, Mas Indi specially put on his UN East Timor polo shirt :> We were all chatting about development problems in Indonesia and East Timor, on which Melissa is working with  urlLink UNIFEM Singapore .  Later I went out to work (yes indeed, on Sunday), settle some things for Charrette preparation. The project team had a meeting with the consultants in Alphabet Bar Amara Hotel (again, on Sunday).  That night, we were invited to have dinner and jam session in Gita's residence, with Bob James and his group! Harvey Mason was also there! Too bad, they were all too tired to play that night after dinner. Nevertheless, Bruno, Hari, Mario, and mas Gita showed up their skills, and Daniel joined them with his guitar.  This is my picture with Bob James      
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Read  urlLink this article from TODAY .  Let me put it simply:  As women are forced now to assume "men's role" (working to earn money to provide livelihood of the family)  It is now time for men to be forced to assume "women's role" (to have a share in doing household / domestic work, and rearing the children)!  Simply, there should be equally distributed tasks, benefits, advantages and disadvantages for both men and women. Let men and women have equal share of salary distribution, leave, benefits, etc. There should be a level playing field between the two genders.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Straits Times put on the headline of " urlLink Radical moves to help new mums - MARCH 3, 2004 ". My quick comment is that all the measures taken are all focused on woman as the only person who is responsible in making babies and taking care of them. No emphasis are given to push equal role between father and mother. The division of labor: men as sole breadwinner and women as "mothers" (in classical terms), is still there. The proposed policies are all focused on the women.  Perhaps those policies, (i.e. maternity leave) will aggravate the position of the potential mothers, in the sense that they will be less desired by the employers.  I personally think the policies are put on the wrong emphasis. As I have discussed with Pierre few days back, it is easy to encourage people to make more babies:    Emphasise on equal role between men and women. Men should be encouraged to take more role in child's upbringing. Let 'unusual situation' such as having the woman as breadwinner and stay-at-home husband be happened. The policies must be focused on the long-term effect, not just at 'maternity' portion.  Less working hours, for both men and women, to ensure more quality time with family. Europeans work for 36-40 hours per week, having saturday and sunday off.  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Muslim WakeUp! Main  seems to be an interesting site. I haven't had a chance to really read it, but it seems that it's a quite open-minded Islamic site, quite liberal. This is my first impression because there is an article in the website quoting Scott Siraj al-Haqq Kugle, who argues that Islam do not condemn homosexuality. I'll read more about this website later.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sudara2,  You are welcome to see these links below. We thought you might be interested to see our first photo studio session with our beloved Canon 300D (gotta have it!):      urlLink Mesra with our tools    urlLink Playing with feelings    urlLink Grooving    urlLink Playing each other's tool    urlLink Peeping    urlLink Blowing hard    urlLink Creating spatial depth     *Photographed by our dear friend  urlLink Judhi Prasetyo   Kepareng, IndRani  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink indrani-news   April 1, 2004 was the day when my microwife turned 26 years of age. And it was 5:30 in the morning when I woke her up asking for a glass of water. At first she grumbled at me for being too lazy to get it myself, but then when she opened our bedroom door there it was... a big brown box addressed to her. Her eyes were wide open and she was terribly curious what was inside the big brown box.  In no time, she was already ripping it out here and there. She saw the word Hohner somewhere inside the box and by then she knew it already that an Accordion was ready to be squeezed in the early waking hours.         Yes, siree... I managed to hide it from her for sometime and up until now I still refuse to tell her where and how I got it.  An immaculate marble red  urlLink  Hohner Bravo III  with 96 bass buttons made in Germany, just the way Rani likes it! :)             Treble: 37 keys, three sets of reeds  seven registers with two repeats  Tuning: Continental  Bass: 96 buttons, three registers  Colors: Black or Red Pearl  Weight: 19 lbs.  Size: 7.25” deep by 17.25” high  Keyboard: 17.5”    What could be better than giving my dearest microwife with anything but a music instrument that will last a lifetime! Like I said to her.... "Squeeze a little more music into your life".... and that's a wrap.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hi. This is Rani working from Indi's computer at his office.  This weekend has been really exciting! My mom is here on a workshop with Ang Mo Kio hospital. The Tobings are also in Singapore, with the little Priscilla! We wanted to take them to Lotus Thai Restaurant, but it was closed on Saturday evening :  I can say that this is the best peranakan food I have ever tried in Singapore. But still, nothing can beat Peranakan Food in Malaka. I really enjoyed the cuttlefish in black sauce, I even drink away the sauce! I met the chef, and he told me the recipe, which is very easy to make:  First, marinade the cuttlefish pieces in tamarind liquid overnight. Do not throw away the ink sac. Then, saute the prepared cuttlefish with Kecap Manis, shredded lemongrass, and some salt. I think this is the right time to break the cuttlefish ink into the wok.  I will try this recipe sometime. The chef told me that he does not use onion or garlic. I am sure enough onion or garlic will make the cuttlefish taste even more fabulous!  After the Blue Ginger, we went to Tanjong Pagar Plaza and buy some fruits, and dried vegetable snack (which I don't really like, because it has lost the taste and texture). We continued to go to Katong Shopping Centre to look for speaker repairer. Guess what did we find at the basement of the shopping centre, a Ghostbuster offering his service! I didn't expect that this thing prevails in singapore, and even more so, Commercialised! I mean this guy locates himself inside a shopping mall!  We walked down to Katong Laksa 49, which is located side by side to Katong Laksa 328. Katong Laksa 49 is well reputed and even get covered by the New York Times! However, i was not really impressed by the taste. The flavour is uneven, and sometimes a bit bland.  We continued to Esplanade to borrow some DVD. We found Swinging Bach, which contains a major performance by Bobby McFerrin singing Bach pieces. He was really amazing, i guess the best vocalist of all time! In Esplanade we met Meng, our friend who we haven't seen for a quite a long time. She is 6 months pregnant, but she and her husband decided to live in the boat, even when the baby is born! what an exciting life, to live in the boat!  On Sunday morning we had Frog Porridge in ChinaTown with mas Gita and mbak Yasmin, along with Tompi and Harry, and also Gian who was having his fourth golf tournament with adults. The frog porridge was really tasty! But the service is bad, perhaps because we don't know how to communicate with them, because none of them speaks english. We then continue to drive down to East Coast, to Nico's studio. There, Mas Gita and Harry did jam session on acoustic piano and upright bass.  All afternoon my mom brought guests to our house and we spent the whole afternoon hosting the guests from South Sulawesi. Later in the evening we went to the concert in Botanical garden with Joyceline and her husband. We drove down using their new Land Rover, which is too clean as a four by four vehicle. We met Chris and Matt who are having their photographic exhibition on the Middle earth later this week.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tahukan kamu bahwa Askar di Jkt sempat lihat Rani sedang bincang2 dengan KD. Mungkin itu disorot kamera tivi pas Fay sedang interview KD. Mungkin Fay ada di tivi juga. Canggih!  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I met the friendly bus driver when I boarded 191 bus from CSC to Hang Jebat. Apparently he still remembers me as a frequent rider of his bus on my way home. He insisted that i need not pay for the bus fare! I'm touched by his friendliness, and we started to chat a bit! 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This weekend  urlLink Fay Mahdzan  come to Singapore to watch Krisdayanti's concert. The concert organizer offered Fay an opportunity for interview, and they would give free concert tix provided Fay publishes the interview in her website. Who would reject such a good offer! Indi and I decided to tag along and introduce ourselves as Fay's photographer. At the end, Fay, Santa, me and Indi got the chance to chat up close with Krisdayanti! The concert was fantastic, and I have to give my commendation to Erwin Gutawa's orchestra for the great music (despite the electricity glitches)!. See the photo below: Santa, Fay, KD, and me. Indi took the picture. I use this blog as a chance to try out the Photoblog service offered by  urlLink Hello   urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If I am undefined by the mainstream, then I have to set out to define myself, and present myself to existence.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lemme just quote a paragraph from  urlLink Absolut Badalu  on the place called home.   ,Indonesia isn't without flaws either. The endless problems with discriminations, pollutions, poverty, corruption, hipocrisy, political turmoil, education, etc. (still a long list to go). But what makes a difference is the people. They are so warm, welcoming, nice, friendly. The landscape is gorgeous. So many untouched beaches around. And I can do whatever I want. I can do more significant things. There is always a way to reach the comfort level if you fight hard (really hard, I mean!). Indonesia is considered "a developing country" (according to the western term) and it's growing. There are spaces for changes. I'd like to grow along with it. Europe is too established. No more real challenges to encounter.   I would like to agree with him on this one.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Suatu hari, kita merasa sangat kepengen makan lidah asap.. Tapi, dimana bisa belinya sebab di singapur orang gak makan lidah?  Walhasil pergilah kita ke pasar Tekka yg terkenal cukup lengkap. Untungnya mereka di sana jual lidah tapi masih mentah! Nah gimana caranya supaya lidah itu dimasak jadi lidah asap? Yang jelas apartemen kita gak mungkin ada tempat untuk ngasepin lidah, atau tetangga nanti pada protes!  Jadi, ini yang kita kerjakan, gampang aja..  Bahan2: -Lidah (terserah berapa banyak) -Air secukupnya -Garam rada banyak -Gula utk ngimbangin garam -Merica yang banyak (kalau peppercorn lebih asoy lagi) -Rempah2 macam basil, oregano, thyme dan kawan2nya.. -Bawang putih secukupnya.. -Liquid Smoke (Hickory) Concentrate secukupnya, barang 3-5 sdm untuk aroma asap.. -Pressure cooker  Masukkan semua bahan2 ke pressure cooker dan masak di atas api sedang selama sejam atau lebih. Makin lama makin lembut lidahnya! Abis itu, keluarkan lidah dari cooker dan kupas kulit luar lidah. Buang kulitnya, terus potong2 tipis lidahnya. Simpan lidah bareng dengan air rebusannya selama semalam dua malam di lemari pendingin, terus tiriskan, dan bisa langsung digoreng pake blueband.. Untuk dimakan dengan roti atau nasi atau kentang, terserah!..  Air rebusannya bisa dipake untuk bikin sup.. Misalnya sup tomat atau sup buntut..!  Enjoy!  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After months of searching, we finally bought cow tongue. It is quite xpensive, but we managed to bargain with the seller, reducing the price from $18 to $15 perkilo. We'll cook cow tongue stew tonight, and we will invite Wicak to come & enjoy the delicacy!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To continue with our previous posting of "mediocre service" in singapore, somehow this week we were all cursed with getting bad service all the time.  First, when we were having pizza hut in Jurong East. The waiter forgot to get his notebook to take down our orders, and even that, he still repeat our orders three times, and never get it completely right! Then when the meals came, he did not put it in front of us. He just put the food on the edge of the table and expceted us to pass on the plate to the right person. Then when we were running out of water, he did not immediately fill out our glass until we ask him to do so.  Second time, when we were having lunch in Cafe Galilee, Jurong East Regional Library. First, the food is expensive, relative to the quality and the quantity of the servings. Second, the service is damn slow. It is so slow, so that Indi decided to cancel his order. And the response of the waitress was, "Oh you can't cancel your order, we have made it, and it will be ready in no time. Please understand, we are having a lot of orders right now, that is why your thing takes a long time". Oh Cmon! if you can't handle the orders, don't set up a cafe! What a lame excuse for bad service..."having too many orders"??? Better close business!  And third, in a taxi. We were so tired working overtime, so we decided to take a cab home. When we arrived, we paid the fare accordingly. Few seconds later, we decided to ask for receipt. To our surprise, the cabbie started to grumble, "Next time, ha, when you want receipt you better say it quickly! I almost press the button to cancel your receipt, because you take so long to ask for it!" Wah, amazing isn't it? A provider of service who get angry and blamed the customer?  Hence me, being too tired, freaked out immediately. I blasted out at him, roughly like this, "Don't you talk like that to your customer! What is wrong with asking the receipt only later? What a bad service you are providing, you should never blame a customer, because customer is king!". Of course i added some swearwords to it too. But, i mean, what is so difficult of printing a receipt? Moreover, the problem is so trivial, that you would not need to be angry at your customer! What a pathetic service. I wished I took down the cab number so I can put it on the web for everyone to see.   What is wrong with people here, why is it so difficult to provide a good and courteous service? we are always amazed to find good service here, because it is a bit rare in here.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last weekend we experienced two contrasting treatments as customer.   The first instance is in Akashi Japanese Restaurant, Citylink Mall. It's an upper-middle-end type of restaurant ($20-40 perperson), so we kinda expect the service to be up to par, or to have Japanese kind of friendliness and politeness. To our surprise, the service turned out to be really crappy. All the girls who works there, seems to be very depressed with their job. They do not provide service with smile. Smile, is a basic thing that should absolutely be available in service industry. When we enter the door, they screamed some kind of Japanese word that I presume it means "welcome!". However, it was not done with any smile, friendly gesture, or eye contact. When we sat and start to flip through the menu, they were not responding well to questions we posed on the menu items. When the food were served they were rushing to put the trays on the table. They spilled the green tea on the floor and did not even apologize. We had to ask them to mop the floor, and when they do, they did not even ask for permission.  It is not that they are not doing their job, but it seems that they just want to get their job done and over as soon as possible. They don't have the sensitivity and friendliness towards their customer. For this kind of upper-end restaurant, I would expect the service to be more than fulfilling orders. However, we were disappointed to see that the service was... only mediocre. Even though the food served were high quality, we were not compelled to return to this place due to its bad service.  On the other hand, Maison de Fontaine was a reflection of excellent service. And it's more affordable compared to other French restaurant in Singapore! The food was excellent, I can say, it was work of arts. I was having pan-seared escalope of foie gras with tomato timbale, port wine, & balsamic reduction as entree, continued with grilled beef tenderloin (160y) with sauce bearnaise & pot gratin (which tastes great, but i am not really into the sauce bearnaise), and was closed with freshly baked apple tart with vanilla ice cream. Indi was having baked oysters w/ cheese (really tastes great!), whole spring chicken w/ madeira wine sauce (the chicken was amazingly lean, fat-free), and for dessert he was having creme brulle with berries. We came to the restaurant a bit late at night, and we stayed there until past the closing hour. Amazingly, the restaurant manager did not try to kick us out of the restaurant even though we stayed there until half an hour after the closing hour. The manager was really courteous. We are looking forward to having another great dinner there!
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My sister-in-law Siska wrote:   Isn't it amazing how little kids are so fascinated by the littlest things that barely catch our attention? Every chance he has, my 3-year-old son takes the time to stop and look at flowers, trees, butterflies, ants, spiders, grass, birds... even some funny-looking rocks.   To encourage his communication skills, I often ask him about the color, size, and other simple facts about the objects that he sees. I also ask him to greet the critters he sees. I don't know why I do this, but it has the most pleasant effect on him. He smiles whenever he says, "Hello, ants!" or "Good morning, birds!" or "Hello cute butterfly". It doesn't upset him at all that the critters don't greet him back, but rather fly or crawl away and mind their own business.  A genuine friendliness is shown in his face. He's happy and content in the friendly little world that he created. As he turns his attention to other things -- although he seems oblivious to what just happened -- his smile and good mood linger.   I tried to understand his simple yet profound happiness, to put words that could explain how and why and what I find amazing in such a naive mind of a child. Maybe it's the openess of the mind; the simplicity it craves, away from the wants, the plans, the worries that clutter our daily lives; maybe it's the feeling that we get when we accept things the way they are and be grateful for them, such feeling we get when we take the time to stop and greet God's creations... or maybe, it's just good to be friendly.   As I was sitting in my car waiting for the stop sign, an orange butterfly fluttered across my windshield. My son wasn't there in the backseat to point at it and greet it, so I say, "hello, butterfly". I know I didn't look cute talking to a bug, but who cares, it made me feel good.   -Siska/Juli 2004  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I found  urlLink Haloumi cheese  in the grocery, and the reciple on its wrapping tempted me to give it a try. Besides, I need to increase my daily intake of calcium for my baby. Hence, today I cook this Grilled Haloumi Salad with Hicory Smoke Bbq Sauce.  Unwrap Haloumi and rinse with water (I found out later that Haloumi is quite salty, and this can be overcome by immersing it in milk for a while, if needed). Season the cheese with pepper and herbs, set aside. Don't put salt, since the cheese is already quite salty!  As for the grilled salad, prepare any kind of vegetable that can be grilled. In this case I use asparagus and carrot.  Lightly smear the pan with butter or olive oil, and grill the veggies until it becomes more tender, season with a pinch of salt, pepper and herbs.   Then, grill the cheese, until it becomes golden brown. Don't add salt. The cheese won't melt, instead, the outer skin will become a bit crispy. The inside part of the cheese is rubbery yet spongy, really, a unique texture. It is really rich!  Meanwhile, prepare the sauce (or you can use any other kind of salad sauce / bbq sauce).  In a saucepan, combine tomato ketchup, red wine, herbs, salt, sugar, and chopped garlic and onion. Add  urlLink liquid smoke  for hickory smoke flavor. Simmer until garlic and onion becomes tender. When necessary, add a bit of water in order not burn the sauce.  Combine the two, and serve! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Actually we've been thinking of some names ever before this little guy is conceived. One thing for sure, it has to have a hawaiian element in it (that's where we got engaged). Lemme just put down some of the names we've been thinking.    Aina (Hawaiian): The earth / motherland  Lani (Hawaiian): The sky / heaven  Noia (?): Bliss / the state of bliss  Neruda: The famous poet, of course! or alternatively, Kundera?  Aidan: Little fire that brings warmth to the family  Others, like,&nbsp;Hawaiian name Moana, Keoni, Ikaika, or Indian ones like Vidhya, Kamma   Any advice? please! please! suggest some names by writing it down in the Comments section below. We'd like to expand our name alternatives. Perhaps we'll give you a Surprise when the name you suggested is being selected later on next year, God's willing!  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We haven't put in our blog that Rani is pregnant. Last week, we checked it using test pack after our Melaka Trip and then went to general practitioner to confirm it. Finally we went to a gynae recommended by Tata in  urlLink Thomson Medical Center , Dr. T.C. Chang. We had our first-time examination using USG today and found out that the baby is only 5 1/2 week old. The gestational sac is only 1cm wide. What a magical experience to have a new living creature emerging from human body!  urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Where and when is human sense of survival being limited to total obedience? (i.e. You have to obey us in order to survive!)  Where and when is human sense of survival forcing people to be entrepreneurial and creative? (i.e. We have to overcome the situation using this, this, and this in order to survive)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I find Singapore similar to a theme park. The path you walk is designated, not allowing you to deviate. The activities are well contained in specified spaces and places. The "system" are laid down for the people "to ride on a specified track", just like "It's A Small World" ride in Disneyland. Everything happens in a highly predictable manner. Most of the time people's appetites are satisfied and sometimes people are made to be excited a bit. Everything looks fine and dandy in Singapore, the great big theme park. Or more appropriately, Singapore the great big Truman Show world?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Great architects are not democratic, they're authoritarian. They exert themselves in a such insensitive way to their surrounding Perhaps that's why Chandigarh failed, Brasilia failed, and  urlLink Koolhaas's Seattle Public Library  also doesn't do very well. Not to forget the EMP Building, also in Seattle, which performs very poorly and does not fit its urban context.  It's easy to sense and feel if one architecture piece is 'democratic' or 'authoritarian'. Just sense it, and feel it, particularly through the scale of the architecture and the circulation path. In my opinion, the Esplanade is one example of an authoritarian architecture, where the scale of the space is never right, and I felt forced to walk within its specified pedestrian path. It is not a compelling piece of architecture.  Hence, does 'iconic' have to be 'authoritarian'? And does architecture reflect a (conscious / unconscious) political intention behind it?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i think nobody wants to get jiggy tonight but us.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday morning i saw three baby birds lying dead on the grassy ground near jurong east mrt station. They were very young, the feathers haven't even grown. Apparently they fell from their nest, which was built at the edge of mrt platform, 10 meters above the ground. Death, what a sad scene to start my day.  By this evening, the dead birds are no longer there. Maybe stray cats ate them. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am so disappointed by the way the the local media described the cause of the 29 june blackout. A short sentence that continously run in ChannelNewsAsia titlebar said: "Blackout in most area caused by disrupted gas supply from Indonesia".  The next day, a friend who works in energy sector informed me that indeed the gas comes from indonesia, however the blackout was caused by tripped valve in the receiving side, that is, in the Singapore side.  I decided to check the info to my friend who works in the StraitsTimes  Hi, what caused the blackout?  Valve on gas pipeline tripped n backup systm faild 2 work  The info i got frm word of mouzh is that the tripped valve is in singapore. However, news blames indonesian disruption of gas supply. i feel news hasn't objectively presented the whole pic, that the blackout is also partly singapore's mistake, not just indonesia's. It's grossly oversimplified  well its called politics  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>