<Blog>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, look at the time - perhaps the pub's open...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         
[ This is hey, v4.4 ]
[ Ending is "la plume de ma tante est prez de le chaise de ma tante - " ]
[ Recipients : croche  ]
you know you can post comments? :P
[ hey croche -- groovy ]

2:56pm ~ > caz
[ This is hey, v4.4 ]
[ Ending is "Spartacus! Boriiis!! I'll give *you* woof-woof! " ]
[ Recipients : croche  ]
tell me what a sad fucker I am etc
[ hey croche -- groovy ]

   Message from croche on alf2.tcd.ie (ttypb) [Thu Nov 30 14:56:26 2000] ...
                             /-------------------\                             
                             | couldn't be arsed |
                             | :p                |
                             \-------------------/
                        Would you like to feel my croche
 

2:56pm ~ > 
   Message from croche on alf2.tcd.ie (ttypb) [Thu Nov 30 14:56:39 2000] ...
                           /-----------------------\                           
                           | nah, I think you know |
                           \-----------------------/
                        Would you like to feel my croche
   
 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      They'd been threatening it for a while but this morning it finally happened: they've taken away the G4.  They  want it in the office, as if it's  their  computer or something...well I claim squatters' rights! I can't play Quake on a frikkin' iBook! It's both slow and exceedingly gey, especially when the hard disk spins down after 20 seconds. I'll try get a pic of it up soon - shame to waste the little digital cam they just happen to have lying around...  
OK, so I don't deserve to complain :-) (Did I mention the other G3 Powerbook?)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nnnngh! Go to fucking bed! askdjfhadhflaskfglad
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm...tough quiz. Tomorrow night's one might be more promising; if not there's always Thursday night in my old stomping ground of Scruffy's :-)  
And I'll be drinking coke all the way, baby. Poo' ickle Dave is, like, sick or something, but then that's to be expected from someone who, according to  urlLink Jas Bligh , has "the immune system of a six-month-old baby". I miss having  urlLink Jas  around to cheer me up at times like this. Er, not.
  
Oh, whingemoanbitchcomplain. That's better.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I've deleted all the test postings saying "narf" and other such inspired things, and this my fr1st ps0t proper. The current layout is very much subject to change, but the basic font/colour scheme is sort of close to the (planned) look of lesinge.org, if and when it arrives at  urlLink csd.dot-ie.com/~dave/lesinge . Inspired, isn't it? Wait 'til you see what I'll be doing with php random number generators and .css files... (cue maniacal laughter)  
Off to pub now to win  another  bottle of whiskey at the table quiz. Mammy and Daddy would be so proud to know their son's education hasn't gone to waste.

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It took me ages to find the train and Frankfurt airport is huuuuge and it took me even longer to find the Aer Lingus desk to check in once I got to the airport and nothing was open and I was really early and bored out my skull 'cos I've no fucking walkman any more and then once I got on the plane there was a little kid who screamed all the way from Frankfurt to Dublin and then we got kicked off the plane temporarily in Dublin so they could clean it or something before we went on to Cork and who did I see in the one tiny section of Dublin airport that was still open only  urlLink Donal , which was very strange and cool, 'specially as it was his bday yesterday too and then we got back on the plane and the little bastard was still on it and he screamed for 10 mins before getting hoarse and falling asleep - result - and then we landed in Cork and my bag was one of the first out and then I met the parents who took me...HOME. I've been homesick all along and never realised it. And Cinco is so incredibly small compared to Freddie...  
Considering squandering my inheritance on a laptop. Now all I want is a Palm Vx and an MZ-R70 to go with it :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's cold, I'm hungry, there's so much to do/see tonight - all in all a perfect recipe for NOT sitting in front of a computer for the rest of the afternoon.  
If I don't post tomorrow, Happy Christmas etc  
Here's  urlLink something amusing .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        
-----Original Message----- From: Claire Swire Sent: 07 December 2000 16:12 To: Chait, Bradley Subject: RE: 
  
I hadn't swallowed for years but yours was yum and very good for me too! 
Apparently it's very good conditioner for your hair too...getting a funny picture 
in my head, giggling out loud and now having to explain to Dave 
  
what's so funny!  
 urlLink Claire Swire : legend in her own lunchtime
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Wankometer  goes through a webpage and, based on the amount of managerial-speak (to whit, "management wank") contained therein, gives it a score.  urlLink http://www.att.com/business/  scored an off-the scale 11 on the Wankometer: can you beat this? If so, let us know; post a comment! (!!!!!!)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I like my electronic choonz so I was very pleased indeed to find  urlLink this   (Flash + patience/fast connection req'd)  and  urlLink this  on  urlLink memepool . Take a look. Oooh! And new additions to  urlLink The Editing Room !
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Takedown.com  is a site devoted to Kevin Mitnick, one of the more notorious crackers in the US, and how he was caught. For the more nerdy among you, you can even watch recordings  urlLink like this  of his online sessions. Fascinating stuff, 'specially when he makes typos :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tidied up the weblog archive section, sorta. Do I really have to use php (through the Blogger interface - eek!) just to get the archive listing on this page?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Those little comment links at the top are there to be used by the way - just mind you don't do what  this guy  did. Just for him, gey.css has been renamed :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some people have  urlLink way too much time on their hands . Actually, the  urlLink entire site  is like this. Cool!  
Just by the by, if you're bored out of your skull and looking for weird shit on the web to keep you occupied, go to Memepool or NTK (links left, under "Daily Surf").   
In other news, I finally found  urlLink Viva  on the TV in the flat, hidden at channel 41, so I now have 4 channels I can watch: Viva,  urlLink Viva Zwei ,  urlLink MTV  and  urlLink CNN . And yes, I  was  bored enough to type out all these URLs...

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Arrr!  urlLink AAARRRRR!!!  A little coding spree has resulted in stage one of the Skins project being initiated! Stage two will involve cookies and other madness, but this is impressive enough for now...top.inc is getting mightily messy indeed...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two new CSS files to be randomly picked, plus the new bit up on the top right there, which lets you know which one it is. Still no content though...  
And if you're unlucky enough to get gey.css, it's obviously a sign of some sort. The computer never lies.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quick note re: the page - currently in the middle of struggling with some  very  simple DHTML to tidy up the left side over there. Funny thing is: I ripped the code from  urlLink an older page I used to have on CSD , but amazingly it refuses to work now (might put up the test page later if you're good). Ffs like...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, what do you do when offered a free gaff when your flatmates go away for a week? Say: "Oh no, I'll look after the dog, it's no problem". The social ramifications (or lack thereof) dawned on me last night. Big Scary Dog&trade; is guaranteed to scare some people off who might otherwise have dropped up, and it also means no late nights for Dave cos the fucking pooch has to be walked!  And  he snores! Fucker actually kept me awake last night despite being at the other end of the hall from my door!  
They could have easily taken him in the jeep (yes, really) too. Hate that dog so much...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Monday December 11th, between the hours of 12:00am and 12:30am in Scruffy's Irish Pub, Karlstr. 8, 76133 Karslruhe, Germany, my Sony MZ-R30 MD Walkman was nicked from my coat. I am not impressed. If I ever find the cunt who did it I will break a 14-year stretch of never even having punched someone in anger,  and then some .  
That is all.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, so long as we know what browser NOT to use in future...  
Quiet few days...well not really, but I'm not telling you lot. Which is obviously the point of a weblog. This is what happens when Mr. Cagey decides to document his already mediocre enough life on the web, I suppose. Hey! At least I'm posting more than  urlLink Cliph!  :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      /me wonders why iCab won't post blogs...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Off to MC the Scruffy's quiz now. Yes, you heard correctly. Any and all disputes, comments and/or queries pertaining to tonight's quiz are to be directed to yours truly. Should be fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FINALLY!  
See that lovely bit of CSS-file-switching code in the previous posting? In seeking to be all cool and self referential I posted it up there but forgot to tweak it so the browser wouldn't actually read it - ie replace the square brackets on the last line with &lt; and &gt; (read the source of this bit and you'll understand).  
Visitors for the last 48 hours have been informed that http://csd.dot-ie.com/~dave/lesinge/css/".$cssfile.".css couldn't be found...I do apologise for my utter lameness.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right: site now changes colour every hour.
  
  
$selection = array("red","green","blue");
$seed=date(G);
$cssfile=$selection[($seed%3)];
print "\n&lt;link rel=stylesheet type=text/css href=css/".$cssfile.".css&gt;\n";
   
More colours to come soon
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Very pretty site , from the man who brought you  urlLink Praystation . 
 Flash 4 req'd 

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well slap me sideways and call me a wanker,  just got a mail from a good friend/sworn enemy whom I hadn't heard from in a good (some would say great) three-and-a-half years. Jaysus, etc. Always a weird feeling when something from the past (aka Watergrasshill) crawls out from underneath a stone and bites your ankles. Dammit, I have to think of something to reply with now...  
 Dear Fuckhead, 
You never visit me and the kids any more... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why does this page look so dark on a PC in comparison to a Mac? Nnnnnnngh. Here we go again with the stylesheet fiddling; so glad I didn't start on the complicated stuff *pats self on back* - laziness DOES pay off :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Craziness at  urlLink Starshot  part deux: I get back from pub, and Freddy (the dog) is not in his usual place in the hall, but in by the bathroom door. The place smells even more strongly of hash, but I settle down in the living room with laptop anyway. 2 minutes later, Kai appears from the bathroom (ah so that's why Freddy was there...). 3 minutes thereafter, Tina appears too. From the bathroom. Ah. So this is what it feels like to be Mal...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bright-eyed and bushy-tailed after 15 or so hours in bed, I wander out into a deserted flat, into the living room and the unmistakeable bouquet of hash. Seems the health freaks aren't so straight-laced after all. But for the fact that I announced my departure to bed at 6 yesterday I might have been invited. I imagine my German gets better when stoned - or maybe I just  imagine  it gets better...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good grief, captain - there are some Germans with senses of humour too! Had  urlLink two psychotic Bavarians  in my room last night. As I type, they're whizzing back to Munich in Tanja's little Fiesta, doubtless doing 80mph in 3rd gear. Just beware of crazy Hamburgers...  
Nothing like a little in-joke to alienate the rest of my, er,  readership...note to Will and Jim: Andrea's a big fan of  urlLink AggSpeak  - we have a disciple. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I could tell people about last night, but then I'd have to kill them. Currently comatose and not looking forward to going out tonight. At all. But I have to. But I don't want to. Nnngh! Irreconcileable concepts....overload...can't....take....*KABLOOIE*
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Physics of pain  
2 weeks from Friday and then total freedom for 2 months! Plans include a trip to the land of tulips and clogs, although not for a tulip/clog appreciation field study, let me tell you. 
  
I might also find myself on an Alp somewhere, a plank of wood/composite anchored to my feet, speeding towards an impact with an immovable object (a ski-instructor called J&uuml;rgen, for example) at a force of &#181;mg (sin A) Newtons, where &#181; is friction, or lack thereof; A is the angle of incline of said Alp, m = my mass (minus blood shed en route) and g = 9.81ms -2 . Hey, Applied Maths might have been the "seventh subject" of my Leaving Cert, but I remembered some stuff, dammit! Now, knowing the coefficient of restitution of my jawbone is required to calculate how far I will fly when J&uuml;rgen takes a swing at me because he was chatting up two blondes when yours truly ploughed into him. This in turn will give my take-off velocity u and angle B, which, in conjunction with A above, will allow us to work out exactly where I will land/where the rescue team can pick me up: - u (sin B) t - &#189;g (sin A) t 2 , you know? I need to go lie down now.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mummy, what does "kernel panic" mean?  
Finally brought my new baby back into the shop to get that missing 64MB of RAM dealt with. Laptop was still in standby mode so I nearly had a heart-attack when this jolly fellow in a big red lab-coat flipped it upside-down and started screwing the access panel off. He ignored my plainitive squeaks of protest naturally and handed it back to me all of 30 seconds later. Probably could have done it myself; I felt like one of those people who bring their computer, monitor, mouse and printer all back to the shop because they got an error message saying the modem wasn't connected properly... Unfortunate upshot of this noticeable increase in speed (Windows reboots faster than ever before) is that Linux isn't so happy. Ah, sod it; I wanted Debian anyway :-)   
Also got the most bog-standard bag possible for the princely sum of IRP 32. It carries the laptop, cordless mouse + receiver and power adaptor + cables... just ; if I try cram a PC card in there it's gonna explode. Probably, like.

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been busy. Site has a few new little tweaks. I've been devouring books since Christmas: Andy McNab,  Remote Control ; Flann O'Brien,  The Best Of Myles  and  The Dalkey Archive ; Bill Bryson,  Made in America  and Raymond Chandler,  The Big Sleep . And I still have L.A. Confidential and some other one whose name I've forgotten to go through - great stuff.  And  I've installed Mandrake 7.2 on the Omnibook  and  I'm starting to r00l a little more at UT  and  I won the legendary Scruffy's pub quiz last Thursday and got  plastered  on the subsequent whiskey...  
And you expect me to sit down and do a blog entry daily as well? Gtf!  
Links:  urlLink Limmy.com ,  urlLink TER's take on Castaway ,  urlLink "Hentai" Helena Kim .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This article  on Slashdot about a new  urlLink informant system  in North Carolina schools, designed to weed out "dangerous" kids, led me in turn to  urlLink this story . That's it - I'm  never  going to the US...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink \´\´3 0\´\´n j00  
 ("we own you", for the perplexed). 
  
And those are only media companies! Can you name all of  urlLink Mitsubishi's  products, for example? (btw, take a look at the source code of the Mitsubishi page, right down at the bottom - Hi Mum!)
  
 Update:   urlLink answer to Mitsubishi question  and an apparently rather famous  urlLink article about the  urlLink Zaibatsu , or Japanese super-corporations. This is good shit, people! Read!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once I sorted out some teeny-tiny security problems, such as having a version of  urlLink this ,  urlLink LeSinge.org  was finally deemed worthy enough of hosting, meaning no more  urlLink  http://csd.dot-ie.com/~dave/lesinge ...unless you want to, like...
 
  
Message from jas@matrix on ttyq8 at 16:56 ...
          +------------------------------------------------------+
          |where in this new page to you acknowledge my brillance|
          +------------------------------------------------------+
EOF
  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink Hi Mum!  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There is a direct correlation between the lack of posts and my having UT to play.
  
Managed to read Enigma by Robert Harris in one go last night, from 12-6am. 
It's a good yarn, better
written if maybe quite as much fun as Cryptonomicon, another Enigma/Cryptography/Bletchley Park saga
by Neal Stephenson.
  
I also have some mystifying bruises on my legs after the weekend. Just thought I'd
 mention that too.
  Met  urlLink this guy  at a party on Saturday.
Apparently .de domains are quite easy/cheap to get...alas, 
 urlLink mine's taken .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder why my laptop only has 64MB of RAM rather than the advertised 128MB? Can't believe I have to bring the fucker back to the shop tomorrow and give more abuse. You could argue that the comp was running satisfactorily fast with its 64MB, and I never would have noticed had I not gone snooping around the System Monitor and subsequently HP's own diagnostic program -  but that's not the point! . I may not need it now but in a year's time when I want to run Photoshop 7 (or just X-Windows!) I'm going to suffer  then .  
Besides, I paid for 128MB so all that's moot. Thought I'd rant regardless.
  
Oh, and  urlLink Cliph moved  and I may soon be getting that long lusted-after DNS hosting. And the laptop problem will be sorted eventually so I'm basically happy in cyberspace. Just don't ask me about college.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm sitting on  urlLink one of these . Bouncing, too. They're right: it  is  therapeutic!  
*boingaboingaboingaboingaboinga*
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I got it. It's heavy and lacks a network card or any decent software whatsoever,  but it's MINE!  *hug*
  
It has a cool little set of buttons on the forward edge which allows you to play CDs even when the rest of the machine is on standby so, yeah, it's an oversized discman too. Unreal Tournament runs like a dream; I've already got that familiar neck cramp from sitting in the same frozen position (w/ sniper rifle - *TAK*) for too long.
  
Jim doesn't know it yet but he's going to be sending me all manner of software/utils/games, 'cos I've got 9ish gigs to fill and I can't play UT  all  day...or can I?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How was your weekend? Mine was a non-stop rollercoaster of alcohol, new friends and old enemies (not mine, thankfully). I learned (and then forgot) how to say cheers in  Kazakhstani and Croatian on respective nights. Then, last night I watched one person (who really should have known better) get very drunk and start antagonising one of  the  most hypersensitive people on the planet, and then a third person almost losing the rag trying to stop the first two from fighting...god forgive her but she's a very determined little girl... Meanwhile the rest of the table had to just sit back and enjoy the show. 
 You Know Who You Are, and I bet you all had worse hangovers than I did, ha!
  
And in other news: 
 urlLink http://www.google.com/search?q=grarg 
 Funny the way an old nick hangs around long after you've ditched it. I even went and put a giant link back to this page on  urlLink grarg.freeshell.org . style="font-size:100px" - aaarrr.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's amazing how many people go and do  urlLink all   urlLink out   urlLink essays  when they post blogs. Who do they think is reading this shit? Who do  I  think is reading  this  shit? Absolutely nobody. Hits may or may not improve if/when  urlLink Mr. Dalton  finds time to stick lesinge.org into that little httpd_conf file deep in the bowels of  urlLink this server . Until then, it's a bit of a 4-person audience....hi  urlLink Andrea, Tanja ,  urlLink Aidan ,  urlLink Cliph ...*sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm. Fixed that table width problem. 
And yes, it  was  that simple..  
...although not before; cluttered code is bad  
Short post 
Long bar -----------------------------------> 
Well 'ard 
Bed now
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *gurgle*...so  urlLink shiiineeyyy ...gaze ye mortals upon yon .pdf file and tremble ye in ph33r...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        
Thu 11 12:07AM [lesinge] =>> mv index.php3 elsewhere.php3 
Thu 11 12:07AM [lesinge] =>> mv blog.php3 index.php3 
Thu 11 12:08AM [lesinge] =>> chmod o+r * 
   
There: that's my front page  urlLink problem  solved! 
  
It's a bit annoying that I always have to write a minimum amount in these entries, or else the little nested table in which each entry sits won't fill out to the right and everything ends up looking arseways...which is an accurate description of how this page generally looks in IE. Is Netscape whore mise und stolz darauf. All IE-only people can go  urlLink here . Pssst! Mike! NS 4.5 looks at your page and laughs!  Laughs , I say!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink My pal   urlLink Jim  is getting a Powerbook. Tax free. While not an Apple fan in any  urlLink strong  sense, I do realise that a 500MHz G3 would pound a 700MHz PIII into the ground. But that's offset by the weight, the shite battery life and the general lack of easily available (read: bootleggable) software. This will be the source of friendly debates for many months to come, involving some or all of  urlLink these words . Yes, Dave, linking to your own pages  is  sad.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink TMB  has got herself into some real  urlLink hot water  this time. Very frightening article, all the same...
  
 
...what happens when the overly sensitive turn their attention to the Web? Will the Web become as diluted as our local dailies? At least broadcast and print journalists have the benefit of company lawyers and funding to provide a defense. What of the lone online writer, who has to bear the brunt of the frivolous lawsuit?  

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blast and buggery! I've been looking around at some other blogs in the last couple of days, mainly the ones linked from one  urlLink tomcosgrave.com , and I come across  urlLink Kitsch Bitch . Nice page; click the "about" link and notice her use and, in particular, spelling of the term "verbal  urlLink diahorrea " (sic). Oh, the shame...what must you have thought of me?
  
Sic(k) isn't the word. So now I have to change this page's title. To  verbal diahorrea (sic) . Obviously.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ordered Omnibook. Yay! Tomorrow we go looking for a mouse and The Matrix on DVD and all will be complete. Then I install UT and bye-bye college. Sing Hallelujah, brothers!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy shit. If you have Netscape and IE on your comp, fire up whichever of them isn't on, and then go to  urlLink http://www.w3.org/Style/CSS/ , the World Wide Web Consortium's offical page on all things style-related. Note the differences? If even the W3C are allowing effectively different pages for different browsers, what hope have the rest of us?
  
IE 5.5 PC: red box on left 
IE 5.0 Mac: red box hovers (rather groovily) on right 
NS 6.0 PC: red box on right, obscuring text 
NS 4.5 Mac: no red box at all!  
Looks like we're back to the old  //--> hide from old browsers  days...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        
Message from  urlLink cliph @ urlLink csd.dot-ie.com  on ttyp5 at 00:41 ...
                              ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~                              
                              "  urlLink helena  links us! "
                              "  urlLink helena  links us! "
                              ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
EOF
  


     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Remember that Dell (see link below)? Well suck on  urlLink this .  And  they have a shop just down the road from me! Tomorrow I hope to walk in there and come back out clutching (for the benefit of those who didn't hit the link) a HP Omnibook: PIII 700MHz, 128MB RAM, 10GB HD, 14.1" screen...and an 8x DVD-ROM drive...for barely over IRP 2000. Oh yea, my pretties. Network cards can be bought later, Windows in English can be re-installed when I go home and I can put up with the keyboard, dammit! I just wanna watch The Matrix!
  
And that wan  urlLink helena  off  urlLink netsoc  linked here too. So I may as well return the compliment. /me waves. Honestly, the things I do for a better  urlLink PageRank ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Drinking, sleeping, socialising, shopping and generally experiencing real life has led me to neglect my poor weblog. I think it's significant that the last one I posted was on my first day back in Ireland, and that this will be my last before Germany. I fly out from Dublin at 7am tomorrow. Good news is that I may finally be getting that  urlLink laptop , the conclusion of a mission begun over 2 years ago and interrupted by failure of a year and a summer spent in Tesco's. So we're happy-ish. 
  
Ok, so I'm homesick! I wanna stay here! *whiiine* - the Dell'll keep me warm though :-)
  
Auf Wiederbloggen
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       5104  
5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 5104 
  
Got my credit card PIN. Happy.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A Pome for James  
*ahem* 
 
Oh James of the shitting-the-pants pool stance 
And more gel than a garage floor 
Oh how we'll miss your Chandler dance 
Though it won't stop us showing you the door 
  
So, that's one less person I have to beat in pool/darts... Seriously though, he will be missed; Scruffy's loss is the  urlLink Darby's  gain. Plus, now I have a further reason to go home for a week or two during the holidays. Amsterdam, snowboarding, home, job: if I pull all this off I'll be some sort of genius :-)
  
Some things I never want to hear ever again, ever:
 
 "Ich bin so schoen, ich bin so toll, ich bin der Anton aus Tirol!"
 "Heeeeeyyyyy baby! (ooh! ah!) I wanna knooowwww, if you'll be my girl!"
 "Halloooooooooo!"
 
 Breakin' the law! Breakin' the law! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Of course, I could just be lazy...  
...and leave the layout like this. We'll have to see how good/bad it looks in Netscape first.  
Rod over at  urlLink The Editing Room  has two new abridged scripts. But  before  you read  urlLink Star Wars: A New Hope  and  urlLink The Empire Strikes Back , I recommend you look at the  urlLink Phantom Menace  script first, so as to fully appreciate lines such as:   
 (Alec Guiness) 
          "Mark.  Go to Yoda. He will be quirky 
          and entertaining.  He will also teach 
          you how to use your high number of 
          Midichlorians.. oops, Lucas didn't shit 
          that idea out yet. I meant he will show 
          you the ways of camera tricks and wire 
          stunts."
  
In other news, it's been snowing like a bastard in Karlsruhe for the last 24 hours.  Fasching  (German equivalent of Mardi Gras) is reaching its pulsating, throbbing climax - expecting much craziness on Tuesday. I have a nice big cold. Played Liam "The Hustler" Tyers at pool today: I won the first game and the last game and he won the seven in between. Oh, and Karlsruhe's most glam couple is once again on hiatus. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Spring cleaning  
As you can see, I've done some pruning of the layout. For a start I need a decently composed CSS file and maybe a simple little DHTML drop-down menu, which would give me a lot more space. And then a few applets and lots and lots of Flash...but nothing too complicated :-P
  
And there still won't be graphics! Or Slashdot headlines! Deal with it!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Okay, my turn  
Another meme to be propagated (see next post down). I'm just hanging on the coat-tails of 
 urlLink these   urlLink two  as per usual.
 
  
1. What was the first record you owned (bought for you)? 
The Mini-Pops LP 
 
2. What was the first record you ever bought? 
Went halves with my sister on Now (That's What I Call Music) 12 
 
3. If you had someone of the opposite sex coming over and you wanted to impress them, which cds would you hide? 
Too many to list all of them: highlights include D:Ream On Vol. 1, Best of Jimmy Somerville and Best of Huey Lewis & The News 
 
4. Is there a song that reminds you most of your childhood? 
More than any other, Karma Chameleon by Culture Club might have been the first song I noticed on TV/radio and where I knew the band's name, not to mention a fair few of the lyrics. I was 5; Sr. Theresa didn't appreciate my singing either. 
 
5. If you could spend a night with five musical artists - three for their minds and two for their bodies - who would they be? 
Minds: 
Liam Howlett 
George Michael 
Tom Morello 
 
Bodies: 
Nelly Furtado (saw her vid on MTV today - OH was that the sun...) 
Uh...Salma Hayek sang on the Desperado OST! Woohoo! 
 
6. If your life was a movie, what song would play over the following: 
Opening Credits: Prodigy, Climbatize 
Love Scene: George Michael, Cowboys and Angels 
Closing Credits: Massive Attack, (Exchange) 
 
7. If applicable, name a song or concert that moved you to tears. 
No one particular song has done this, but lots of songs hit the mark on a particular day and I sometimes find my eyes watering and the hair on the back of my neck stands up. It's not an emotional thing as such; it could be Limp Bizkit (opening chords/build-up from Take A Look Around, anyone?) or RATM or even Britney Spears, but it'll do something on the day. *shrug* 
 
8. What do you listen to when you are... 
Fucking: It was the Smashing Pumpkins last time, if I recall... 
Waking up: Currently: Doedel Up by Guano Apes 
Bored: Er...I play UT :-) 
Excited: Propellerheads, The Crystal Method, random progressive house if it's around 
 
9. Name one musical artist you would like to see banished: 
Only one? Who remembers Roy "Chubby" Brown's hilarious rendition of (Who The F*** Is) Alice? 
 
10. Name one musical genre you would like to see banished: 
There is a particular style of music unique to Germany, listened to by the over 50s. It's not traditional, necessarily; its only prerequisite is that it be easy to sing along to, usually whilst drinking (and preferably clapped to on the 1-3 instead of the 2-4). It will be warbled by someone for whose hairpiece an entire colony of yaks was put to the sword and it is far, FAR worse than ANYTHING Susan McCann or Daniel O'Donnell and their hell-minions could throw at you in Ireland. It's called Schlagermusik and, for the record, this is the category both Johnny Logan and David Hasselhof fall into. 
 
11. Name a song you would rather hear never again: 
Bryan Adams, Everything I do (I do it for you) - I second Cliph. 
 
12. What now-defunct band would you most like to see reunite (living or dead)? 
The Doors 
 
13. Name an album that is perfect all the way through. 
Radiohead, OK Computer 
 
14. Music you like that could be considered a guilty pleasure: 
A surprising amount of Lou Perlman's progeny, not to mention Limp Bizkit (I hate Durst too, but the band play well,  OK??? ) 
 
15. If your music collection was about to go up in flames, which five cds would you save? 
Chemical Bros - Surrender 
Asian Dub Foundation - Community Music 
Radiohead - OK Computer 
Jimi Hendrix - Blues (as soon as I buy it!) 
Leftfield - Rhythm and Stealth 
 
16. Is there a song that describes you or a situation you've been in so well that you could have written it? 
George Michael, Cowboys and Angels 
 
17. Which underrated artist deserves more attention? 
Hybrid 
 
18. Has a song or artist changed your life in any way? If so, how? 
There have been artists that have caused huge changes in my taste in music, but nothing that has really spilled over into my life. 'Cept maybe for Jimi :-) 
 
19. What is your favorite soundtrack? 
Pulp Fiction 
 
20. Best music-related movie: 
The Commitments 
 
21. What would your dream band be? 
The Dewaele brothers + Liam Howlett + Thom Yorke + Academy of St. Martin in the Fields 
 
22. Do you miss the days when MTV used to, like, show videos and stuff? 
I've not had access to MTV for as long as others might have, but even I've noticed a decline in standards. 
 
23. What is your favorite all-time video? 
Pearl Jam, Do The Evolution 
 
24. Current favorite radio hit: 
Guano Apes, Doedel Up 
 
25. What's your favorite artist/band(s) of all time? 
Sergey Rachmaninoff 
P. I. Tschaikovsky 
Chemical Brothers 
Massive Attack 
George Michael 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       All your memes are belong to us  
So, you have this game waaayyy back in the 80s called  urlLink Zero-Wing , with  the  most dazzling  urlLink intro sequence  ever seen in  urlLink 16-bit computing . So dazzling, in fact, that they ran out of money to pay for a decent interpreter/script writer. Then, just recently,  urlLink some lads over at a computer gaming clan site started doctoring some images . This was drawn to the attention of  urlLink Memepool , so it wasn't long before someone threw together a little  urlLink Shockwave movie *.  
This, boys and girls, is what we call  urlLink propagating   urlLink a   urlLink meme .
  
 * local copy hosted at  urlLink CDU  
   Update!! 
 urlLink allyourbasearebelongtous.com  - registered Dec. 6th, 2000 
allyourbasearebelongtous.net - registered Jan 30th, 2001 
allyourbasearebelongtous.org - registered Feb 14th, 2001 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ireland? Oh, you mean England...  
It's 40 times the size of Ireland and 7.5 times the size of Germany; population of 16.7m; more natural resources than you can shake a stick at; capital Astana (moved from Almaty in 1998). Its president is one Nursultan A. Nazarbayev and its prime minister is Kazymzhomart Tokayev. And I bet you haven't a clue  urlLink where it is .
  
I find the Irish in particular are always a little surprised when they're abroad and meet a foreigner who knows absolutely nothing about our little country, bar maybe having a vague (and generally wrong) notion about Northern Ireland. I've had this a few times until it occurred to me: why should they? Especially when I meet a Kazakhstani (re)immigrant who knows more about the Irish/Celts in general than I do. My mission in life is now to read up on Kazakhstan (link above) and every other country, er, in the world;  then  I'll be entitled to be outraged at some Johnny Foreigner's ignorance of the Emerald Isle :-)
  
Also, history of the  urlLink Irish republic  in a nutshell, courtesy of the  urlLink CIA World Factbook : 
" A failed 1916 Easter Monday Rebellion touched off several years of guerrilla warfare that in 1921 resulted in independence from the UK for the 26 southern counties; the six northern counties (Ulster) remained part of Great Britain. In 1948 Ireland withdrew from the British Commonwealth; it joined the European Community in 1973. Irish governments have sought the peaceful unification of Ireland and have cooperated with Britain against terrorist groups. A peace settlement for Northern Ireland, approved in 1998, has not yet been implemented. "
  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A spoonful of sugar...  
 urlLink ...helps the medicine go in! . Thanks to her royal bounciness  urlLink Jules  for this.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Look look!  
As a result of the previous post + idleness, I threw in a new link. Bottom left, between "feedback" and "uptime"...oh alright:  urlLink here . Satisfy your stalking cravings even more and laugh at my pitifully low hit count (not bad since January 5th, really).
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       [00:13 14/02][styx.uwa.edu.au]  Hi Jules! 
 [08:40 14/02][trac.ba-karlsruhe.de]  Hi Andrea! 
 [14:21 14/02][iaipc117.iai.fzk.de]  Hi Max/Rob/Nick! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why do we never - ever - h&auml;&auml;h?  
 urlLink Buying tomorrow , single or whole album I dunno yet. Probably just the  urlLink single . Aye.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Whoah...  
I am overwhelmed by the weirdness that is  urlLink Bowie . Perhaps someone could  urlLink explain ? (I don't like mailtos either...)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       IndirectX  
Check this out: a  urlLink magazine  goes to great lengths to promote a big  urlLink demo  on its coverdisc, but fails to supply necessary  urlLink driver  to run said game. I must have been asleep when Microsoft bought Mechwarrior from Activision, but they're sure going to town with MW4, especially since it requires that blessing/curse of all PC games: DirectX, version 8 being the latest incarnation. PC Player included DX7 on the disc, of course, 'cos that's useful...  
...which is why I've to spend nearly an hour downloading 8...not impressed.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Rad  
So, yeah, I can snowboard now, sort of. It's theoretically possible for me to get all the way down a piste without falling, and not falling became a very major issue on Sunday (second day) when I woke up and realised I couldn't move. Anything. At all. Mind you, this morning was as bad, as will be the next few, most likely; such a sudden transition from couch potato to Alpen-trash is bound to be a little traumatic. Still, I have an assortment of colourful bruises in improbable places to show off not to mention a nice colour after being out in the sun for two full days. I just wish I could do anything other than blink without wincing.  
Fuck it -  chicks dig it, bruises heal, pain is temporary, glory is forever! *  
(Who am I kidding? I want my Mammy...)
  
 *with apologies to  urlLink No Fear . 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I don't need no steenkin' body clock  
So it's 3:17am CET and I've just got out of bed. We leave for Feldberg at 6:30; that's where the snow is (or isn't, as the case may be, seeing as how it's been so warm all this week). By the way, a solemn resolution: I'm never staying out after pub closing during the week again. Hopefully someone I know will read this and hold me to it...  
Here's  urlLink something pretty . Oh look, I can see my house!  
4:22 - time to get dressed/packed. No gloves, no waterproof clothes, no sunglasses, no idea if I should bring a sleeping bag or not...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Lamer than "Jesus Christ"  
 
From --------Thu Feb  8 01:30:28 2001 
Date: Wed, 7 Feb 2001 15:23:11 -0600 (CST) 
From: -------- 
Reply-To: groupies@memepool.com 
To: groupies@memepool.com 
Subject: Re: MY FINAL WORD 
 
On Wed, 7 Feb 2001, Dave Michael Denis Whyte Esq. wrote: 
>Ya reckon? I just registered lamerthanjesuschrist.org with namezero; you 
>can even have ------@lamerthanjesuschrist.org if you ask nicely. 
 
Dave, you are not only the most surpassingly intelligent person
I have seen in my life of stints at Sorbonne, Trieste, Oxford and
Harvard, not just the most courageously initiative among any I
have read about from Alexander the Great to Field Marshall Rommel,
not merely the saintliest I have encountered in my long line of
spiritual communions from Cyprian of Carthage to Pope John Paul,
but also a surprisingly interesting guy for a memepool groupie
and an exemplar to us all. It is perhaps the only combination of
virtues which would ever lead me to ask, courteously and with the
utmost humiliity--will you please fucking give me that lame address?
 

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ye Sunday Pilgrimage  
So, I'm not black and blue in the Black Forest yet - "Nein, nein - das machen wir am  n&auml;chsten  Sonntag!". Ach  so ...
  
 
function open_window(url) {
mywin=window.open(url,"mywin","toolbar=0,location=0,directories=0,status=0,menubar=0,scrollbars=0,resizable=no,width=210,height=320");
	}
 
Because of this, the hour of the pilgrimage draws near. I refer, of course, to my weekly trip to the train station here to get a  urlLink dead-tree copy  of the  urlLink Sunday Times  for a whopping 10 Marks (about IRP 4). Worth every pfennig, even if it's the English version (natch) and it doesn't have the magazine. As long as I get News Review, Sport, Culture and Doors I'm happy. I can see all the tabloid readers wrinkling their noses at the mention of "culture" but don't worry, it's just a glorified TV Guide. 
  
Usually my next destination on leaving the newsagent is to walk around the corner to McDonalds and partake of some junk but not today! (audience gasps). Today I'm being fed by same non-boarders with whom I thought I'd be on the slopes today; it's just their way of apologising for my stupidity, I'm sure. I'm sure it'll be lovely and I know it'll have lots and lots of salad and I really like salad and I hope in fact that there's nothing else  but  salad 'cos that'd be delicious. Yes indeed. Another lettuce leaf? Oh thank you. Oh no, I normally nibble like this; don't have much of an appetite, you know. If you'll excuse me, I just have to nip down the street to McD's to, er, check something...


     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Fame and fortune  
Whee, I got linked! That young fella  urlLink Cosgrave  has gone and added me to his Irish blogs list. Tom actually gets regular hits from people he doesn't even know in real life, so I'm only too happy to hang onto his coattails and pick up a few fans (ahem). Sooner or later I'm also going to have to submit this steaming pile of crap to  urlLink Doras  for review. That might conflict with the disclaimer I just had to put on the  urlLink jokes page  though. Hi Rob - Booyakasha etc. No, actually I  enjoy  hitting n(ext message), e(xport file), public_html/lesinge/jokes/anotherfingjoke, y(es), return - for half an hour every day! I'm going to organise some sort showdown between Rob and my other big contributor, Dara. What, I don't know, but it'll be ugly. 
  You saw it here first, ladies and gentlemen! Spam Wars, only at LeSinge.org! Put that in your Doras and, er, slam it.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Duuuude!  
Total snowboarding radness may be taking place sooner than I thought - ie next Sunday, just a few miles south of here down't Schwarzwald. It's gonna be very ugly but at least I won't be along in my ignominy; three out of the four of us have little/no experience. Broken wrists ahoy!

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Did I forget to post *again*?  
Here's why:
 
  SCRUFFY'S IRISH PUB QUIZ  
 29 th  March 2001 
 
[insert actual quiz here....] 
 
Comments, queries, abuse etc to be directed to  Dave  or  Charlotte  
 
  No mobile phones, fax machines, pagers, PDAs, ham radios, GPS receivers or portable encyclopaedias please, or we'll set Emily on you, you cheating bastards.   
 (No animals were harmed in the making of this quiz)  
 If you're bothering to read this, you've waaaay too much time on your hands 
 
 
They won't know what hit them...

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Terror bombing  
I was chatting to a lad from  urlLink Kassel  yesterday and he mentioned that his home town wasn't really the prettiest of places, full of grim 50's architecture, mainly because the Allies had pretty much razed it to the ground in the autumn of 1944. Apparently there is only one -  one!  - building over fifty years old in the city centre. So the question arose in my head just now as to why armies bomb cities at all, what with the high probability of civilian casualties etc. A quick  urlLink Google search  brought up  urlLink this chilling article . In short: that's exactly why they do it. Aren't humans great?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       du -kc  
...is a UNIX/Linux/*BSD command which, in this case, returns the total disk usage (ie size) of any given folder and its subfolders, in kilobytes. I just looked at  urlLink how much space my web folder is taking up  and ohdearieme...  
I've got the  urlLink fear of god  all of a sudden, so it's been decided:  the  urlLink Junk page  is going  in a few days, and with it the contents, all 73 MB's worth. Pay attention, Rob and Andrea: this is your last chance to get anything you want out of there! I might keep a few of the best, like the  urlLink Matrix farting vid , the  urlLink explantion of the word "fuck"  and so on, but the rest will be purged mercilessly. Most of them are crap anyway and god knows  how  many duplicates there are.
Any attachments I get in my mail from now on will be held up there for probably not longer than a week, just so that I can get a chance to download them myself - which was the original function of that page anyway.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Palm and her V sisters  
You know something, I came very close to scripting a version of this site suitable for AvantGo just now. But then I realised how much work brain-power would be required and I thought "Nah, sod it - I'll go for a pizza instead".  
But before I go,  urlLink guess who 's gone  urlLink all   urlLink mushy  on us! Apparently she doesn't even  dig  UNIX. On a tangential note, my favourite sig that I've seen on  urlLink Slashdot  is: " urlLink UNIX? They're probably not even circumcised. Savages ".   
Oh yeah...pizza...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Lech mich; ich war beschäftigt  
I don't know how true this is of anyone else, but the frequencies of my postings are in inverse proportion to the scale/importance of my activities in the real world, ie. the more of a life I have, the less I blog.  
I bought one of  urlLink these , in "ice" (clear plastic to you). Technically, I can't afford it but this at least will force me to stay in my job until I've earned it back. Consider it an advance. It's frightfully cool, though. Same memory and innards as  urlLink this , not quite as pretty and lacking a rechargeable battery (2x AAA, alas), but pretty much half the price. I've a meg and a half's worth of newspapers to trawl through now, and later on I'm going to install the  Gameboy emulator!!! . Toys rule.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Sunrise! Accckkkk, I'm meltiiiingggg...  
Well whaddaya know, I managed to get up, unlike last week. I hate this job already.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       dave+green+wanker?  
[1674][22:37 11/03][deviant.demon.co.uk][ urlLink  $HTTP_REFERER  ]
  
This is definitely the best refer I've  ever  got. Who at demon.co.uk thinks Dave Green is a wanker? Who, indeed, is Dave Green? A slightly  urlLink more focused search  on my part came up with  urlLink this Dave Green . His page is W3C compliant and his hobbies are coxing, cricket and croquet. Maybe, just maybe.   
But a little more digging (ie. scrolling) unearths  urlLink this Dave Green  who even has a   urlLink spoof page  devoted to him and  this  is the very same  urlLink Dave Green  from whom I (and thousands others) get my weekly  urlLink Need To Know  mail.   
Does this, like, make me  urlLink famous  or something?
  
  Update : ...and why did Win98  urlLink BSOD  immediately after I blogged this? Dark forces are at work, methinks. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hmph...  
"Hewlett-Packard, for instance, certifies its Omnibooks for Linux. The company doesn't sell laptops complete with Linux, but the configuration is certified to accept the OS. Linux developers already have been setting up such laptops, said Webb McKinney, vice president of the personal computing organization at HP."  
( urlLink from C|Net )  
So why can't I get XFree86 up? Oh yeah, I forgot - I'm lame...  
By the way: note the time of this post, people! This is against the very Law of Nature herself!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Playin' Solitaire 'til dawn...  
I have this great tendency to get really absorbed in anything not related to an upcoming deadline, absorption being directly proportional to said deadline, hence my having got really good at Solitaire over the last 48 hours. I have my first class tomorrow and I'm a tad nervous, pathetically enough. There's quite a bit of preparation to be done on my part beforehand and yet...and yet I really can't be bothered. Other times it's been this and other web-pages, Quake, a good book or just plain old getting pissed in the pub. Those who know me well will instantly recognise the same self-destructive tendency that caused me to fail second year in college, not to mention the likelihood of it happening again this year. I am in dire need of motivation. Any takers? (not Caz).  
And yesterday I actually  did  play Solitaire 'til dawn...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Eye candy  
Helena's  urlLink redesigned  a bit. V pretty (even in Netscape).
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Poutain du merde  
 urlLink Gotta love those crazy Brits!  
 urlLink Gotta love those crazy Irish!   
Links shamelessly ripped from  urlLink NTK .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Shut Down TMB!  
I wonder if  urlLink The Misanthropic Bitch  is running out of steam? At the height of her powers she attracted quite a bit of attention, both  urlLink good  and  urlLink bad , for her articles on everything from politics to censorship to stupid names for kids - and then there are the  urlLink teen mothers ... There's a wealth of articles stretching all the way back to '97 and some are absolute  urlLink classics .  
Today she put up her first article in two months, in reply to a mail from yet another irate reader and once again on the teen mothers subject. Funny and all as it is, one wonders just how far you can flog this one topic. Maybe it'll pick up. Join her  urlLink mailing list  and you can keep tabs.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       IHRE GANZE UNTERSEITE SIND GEHOEREN NACH US  
So says  urlLink Babelfish . To see just how bad it can get once you cycle from English to German and back again a few times, look at  urlLink this .
  
Shouldn't I have been at work at 7am today? Didn't I wake up at 12? Isn't this a bad thing? So I'm a little ill, nothing I can't ha- (collapses into furious coughing fit, during which time face goes from red to purple). Somebody bring me an aspirin, for the love of God!
  
Here's  urlLink something every man needs to know . Ta, Rob. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yipe  
 [1458][23:17 06/03][host213-123-63-59.dialup.lineone.co.uk][] 
 
&lt;Adam-uk&gt; I made a visit to your page and I think it is downright awful I am going to scoop out your brain with a sharp hook for making such an atrocious website. 
 
 Adam-uk is Air@host213-123-63-59.dialup.lineone.co.uk   
 
Isn't this sort of thing, like, illegal? (The threat, not the editorial comment...) Couldn't I call LineOne and give abuse? Could I not, in fact, should I wish to pursue the matter, get him arrested? Little (expletives deleted) like this are the reason that parents and politicians get in such a lather over their kids using the internet. Argh!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       $HTTP_REFERER: "http://lesinge.org"  
My, er,  urlLink thousands  of loyal readers will no doubt have noticed the shiny new addition a few days ago on the right of this page. Having just tweaked it to include the date of inclusion too (this involves me writing it down by hand, mind!), I reckon it's done. Ladies and gentlemen, I give you the Memepond. Inspired in name and function (albeit considerably simpler) by  urlLink this , it's just a place where I'll be dumping cool links I find, and consists of the most recent entries on the right-hand column of most of the pages, backed up by the entire (and currently rather small) collection in an  urlLink archive . And yes, the right-hand bar showing the most recent and the archive page both run off the same  urlLink source .
  
In other news,  urlLink Cliph  has ditched  urlLink Blogger  in favour of  urlLink Greymatter  for his 'blogging activities, so well done there. There are also unsubstantiated rumours of a joint CDU/LeSinge (http://chicks-dig-monkeys.net?) design effort for our  urlLink mothership 's site. It's all very exciting.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Smoking? Why no, officer  
So Elaine, who'd been gracing Karlsruhe with her presence for the last 10-ish days, is on the plane back to Ireland as we speak - assuming she's capable of standing upright. We celebrated her last night (she's pissing off finally!) by staying at Highlander and then going back to Les and James' place (and if you don't know any of these people, deal with it) at 8:30am on a Sunday and partaking of some Grade A Class B herbs. The word "debauchery" springs to mind. Some serious body-clock readjustment is now in order. At least I got to sleep this afternoon, though; the intrepid traveller is probably hallucinating now... 
 
With the departure last week of  that other loser (who apparently lives 50yds from this week's loser), we are again reduced to three Corkonians: myself, the other Blonde and the Hustler. If/when I can be bothered, one of these days I'll do a lovely "My Friends in Karlsruhe" page with pretty pictures and everything so you'll be able to put faces to all these names when I start libelling them etc. 
 
On a different note, here's  urlLink something funny  at  urlLink  This Is My D.N.A.  .

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
Broadcast Message from csd@csd.dot-ie.com 
 (/dev/ttypd) at 23:06 GMT... 
 
 urlLink ALL YOUR BASES ARE BELONG TO US!!  
 
----- 
Broadcast Message from cliph@csd.dot-ie.com 
 (/dev/ttyp1) at 23:07 GMT... 
 
BASES?!?!?! 
 
base*s*?!?!?!?!?!?!?   
That's our  urlLink Clifford , always a stickler for the correct misspelling.




     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Broken clocks and other stories  
Crap day. As soon as my  urlLink flatmate  buggers off out of this room I'm attacking a half bottle of cheap red; that'll cheer me up. Canonical alcoholism, if only for an evening.  urlLink Cliph 's depressed too, and we're sitting here trading melancholia through  urlLink CSD . I'm starting to feel better already - and did I mention that Cliph and I have never met in real life?

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's ART...  
 
... urlLink goddammit ...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Intellectual labour  
I'm now "working", that is to say: I'm preparing (my half of) the Highlander and Scruffy's quizzes for Wednesday and Thursday respectively. This involves wandering around news sites looking for tidbits, poring over  urlLink uselessknowledge.com  and lurking in DALnet's #trivia irc channel. Then it all has to be typed and translated into German and printed and photocopied (at our expense!). Then on the night we're correcting papers the whole time and then one of us does "the show"...I won't even tell you what we get for it, suffice to say that it doesn't justify the time and effort spent.  
But it's fun and I get, like, rispekt 'n' stuff. Aarrrr.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Didn't term start today?  
Don't I have lectures?   
Uh...never mind.  
/me waves at Serra :-P
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mmmmmm  
I'm slouching in bed, knees up to support the laptop and listening to an old edition of  urlLink Geeks In Space . This is very pleasant. If I could find a cheap pizza-delivery place and someone to buy me bogroll and toothpaste etc I would never ever leave this place. I could carve out a little life for myself on the net, although perhaps avoiding individuals like  urlLink this poor girl ...
  
 urlLink Will has relaunched . The other day he sent me this:  urlLink 1.5MB of chunky kung-fu goodness . This looks like it's #3 in a series - anyone who can track down the other 2 (or more?) wins a free 
 urlLink CDU  nipple clamp. Nipple clamps make Baby Jesus go "Oooohh".
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Excess  
This week has been a gastronomic extravaganza. I have eaten out every night from last Monday to last night. I have consumed much steak and chips and pasta and coke, and I've only been to an ATM once... Aren't mothers great? Herself and auntie left this morning. I should have gone with them to the airport but kind of slept in, and they were rather unimpressed with that. It was a crap way to end the visit, and everything else had been going well up to that point (amazingly). In a frantic attempt to get rid of money yesterday, my aunt even bought me two books, one of which is Sophie's World. Read a borrowed copy only a few weeks ago but, as those of you who've read it will know, it probably requires at least another run through before all the concepts are taken in. Etc..
  
Jesus, this is a boring post...I seem to have temporarily lost my artistic zing when it comes to blogging. That'll be the hangover, then.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Joy overload?  
It's 5:08am and I'm in my room. I'm absolutely exhausted but I'm terrified that if I leave the computer now, it won't work tomorrow morning or when I turn it on next, just like it didn't last time.   
I've a 5m cable which should be just enough to move everything across to my bedside table, if I switch ends in the bed...this way I can stay on  urlLink IRC  as  urlLink LeSinge-[asleep] .   
Now that's what I call achievement.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Thanks, Jen...  
Subject: LeSinge comment - How do I miss thee? 
 
clcs4073-14.lcs.tcd.ie (134.226.72.113), 18:52 
  
How do I miss thee? Let me count the ways 
I miss try scathing scarcasm  (sic)  and thy pizza eating ways 
I miss thy dry wit and thy sleeping all the days 
I miss thy sciving  (sic)  off and thy drinking all the time 
I miss thy bad influence and thy something that will rhyme(:o)) 
I miss thy constant dossing and thy always being late 
I miss thy doing worse then me and making me feel great ;oD  
 
How's  that  for a welcome back? Network's back, btw. I rule.

     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Gasping for air  
No time to blog - entertaining my mother and aunt who arrived yesterday and will be here until next Sunday. Swapped PC card today and hopefully this will be an end to my net deprivation. Proper update as soon as that happens. Are you  urlLink all  missing me?  urlLink Tell me how much  :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So close and yet so far  
Finally got connected from my room last night after splashing out on a PC card, and for a while it was luverly, only problem being that I couldn't seem to send/receive cookies (?!). Then everything died. Tried to connect again this morning and nothing doing. Is the network just temporarily down (please, God), or did I change some setting and forget about it? (I was tired/drunk). Or, horror of horrors, is the f-...damned card after packing it in  already? 
  
I am particularly unimpressed at having to check mail and write this entry from an internet cafe, and yes, that is how far I will go to stop the  urlLink memepool  groupies mailing list (200 new in the last 18ish hours) from becoming unmanageable...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Aha  
Silly me - I knew it was there somewhere. The  urlLink AvantGo link for my ireland.com page , that is.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Good and bad  
Get a load of  urlLink this . It's Ireland.com's breaking news section, but not as you know it - chopped and cropped so it'll fit on one of  urlLink these  or  urlLink these . I'm rather proud of this, although in reality anyone with half an ounce of programming experience could do it  urlLink in less time and with less code . I'll set up an  urlLink AvantGo  channel proper, just as soon as I ask Cliph. Gee, maybe the  urlLink Irish Times  will hire/sue me!
  
 The user is specifically prohibited from modifying, publishing, transmitting, selling, participating in the transfer or sale or reproducing, creating derivative works from, distributing, performing, displaying or in any way exploiting any of the materials on this site or the software or materials relating thereto in whole or in part... 
  
The irony of all this is that I can't check it myself because, as of yesterday, my computer is seriously banjaxed. As far as I can work out, the supposed  de fragger went and completely fragged either the bootloader or the (Mandrake) Linux (for Windows - yes I'm lame) system image file (c:\lnx4win\linuxsys.img) so now I can't boot past, er, "stage 1". Might be solved be reinstalling Lnx4Win and hoping it overwrites the previous junk but otherwise it's recovery disc time. Words cannot describe how much I hate Microsoft today.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Summertime!  
Summer has arrived with a bang. The last two days have been scorchingly hot with nary a cloud in the sky. I moved into new student room last Friday, plonk in the centre of town, right beside the castle and the gardens. The room has a network connection (once I get a PC card), its own bathroom and more storage space than you can shake a large suitcase at. This is all stuff I was lacking whilst with those lovely  urlLink Starshot people , so now we're happy. 
  
Meanwhile, I'm not going to pass this year, but it's cool enough here that it might be worth (possible?) saving up enough cash to repeat. Must scope that idea out; I've got until July 31st to decide. I'm currently suffering from a serious case of Flanagan's and Cann's Karlsruher Vortex Syndrome, named after Lesley and James respectively, who finally escaped back to England on Sunday after coming here to play a gig some 14 years ago. This place won't be the same without them (stroking beard and gazing wistfully into the middle distance). Just for the record, I'll be here six months on the 10th of April and  god  has it flown... 
  
Actually, I think I'll stay here and open a bar. Yeah.... :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Bags and baggage  
Well, LeSinge.org will arrive back at my old  urlLink matrix account  in 24-ish hours. I know that, in the great scheme of things, losing a shell account and having to move your e-mail/website is somewhere below, say,  breaking a nail, but it's the manner in which it happened that really fucks me off. 
  
A bunch of scumbags took it upon themselves to orchestrate a DDoS on an inconsequential little server for absolutely no good reason, and now one guy's pride and joy, into which he and many others poured hours of work in their spare time has to come down. Free shell accounts with all the mod cons, not to mention free DNS hosting on a machine on a major ISP's backbone do  not  come around every day. 
  
I'm really sorry for Colin but at least thankful for his giving me an account some 2 years ago. I've learned an awful lot of UNIXey, webby stuff, first on the NetBSD SPARC and then the FreeBSD i386. The advantage of having a backbone connection became really clear to me when I went abroad and realised just how fast dialling in was compared to my TCD accounts. It was brilliant while it lasted (not to mention damn near irreplaceable).
  
Thanks for everything. Shit that it had to end this way.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I did not need to wake up to this...  
I was woken about a half an hour ago by an SMS from Jim, telling me that  urlLink CSD is shutting down for good .
And that is REALLY FUCKING SHIT.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm back, sorta  
I got bored with being bored with the site so I may as well throw something up here.
  
So, the  urlLink lads  came over last week. We got pissed (and more), played chess, swapped abuse, and I was officially voted gey by their two-man committee. My computer's hard disk is considerably fuller than it was before, positively bursting at the seams with Photoshop and Illustrator and Fireworks and Flash and Jimi Hendrix and lots and lots of books. Apart from Will (at my behest, admittedly) deleting a rather vital system file because we reckoned it was spyware (inetinfo.exe is  not  spyware!) and my only finally recovering it this morning, all was well. Photos have been taken (one Jennifer Kelly is in for a surprise) and they're due to be posted on  urlLink Neural Blade  shortly.
  
Today is a public holiday in Germany and the sun is splitting the stones, so a bunch of us are heading to  urlLink Schloßgarten  with beer, food and a frisbee to get tans etc. This is The Life&trade;.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Eh...hello  
Another Wednesday, another quiz. Another cloudless sky, another afternoon in Schloßpark. Another Coke, another cigarette. Must go phone people and drag them out.
  
And I can now officially say that I know someone who knows someone who actually shagged a sheep. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's looking good...  
This here  urlLink hobbiton account  isn't half bad, you know. From a pure free webspace point of view it rocks, in fact. Been sussing it out for the last few weeks and I've not been disappointed.
  
Mmmm...indeed...
  
 urlLink http://lesinge.hobbiton.org ! I even get a  urlLink relevant sounding mailto ! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The "E" trams  
The great thing about living where I do in Karlsruhe is that, at the end of the night, the last few trams all go past my stop on their way to their beds out at Rheinhafen. These trams are denoted by the letter "E", so the 6, which normally ends at Mühlburger Tor, continues on towards my place as the 6E. Ditto the 1 and the 4, none of which normally go my way. 
  
What does all this mean? It means that I can stumble out of the pub at 1am on a Monday morning and not have to wait longer than 5 minutes for a tram, because no fewer than six of them can take me home. And that is why Weststadt rocks.
  
Oh, hi - I'm blogging again :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hanging on for dear life  
We're approaching the eleventh hour, the frenetic climax, as events unfold which might see Dave getting his Life some way In Order. It all depends on Oliver (Ph.D), Gunther (Ph.D) and Anja (cute). And me. Gonna prove my salt this week or not at all.
  
It's been a mad and very alcoholic week which I wouldn't say was wasted, at least not in the social sense. My mate  urlLink Ian  bought a very shiny laptop (yay!) at a knockdown price (yay!) - running WinXP (er...). And I've finally got a webcam but I've nowhere to publish the damn pics. For the love of God, someone give me a shell account with Apache and  FTP  access.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Theophilus O'Shaughnessy and the Suicidal Tendencies    
Nick McGuinness and the Chronic Arsebiscuits  
Ulick McGee and the Pheasant Pluckers' Sons  
Lord Aristotle of Chipping-Sodbury and the Splendiferous Nipple-Tweakers....  
 
Teehee :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I think I'm still pissed  
I woke up an hour ago :)  
Here's what I did yesterday: woke up at 9, got to work at 10:10, got out at 6, and went home, picking up a Chinese on the way. Arrived to find two letters for me, one containing my long-lost credit-card and the other my German residence permit. Got to Scruff's for the Hallowe'en bash at 8:30, working at the door, charging the DM10 entrance fee and giving out schnapps shots. I had several of these myself, along with a couple of pints of Hefeweizen. Finished up at about 12:30 because the place was full and I had more or less graduated to a barman role instead of catching people coming in the door. The place was packed; I got exactly 100 people and god knows how many others arrived after I'd finished. Continued drinking Hefe and partook of a couple of shots courtesy of the proprietor, which oiled the wheels nicely. We closed up at 3-ish and me, Paul and Colin headed for the  urlLink Old Dublin  armed with the night's tips which would pay for our drink there. There followed a quest to find a taxi and when we did get one the driver was straight out of the Kit-Kat ad. He gave out to  us  for  making  him stop at a crossroads and continued in this vein right through the entire journey, with Colin eventually siding with him and leaning back to lecture myself and Paul who were in the back creasing up at the Kit-Kat thing. A few ciders and shots later, at around 5, I eventually got it together enough to ring a taxi and I came home.   
Nothing went wrong, I didn't make an eejit out of myself (because everyone else was as pissed as I was), and basically a very pleasant evening was had. I spent about 10 marks playing Trivial Pursuit on  urlLink this , paid not a penny for drink  and  got my wages and a groovy  urlLink Guinness  (staff) Hallowe'en t-shirt ("Zeig mir das Dunkle in dir") to boot! Today is the first day of a long weekend and I'm at the Scruffy's quiz tonight.   
Rockin'.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Um...  
So, eh, quite a bit has changed in the last six months. Relationships with Oliver, Gunther and Anja have respectively ceased to be, continued as before and blossomed. Dermot's buggered off to Ingolstadt; Ian from the last post is gone most weekends...
  
And somewhere in that period I decided to code  urlLink my own weblog  because I  really  hate banner ads. Go visit; I may not be back here.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      New Blogger is shiny, you know. Comments and shit are cool. I'm  urlLink over here  these days, incidentally.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>