<Blog>

<date>31,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I agree that Battleblog is ok to do whilst hungover.  Good clear indication of transfer to your personal log John.  When the pain is gone, move on.    I'd like to say have a happy new year to all in blogland.  Have a happy century, happy year of the snake (...or duck),  and happy 3rd millennium.  I personally feel we should remake the calender with July, 1969 as our starting date... no not Woodstock...mankind's first step on another celestial object, the moon!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I believe any spoon will do John.  Pour the guiness secondly over a spoon so that the pressure doesn't penetrate the Bass or whatever the lower lighter beer is and I think that's it.  I might be wrong, because I've never actually made a black and tan, but I think that's the idea.  Let me know how it went.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Well, at my parents house the drunkenfish comes up as corners of pictures and totally out of whack.  Now, I understand a little of John's recent complaints.  I haven't been catering to 800x600 cave people or netscape even for that matter.  I took a look at Tanque, just to see if he catered to the display impaired and he does.  Well, I'm not gonna let that punk ass site out do my user friendliness, so my next goal is to make the pages look halfway decent at the incredibly low resolution in which I'm finding so many people view the net.  Another change to the the site is going to include deleting two of the original bloggers, because they are not blogging.  I know... harsh language for drinking buddies, but if you don't use it, you lose it.  They'll both be given an e-mail and if no response is sent then there will only be 3 bloggers on the drunkenfish.  Hopefully, we'll be able to rustle up so more bloggers soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
       In 1555, Nostradamus wrote:   "Come the millennium, month 12,  In the home of greatest power,  The village idiot will come forth  To be acclaimed the leader.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I did the  urlLink machine version  of anagram fun and I didn't come up with much, but I at least feel better about my anagram,  which the machine actually didn't come up with. 
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      "one ninjas member" was all I could come up with for an anagram to Benjamin Emerson.  That kinda sucks...need to think about it some more.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      There... that eel is much better.  I got alot done on the page today, but no one will ever notice.  First of all, my story pages all really just hooked up to tanque.org before and now they're legit.  Also I got the pictures and links on proper for those pages... like I said, it's not very obvious, but it took me a while.  You don't have much time before the end of the year Jim.  I sure would like to see something from anyone in tanque.org as well.  I realize by whinning, that I'm not winning over any potential writers, but I don't seem to be winning over any potential writers anyway, so what the hell.   That  urlLink article  that  urlLink Amos  hyperlinked to on his page is scary... I already suspected that the Supreme Court was going to remain republican simply because of the retirement times chosen by the republican majority, but to see the hearsay right on the written page sent a chill up my spine.  We'll see how many of them retire in the next 4 years.     
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Haven't bought any family Christmas gifts yet, except for my mom's, which I just received an e-mail from Amazon.com saying it wouldn't make it by Christmas.  I'm not off to a roaring start this holiday season.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      This is very annoying... I can't keep my eel picture up on the page because everytime I post, the blogger html deletes it.  hmmm... I suppose, I'll have to figure something out here.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Man... I was at my company Christmas luncheon and a lady asked, "Guys, we need these chairs put around the tables."  and I'm thinking "Guys?  Why is that a guy job?"  I got up and helped lift chairs from the stack to put around the tables, but I'm really getting sick of women using chilvary as an excuse to be lazy.  I don't feel better about myself for lifting heavy objects.  Actually, I just feel like a moron for listening to whatever woman is using me.  I've had ladies stop in front of a door and expect me to walk around them to open it for them.   "Bitch!"  I'd just as soon push them on the ground to get to the door.  It's especially bad here in the South.  My boss (who is a woman) will always tell other women, "oh, let the boys do that for you."  Homey don't play that.  Actually, the pathetic part is I do.  But anyday now, I'm going to put my foot down and say, "no you lazy bitch, carry it yourself."  Well, someday maybe.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I know that eel isn't too impressive, but I couldn't find much on eels.... I hope with further searching, I find a more worthy eel.  If someone else knows of a better eel ... let me know.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I posted earlier talking about Alanis Morissette and I thought that I really only liked that one song "Thank U", but I just listened to the whole cd and I feel a little more deeply about the whole project.  Yes, I'm drunk, but I think that even though I don't identify with the things she says all the time, and yes alot of it sounds musically the same, but she is speaking for herself.  Just like Lennon did.   It's nice to hear.  I recommend a second listen, incase anyone has dismissed Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie.  It seems to me to be an honest cd and the musical effort is very worthy.  Just thought I'd plug that, because there isn't much today that is in that realm of truthfulness with that kind of skill.  I recommend logging on to Napster and downloading any song off that album at random.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I just thought of something...  believe it or not.   BattleBlog probably is viewed by alot of random people simply because we blog often in a short period of time.  On the main blogger site I always like hitting on the recent post of others and while BattleBlog is in motion, it probably appears several times, appearing very often on the list of choices that have just been posted to.  Also at a drunkenfreindly time, so the name might even inspire a click.   Follow?  That's really kind of a scary thought.  Yeeeha!
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      . urlLink Single gene changed, fruitflies life span doubles 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Well, now that Gore has been thouroghly fucked in the ass, do you suppose he has been softened to the plight of the average american?  Does Prince Albert understand that wall of cold indifference that stands before us all and leaves us powerless to affect the powers that be?  Perhaps, this will create a greater man of Al Gore.  Perhaps a real defender of the american people will be born from this experience.  Perhaps, he'll just fly into a maddening swirl of jealousy and hunger for power.  Time will tell, I suppose.  What has this election done to me?  Well, the illusion that the Supreme Court is some kind of sanctuary for truth and justice has been obliterated.  No institution is beyond corruption and it is a part of growing up, to understand that.  I also feel that no individual is beyond corruption.  I guess that means that controlling my own morallity and sense of justice is about the only thing I can do.  A friend of mine asked me the other day how I could possibly have morality without believing in God.  "You could do whatever you wanted," was the phrase used.  True.  One can do whatever one wants to do.  I think the world is more beautiful knowing that, fully understanding that, and then marvelling at how well we all actually get along.  It's amazing to me.  Certainly our societies are not morally held together by the instituions of religion.   We can easily take a glance at any moment in recorded history to see that there is corruption in those systems.  The individual is the foundation of morality.  The golden rule.  No governmental body is ever going to be perfect, but the lessons, like this Supreme Court decision, dropping the atomic bomb, the creation of Israel, letting Rush Limbaugh have a radio program, etc..., hopefully teaches us and fills our history, our collective memory, and aids us in making better choices in the future.   The song "Thank-you" by Alanis Morrisette is a good reflection of that thought.    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Here is the ultimate way to experience  urlLink Mardi Gras .  Check out the pictures page on that site.  I gots to get me a sneaky leaker!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Go China!   urlLink Manned Spaced Flight within the next 5 years .  Coolness.  Maybe China can get the ball rolling a little faster on space colonization.  I'm taking off work 30 minutes early so I can get home in time for Gore's speech.  I am so ready for a political revolution.  We don't need to change the things that work... just the things that in this day and age are idiotic.  Our system failed this election.  I'm sure Gore will be very statesman-like and concede gracefully, but part of me wants him to address my anger.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      How many times can one refresh the screen while on the AP newsline?  I think I set some sort of record today.  Well, the Supreme Court got sleepy I guess so they quit for today.  "Yawn... we're the Supreme Court, no one is going to rush us.  We already knew how we were going to rule on all of this way back on friday anyway.  Silly lawyers.  Silly voters." 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Jimmy had a good idea in the drunken battle blog and now it's real.  Certainly you can write drunkenly on your own weblogs, but this might be fun.  Let me know if you people want these posts anonymous or with a name stamp.  For now, you will be identified.  I repeat, you will be identified.  I wanted to go off on the  U.S. Supreme court and the Florida legislature, but I just don't have the energy.  There truly is no thing as justice. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      ...and uh... let us all bow our heads a moment for the god of rock n' roll, Mr. John Lennon.  I remember in 1980 walking around in a slump for weeks trying to look more depressed than my musical buddy Will Sibley in school, so that he understood that I was a bigger Lennon fan than him.  I still have my beat up old White Album Lennon photo above my bedroom door as I always do in every place I've ever lived.  When all is said and done though... I don't believe in Lennon..... I just believe in me.... Yoko and me... and that's reality.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Wahooooo!!!  They're counting ballots in Florida!  I can't help, but think that the Republicans are just plain evil for pushing their power in the legislature to override the will of the people and decide for themselves who their electoral votes should go to.  Just plain evil.  It's a sure sign that we need to take those ancient powers away.  I think nobody has bothered to take them away, because they never imagined in this day and age that anyone would stoop so low as to use them.   We are an edumacated society now.  I would certainly not want my vote overriden by someone who thinks they know better than me.  urlLink The space microbe!!!  That is cool.  It seems though, that it would be very likely that a) the weather balloon was contaminated or b) it swirled up to the stratosphere by natural processes or c) we find that the biosphere is larger than we previously thought.  I don't find it too suprising either that it was a totally new species of bacterium.  I would suppose their are thousands or millions of unknown bacterium.  Still, I do favor the theory that life was brought to earth by comets and asteroids.  I guess that makes this part of my blog and the entire news report kind of meaningless all around.  I sure wish we could have somekind of wonderful scientific discovery that knocked us all on our collective ass.  I sure could use that kind of boost of excitement right about now.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      John not only removed the chocolate from his chin, he removed his first post!  That's not the true spirit of drunkenfish.  You live with what you say here mister.  They'll be no nancyboy retraction because you kinda sorta feel some sweet thing might be offended.  What's the fun of drunkenly making an ass of yourself, if you erase it before anyone gets the chance to read it?  On another note, the DSL dude never showed up.  It's been over a month since I placed my order.  Screw 'em.  I'll wait until later to get it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the DSL installer dude is coming in the morning.  Should I clean up my pad for the DSL dude?  I don't think so.  I mean the most he could say would be, like "Fuck, you're a slob!" and that would be the end of it.  Well, I've finished off the Stoli an O.J., so I guess it's bedtime.  I'm counting on him showing up at 1pm since he said he would be here between 8am and 12pm.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      last test...  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      IT'S ALIVE!!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      test..
     

    
</post>

<date>04,December,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Testing... 1 2 3  hellllloooooooo......
     

    
</post>

<date>31,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ok.... I know... this all looks like shit, but I'm just playing around.... bare with me a while.   By the way, this is or was a cool picture of IO, but it just really doesn't have a place on this page I'm afraid... it's a real photo... not a painting.  I'm going to leave this up for a very short while so all can see the beauty of this volcanic moon.  Io is a moon around Jupiter slightly smaller than our own moon.   Some cool trivia:  It is said by scientists that sometimes lightning travels from Jupiter to the surface of Io and that it also has a weather system in this thin atmosphere that includes yellow sulfur snow.  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Wow!  Blogger is flying now.   ....well, it's flying, but it still didn't let me publish on my first try.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I might not be addressing what is being asked, but Emily Dickinson will do anything to acquire the sympathy of the audience in her head and the toad is the lowest thing she could think of to compare herself to.  At the same time, she defends her miserable state by declaring that she is just like anything else in this world.  She also turns on those who she feels are without pain and who don't understand her self-centered misery by calling them braggarts.  I can't stand reading Dickinson because it is too close a reflection of that pathetic part of me that is always present.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Blahhhhh....  I was sick all week-end.  Work was about 300 percent more stressful than it usually is.  I'm learning the same software that Sonya is.  Dreamweaver, Flash, and Photoshop.  My pirated versions are older than the current versions, but hopefully it's enough to get started on them to somewhat know what I'm doing when I get to England.  I'm also looking into Mercantec SoftCart because small businesses are what I believe Chris' company is going to cater to.  I haven't played with that one at all yet, but at least I can kind of visualize how I need to use it when planning my templates.  No, I don't have any templates made yet, but I think I'll make up some practice ones to get familiar with the whole process before I get there.  The real ones will come after I see exactly what we're looking for.  Doesn't seem right that a Yank like me should be designing the look of an English website when I know absolutely nothing about England.  Anyway, who am I to argue.... I'm going to ENGLAND!!!!   YAAAAAAAAAAHOOOOOOOOOOEEY!!!!   Of course, this move and career change isn't doing much for my stress level... I'm a mess.   I mean it's nice to trade in all of your current worries for a new set of 'em, but that whole grey sea I see before me isn't the North Atlantic, I'll tell you that.  On the preparation side of it all... I haven't started the passport process yet, I haven't sold my car, (although I just put almost $1000 into fixing it last week), I haven't shipped my computer yet (which I'm told takes at least a couple of months to get there by boat.),  no salary has been agreed upon yet,  I have a basic understanding of some of the software I'm suppose to know, but I have no real practical experience with any of it, oh yeah, and my credit cards are at max and I'm broke.  Killer, huh.   Did I mention?... I'm going to ENGLAND!!!!   YAAAAAAAAAHOOOOOOOEEEY!!!!!  Luckily, tax returns will hopefully be accomplished this week and that should remove quite a large chunk of the credit card debt. (especially with all that student loan intrest I paid this year.)  The car selling is my greatest money obstacle and that will clear the rest of my debts and leave me with about $2000 for setting up in the new place.  There is still some hope left that this will all work out just fine.   Feels kinda good to vent all this. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      All my dreams in the last year have been real life situations for some reason.  In the past, they have always been really tripped out.  There's got to be some underlying significance to that fact, but I can't come up with any reasonable explanation.  For example, my dream this morning started with me in a typical working environment for some company selling products.  I was sitting at a long table in a room with several other long tables and about 40 people (workers and customers).  An African-American woman holding the hand of an eight year old girl was talking to me about a product she might be interested in.  At some point in the conversation she had decided that she wasn't interested.  Her eight year old daughter looked at me with a very sad face because she wanted it.  (I have no idea what the product was)  Anyway, for some reason the sad child's face made me chuckle and say to her "You know, if you whine and cry enough she may just buy it."  At that, the child smiled at me.  The woman was right there still holding the childs hand, but was involved with other thought processes.  The comment by me was meant to be heard by both of them, but apparently she missed it and not being concerned because it really wasn't that funny anyway I went back to working on whatever I was working on before the woman approached me.  Shortly after that, I heard the woman scream at her kid to shut up or she'd spank her right here in front of everybody.  The little girl started bawling and pointed at me saying, "that man told me to!"  The mother glanced in my direction and so I thought maybe I'd save the kid a spanking by saying, "yes ma'am, I did say that but..."  I was going to say that I meant the comment to be heard by her as well, but she cut me off saying, "You don't use my kid to sell me a product!"  The entire room of people were staring at me.  An elderly woman who was some really high up person in the company decided to approach me speaking very loudly.  "Listen, you don't ever..."  I cut her off.  "Look, when I said that, I was just thinking that..."  The old woman cut me off.  "No!  You don't treat a customer..."  She was speaking even louder and everyone was watching.  At this point I kind of lost it and cut her off with an extremely loud, "HEY! Get out of my face, lady!"  At this there was a deep shocked breath from everyone in the room.  Not only had I tried to use a child to sell a product, now I'd screamed and upset an old lady.  I looked at my boss waiting for the enevitable "You're fired!" but instead she said, "why don't you go grab a cup of coffee, Ben", which was probably just a nice way of saying, "You're fired!"  I said, "Thank you.  I'd like that about now."  Then I woke up.   Has my mind lost all creativity?... I don't know.  I really preferred the tripped out dreams more.  When are they coming back?
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, a woman was suppose to come see my car today (to buy), but she never showed up.  I'm sure glad I didn't waste the time of cleaning it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      is drunkenfish back up?
     

    
</post>

<date>18,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I agree with John that without religion, the basic principles of good and evil are meaningless.  (therefore, under my beliefs, the basic principles of good and evil are meaningless unless I'm talking to or about a religious person.)  I have my own definitions of what I believe is good or bad in how to live life , but I don't feel that an individual is good or evil.  It's all relative for each individual. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I remember in the not so distant past, physicists saying they could slow down light in a tube to some ungodly slow speed and now I read  urlLink this.   I'm not sure of the use, but damn, that seems an awfully powerful accomplishment.   Actually, it's unfathomable for me to understand.    
     

    
</post>

<date>15,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      No, I'm not finished bitching about religion yet.  While we're at it, we need to tax the church!  I read where churches are giving campaign money to elections.  What the hell?  I'm not going to just sit here allowing my country to turn into the religious right.  Am I going overboard here?  The republicans say that we should play nice, since Dubya is in office now... "we need to heal".... fuck you, we're gonna stick you in the ass just like you did to us over the last 8 years.  We're not going to let you make one feeble step in the wrong direction.  (like I have a say in any of this)  Already, Dubya is planning to overturn environmental and social programs. I hope the liberal left is an awesome foe for the right.  Never will it be time to give in to the dark side.  I got a little sidetracked on my religious topic.  Perhaps, I'm really not upset with religion at all... just the right wing's connection to it.  Nah, religion sucks too. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I just read  urlLink an article  about the Bush presidency and it seems as though they will do everything in their power to blend church and state.  Ugh....  back to the middle ages!   John's talking about God is a personal thing and I think that's cool (kind of like me talking about one of my 50+ personalities), but when the government starts making policy around these beliefs, it bothers me.  I tell myself to just get off the religious condemnation, but it keeps slapping me in the face.  How can I just sit quietly when most in the world base their decisions on mythology?  I'm sorry, it's rude to put down others beliefs, but I just don't get it.  Did I miss that drug?  I thought I had 'em all.  Anyway, I'm the last to say what is real and what is not, but (for the millionth time I've probably said it)  the government has no business in religion.   We are a secular state . ..I just sound like a jerk everytime I mention this subject...  Oh, screw you people of Earth!   The monks and demons that fly around your heads are real because you created them...... you are the only God of yourself.  Blah, blah, blah.......  Like I'm actually going to convince anyone by being an ass.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I have decided that (as Ned hinted at earlier) I was kind of an ass when I deleted users for not posting.  I've changed the fascist policy and now believe that it's a free blog page.... blog as you like, I won't delete anyone.  Also now, our lovely friend Yogurt is back in action in the second chapter of John's sci-fi, The Tea House.  Check it out! 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm feeling all warm and fuzzy inside for donating just now to blogger.  Wait the feeling is fading, I must make others my scapegoat to bring the feeling back.  I will use the tool of guilt!  Have you donated to blogger yet?  Well, have you? You can bring the feeling back  urlLink here .
     

    
</post>

<date>08,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Man, it's impossible for anyone who actually needs money to get a loan.  Yes, I know, a lesson I should know well by now.  My credit is good, but I don't have colateral.  Student loans are a bitch!  Anyway, I was checking out a newspaper article on the Manchester scene and they said that just about every person under the age of 30 is in a band, just left a band, or is managing someone else's band.  Also, the article said it was one of the largest concentration of college students in Europe.  Another bonus to my lifestyling.  I'm hoping to get my own flat very quickly, but I'm a little clueless on how that all works with a temporary working visa.  I need to just settle my brain... whew... breath....  ok... I've got 2 months of N'awlins left before I'm off.  I need to start learning web design or this whole thing is going to be a bit embarrassing.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I really should have battleblogged last night.  I hate to waste a good drunk like that.  Well, actually it wasn't a total waste, I did finish another Crunch chapter.  I'm playing two new computer games an awful lot lately.  One is Diablo2 which I play with Jimbo and the other is Vampires, The Masquerade.  Both eat up way too much of my time, but I'm sure I'll be sick of them soon enough.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Andy Kennedy from the sunny state of Florida!  As a new blogger to drunkenfish, I'd like to encourage you to post often and write stories and encourage Jim and John to get off their collective ass and write stories also.  Really you can do whatever the hell you like here, but I thought I'd at least get my wishes out front in the open.  Try sampling the DrunkenBattleBlog... it's yummy.  It's becoming the covenant of the Drunkenfish neighborhood to pick a sea creature picture for your blog page as well.  Wow...so many demands for a page of drunks.  Anyway, like I was saying... WELCOME ANDY!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I finally made up my mind where I'm moving... I thought I had made up my mind many times before this, but I think I'm solid with this one.  ENGLAND!!!!!!   Manchester, England.  Cousin Chris is setting me up for the trip, getting me settled, and giving me a job in his new company.  I'm hoping to get heavy into web page design as my career, but I'm very willing to work as a tech until my designing skills improve.  I looked at Flash for the first time today.  Cool program... I just have to take it home and play with it.   Anyway, I'll be moving at the end of February.  Hope I can sell my car and computer by then. Fuck yesssss!  I'm very excited.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm going to be without a computer for awhile 'cause I'm boxing this one up to send overseas.  Looks like you have the drunkenfish to yourself John.  I'm sure I'll find some computer somewhere to report in from time to time until I'm set up again.  Wish I had something really cool to say at this point, but alas the brain cells aren't sparking...  as they say in English, "I'll talk to you later!"
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      sorry to post your story without asking John, but that was the first complete chapter I've got from you and I can't resist.... A new story is born on the drunkenfish.... Chapter 1, Bonobo Man!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My favorite Prez was FDR.  I probably don't have alot of intellegent or knowledgable things to say about the man, except damn could he make policy.  The country was in hardship and he put people to work no matter what it took.  He really didn't seem to be confined by the conventional methods of the current political system... it seemed to me that the man had a mission to save our country in any way possible and he did, by using intellegence and compassion and common sense.  Three cheers for the great mind of FDR! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My last day of work and I'm awake 5 hours before I have to be awake.  I'm just going to go in early and get it over with.  Wow, I have 2 weeks of free time... hurm, what will I do?   I'll do what any respectable Drunkenfish would do with 2 weeks of free time in New Orleans during Mardi Gras... I'll watch T.V!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I think finally I have to just let go of R.E.M. Up really hurt me and I don't think this new album is going to help me recover.  Oh to have the days back of Seven Chinese Brothers, or South Central Rain or Moral Kiosk or even Gardening at Night....  The snail's pace of evolution for the band that involves repeating songs from previous albums and altering them ever so slightly annoys the hell out of me.  Anyway, with that wonderful introduction here are two new songs off the new album "Reveal".  urlLink  The Lifting   and   urlLink She Just Wants to Be. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's the day after Valentine's Day and I think I'm going to puke.  Not that I have anything against Valentine's Day, but just because I'm one of those pathetic bachelors that went out drinking at the meat markets looking for those single women who were trying to be a part of the Valentine's feeling they had welling up in themselves.  I came very close to asking the beautiful young barmaid if she would mind if I just stuck my pinky in her exposed white supple cleavage for a few seconds, but that's about as close to love as I came to last night... I am deeply suffering from the hangover from hell.... Help!  I need morphine.....
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Did someone say religion?  (caution: I will deny that I've said anything of which I'm about to say because this is an experiment to allow myself to express a side of me that has to this moment been neatly tucked away as irrational and therefore not explored.)  I've got secret beliefs that come much closer to Wicca than any other organized religion.   Kind of scary to admit and impossible to defend, so it's not something I'll be discussing in too much detail.  This loosley strung together belief system provides me with an explanation for the events I have witnessed in my life in which an overwhelming feeling pulled me from my trained rational perspective.  For instance, I believe that those who die violent deaths have a tendency to hang around after they're dead.  Yes, I know that one is straight out of the horror movies, but I've got my reasons.  I believe that when you die that you are not suddenly enlightened to the ways of the universe.  If you believed in God when you were alive, you probably will when you're dead.  I really don't associate religion with moral structure... I suppose most would think then that I've missed the point, but for me as an Atheist all my life, I have tried to live a loving, harmonious co-existence with my fellow human beings and it was not my fear or admiration for a deity that has held me to my behavior.  To me, religion or mythology or mysticism are all just an effort to explain beliefs that were not explainable through rational means.  (like the feeling of having an immortal soul when no evidence supports it.)  In any case, I agree with all the moral conclusions said in recent posts and i think it really doesn't matter how you rationalize your reality as long as you can create an enjoyble world for those around you and as long as you show enough respect for others to let them feel comfortable in whatever workable reality they have chosen.      
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Anyone coming to New Orleans for Mardi Gras?... if so look me up in the book when you get here.  I'm not leaving New Orleans until after gras, of course.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ned - Alright, I retract the silly quick base pi response... I suppose you have to have a whole of something to base a number system on.  I guess my final guess on the subject would be that changing the numerical base would have absolutely no effect on turning pi into an exact number.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      By the way, does anyone know how to stretch a background image in html so that it would adjust to any sized screen area with a smaller file?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Either I am on drugs now that I don't see the logic or I was on drugs when I made the assumption that base pi would produce an exact number for pi, either way I challenge you to prove the theory wrong.  yuck, yuck  :)
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ned, the answer to your question about a numerical system that makes pi an exact (you said even, but I assumed you meant exact) number is yes, base pi.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I know this is a huge ass background file.  I'll see what I can do to lessen the load of it, but I like it.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      oops... misunderstood the miso soup thing... I was thinking of a competing writers' forum, but alas Sonya was talking about a published book of short stories...  sorry.... I take back the booooo thing and all that stuff about the foul angel from heaven and being forsaken, etc... sorry, nothing to see here.... *whistling a casual tune whilst pretending to read an upside-down magazine*
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Miso Soup?  *whimper, sniffle...*  Fine... Mark this Day!  The Drunkenfish writing forum will be BIG, you'll see.... Lo and behold the clouds parted and a holy light shined down upon the small drunken site exposing the young men of Benjamin and John who looked up at the Miso Soup God screaming.... "Boooo!!!  You foul angel from Heaven... we will not be forsaken...boooooo!"
     

    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      What the hell is going on over there in the tanque?  Those people are brutal with each other.  (Cat imprisonment, A mob of seething women, chickenhead licking, ...)  I'm sure glad we're so much more civilized over here at the drunkenfish.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      couldn't make it happen as a backdrop... anyway,  urlLink here  is the picture I was talking about.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Congrats on the NPR reference library gig, Amos!  Sounds like an organization that fits exactly with what I know of you.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      More English trivial differences...  People are always asking me if I'm alright?  "You alright Ben?"  It took me awhile to understand that they are just saying:  How are you? or What's up?  I'd get really strange looks when I would say "I'm fine... why?"  I was figuring they had noticed something wrong with me.  Also I'm told by loved ones around me that I have two looks in my way of dressing.  One is a country bumpkin (that's my flannel and jeans look), the other is the old man look (that's my sweater, button down shirt, and dress pants).  I was asked yesterday if I ever get stared at... I replied, "well... yes, but I thought..." (as I looked up to a room full of friends shaking their heads).  I'm told that if I'm going to pick up an English bird then I've got to change my American look.  Do I let others dress me and admit I look like a nerd?  Do I stand my ground like a man and say, "Rubbish, I look fine."?  or maybe I should just say, "I don't care what I look like, and then slowly transform on my own."   Some suggestions to me were 1.) Cargo Pants... sorry, never going to happen; 2.) Leather... maybe a jacket, but that takes money that I don't have at the moment; 3.) Lighter weight, darker coloured (yikes my spelling is changing) sweaters without the collared shirt underneath....hmmmmmm, no.  Damn it! I'm not a doll !!!  I think, I'm just going to go with the flowered Moomoos, sandels, and perhaps a comfortable bonnet. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Hmmmm.... Superpower?  I already have the superpower of being able to have an entire conversation with another person by only listening to the key words.  Is that a superpower or just being shallow?   The power to keep a job would be nice.  A little will power would be nice.  God-like power is out of the question because that would complete the process of removing me from humanity and I'm really doing my best to hold on to that.  I suppose I would like my eyes to glow red when I was mad at someone, like in "B" movies.  That would keep most people off my back. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I miss hearing from you John.  Are you giving your wife some quality time away from the posting?  Not that posting isn't real life or anything.....
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I didn't think I'd just be writing about all the minor, quirky little things that make England different, but I guess that's what's on my mind, so what the hell.  The toilets here have longer handles for the most part and are located on the opposite side of the toilet from the ones in the U.S.  It takes about 3 flushes for the water to actually start flowing, (this is not just the toilet in my current residence, it's all over) but once it starts flowing everything is off to the races down a very large toilet exit and a very large sewage pipe.  Toilets don't get stopped up here very easily because of the larger pathways to sewage freedom.  That's all and good I suppose, but it makes it very difficult for me to win my favorite game, "Beat the Toilet." 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Jim A. - I have noticed a change in Ned's posts as well.  Has Ned reached a new plateau of content with life?  Is he just at ease with himself because of the splendid heavy activity of tanqueville?  or as you said before, maybe he's just smoking alot of pot.  Anyway, Ned's new glasnost policy warms the heart.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Where's Decaffe Jake staying Jim?  I know you wish you could bring him along somehow?  ...and yes, marijuana should be legal and heavily taxed... but even though I am a drunk, I still think booze and cigs need to be taxed heavily too...and as I've mentioned before... CHURCHES NEED TO START PAYING TAXES!!!.... and while I'm at it... we should have a wealth tax and not an income tax.... Oh, I need to start getting ready to leave on today's field trip.  I'm going off to visit three of the coolest (according to Chris) castles of Wales.  I've been nagging him since I arrived.  Apparently the English don't get along too well with the Welsh, because everytime I mention Wales the people around me roll their eyes.  I like listening to the Welsh radio station here just to hear them talk in Gaelic.  Beautiful...  I can listen to it all day, but the English can only take a few seconds before their brains melt.  The castles I'm going to today, as expected, were built by the English while conquering Wales.  One last note before I scarf down my sausages and pork n' beans and head out for the day... the traffic lights here are a bit strange... you get a yellow light before the green light.   I suppose it gives you the chance to push the gas pedal to the metal so that you are ready to pop the clutch on the green.    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Back Amos!
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Damn, I was a depressing monkey last night.  Amazing what a couple bottles of wine will do to a person's emotional state.  Amazing what a good night's sleep will do to improve a mood as well.  Yuck, I think I'm gonna puke... not from a hang over, but disgust from the memory of being so sappily melodramatic.  Anyway, IT'S ST. PATRICK'S DAY!!!!!!!!!   Time to start drinkin'....
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I walked through Liverpool, but not much happened.  I saw the Cavern.  I saw the statue of John Lennon leaning against a wall.  Nothing hit me very strongly.  I did get into a discussion with Chris late into the drunken night about an old friend that committed suicide and tears came from my eyes, but I felt only too foolish for being so drunk.  Chris was very kind and I hate to use up my empathy points from other people just because I'm drunk and pulling forth emotional scenes that I should be well over.  It's very late here and (did I mention?) I'm drunk and I'm going to bed.  St. Patty is today and I've got to get what sleep I can to be as complaisant as my currently unsettled soul can be in the daylight hours of another drinking fest... night all.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Wahooo!  I'm sitting in an office building, looking over the fine city of Liverpool.  In a few minutes, Chris and I are going to look around the city and I (unlike Chris) will be looking for Beatle nostalgia.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm not a religious man, but this god-seeking man who I can tell by his bottle labels is obviously some sort of kindred spirit to John, makes an awesome liquid  urlLink peppermint soap  that doubles as a shampoo.  No, I wasn't paid off by a buddy to push this stuff... I just love it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Oooooooo Dreamweaver, I believe you can get me through the ni-hight!   Ok... I'm sick of reading my Dreamweaver book and I just started.  I can't wait to learn info like in the Matrix...  "Can you fly that thing?"  "Not yet...  Operator, I need a Dreamweaver 3, Flash 5, Photoshop 6, Fireworks 3, Dynamic HTML program and I need it now!" 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I hesitated to buy Jack and Cokes here, thinking maybe that was just an american thing, but everyone reassured me that every place has those.  Problem is they come in a glass slightly larger than a shot glass and only about half full.  Last night I was out in an Indian Cuisine Restaurant and ordered a Jack and Coke and the man said, "would you like that in a tall glass?"  I enthusiastically said, "YES!"  When I got the drink, it was in a very tall toothpick sized glass about 1/16th of the way full.  I have switched my drink now to cider.  There is lots of it and it's cheap.  I got the chance to jam on the guitar last night for the first time in a while.  I just played the standard blues riffs and chords, but it was loads of fun for me.  They have my brand of cigs here, Camel Lights, although they don't really taste quite the same and instead of it saying Turkish blend, it says American blend.  hmmm....
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I hit backspace and my last whole blog transferred to the great beyond... who knows where that is... anyway, here are some of the things I mentioned...  1.  There are huge thugs wandering the streets of Manchester with smashed in noses, no necks, and tiny blue eyes... straight out of a bugs bunny cartoon.  They're everywhere!  I think they are descendants from the rugged factory workers in which this city was founded.  2.  Coffee is huge here...much more than tea.  Everywhere I go, there is a Starbucks filled with people.  Everyone I met here has about 6 cups of coffee a day.  Must be a recent northern England phenomenum.  3.  I haven't found any good T.V. yet with a few exceptions.  There is a show called The Royales where a welfare-like Manchester family is just sitting on the couch every episode watching T.V. and the acting (as a rare exception from any other show I've seen) is very good.  The quiz shows here are all about british culture... I can't answer one damn question.  I'd rather be out and about instead of watching T.V., but I don't have transportation, so I'll entertain myself however I can for now.  I'm going to go out to a friend of Chris's tonight to jam and drink, so maybe I'll get some more real life stories to tell tomorrow.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I do have to mention Chris' darling little 3 year old girl Sophie, who I am completely impressed by.  We went into a restaurant today and she sat down in her chair and said in the cutest english accent "This is a fine place, isn't it?"   She then put her napkin in her lap and said to me, "you need to put your napkin in your lap, Ben."  I said, "You're right, thank you." and did so.  When my food came she asked me, "would you like me to cut that for you, Ben."  I said, "no, I think I can do that, but thank you very much for the offer."  She smiled and started trying to cut her own food.  (mommy had to help a little, but for christ's sakes... she's 3 years old!)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The keyboard command to post (if you ever have a defunct mouse) is "ctrl - enter".  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm here....  My first impression of Manchester is "Communist Indiana".   The countryside looks exactly like Indiana to me, but the buildings and houses are all red brick and exactly the same as if it were all government housing.  The roads are all about the size of bicycle paths and there are no overhanging wires.... other than all that, there doesn't seem to be much difference.  No one on the street says hello and when I say "hi" they just look at the ground and quicken their pace.  It all changes though when you are sitting down indoors somewhere public and they suddenly morph into the friendliest people you've ever met.  British T.V. is hilarious... the daily soaps remind me of poorly directed jr. high school plays, but the news stations are refreshingly international and seemingly unbiased.  It's funny to me to sit in a pub and look at two ladies in their sixties gabbing away over a glass of scotch as if they do that everyday (and they probably do).  So far, so good... I will have more to say hopefully once I've seen a bit more.  Now if I can just figure out the keyboard commands to post, then I'd be in business.... the box with my mouse hasn't arrived yet.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink SETI@home  has been out for some time, but for some reason I never signed up.  Feeling the guilt, after watching a SETI discussion group on T.V., I installed the screen saver and let it run all last night.  The data I was processing was recorded in December of 2000.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm going to add Chris Lea, my cousin, my boss, my landlord, my punching bag, to the drunkenfish.  I don't think he will be posting at all, but he wanted to check out blogger, so I added him just in case he gets the inspiration.  No more introductions for people on the drunkenfish and no one will be offended or anything if they are not added to blog links on any page.  I think that the drunkenfish is a different beast than tanque.  John has become the drunkenfish for me with his excellent posting, but I value all my friends on the drunkenfish regardless if they post or not, so with that...  cheers.  Jim S., let me know if those girls you talked about are interested in posting.  They are very welcome here.  Run to the fish.  Run to the fish.  All are welcome in the fish.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I couldn't go to bed without mentioning my God act thingy even though I'm sure if anyone read it, they just gave a distasteful look at the screen and moved on.  I guess I just know the people (Ned and John) talkin' about him or her or it (God), well enough to know that they know how much of a teenage brat I am about that subject.  I was thinking maybe they would find humor in my assness.  I hope that's the case.  Anyway, good night all.    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Hey!  Congrats, Ned.  You made the " urlLink blogs of note ."  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Amos - I can't help thinking how easy it will be for the government to manipulate the media and vice versa when all they have to do is make deals with a few individuals.  That's one big part of what scares me so much about all this loosening of limitations for media expansion.  The media argues that with the internet in place that no one is cut off from information, which is a good point, but I still think that too much power lies in print, radio, and television to let the expansion limitations disappear.  Thanks for the newsclip.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
        Conversation with God - A Play in One Act - by Ben    Ben: God, I think you're a crock of shit.  God: *no response*  The End  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I finally finished "Vampire The Masquerade -Redemption".  Wish I could say that was a cool novel or something, but no... video games are about all I spend my free time on these days.  So far, I don't have any paying customers, but there are several on the horizon and I'm doing sample sites to hook them into a deal.  I'm charging about $1000 per standard site with hosting included for a year.  We're all still working out the kinks in our process at the moment, but I'm hoping the company will be in full swing in about a month.  The company is made up of my Cousin Chris - Technical Director; His wife Bridget - Operations Director; Her brother John - Sales Director;  and moi - Web Designer. (I'm not actually legal to work yet, but that should be coming along soon as well)  I'm pretty excited about the whole thing and my end of the business is ready to go, so maybe now is the time that I should be sitting back and enjoying a good book.  Our company site, isn't exactly finished yet and to tell the truth, I'm not real happy with it, but I'm experimenting alot more on the other sites that I'm making and hope to improve the company's site by the time we're up and running. I've posted a few pictures.  I can't wait to take the camera out on the town one night.  Anyway, I've been moved by reading everyone's posts lately and wish I had something to add, but not much is going on with me and adult matters are not my specialty.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sean - I noticed that Drunkenbattleblog was blank on netscape soon after it was created and didn't know why.  However, my parents use netscape exclusively and I haven't felt the inspiration to fix the problem.  I suppose if anyone has a moment to waste on reviewing the code, I will listen and correct it, but  I just can't find the energy to address it myself for the reason of it being blank for my parents.  (if my parents are reading this... trust me... there's nothing to see there anyway.  Nobody has been drunk on the battleblog for sometime.  I know they won't believe me, but I thought I 'd say it anyway)
     

    
</post>

<date>18,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My love to you and your mother, John.  Send news at your convenience.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Dune the miniseries?   Didn't know that was out.  Didn't realize they were redoing  urlLink Planet of the Apes  either.  Man, first I get all riled up about the same old political issues that everybody has been talking about for the last three years or so and then I'm all excited about these two sci-fis that apparently everyone has known about forever already.  I need to start talking to other humanbeings, besides myself, for a change.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The F.C.C. is loosening it's rules on media expansion limitations  and America's reality is about to be narrowed.  I can't help thinking that the Republican atmosphere in the States is just handing over what remaining control they possess to the corporations.  Actually, perhaps the Republicans are the corporations and are just loosening restrictions on themselves.  Something funny is going on over there and I don't know whether my response should be shame or rage.  What if in the future, this period in history is known as the Corporate Coup?  The people have lost their voices and the corporations and the Repuppetcans are running amok.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Napster is funny as hell to me.  Just mispell your artist or title slightly and lo and behold, there it is.  do you want to find some U2?  well, try "youtoo".  Teenage dirtbag? how about teenage dirtbage.  If you want any Lennon, just drop an "n" (Lenon)   Easter is only slightly different here.  I wanted to dye eggs and hide them, but Bridget looked at me funny and said "Real eggs?"  I said, "Yeah, what do you hide?"  She said, "the kids here would start bawling and get mighty grumpy if they found real eggs instead of chocolate."  By the way, I got a big chocolate egg with my name written with icing on it.  Yum.  I asked if they could just hide little bottles of jack around the yard for me, but I suppose that would be too expensive.  Especially here. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm having fun tonight with my Google search on the main drunkenfish page.  I like seeing for instance who used the word "fuck" more often.  I'm sure I'll get bored with this soon and then it will be off to Ned's Google Search for more of the same.  I wonder how many times Ned has said "Hurm".
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I am feeling that the DrunkenBattleBlog is going to waste because Jim is busy moving, John is pretty much in the spirit of drunkeness 24/7 so he just posts on his site, and I live with a married couple and a little kid at the moment, so my drinking is way down.  If anyone would like to be a part of DrunkenBattleBlog, for those times when you just need to get it out in an altered state, please e-mail me with the title "Bring it on".  You don't have to post, but it will be there if you need it.  From this point out DrunkenBattleBlog will be completely anonymous (no name tags).  Unless you drunkenly reveal your identity on accident or on purpose.  My e-mail is   urlLink mindevol@hotmail.com            Remember, you don't have to post, but it will be there if you need it. This offer is not just for Tanquers or Drunkenfishies.... Anyone is allowed to DrunkenBattleBlog!
</post>

<date>10,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sonya - Congrats on the orange belt!!!  I think an axe kick is a glam metal term referring to the process of balancing your axe on your foot while swigging a bottle of jack and then catapulting it into the air to catch just in time for the solo. *snort*, *laughter*, *groan*  (Hey John, do you wanna take back that comment about me being funny now.)  Adam - I used to write music, but have temporarily put it aside until I figure out a decent way to make some money. You might think, "nonsense, you can play and do that at the same time," but actually I'm just talking about any money at the moment.  No money, No instruments, No inspiration.  I do Guitar/Bass/Harp/Sing/Songwriting.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Rob Corwin!  Ned actually lets his new people prepare and launch with style, but not here in the Drunkenfish.  You're just thrown into the tanque with the rest of the drunkenfish and told to swim.  Rob is an old friend of Ned and mine from jr. high, high school and my first college.  He is a very talented graphic artist with a masters in painting, so I'm hoping the blue and white bland screen that I stole from the blogger template will change as he learns html. I'd wait until he actually posts something before actually welcoming him in... (the drunkenfish doesn't have a very good reputation for introducing bloggers who actually blog.)  Thank you John and Jim for sticking around with me... I have high hopes Rob will be around for awhile as well.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Adam!  I hope you and the other tanquers don't mind links to your pages.  I read (almost everyday) the entire tanque pretty religiously.  Besides, I get a little jealous using Ned's page for links so much.  It's not Tanque.org/df anymore, but I just can't ween myself away from Ned's teat.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      well, at least it loads faster...
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      A few of my thoughts on Pop music-  1.  Pop music is time specific to the date in which a piece is written.  It is geared to please the masses using compositional methods commonly used in the now to please the largest possible audience of the now.    2.  A non-pop song can turn into a genre if others follow the styling, thus leading to sound-alike songs that can become pop as the genre progresses (or in most cases digresses).  I think it would be a mistake to call the creators of a genre, pop.  (Thus early punk will never be pop, but modern punk could creep its way to pop status if it isn't there already)  3.  The Beatles were very pop in their early days because they borrowed compositional methods from popular culture, but I would have to say that alot of songs on Revolver through the White Album were not pop because of the experimentation involved.  4.  Most of Pink Floyd was not pop because of the experimentation involved even though experimentation was popular, as was Pink Floyd.  5.  Pop should not be mistaken for commercial.  (Commercial being music created by a producer)  Shit... need to get back to work...   
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ugh... I am so frustrated with all the red tape and bureaucracy that I have to go through to get anything done here.  Today I went to accept a deal for an apartment and then they told me that I owed them 118 quid for them to process my U.K. credit check.    I said, "well, I don't have any U.K. credit.  I just arrived."  They (meaning the property management agency I'm dealing with) said, "Oh, well in that case you have to pay your entire rent up front or get a Guarantor (co-signer)"  I said, "Why can't you just check my U.S. credit?"  They said, "We don't do that."  I said, "Well why don't I go ahead and pay your processing fee and I'll tell you how you can check my credit in the States for about 30 quid."  They said, "Sir, we don't check U.S. credit."  I gave in and said, "Ok my boss will be my guarantor.  Just give me the Guarantor forms and I'll bring them back tomorrow."  They said, "We can't give you those forms until you fill out the credit check forms."  I said, "But I don't have any U.K. credit.  I just arrived."  They said, "I'm sorry, but you have to pay us the 118 quid and we have to process the form anyway."  I said, "But in a worst case scenario where I had the worst credit of anyone in all of the history of the U.K. it wouldn't matter because you are requiring me to have a Guarantor anyway."  They said, "I'm sorry, we have to process your credit report before we can continue with the process."  I said, "May I contact the landlord directly to work this out with him/her?"  They said, "I'm sorry that's privileged information."  I said, "ok, I'll tell you what.  I'm going to go home and fill all this out and I'll talk to you tomorrow."   (I'm not going to fight this because I just want the stupid apartment and start my life already, but sheeez!!!)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Birthday Chris!  May 30th  Happy Birthday Ned!  May 31st
     

    
</post>

<date>30,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'd post Ned's D&D stats, but it would be from my memory and what I know of him from the Tanque.  Besides, it's his birthday tomorrow and I wouldn't want to embarrass him with unusually low stats.... oh what the hell,  I'm game...  Ned's Stats -  Str - 13 Int - 16 Dex - 12 Wis - 15 Con - 14  oh yeah, and that high Constitution is because he is a big guy who can take alot of damage.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ben's D&D stats:  Str - 12 Int - 14 Dex - 13 Wis - 14 Con - 8  My ego might have boosted the Wisdom a little high.  Hmmm... what class would be best for those stats?  Perhaps a Bard...  What about a permanently drunk ninja in very poor health?  After all Benjamin Emerson is an anagram of "mm One Beer Ninja!"  or "Beer Ninja Omen m"  Didn't work out entirely with that anagram, but it's damn close.  I think I'll just have the m's officially removed from my name so that it works.  Benjain Eerson  It's just a little weird (like  urlLink Phil  said) to post one's own D&D stats, but how about this for crossing social faux pas lines:  Here's what I think John's and Jim's stats are:  John:   Str - 15  Int - 14  *Dex - 13  Wis - 16  Con - 14             Jim S.:    Str - 11  Int - 16  Dex - 14  Wis - 13  **Con - 15  *note- John's hand-eye coordination is about 17, but his lowered Dex score is due to my perception of his agility. **note- Jim's constitution might seem high for most people that know him on and off.  He's not a big guy that can take alot of damage type of thing... sheer will power and determination after he has chosen to put his Coors light down and get off his ass though...  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Wahoooo!  Bought my ticket to Amsterdam.  Leaving the 6th and flying back on the 9th.  Not long, but it should be fun anyway.  I'm meeting Rob.... can't wait.  I move into a new pad in "Didsbury", (That's the correct way to spell it.) on the outskirt of Manchester... heavy student area.  I move in on the 1st so I might be off-line until I get things set up.   Going to be a busy early June.  I've been convinced to shave my head this weekend.  Tres european, but I'm going to look like a freak with the amount of times I've been hit in the head.  Maybe it will give me the tough guy look I always have been lacking to pick up the chicks.  If not, I suppose I have enough money to cover that problem in Amsterdam. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      A  pound in your hand means something.   Lesser change doesn't quite do it; but a quid in the palm makes you feel like "shit, I can have this or that." It's a very solid coin.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I just witnessed a magpie making noice on the ground in front of a cheshire cat, sitting on a fence.  It was strutting in front of the cat that I have seen eat 2 of his offspring.  What feeling is that? It's not revenge.  It's not regret.  It's pride.  And I think I have never seen a "fuck you" so well displayed in all my life.   I loved it, and I'm not quite sure why.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      You go  urlLink Bill !  It seems as though, and I know I don't know you well enough to say this but, it seems as though you are outside of the game my friend.  You needed it.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've found a little section of life around Manchester's outskirts that reminds me of Little Five Points from Atlanta.  Not exactly, but I believe this will be where my home will be.  Ditsbury...I didn't spell that right, but I'll correct it later.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I really felt what  urlLink Liz  said yesterday.  Is the Fishtanque becoming self-aware?
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      alright... I'm falling in love with this R.E.M. album me... It's just like old R.E.M. albums that I slowly fell in love with me....me...me...me....  why not?  why?  I don't know.  It's just happening.... it's different from past R.E.M. albums, but that same slow love affair that grows more with familiarity and listening... listen... grow... me.  I hated it... I hated it's slow forced melodies... I find me after a while of it.... me... why?   I don't want my music to be that... so?  who cares... I don't have to be that... My friend is still there though.  I am still watching and listening to every friend the same way... doesn't matter how different... I'm still watching and I like. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Kudos is due Mr. Jeffords for his righteous separation from the right!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sean  - I wish I knew more about the Manchester music scene, but I've been staying in a house way out in the suburbs and I haven't seen much of anything but English T.V. since I've been here.  I'm moving out to a satelite city of Manchester called Altrincham on June 1st, so I hope to experience a bit more of the night life.  I haven't heard the name Joy Division in a while.  I can't say that I know much about them.  When I think of Joy Division, I think of a mix between the Clash and Velvet Underground.  (I may be way off there)  I'll certainly post my music scene findings as soon as I experience them.  I'm hoping that I will have alot more to post about after a month or so of getting set up in my new pad. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Two songs that are growing on me from Reveal:   urlLink Saturn Returns  and  urlLink Chorus and the Ring .  I know I said it all sucks, but I'm not listening to me anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Did I get your ass right, John?
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Virtual model of John after a month of his new routine.    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Great news for me... I just got my visa and papers that have been swirling around the governmental offices of the U.K. for a while.  I'm legit now until November of 2002.  Yeeeeeeeha!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I watched this really cool BBC program on Lake Vostok today.  Apparently they have found that life has survived for millions of years in microbial form, not by photosynthesis, but chemosynthesis (hydrogen sulfide more specifically) that is usually given off from heat vents that well up inner earth gases.  They also talked about a cave system that was teaming with insect life (all brand new species) that had been shut off from any contact from the surface (no light, or rain water or anything) for millions of years.  The whole ecosystem fed off of microbes that used chemosynthesis.  What makes me mention all this is the fact that I am totally consumed with astrobiology these days or at least the prospects of it.  Europa with it's deep water oceans under 4 miles of ice could be teaming with life.  Thank goodness there are dedicated scientists to do all the dirty work while I can just sit down for 30 minutes and watch a video about it.  By the way, I've put little pictures with colored splotches (not a very artistic way of doing it, but it works) next to the stories on the main drunkenfish page.  At the moment, all the pictures have red ovals which means that the newest chapter of that particular story is old.  Yellow means less than six months and green means that they have been created less than one month ago.  Maybe somehow I will be inspired to see some more green splotches... we'll see.  As always, I would be extremely eager to get the first chapter of a story from anyone.  My mom sent me an email thanking me for my contribution to her burgundy flowering plant for Mother's Day.  Ummm.... I suppose I should call each of my brothers to find and thank the responsible party.  In my defense, Mother's Day is celebrated on a different day here in England... I still don't think that would fly with my mom though.   
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I screwed up somehow, or my dreamweaver did, or something funky happened when I synchronized my site with the server... anyway, the drunkenfish page I designed is gone... no big deal I suppose, I'll just redo it.  R.E.M's new album sucks royal!  I have to admit, to me a band is a friend and it is always hard to let go of good friends when they have changed too much to be around anymore.  I've given R.E.M chances, but Up and Reveal are too far gone to continue my relationship with them.  Good bye old friend... I love you.  Coming soon in June will be my "Mars Blog"  A journal from my granddaughter Laika in the year 2066.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sonya?   ...damn!  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      There was an error in Regan's webpage that was preventing her posts from going live.  Along with the correction, I have put up some of her poems on her site.   urlLink Check it out.   
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I just can't send Regan to the Malebloge... not yet.  I ask of thee that thouest save poor doomed Regan for just a short while.  Thus now I ponder the eternal question (besides that "who am I?" crap).  Can a soul survive and return to the living after the torture of... THE MALEBLOGE!  Bwah, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha...  We'll see.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink "That wheel in the sky keeps on turnin'."  I hear ya brother Bill.  Praise be, my Perry, praise be.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I hear your name thrown around all the time and you've been on Ned's blogger list (without even having a blog) for ages.  Welcome Phil!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The Babel Fish is small, yellow, leech-like, and probably the oddest thing in the Universe. It feeds off of brainwave energy, and as a by-product, excretes telepathically, the intended meanings. The outcome of which is that if you stick a Babel Fish in your ear, you can instantly understand anything said to you, in any language.  The Babel Fish is, or rather was, the centre of a major controversy. The chances of anything so mind-bogglingly useful evolving by chance can be considered a positive proof of the existence of God. This causes other, greater problems.  As God will refuse to prove that he exists, as proof denies faith, and without faith He is nothing, He is confronted with a problem. The Babel Fish is a dead giveaway - it proves that He exists, and therefore He doesn't! God was reported to have vanished in a puff of logic at that point.  As the Babel Fish is now widely available from any convenient Sirius Cybernetics Corporation 'Babel Fish Dispenser Aquarium', most of the population of the galaxy have one poking in their ear. Thus, the Babel Fish has effectively removed all language barriers, and has consequently allowed so much more to be communicated; it has caused more, and bloodier wars than anything in the history of creation.    
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      ..so long and thanks for all the fish, Mr. Adams.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      gosh... have you ever written something really stupid, only to have blogger go down on you (like the crack slut bitch whore she is... but damn do I still love her) before you can delete it?    I spent the last 4 hours in nervous panic trying to get rid of my last post.  whew, it's gone!
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Birthday Jimmy Stewart!!!!  Wish I had some comprimising photos to post, but alas I'm in strict contract to certain media corporations to not display those pictures until it is in the best intrests of invested parties as to make a reasonable profit from such a posting.  I wish you would quit fucking around and get famous already.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      John- your ring is in the bathroom or the bedroom.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Heather - I was a mess when a death occured suddnely early in my adult life.  I don't know how I would react now.  I remember the shock and the feel of something ripped away without warning and feeling like, damn, that's not suppose to happen.  At the time, it also put me into a deep depression on a personal level because I realized my mortality and how my number could be up at any second and it also unleashed alot of other built up repressed feelings of my own.  I would like to think that I would be less selfish in my suffering now, but it's hard to tell until you experience it.  Anyway, I wish you the best in trying to cope with the feelings that make sense, like in honoring your friend, but also in those thoughts and feelings that don't.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Hello and welcome Regan!  Be sure to check out those hipsters over at Tanque.org.  They're extremely friendly people and I'm sure you'll have lots in common to talk about.    
     

    
</post>

<date>06,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've wanted to put out the 7th chapter of Crunch the Wonder Dog for some time now, but I've just not been into it enough... I feel I let Crunch down in the 6th, by not being enthusiastic enough with the story.  I know he is a made up dog, but I love 'em and I just don't want to let his spirit down again.  I've scraped the beginnings of 3 such 7th chapters because all I had down was the logistics of the situation, just like I did in the 6th.  hmmmmm....  I guess there is no need to rush a good rush.  If the 7th comes to me in a rush, like all of the best chapters I've written, then I'll put it up.  What I want to write about is Melody Howl, even though the story sucks... Maybe I should just follow my whims and keep writing Melody Howl in the disregard part of the main drunkenfish page to get me past this hump in writing.  I should probably be writing this babble in the drunkenbattleblog considering my condition, but it doesn't really fit there either.  Blah, blah, blah... The Fortress of the Vampire will probably be coming soon for Melody Howl.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Like the site Jimmy Stewart!
     

    
</post>

<date>04,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      some mars calender points of interests...  1. every unit of time will be 1.0275 times longer than its terrestrial counterpart, but we will use the same named units and structure.  2. The martian year is 669 martian days.  3. Since mars has an elliptical orbit, its seasons are of unequal length with 66 martian days in Leo (Leo 24 being aphelion 'farthest away from the sun') to 46 martian days in Aquarius (Aquarius 16 being perihelion "nearest to the sun')  4.  The dust storm season on mars starts in Capricorn and last until Aries.  Dust storms are caused by carbon dioxide being released into the atmosphere from the melting frozen antarctic during the relative hot southern spring and summer (it's much closer to the sun than the rest of the year) creating the atmospheric pressure of the planet to raise about 12 percent in the course of a few months. This causes the high wind dust storms that start at the south pole and spread north throughout the southern summer season, sometimes engulfing the entire planet.   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
         This is kinda cool to me.  This is the mars calender that will most likely be used by martian colonists.  Each zodiac sign represents the position of mars as viewed from the sun, so at midnight during that zodiac month, that constellation should be straight overhead.  If you put a penny on the diamond of a year of the outer circle (mars calender) and then put another penny on the 1st of January in the inner circle (earth calender) and then move them together one diamond at a time counterclockwise, you can determine the alignment of earth and mars at a certain time of year and the corresponding calender dates.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Whew... that was a much needed break.  I feel better now.  heh,heh...  I've been having dreams for about a month now on corporate media conglomerates.  The first one happened out of no where.... I wasn't even aware of any developing situation.  It was about my local newspaper in New Orleans buying up all the other newspapers in the States, one by one, and I was getting all worked up explaining to my family what was so horrible about that.  I woke up and turned on my computer that has the NYTimes as my front page.  Lo and behold the lead story was about the FCC loosening restrictions on corporate media expansion.  Anyway, it shocked me enough to feel a certain obligation in pursuing the subject, so I'm following my subconscious and posting links to articles when I run across them until the dreams stop or I lose interest, which ever comes last.  I haven't had whole dreams on the subject since the first one, but it just keeps  popping up in conversations throughout my dreams.    urlLink "If the flow of human communications is controlled by global media companies, how do we ensure that social and cultural points of view and political expressions that may differ from those of the companies who own the frequencies will be allowed to flow over the spectrum?"   
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Good - Happy Birthday Shari and David !!!   Welcome Heather !!!  Bad - My blog has been absolutely boring lately.  There is so much positive energy going on in this here bloggin' group, but I'm not a very positive person at the moment.  I'm going to take an unknown amount of time off from blogging, until I get an attitude change.  If anyone needs anything let me know.  My e-mail is on the battleblog and main drunkenfish page.  Ta.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I don't have the time to make a proper posting because I am on someone elses computer, but I just wanted to give my deepest sympathy to John for the death of his mom, and also to Rob Corwin for the death of his father.  I should be back online by mid July.   I miss reading from you all.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Moving Day!!!  I can't wait... Chris and Bridget and Sophie Lea have been extremely good hosts and have made me feel very comfortable living with them.  The business has had some unavoidable delays, so things haven't moved as fast as I would have wanted them, but hey, that's life.  June for me is going to be Flash, Flash, and possibly some more Flash.  The company start day is now set at mid-July.  Actually, although I would have liked to have been independent and rakin' in some money by now, it's probably best that things went this way.  The delays have allowed me the time to practice skills, get a better understanding of the competition here and what our company's direction is likely to be, legally get me set up to do things in a proper fashion instead of under the table, and enjoy a cool oppurtunity to hang with and learn from the Lea family.  I'm going to be offline for awhile until I get everything functioning in the new pad.  I feel like I've finally arrived in England today. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry, I know it's rude to make such nondescriptive posts like that, but I was really tired and just wanted to say something before I went to sleep for the next 24 hrs or so.  It was just a psychodelic experience basically, where the dosage was just a little too high for me.  My main fondness of the vacation was sitting with Rob at the cafes during the day, people watching and discussing the past, present, and future.  Shrooming has been tons of fun in the past, but a gram of Hawaiian is apparently too much for me these days to handle myself out in public.  I was suppose to hang with Rob until his train left, but I couldn't make it and opted for a cab ride back to the safety of my hotel room.  It was probably a terrible thing to leave a friend in that condition at a train station, but it really wasn't a choice for me at that moment.  Anyway, I made it back to the the hotel room safe and sound and within the hour Rob showed up again because he missed his train.  I was really glad actually that he made it back because I was in major guilt from leaving him there and I wanted to say "sorry".  He actually managed to reschedule his train in that condition and everything... I was proud of him because I couldn't have tied my shoes.  It was a long, long night after that without any sleep at all, with voices swirling around my head in foreign languages and jumps through various memories, and a stomach that wouldn't quit torturing me.  The night before the shrooms I was mugged walking home.  I wasn't hurt, but my pants were ripped off from the six guys who attacked me and my wallet with everything that legally makes me, me was taken.  The most embarrassing part was having to wave down a cab in my underwear and ask for a ride, even though I didn't have any money.  The cabby was very generous.  Anyway, I didn't think I was going to tell that part of the story, but I guess there it is.  I believe that it sent my thoughts in a bad direction during the next night of shrooms which aided in my inability to handle being out in public in an altered state.  The good thing is that I left my passport in my suitcase, so I didn't have any problems getting home.  Last night, back in England,  I woke up and there were hands reaching around the corner of my bedroom door throwing butterflies and flies into my room.  It really scared me until I realized that hallucinations are part of the game with shrooms (even though it was the next day)  The metaphor I guess is pretty clear to me.  I hope that was the last night of shit like that though.     
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I met up with Rob in Amsterdam.  All I can really say about the trip was that it was damn good to see Rob.   We chose the red pills and ended up much further down the rabbit hole than expected.  It was a strange trip indeed, but somehow we survived it.  Na zdorowie, Rob!
     

    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      - Congrats Clint! - Happy Birthday Liz! - I'm glad to hear you're back to work Phil.  It's always more fun to ball your meat than to let your meat loaf.  (Quote was borrowed from a recent Jim S. post which was quoted from something John said I believe... anyway, I just wanted to say meat loaf too.) -love the spicy scale, Sean.  Everything hot should have to include that on it's labeling.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm sitting in the world's biggest internet Cafe.  easyEverything!  Looks like about 10,000 terminals in here.  Well, as suspected I cannot find Rob anywhere.  We could have done this whole thing different, but what the hell, I'm in Amsterdam and having fun by myself.  Went to a few bars last night and tried to mingle with the locals.  Everyone I've met so far (that's about 5 total) has been really cool.  There's nothing like a trip to Holland to make you feel real unedumacated.  Even the beggars speak several languages  (There's quite a few of them around actually.)  I gave a bum 5 G yesterday and he gave me a piece of paper with his internet site on social and economic conditions of Europe.  That's http://www.geocities.com/eurodos for those interested. This is a city of beautiful young women, riding bikes.  It's like finding the secret valley of the butterflies or something... They're everywhere... (women on bicycles, I mean)  Well, my intention is to hit the museums today and go a little nutty tonight with some sort of self-indulgence.  I'm at the Linda hotel, just in case Rob reads this. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I leave for Amsterdam in 4 hours.  Cheap flights pick fun hours for travel.  I'm going to be dead sleepy when I get there.  The place I'd like to stay at has an internet cafe, so I should have no problem making a post or two from there.  After I get back, I will be moving and trying to set up my ADSL in the new pad, so I might be offline for awhile. (my guess is a couple of weeks, but who knows.)  Meeting up with Rob in Amsterdam is going to be difficult.  I tried to get him interested in starting a hotmail account so we could communicate on the net, but he didn't go for it.  Instead we're going with my mobile phone, but I really have no idea if it is going to work there or not.  It might just be me alone for three days, oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I first met Ned when I was in 7th grade.  I had just newly joined Troop 131 of the BSA and I found myself sitting in a corner a little scared because I didn't know anyone.  Ned came up and introduced himself and let me hang out with him.  I remember being so relieved.  I could easily have gone months without talking to a single person.  No offense to Rob (cause I love 'em too) who was in the same troop, but he never paid attention to me at all until he figured out that I could be a dungeon master for him.  It's a good first memory of Ned as being a selfless, generous person.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the system prevails.  My problem with dealing with the property management company yesterday was my concept of "they".  When I switched from talking with the person I was dealing with to the department's manager, my situation was completely different.  The manager, after my explanation of the situation,  was extremely helpful and said that she would return a portion of the fee for the application and said the remainder was for their efforts in setting me up and contacts to the landlord and that she would look into checking my U.S. credit and that most likely she could wave the need for a Guarantor.  Cool huh.  You have to be speaking with the right person to get things done properly.  Live and learn.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Heidi - um.... what John said.  It might not be original, but I feel the same way.  I don't correspond with you much, but I always read your posts and I think you are a very positive influence for me.  I wish you the best of birthdays.  By the way, you have a very bright yellow aura.  I can tell, even though I've never met you.  Cheers.  Clay, John, Ned - Sorry my memory doesn't go back that far anymore.  All I remember from the moody blues concert was John pouring a beer into the Sangria on the back of the truck and everyone getting pissed off.  I remember Clay carefully explaining to John, as if he were a child, why he shouldn't have poured that beer in there.  I faintly remember not being able to get into the venue for the concert and hanging out near a gazebo type of thing and listening to the music from afar.  That's about it.  Anyway, I'm sure I had fun.  Don't remember who all was there besides those two.  I do have to mention though that I think we, meaning Clay and I, went to more than one moody blues concert and thereby may have had two separate adventures; one with John, one with Ned.. or maybe two with both... I hope this helped us all understand... I'll shut up now.  Jim S. - Sorry, I didn't say it before... Congrats on the new job!  I've not said much because it's just typical Jim.  Keep on conquering my friend.  Liz, Heather - Kewlllll....  urlLink new domain for Liz,  and for  urlLink Heather .  Jim A. - You're such a good dude.  I know the drunkenfish is a wild unpredictable beast, but you stay in spirit always and I am very appreciative.  Thank you.  Through trial and error, eventually we'll get some posters who actually stay... you'll see.  Also I'd like to say, "damn, that is a cute baby... are you sure there wasn't some kind of mix up at the hospital?"  Amos - I probably shouldn't chime in here, because I don't have any suggestions, but I'm looking for a sci-fi writer with the same convictions as Ursula LeGuin (sp?) in fantasy.  I've never found them.  It all seems to turn into soap opera crap that could be placed anywhere in time.  I guess my suggestion, out of ignorance of what is around now, is to go back to Issac Asimov or David Niven.  Someone, help me find good sci-fi, please.  Amy - Whoa!  is that Motor Girrrrrrl going  urlLink pink ?  Kinda girrly isn't it?  I'm just giving you shit 'cause you said you'd be changing it soon.  Sonya - Love the art.  At first I thought it was a photograph and then I had to look at it a sec and I thought, wow... what a powerful view of visual CBD perspective.  Ben - I had one of those deep but painfully simplistic dreams last night, that I was crying and my mom came up to me and asked why I was crying.  I said, "It's nothing, it's stupid really, it's not worth telling you."  She said, "C'mon tell me, what was it?"  I said, "For some strange reason, I'm feeling distressed from the thought of how much pain has been distributed throughout the human race throughout time because of pure ignorance and lack of communication."  She smiled and said to me "I know what your feeling.  It's all true and you should know that feeling, but don't dwell on it.  It doesn't help you to dwell on that."   Well, I woke up.  Not much of a dream, but somehow I awakened feeling extremely naive and lost in the world and it took me a few minutes and a cup of coffee to feel more in touch (or less, not sure).  Just thought I'd share. (I'm not trying to be deep here, I'm just telling the dream as it happened.)  I've been off balance all day.  I talked to Chris today at a Cafe about some personal things in life that troubled me, but I didn't really feel like it was me telling him this.  I was wandering somewhere above, looking down, and thinking "is this real?"  I didn't feel connected to my voice.  I'm not a teen-ager, he doesn't want to hear my bullshit.  Am I growing old enough to know that my problems are trivial or am I just realizing that sometimes I just talk to hear myself talk?  I really don't know.  Anyway, I used to feel better after confiding in others, but now I just get this really empty feeling that takes me a day or two to shrug off.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sean  - Tenacious D rocks!  So that's how it's done... thanks, Jack Black.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm finding that Web Design entails alot of script writing.  Duh... Why can't it just be about playing with pretty colors and inserting stolen pictures from the web...  You mean you want your page to actually do something?  Shit.  I suppose it will get easier as we develop a library of these things over time.  Hopefully, my lack of Java knowledge will improve as I bungle through simple scripts with the help of Chris.  I'm sure I'll be crusin' the net, stealing whatever I can find that's close to what I need to make happen.  sigh...  I wonder if Pizza Hut is hiring.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Amos  - that's the intro to a song called Pinkeye from Ween's "The Mollusk".  I thought it sounded drunkenfishy enough to be the drunkenfish theme.   urlLink Clay  - Welcome Bro!  I told everyone of your appearance before but it was at the very end of a long day of posting so I don't know if anyone read down that far.   urlLink Ernie  - I don't know you, but welcome to the drunkenfish.  A friend of Jim Stewart is a friend of mine.  I'll try to get some links up to your page sometime today.  Clay and Ernie - Be sure to check out  urlLink The Tanque .  Otherwise, the posting might seem a little confusing.  Besides.... it's just great reading material.   
     

    
</post>

<date>25,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Beautiful baby!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've disconnected my setihome link on the main drunkenfish page because a gambling page has taken it over.   I can't think of anything to combat it, so I'm just getting rid of the link until it comes back legit.  I e-mailed a couple of possible interested parties.  That's all I can think to do.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm venturing into unknown land by inviting my beloved brother into the drunkenfish.  I hope he stays with us.  Welcome,  urlLink Clay .
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Shit, I didn't get much done today work wise.  Cruisin' through insurance company webpages to get an idea on what I should do in designing one.  On the otherhand though the Drunkenfish had a productive day.  Had a blast reading on the  urlLink drunkenbattleblog. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Check this out , Rob Corwin was just in a cool art show.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Hang in there George Harrison .  It's been a rough decade for that man.  When John Lennon died, Will Sibley and I spent weeks trying to show each other that we were bigger Lennon fans than the other by acting out a constant state of depression.  I remember being truly hurt, but I was also aware that I was putting on a little more of a performance than was needed for the oscar.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Amos  - Ethniklashistan is finally a solution from the U.N. that goes beyond the desires of the countries in power and focuses on the need for peace and stablity in our world.  Oh yeah, and Amos, I just received a letter from President Bush saying he was going to send me a check for 300 bucks.  Well, God bless President Bush!  I always liked that guy. 
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink John  sent me some pictures the other day of him and his wife and "the unknown man" out in the bright light, beach, palm trees, etc... I'm thinking, cool, vacation pictures, but I keep forgeting he lives there.  That's an everyday thing.  Must be nice.  ( Am I subconsciously pitching Florida again... what's with me?  Maybe it's because here in beautiful Manchester England I haven't seen that yellow thingy in a while, what did they use to call it... oh yeah, THE SUN!!!)   By the way  urlLink John , loved the nanotech articles.  It makes one go wildly into futuristic tangents of thought.  I think though that they are being a little misleading by talking about the very beginnings of the technology research happening within a decade and then without any reference of time, leaping to what nanotechnology, to my understanding of it, won't happen for another hundred years.  One can envision dropping a drop of fluid from an eyedropper on top of a skyscraper (steel, ceramics, copper, glass, silicon, etc... ) and in that drop would contain thousands of tiny robotic assemblers, half of which are programed specifically to assemble more assemblers.  What armed monster robotic army from hell, all carrying little vials of this fluid, could be formed from that.  Probably one plenty big enough to take over airports and other transportation centers nearby to spread out through the world fairly quickly.  yeeeeshhh!  I know that's a pretty limited vision of nanotechnology, but hey, it's fun day dreaming about it.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      alright, I'm starting to miss my daily Ned blog.  Where has our hero wandered off to?  Everyone needs their moment of peace and relaxation, but I'm a selfish person who needs his Ned fix!  Ok... breath Ben.... Ned is a real person who needs the same things as you and everybody else does.... whewwwwwww... ok... I accept your absence Ned.... I'm ok with that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      There's really no mercy in the word mercenary, is there?   urlLink Look at what the new nazi party is up to now .  What are we allowing to happen?  Can we honestly condemn the Germans for not seeing what was going on?  Hopefully we can, and we'll change this before we are too deep in the shit. The domestic problems of this country should be handled within this country.  We can't bully the world into solving our problems.  Bush really is scaring me.  Who is responsible for keeping his actions under control... us?  Shit... how do we do that?  It seems we've given him a free four year pass to play our system for everything he wants out of it.  He's a crazy man.  How do we impeach him before he does too much damage?
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Cletus, grow up, will ya... You can't stay in mommy your entire childhood.  Perhaps that may mean losing some of your comforts, but that's life.  Welcome to the real world.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I get these patties out of a box and throw them on the grill.  The front of the package says contains select cuts of 100% Beef, and of course the 100% Beef inside a picture of a blue ribbon is huge.  So I'm thinking, cool... until I bite into it.  Jesus!  This can't be real beef.  I flip the package over and see the multitude of ingredients.  I flip back to the front and notice the word "contains" suddenly has a slightly different meaning to me.  Bastards! 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sounding like I was pitching Florida there in yesterday's blog, but mainly I was just thinking of my dog.  I'm on the wagon from booze and cigs.  We'll see how long that lasts.  Gotta shake up the old physical body and rejuvinate the soul every now and then.  I think that if I could drink without smoking then I would never smoke again.  Unfortunately...
     

    
</post>

<date>18,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I used to live in a house... in florida... a sanctuary in the middle of an urban wasteland... with my dog Louie.   damn, what I would give to be back there now.  Sorry, just remembering a nice moment in my life.  I move on.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Some notes on Mars Blog: I knew when I started that this was a little too involved of a project than I was willing to put the effort in for, but I went ahead with it anyway, because, what the hell, it's only a blog.  Not too much lost if I give up or fail.  Jim S. has hinted at wanting to keep a  character journal on the same blog as Laika.  I would very much like other writers on the Mars Blog.  I'm afraid that if I just write it by myself that it will disappear in a month or so.  Some guidelines, actually the only guideilines, is that I'd like to keep it believable.  (Even though I'm hinting in my last post of a martian ecosystem beneath the surface, that doesn't necessarily mean that will happen.)  Major issues that would affect everyone, should probably be bounced around a little first.)  Also the writing should have a reason for being on Mars.  I would rather not have a Deep Space Nine on my hands that is just a soap opera that could be just as easily in Beverly Hills instead of Mars.  That all said, anyone who wants to start up their own character is cool with me to give it a shot for as long as they want to keep it up.  If you want your character in a different city, career... all that's probably preferable, but I'd like to at least keep the time and dates for posts sychronized somewhat.  I'll send a copy of the number of days in each month and an explanation of time units on Mars for those who are interested in writing. Basically you can look at the date and just add one day if you are posting on the next day in our time.  It sounds like a huge effort to get involved in, but no love will be lost for anyone who starts and quits or writes incredibly bad or anything.  The readers don't have to know who is writing what character story either.  It will be your show, it's just for fun.  I hope some take me up on the offer.   
     

    
</post>

<date>16,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, Heidi.  I haven't heard the name Will Sibley in ages.  I used to hang out at his house everyday from about 5th grade to 7th.  We made an awful movie together and formed my first rock band where we mainly would just pose and mimic the Beatles.  My parents finally baned me from seeing him because we played hooky from school in 7th and got drunk on Gin and orangejuice and rode the bed matresses down the stairs all day at his place.  I'm not sure who told on me in that scenario, but even if it was Will, I forgive him.  I had gotten away with it scott free until the Principal called my mom three days later.  Cheers to Will, an old friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've grown to love all the black and white movies they show on T.V. here.  There's always some character with a silver flask, who always offers it to the hero.  Some movies the hero takes a swig, others he politely declines.  Just an uninteresting observation, I thought I'd pass on.  By the way, Chris Hill, everyone here calls shopping carts, trolleys.  I guess that makes everyday kind of funny in that way for me.  I'm just casually wandering around in random fashion with today's post.  A "cowboy" here is a hack.  Took me a little while to figure that out, because it's very common to use the expression in commercials.  Speaking of commercials, has anyone seen my favorite commercial of all times.  It's a new Guiness ad shown here in Britain called The Dream Club Ad.  Damn, I love that commercial.  One last random note of pleasure, I told my Plumber as he was walking out the door to "have a good one."  He paused in confusion for a second and then said with a smile, "Oh... right, Cheerio!"    
     

    
</post>

<date>14,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      flies... I don't know what to make of 'em.  part of me want's to kill 'em.  part of me wants to understand 'em. part of me wants to understand them and then slowly torture them into reality. I don't think that's too heathy an attitude.  just a thought.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I love Jim and John so much sometimes it hurts.  ok... I have to ruin it by saying that I'm drunk, but what are you going to do about it.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Strange days indeed, most peculiar mama.  Maybe it was just my hangover, but I walked around the streets today with a psychic mind from hell.  Every person I saw came a flood of information about that person.  I'm guessing that it was all my imagination, but I felt as though I could see everyone for real.  Strange indeed.  An old man strolling along with his overloaded walker, full of groceries was walking next to me.  At first, I felt pity, then I noticed he was jamming out with headphones to bob dylan.  A whole wave of thought enveloped me.  He had a smile on his face.  I looked around and I saw a girl holding the hand of another girl and I noticed that she held a poster in her hand and that they were shopping together and were having fun.  I started to look at all the people around me and realized I could tell a lot from just looking at them.  All these people were, when it comes down to it, a lot like me.  I had to just sit down on a wall and watch for a while.  Why haven't I noticed this before?  Maybe I've been a self-centered bastard all my life.  Don't know...  I seemed to be able to make up whole lives around all the people that I saw.  Probably, way too much assuming, but it made all of these people real to me.  Suddenly, I was not alone at all in this world.  I could see the pain, joy, boredom, rage in all these people by casual observation.  I'm still piecing all this together, but I can't explain what a revelation this morning was to me.  I'm afraid this only shows my narrow tunnel vision I've had all my life, but I thought I'd relate the feeling somehow.  anyway, I'm going to head off to the library again.  I hope these thoughts don't turn into some bad acid trip kinda thing, because they feel intense to me.  I hope it's just me growing up and that this particular feeling is just a natural human evolution thing that happens to everyone.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry Jim, I just couldn't take it any longer with the 3's company theme.  I'm just not man enough.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've invited an old friend, Chris Hill, to join in on the drunkenfish fun, but as always I don't expect much posting because he is in the Navy and doesn't have the time to post regularly.  Anyway, he's up and can post when he likes.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I can't think of five albums I lick drunken wounds on, maybe it would be easier to think of 5 albums I listen to that I don't lick drunken wounds to.  I listen to the white album definitely, and pink floyd's wish you were here, and R.E.M.'s Green, and Moody Blues' To our Children's Children's Children, although that seems a bit sappy musically.  I guess to round that off I listen to John Lennon's Plastic Ono Band.  Here are 5 songs that I've stolen from Napster that I tend to gravitate toward when I'm drunk as well.  urlLink 1. SpaceShip - Sean Lennon   urlLink 2. Girl From the North Country - Bob Dylan   urlLink 3. Uncle Albert - Paul McCartney   urlLink 4. Given To Fly - Pearl Jam   urlLink 5. Baby Bitch - Ween 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sean - It's been on the news here that the conservative party is advocating the legalization of marijuana to separate it from the element of crime.  Their philosophy, which makes sense to me, is that marijuana only leads to harsher drugs like heroin if the people who buy the pot have to buy it from the criminals who also are involved in other illegal sales of drugs.  The conservative party?  I don't get it, and am just assumming that either I'm just dreaming or that it is some desparate Tory scheme to recapture the youth vote.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ughhhh!!!!  Jimmy has hacked the main Drunkenfish page song!  I'll leave it up for a while 'cause I'm still laughing at it.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I finally get back online and blogger is down.  Damn.  I'll publish later I suppose.  Man, it is good to be back.  I can't believe I went more than a month without the internet.  Did I learn new and exciting activities while I couldn't play on the net?  No!!!  I sat in my chair and stared at my computer in disgust the entire time.  I'll try to start up the Mars Blog today and write in some excuse for why it has taken so long for our hero Laika to get there.  Alot happened while I was gone, and I'll try to read back on some of it, but I'm sure alot of it will just have to be missed.  I haven't started reading yet, but I'll start tonight. My company hasn't started yet, but the pieces are coming together now and everyone is back from vacation so I'm starting to get excited.  Soon, I could be actually working again.  Never thought I wanted to work, but I am soooo bored that I trully would like to get started.  I'm starting to see a little more of England now.  I've been hanging out at the public library these days, because without money, that's the only place I can think of to hang out away from my apartment.  Anyway, good to be back.  
     

    
</post>

<date>31,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
        Cool LOTR movie pic.  It's not a painting.  You can really see that the artists from all the LOTR calenders they used to put out have an influence in the movie design.   urlLink Here's a site with a bunch of them. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Whoa!  JimS., I forgot about Bob and Pete.  (The Roaches in Fat City)  In reality we didn't just have two roaches, one named Bob and one named Pete.  Roaches don't actually come in pairs like that of course.  There were hundreds of those cute little guys.  We just called anyone we saw that was lean and mean, Pete, and the fat and slower ones, Bob.  Since John and I both slept on the floor, it was easier to handle their presence by pretending they were pets.  You'd wake up in the middle of the night and see right in front of your eye this big roach with long antennae feeling all around and instead of screaming, you'd say, "Hey Bob!", with a loving smile.  Then one would dart across your toes and you'd say, "My, my, aren't we fiesty tonight Pete... Goodnight boys, gotta big day tomorrow so I have to try to go back to sleep.  Have fun!"
     

    
</post>

<date>29,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      JimS.- I realize you said take these facts with a grain, but just for interest's sake I believe the fourth closest star is Banard's Star and it's only about 6 light years away, meaning you would only see 6 years into Earth's past.  I think.  I love the facts spread though.  I've always wanted to know the speed stuff, but never got around to looking it up.  Cool. I love that shit.  John - What can I say?  I think of you often.  Happy Birhtday, my friend!!!  Let's see here, I've already told the story about how we met in the restroom at highschool and you introduced yourself by playing your drumsticks on the urinal while I was taking a pee and you asked me to join your band with Dale Bryant.  I thought you were a freak then, and I still do now.  I should be able to come up with some John story I haven't told a million times.  There's a bunch of police stories I know, like drunkenly falling down the escalator in front of the policeman, and drunk driving a van across a golf course with a bunch of police cars chasing you at an amazing 15 mph until you drove into a sand trap, and losing your job at the carwash when you forgot to lift a lever and knocked the cherries of a police car...  Well, I digress.  There are too many of those kind of stories to tell and besides, that's all behind you.  There's plenty of drunken stories like, Fat city brawls, the gay nightclub in West Palm, the hot tub incident in Carmel... nevermind... I can't do that to you.  ...and you might resort to an eye for an eye.  How about a few good locational memories?   The kitchen in Fat City where The Great Condiment War started, where the linoleum drunken water slide was created, where we hung all of our cool artwork.                                                                     The band room in Muncie,  where you slept with your head on the pillow in your bass drum, where we finally realized the extent of Jimmy's morning grumpiness when he visited once, where we played Revolution for             Lisa McMullen, where we had countless parties and wrote many songs.  O.K. all that was just for John's memory, but here's a story about John. Don't worry John it's not about the cancer/jockitch mix-up that you went to the hospital for either.  Actually it's not a ha ha story.  It's not even a single event story.  It's kinda sappy sentiment.  It's an observation about John that changed my life completely.  I was always concerned throughout my young adulthood about whether I was good enough to be friends with this or that person or were they good enough to be hanging around me.  I had this whole level system going through my head.  I used to watch John hang around and have serious discussions with people I considered trash.  I saw it as a huge flaw of John's.  I didn't realize what emotion I was perpetuating constantly about these people.  It was hate.  I never bothered actually talking to people to find out about their true character.  As time went on and I had more and more life lessons of my own, I discovered that John had always been a saint with strangers.  He just seemed to learn that hate wasn't worth it very early on in his life.  My level system has almost, but not completely, dissolved by now and it's been a liberating concept for me.  I have to say that observing John's empathetic behavior towards others throughout my lifetime has made me a much better person.  Thank you John.  P.S.  If any gorgeous women got all choked up about that last paragraph, my e-mail is mindevol@hotmail.com.  I would love to get together and discuss it in person.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Amy - I just explored your links and took a look at your friend Melissa's blog and she says she's dreaming about throwing things around, breaking things, and hanging out with you.  With you dreaming about earthquakes, maybe you two share a common situation that has slipped into both of your subconsiousness.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      This weekend I was at Chris's throwing the football (american) around and a Limey named Ian actually went to that so often talked about place that I've defended in my mind a million times over.  The American Football Player is a wimp for wearing pads thing.  It went something like this.  Ian :  "Have you ever heard about or seen English Rugby?"  Ben:  "Yeah, but I haven't seen it much on T.V since I've been here.  Is it out of season?"  Ian :  "Yeah, Cricket is being played alot now on T.V.  Rugby is a little like American Football, but it's a little rougher of a game.  They don't wear pads like in American football."  Ben:  I wanted to smile, nod my head, and politely say, "yeah...yeah... So I've heard."   but what instead came out of my mouth was.  "Yeah, I'd like to see what would happen if an average American 350 lbs defensive guard met an average 180 lbs English Rugby player in an ally."  Ian :  "Then the American Football player would definitely need his pads."  Ben :  "I think the pads are used in American Football because the players would die if they hit each other with the force that they do.  I guess frolicking around on the grassy field with your pretty colored, pulled up socks and your shiny silk shorts is enough to protect you from an English Rugby hit."  Ian :  He said something that everyone laughed at after that, but it didn't matter to me because I didn't hear it.  I was already reveling over my cleverness in a dream-like trance of pride.  So, I might have lost the arguement.  I don't know, but at least I convinced myself that American Football is rougher than English Rugby.    I don't even watch sports.  I have no idea what I was trying to accomplish.     
     

    
</post>

<date>27,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Brad and Mitch!  Enjoy the Blogging experience and be sure to discover Tanque.org.  These are the folks that most of our dialog is with.  If either of you like to do any creative writing, I've tried to keep it a theme of the Drunkenfish.  Currently there are only three projects in the queue.  1. The Mars Blog - Create your own character in the year 2066 and keep a journal of this person's activities in a martian colony.  2. The DrunkenBattleBlog - whenever the urge strikes you to write in a drunken state, you can have at it.  It has become more recently used for the day after, but there are no rules.  3. Stories on the main Drunkenfish page - Currently it's just pieces of my stories, but this is the oldest running project and the one closest to my heart.  I'd like to take down some of my stories that have hit deadends, but in order to keep the idea up, I'm leaving them there until others write some stories.  If any of these projects interest you or if you want to create a new project, just let me know at  urlLink mindevol@hotmail.com
     

    
</post>

<date>27,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My best wishes are with Carrie and Shari on their journey back to academia.  In accordance with what Ned said, I almost wish sometimes I was taking classes, almost.  By the way Carrie, I always favored merchandise with anything to do with Grover from Sesame Street, but I'm sure you probably have different tastes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>25,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've not broken a single bone my entire life, except my skull.  1. Age 3:  My brothers dropped an airgun from the roof of a fort on stilts onto my head in which led to me running around the back yard with blood spurting from my head like chicken on Sunday morning.  Stitches on that one. Not sure how many.  2. Age 10 - Rock fight!  Alot of bleeding from the head, but I don't think my skull was in too bad of shape.  3. Age 21 - On a tab, my friends decided to lock me in my room for my own protection, but instead I decided to escape out of my bedroom window, which didn't lead outside directly.  It lead to the basement stairs.  I got out to the basement stairs ok, but the door to go outside from there opened into the stairs and my friends came around to stop me from escape.  Well, the door opened and I went backwards down the stairs on my back and through 5 pane glass windows which were laid against the wall at the bottom of the steps.  I remember lying there looking up at a silhouette at the top of the stairs that said, "Is he dead?"  I'm pretty sure I wasn't.  4. Age 26 - Clay told me the damn rope swing was safe and that they used to swing on it all last summer.  I grabbed the broom stick through the knot on the rope and swung over the very large chasm only to hear "snap".  Next thing I remember was what seemed like an hour long ride down the hill on my back using my head as a battering ram to clear the path.  I climbed back up the hill afterwards with bloody head and face and was offered a fifth of scotch by loving brother Clay, not to tell his wife.  I accepted.  All in all though, I think I'm just fine.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Dave - No, I don't have anything but memories of my grandfather.  I do remember reading through a book called "The Bluebook Project" and reading a testimony by Jimmy Carter about a UFO sighting and looking up to see my Grandfather smile at me.  I thought he was going to take it away from me, but he wasn't concerned.  I was about 7 years old I think.  That's about it though on the UFO thing.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Clay, you ignorant slut -  I didn't mean to trash the reputation of a great man.  I just thought it was kooky and entertaining that when I typed his name into google, I got all this UFO stuff.  I only quoted that article, because that was the only article I found that had something to quote besides his name listed and the photograph.  Personally, I'm not ashamed that he was a founder of the NICAP, but I suppose you and Dad disagree with me.  So there!  THpbbbphhht!  P.S. I've removed the quote, but not the page.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've never met you, but I'm always learning new words from your blogs.  Happy Birthday Jim Robinson!  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Wow, my grandfather was one of the Real Men in Black.  I did a search on google for him and it came up with a bunch of pages on UFO's.  His name is Col. Robert B. Emerson.  He was one of the founders of the NICAP.  I told my Dad, but I think he doesn't want his father to be remembered for that.  I think it's cool.    Here's a  urlLink page.      some other pages I found him on include:   urlLink http://members.evansville.net/slk/state64.htm                                                                 urlLink http://www.li.net/~rjcohen/nicap.html                                                                Here's a picture of him, but they named him Ralph B. Emerson by mistake                                                                   urlLink http://www.nicap.dabsol.co.uk/photo.htm    
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ben's Resume  Objectives -  To get as much money as possible for doing a half-ass job until my eye catches something better to do.   College Career -   Two years at Ball State in Music Theory  1 semester at Dekalb Community College to prove that I could read for Georgia State University.  2 semesters at Georgia State University in Music Recording and Production.  2 semesters at Georgia University as an Anthropology Major.  2 semesters remaining at Georgia University as a History Major  2 semesters back at Georgia State University in Political Science  2 semesters back at Georgia University as an English Major.  2 semesters and then graduation with a BA in Geography and a minor in History from Georgia State University.  GPA 3.3/4.0  All D's and F's were removed from my record upon every college transfer.   Work History -  Current Job - Web Designer - Greenforge Consultants Ltd. - Manchester, UK - 7 months and still going strong  Systems Administrator - The Blood Center - New Orleans, LA - 1and a half years - quit  Network Technician - Adeeta - New Orleans - 6 months of contract work  Night Supervisor - Pelican Park - New Orleans, LA - 8 months - quit  Book Store Clerk - Waldenbooks - West Palm Beach, FL - 4 months - quit  Clerk - Texaco - West Palm Beach, FL - 1 month - quit  GIS Programmer/Cartographer - West Palm Beach County Government - West Palm Beach, FL - 2 weeks - never returned from surprise drug test  Photographic Production Engineer - National Enquirer Publications - 2 months - quit  Waiter - Appleby's - West Palm Beach, FL - 2 days - quit  Home Inspector - 5th Avenue Buliding Inspections - West Palm Beach, FL - 1 year - mutually agreed with boss to move on  Home Inspection Report Reviewer - Radon Analytical Laboratories - Indianapolis, IN - 1 year - quit  Laborer - Middle Earth Service Company - Indianapolis, IN - 3 months - quit  GIS Programmer/Cartographer - Gwinnett County Governement - Lawerenceville, GA - 1 year - quit   Enviromental Science Teacher - Outdoor Activity Center - Atlanta, GA -  signed up for 6 months, did not sign up for a second term.  ((This is where I graduated from College))  To go into my job history before this poiint would be extremely time consuming and insane.  I count close to 40 jobs from what I remember.   Activities -   Garage Bands, T.V., Computer Games, Miscellaneous chemical abuses, Amnesty International, job hunting.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The attitude that I've always expressed with my clothing has been that "I don't care about my clothing."  This is a skill that I have dedicated much time and effort to masterfully craft.  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The picture on the right also spells a word.  The picture on the left is a couple kissing under an arch of grapevine.  It took me forever to see the one on the left.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well my company's site went live today.  It's still not finished, but the main framework is done.  Still need to add pictures, sounds, and my portfolio, but  urlLink here  it is.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Clay - Happy Birthday tommorrow!  I think you're taking your frustrations about your lake out on that poor innocent man, the Governor.  If I were you, I'd go over to Jim's, get really drunk, and then spout off your opinions to his neighbor in person.  But that's just me I guess.  Jim S. - I think the haze is boredom and the only thought to keep you going is that there must be something better just around the bend.  If there isn't anything naturally occurring around the bend, I'm sure you'll create something wonderful anyway.  Hank - I miss ya.   Heidi - You cheeky bird!  Are we feeling randy?  Are you wishing from all these responses that you didn't even mention the boy crazy thing?
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
        &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;  Just two pictures that I like.  You can see two different things in both of them.  The one on the left is a little more difficult to see.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Mon Dieu!  It works.... If I could just get blogger to make my first date the right size, I'd be in business.  Check out the links.  FLASH!  Ahhahhhhhhhhh.... Savior of the universe!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My site here is going to be under construction for a while.  I'm trying out a few things a little at a time.  Maybe in a week or so, I'll have a finished design.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've been wrapped up in business B.S. for awhile.  Things are starting to pan out into a steady work rhythm now, so I hope I can start posting more regularly.  I love the new designs I'm seeing.   I'm jealous as hell.  As soon as I get a free weekend, I'll have to try to keep up with the Jones'.     urlLink Sonya  - Wow...  I absolutely love your artwork.    I can't get over what a talented bunch of people this group is.  You guys always surprise the hell out of me as I learn more and more about you.  Not much going on here... work, work, work.... I'd like to talk about something else, but that's all there seems to be at the moment.  I know, I'll make another trivial differences of England and the States list.  Some good things about England -   1.  A jar of peanut butter only costs about 60 cents and really tastes like it uses real peanuts.  Soup in a can that says it has meat in it, actually has alot of meat in it.  2.  A great deal of the T.V. announcers here have severe lisps.  (It cracks me up at least once a week.)  3.  After a rain, these giant snails come out everywhere.  These things are huge, and look like something out of a Lewis Carroll story.  Also, I prefer magpies to crows.  Magpie's just seem to have a whole lot of personality.  They look just like crows except they are white with black wings and a black head.  4.  English documentary's are in my opinion the best in the world, and I get to see alot of them here.  5.  I've got hypothyroidism and have to take a pill everyday and go to the doctor's for a blood test once a year.  The visits to the doctor and medication for this is free for me here.   Some bad things about England -  1.  England closes at 11pm.   2.  You have to pay a monthly tax to watch regular airwaves T.V.  Also, I pay an $800 city tax (for fire, police, museums, etc...) on top of all my regular taxes.  (The English sure do know how to tax.)  3.  All the radio stations have the same fucking dance beat 24/7.  With my napster now out of reach, I'm in musical hell.  4.  A bottle of Jack cost about $50 and a pack of cigs cost about $7.  (It's kind of good, I guess, 'cause I've had to quit both.) (wine and beer are the same price as in the States)  5.  Tabloids, tabloids, tabloids!!!  This country is star gossip crazy!  Well, that's good enough for now.  I haven't sat down and actually read through the blogs in awhile.  I'll try to catch up on the most recent ones.  I hope everyone is doing well.  Cheers.    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome back  urlLink Becky. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      wow, thanks for the  urlLink link  Ned.  The Cave of Time brings back memories.  I think I read all of Edward Packard's Choose Your Own Adventures. I even wrote my own in sixth grade.  I think I got to about page 200 before I quit.  Of course it was complete with my own pencil illustrations.  Wish I could find that.  It must be somewhere in my parents' attic.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Jim A.  - I like swami.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah.... someday I'm gonna own this pathetic little island.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sean  - I like the new look.  I almost feel like changing mine now.  Don't have that kind of energy at the moment though.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Let me set things right about the Chris thing....  Chris Lea is my boss, cousin, friend, money source.  Chris Hill is my friend, Floridian,  Navy guy, Jenwei totin' mutherfu...  I love them both very much.  hope that clears things up.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      CHA CHING!!!!  I just sold my first website to an insurance company for over a thousand quid!  That's about $1,400.00 for you Yanks. Yessssssss!  It's not up yet, but I'll link to it once it's in action. Da gears be a rollin', and da money be flowin'.  (I'm doing the cabbage patch dance as I say this)  Hopefully, Chris didn't name this company Greenforge for nothing.  I have our company site up, but I designed it when I first got here so it pretty much sucks.  I'll be revamping it sometime this month so I'll give a link then.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sean ,  urlLink Dave ,  urlLink Phil  - I haven't read any sci-fi for a while... ok, I haven't read anything for a while.  I'm taking the entire list you guys came up with to the library this weekend and will pick one of them from my impression of the pretty picture on the cover or maybe something intriguing from the back synopsis.   urlLink Chris Hu.  - First off, to prevent further confusion, I will now refer to Chris Hill as Hank and continue calling you Chris.  Secondly, I think it is entirely cruel to make it impossible to back up from your site.  Oh yeah, and I love the design, although it makes me doubt my worth or even my existence as a designer.  Luckily, I live in England where the standards for a decent site are much lower.   urlLink Sonya  - Sorry about the confusing CBD (Central Business District) reference.  Jim S. says that it is a N'awlins thing, but I could have sworn I've heard that term in other cities.  Anyway, I felt that if I went down to the CBD of any large city and wandered around for a while, my mind would have a picture engrained into my visual cortex very much resembling your painting which would then be stored away in the depths of my cerebellum to be brought out when anyone said a word that even slightly hinted at a CBD.  Now that you have shown me this painting, I've brought my own version back into conscious thought, put it and your painting into my frontal lobe for comparison and analysis, and after a week or so both will be put back into memory as a new thing.  Of course there are emotions attached to these visuallizations and everybody probably feels a little different about this kind of image, but that's the beauty of a picture like that.  Being a suburban boy who eventually moved to the big city, several in fact, it represents the cold, harsh reality of a netless adventure.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Hank  - I think John and Jen are a myth as well.  I went to his wedding and there was this big guy in a tux who was pretending to be John, but the booze was free so I didn't say anything.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>27,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I would really like to know the story about that plane that crashed near Pittsburg.  I can't imagine what heroism went down there, but I'm sure there will be several TV movies in the future to let me know.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      There is this school next to me that is a school for troubled kids.  One of them asked for a light when I walked by so I complied.  I hung around for a few minutes to ask them about their institution.  My reasons were not for their benefit, because they have been throwing bottles and standing out in the street stopping cars.  I thought I might get some insight by trying to be friendly and mixing in to see what they were up to.  Lo and behold, I discover that I am concidered an adult.  They all started fidgeting and many walked away.  When did I become an adult?  Oh well, my intentions, like I said weren't for their benefit, so I suppose that scene played out for the best.  I walked away without further questioning.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've taken an unexpected break away from the blog, not just writing, but reading.  I'll try to check back up on everyone today.   I am reading a very cool book.  I mentioned it before, but I hadn't started reading it at that time.  I didn't even need to read "Life on Mars" by Paul Chambers... what a piece of crap.  Everything that was in that book by a real micropaleontologist was in this new book I'm reading in a few paragraphs.  The new book I'm reading is by a spelunker.  (Excuse my spelling on all this)  He's not even a scientist, but he's really done his research and he actually has worked with many of the crucial scientists involved in all this.  He makes me want to drop everything I'm doing and learn how to explore caves and work for scientists exploring life there.  If anyone is interested in by far the largest group of life on earth and the oldest, one which lives deep beneath the earth's surface without oxygen or sunlight, I highly recommend this book.   "Dark Life" by Michael Ray Taylor.  The prospects of life in our solar system other than on Earth seem very good.  The universe must be full of it.  On another view, he also goes into the life around us.  Your body has ten times the amount of organisms living on you as you have actual human cells.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've been watching this documentary that's been on T.V. on a weekly basis here called Blue Planet about Deep Sea exploration.  God, it's amazing.  Are they showing this in the States now?  I wish I could post some of the pictures that they are showing, but I can't find them on the net anywhere.   urlLink Here's a link to the documentary site.   I'm kind of bummed with the site because it is geared at kids only, but I did manage to steal a flash cartoonish animation of what I think is called a rat trap fish and put it on the main df page.  They have two red glowing headlights under their eyes and a huge mouth that extends.  I could not believe all the bio-illumination that is in the deep ocean.  I am currently reading two books, one called Life on Mars (just finished it), which I can't recommend too much, but it did explore possible ways that life could exist on Mars and the other book is Dark Life which is about life that exists in deep caves that use chemosynthesis instead of photosynthesis.  Anyway, this Blue Planet documentary went into the ocean ridges that pour out sufides from the Earth's mantle supporting a whole ecosystem at the bottom of lightless ocean.  I knew about that already, but then it went into a whole ecosystem that survives off methane gas at the bottom of the Gulf of Mexico.  Never heard of that.  It was complete with an underwater lake.  Yes, that's right, an underwater lake.  It looked so cool.  It's saline content was more heavy than the surrounding water so a lake formed under the clear waters of the deep Gulf.  Cool stuff, I highly recommend checking the documentary out.  They are showing a great number of never before seen species.  Supposedly, man has only explored about 1% of the ocean floor.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I don't feel that religion for the most part has a negative influence on World Peace.  I think many wars have been waged in the name of religion throughout man's history, but that religion was not actually the cause.  I feel that more likely it has been used as a tool by rulers of nations to unite it's masses and gain whatever they felt like gaining from other nations. Mainly I blame sheer ignorance, which with the resources of this modern age is hopefully becoming less of a factor.  All major religions teach peace, tolerance, and love.  I think the world of today is much more aware of the difference between the majority of people who adhere to their religious doctrines and the minority who alter the purpose of these doctrines by picking through details that do not reflect the larger message.  I hope so, anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Maybe this is insane, but I have the need to hear Beach Boys music.  Call me crazy.     urlLink I get around    urlLink Good Vibrations 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My friend Stinger sent me this PBS  urlLink link .  It's a good overall look at Osama bin Laden and his views towards the West.  The interviews might be a refreshing source of information for those that are tired of speculation about the man.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm very relieved to know that we will not be at war with Pakistan.   urlLink Sources: Pakistan OKs U.S. Demands  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Is this all part of Osama bin Laden's plan?   urlLink Here's one Afghan-American's point of view. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Hank?  I know that's pointless to ask, because he is a Navy man, but .... hank?
     

    
</post>

<date>13,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I must say that my thoughts are with President Bush in traveling around the country to various venues.  Even with all the extra security, I think I would be pretty damn scared to be making so many public appearances.  At the same time, he seems to be maintaining his composure.  Cheers, George.  I hope that you are holding yourself together.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Last night I went out with Cousin Chris to see a movie that I would have never gone to see normally (Rush Hour 2).  I can't say that it was a spectacular movie or anything, but I have to admit that the lightness of this movie is exactly what I needed.  Before the movie I ate an entire plate of the hottest Chicken Vindaloo I have every eaten in my entire life.  Tears were flowing out of eyes, sweat poured from my forehead, I used up my alloted amount of napkins quickly to contol my nose leakage, and the room shifted back and forth like in the peak of an acid trip, but I would not stop eating until it was gone.  Anyway, if Chris is reading this, even though I looked and acted like a zombie from hell during the meal and before the movie, I am glad that we decided to go out and do something.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      What I see here in England is amazing support for America.  One big concern though, is that they feel the Prime Minister has given Bush a blank check to do what he wants without question from this country.  Alot of focus has been brought to attention about how this needs to be a worldwide effort.  Powell's comment today, "We will not be constrained by the fact that we are working with others as well", was somewhat understandable from my point of view as an American, but I believe it is very unnerving for most in Europe. Another issue that I am sure is on the minds of those around me, but which I haven't heard a thing of from the newspapers, or on T.V., is racial relations in North England.  The Pakistani's have been treated like second class citizens here, (e.g.  There is a 5% unemployment rate overall and a 30% Muslim unemployment rate, and it is not that Muslims do not want to work), and as a result I'm sure most of you have heard of all the racial riots that have been taking place in the last few months.  No riots or racially motivated crimes have hit the news since the big event on Tuesday and I hope this calm lasts as long as possible.   So many issues are connected to the upcoming events that I certainly feel unqualified to make predictions, make statements of belief, or even ask questions to the public at large that would fuel opinions based purely on emotion or contruibute to the chaos of misinformation.  I hope this group understands that I live alone in a foreign country and it is only my comfort with this group that I have the nerve to express my ideas so openly and so untested.  Most of me feels that I should shut up and just wait and watch, but that other part of me can't help poking and prodding in a search to define what is happening.  I'm very thankful to have this forum to express myself and I'm very thankful that I get to read such thought provoking insights from the Drunkenfish and the Tanque. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I was quick to anger; couldn't help it.  I understand that most of you may disagree with what I said yesterday, but I stand by it for the most part.  The World War III stuff might have been pushing my envelop for prediction.  Of course we need to gather information and proceed with knowledge and forethought.  All of NATO should act on this together as a checks and balance system, to make sure we are pursuing a just course of action.  Countries like Afghanastan and Pakistan who use their government and intellegence agencies to train terrorists must be stopped though.  We cannot sit back and let this type of organized terrorism keep growing.  We have been warned for years by the countries that are consistantly victimized by this, but understandably we could not comprehend the true urgency of their pleas.  I am and will always be a pacifist and a supporter of human rights.  Every measure should be taken to preserve these ideals, but I believe we have a responsibility to ourselves and the world to lead the way in ending these intolerable organizations of zealot murderers.  I hope that we can use a surgical approach to this, but somehow we have to get the job done.  Perhaps the best way to achieve this would be with the aid of those countries accused of harboring terrorists and even with those that are supporting and training these types of organizations.  Ideally, those nations involved in these activities would work side by side with us to correct the situation.  However, I don't believe that it will be  that  easy.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      This whole thing sank in last night and this morning for me.  My initial reaction was that bombing was entirely the wrong way to go, because it would just be killing innocent people and escalating American hatred throughout the middleeast.  I didn't even comprehend going all the way with this to World War III.  Now that I look at the options and the gravity of what has happened, I think we should prepare for war against all the nations that harbor our enemy.  I'm absolutely stunned at what is happening here.  This kind of terrorism absolutely cannot be allowed to happen.  I believe as the only superpower that we have the ability to save ourselves and that the survival of our way of life is worth preserving.  I believe we, the U.S., will have many allies in this war.  We will not be alone.  This isn't an angered child striking back from frustration.  It's an entire civilization, incorporating most of the world's population, who will not allow our nations to be subjected to living in a constant state of fear.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Is it going to be Iraq, Afghanistan, or Pakistan?  I fear and loath that one of these places will be hit soon.  I would much rather organized assasinations, rather than the usual response of bombing.  Bombing is going to just result in the deaths of innocent people and multiply American hatred around the world.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      wow...
     

    
</post>

<date>10,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sean - Was that a dream?  The virtual world people  are  real, aren't they?
     

    
</post>

<date>06,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome back  urlLink Jason !  I started him out about a year ago, but things got sidetracked and I was a cruel dictator of the drunkenfish back then.  I deleted everyone who hadn't posted in the last week or so.  In any case, things are a bit more loose now, so have fun my friend.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm a little drunk, but maybe this is a valid question.  Is the inner region of our galaxy older than than the outer?  I just read the  urlLink nytimes article  about the black hole in the center of the Milky Way.  I can't find anything on that subject.  I'm thinking about whether the solar system was created by the friction of  this black hole or if it was created before hand and then pulled in.  A huge gap possibly in my astronomy knowledge, but maybe someone can clue me in.  My thinking is that most solar systems had to result from the friction of this thing in the center of our galaxy.  The black hole originating from a bunch of gas particles that just happen to be near each other to start the gravitation thing happening would seem to be rare enough of an event that the rest of all of this would have had to have been created by this original phenomenon.  Yes JimS., there's that word again that clues you that I'm drunk.  Actually, I'll say this theory, since all know I'm drunk, that dark matter is everywhere and that there are areas that gravitation pulls together large concentrations of this which forms mass and pulls things by the nature of the process of gravitation into it and what we see are the byproducts.  (particles, light waves)  These things are just reflections of the dark matter gathering together producing these energy responses.  I'll shut up now, because I don't know what the hell I'm saying.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I found an article on the web by my fantasy wife, Deirdra Funcheon.  That's who I lived with in Florida with John and Jen.  She's dreamy.   urlLink http://www.nypress.com/13/47/news&columns/feature.cfm 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ned again - I'm going to try to convince Chris Lea to start Geocaching with me.  With winter coming up though, it might not happen until spring.  It might be worth it to go ahead and do it in the cold.  Who knows?  By the way, I'm a vid-game junkie myself, looking for a fix.  My ADSL connection is pretty good, although each leap to get to where you are might make things hairy.  Don't know, but I'm willing to try.  I'll go out and purchase Unreal Tournament soon.  I have Unreal, but I'm assuming the Tournament is a separate thing.  Another game that I have and find extremely fun to multiplay is BattleZone 2, if anyone is interested.  I used to play Jimmy in the arcade play, but for some reason could never convince him to play me in my favorite part of the game which is the strategic game.  He's probably just scared of my superior intellect.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ned - I've never had a job long enough for it to define me.  I'm not a good enough artist of any kind for that to define me either.  When people ask me what I do, I generally either joke and say, "you mean today?" or  "I watch T.V. generally," or I just say whatever my current job is as if I have had a career at it.  It has become a big problem really.  I've not built any skills.  You may think your job is easy, but that's because you are surrounded by it everyday.  Whether you feel you are an expert or not, you are.  You've started a career, built on it, and now it seems like cake.  You're paid for your knowledge, not your difficulties in performing the job.  God, I'd be a millionaire if I could just be paid for the stress I create for myself.  I honestly cannot think of a single profession that I would be comfortable doing for the rest of my life.  Most people probably don't.  The difference between me and most people though is that they are willing to stick with something long enough to make that thing comfortable.   I think the key to this whole career thing is to pick something and stay with it for at least 10-15 years.  After that you should be able to make safe financial moves towards things of interest instead of necessity.  I'm not saying that there aren't those special people that love what they do, but to me that fits into the same catagory as finding that one person that is made for you.  Either you are lucky enough to trip over that or you're not.  I don't think either is something you can search for.  Anyway, I'm starting to think on both of those issues that you should grab the best thing you can find and then work at staying with it.  (Did I just do a plug for monogamy? ... and in that sense am I suggesting that you should give a relationship 10-15 years until you can make a safe emotional move towards something of interest instead of necessity...  hurm...)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Good eye JimS.  Yeah, I was drunk.  Maybe I shouldn't have even mentioned that subject yesterday.  I don't usually like deleting things, but I'm doing it this time.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, this is my last post on this computer.  I'm packing it up tommorrow to sell before I leave.  What will I do without a computer!!!  No worries, though..  Jim has plenty and it will definitely be a priority of mine, once I'm back on my financial feet to purchase another.  My blogging has slipped back into boring short dribble lately.  Some may say. "lately?"  I say, "suck my..."  no I don't, I just shrug my shoulders and don't say anything.  Sort of how I blog.  I remember surfing the net and providing links and speaking occasionally about life and embarassing the hell out of myself with drunken posts... What's happened to me?  I've turned into a PC (two meanings on the PC) zombie.  I really am embarrassed for myself.  I haven't been creating any art in the last three years either.  I sure wish my brain would come back.  It's not like I'm doing anything more important, so where the hell is my brain?  My creativity is gone.  I can't even pick up a fiction book... I used to love 'em.  I stare at the cover and decide it would be a waste of my time.  Like I said before, "I'm not doing anything important!"  I'm hoping that seeing old friends might pull me out of this funk, but I know it all comes down to a decision from me to save me.  I'm not apologizing for my blogs, I'm just saying that I too, recognize how fucking boring they are.  I'm not going to worry about it too much though.  Everyone blogs in a different way and just as darkness helps us appreciate the light, boring helps us appreciate the facinating.   Here's my  urlLink favorite commercial  in England to make up for the lack of entertainment in this last forced blog from this place.  After you enter the site, visit  Great Britain  and  play the Dream Club Ad .  They might show it in the States also, but if so, it's always worth a second watch.    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Chistopher  - "Love Shack, baby Love Shack!!"  (Sorry, it's the psychotic, axe-wielding, circus clown in my head that made me do that.)
     

    
</post>

<date>27,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'll be leaving England on the 4th of November and landing in New York around noonish... I want to visit the WTC for awhile and then I'll take a bus from there to Indy.  Thankyou Jim S. for all your support for me in this move.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I don't think register.com was that fast at locating the new server from this site, but I have moved it none the less.  It's up for now, but it will switch to our new server soon.  Bluemarble just isn't reliable anymore so we've been temporarily moved to the Greenforge server in Liverpool.  As soon as Jimmy's server is up, (and I haven't even asked Jimmy, but I'm assuming) we'll switch over to his server and then we will have more control over our stability.  Sort of the same reason I'm moving back to the States in light of my financial situation.  Anyway, I think all around I'm making the right choices.  LONG LIVE THE DRUNKENFISH!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Whew, what a hangover.  Did you say something John?  Love?  Of course brother, unconditionally.  That's always a given.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's official.  I'm leaving England.  We gave it a good shot and the company is still going to be in place, but it's going dormat for awhile.  I don't think I will be involved in it's revival when that time comes, but who knows.   I don't have any details yet, but I believe I will be landing in Indianapolis in late November or early December and then driving with JimS. down to West Palm Beach, Florida, where I'm planning to live.  As far as a job?   Damn, got me there.  My guess is that I'll probably deliver pizza for a month or so until I find a computer tech job.  I'll probably try to put web sites together from here out on a per project basis for extra cash.  Moving is always such a bitch.  From the moment I decide to move to the moment I'm sitting alone on my new home's floor with a beer in my hand, I'm never quite myself.  I just go into transfer mode with all my thoughts bent on scanning my memories and analyzing posibilites.  I remember Sting said something very simple in an interview once that always has stuck with me.  (I'm paraphrasing here)  "I think the greatest beauty in life is not knowing what is around the corner." 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Todo Hardbottle here.  Is that a Heidi I see stirring about in the drunkenbattleblog?  Cool.  I haven't been there for awhile as a legit drunk, because I guess I've gained some respect for myself.  NOT!  I've just been too drunk to type.  Sorry to hear about the eye trouble Di.  Those only occur to me when I have dates.  Phil - Let it out brother!  I identify with your current situation.  Hope things turn up on the flip side.  They usually do.  Liz - I agree that there is a certain stress level created by all these terrible events..  Not to give terrorism it's prime objective, but it really does do what it is meant to do.  Hopefully, this blogging community helps us realize that that stress is real, it can affect our daily lives, and that we can overcome it.  (Don't mean to sound like Dr. BuddaBen)  Ned - Two negative numbers multiplied together produce a positive number because Jesus wants it that way.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome back dumbass!  *sniffle, sniffle*  I feel like the whole family is back together again.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome back Sonya, you were missed.  I hope you and Sean enjoy your new location amongst good friends.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      When I arrived here, I was presented with a common English dish, Beans and Toast.  To me, two starches just do not go together in one dish.  Over the year that I've been here though, I've noticed that when I'm low on groceries, the two things left in the cupboard are, you guessed it, bread and beans.  When in Rome, I suppose.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I may be way over simplifying this, but it sure would be nice if a respected Islamic figure would stand up and denounce Osama bin Laden as not representing the Islamic faith.  I think that would do alot for allowing muslims around the world to realize that this isn't a fight of the west against Islam.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm just the kind of dude to ruin a good thing by over doing it, but here's another test.  This one's short and stupid, but I love Selma so I had to share.  The Simpson's character I'm most like is:  Selma Bouvier   urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks for thinking of me Liz!  I wouldn't want anyone to go through that much trouble for me though.  I'll just have to concentrate on learning how to use the spray.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Osama bin Laden has financed the Taliban and is so close to them that he has even married off one of his own daughters to the leader of the Taliban, Mullah Muhammad Omar. The Taliban have provided refuge for bin Laden since 1994 while terrorist camps producing holy warriors on a holy war against the U.S. have been steadily growing in production.  I'm convinced that we need to do something about this.  I hope that more permanent lines of aid can be provided for the Afghan people after we gain further control of the area.  The people of Afghanistan certainly have my sympathy for the suffering they have been going through for such a long time, but Bush would go down as the idiot of the millinium if he didn't do anything about terrorism, given this opportunity of more world support than we have ever had on the issue.  I support the U.S. efforts to destroy terrorist strongholds and believe we must send a clear warning to those that support these networks.  I suppose that I will have problems with various steps along the way, but I feel it would be naive to suggest that we should only negotiate without action.  
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm sorry for being so trivial in such serious times, but are those stitches on Bush's head?  I cannot even approach the events that are happening this evening... I just have to wait and watch.  I think and hope that we are doing the right thing.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I can't find stick deodorant anywhere in England and have been forced to learn the complicated task of using spray.  I just failed my first lesson by not noticing the spray nozzle was pointed in the wrong direction.  Nothing like a quick burst of butane to the eye to make a person feel stupid.  I hope this twitch won't be permanent.  I've been trying to use roll-on, but I've lost most of my underarm hair by very painfully removing them one hair per morning.  Can't I just take a pill to hide my smell?  Why did I just tell everyone that?  I also, blame the coffee.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome  urlLink Di-Havanna ... I hope she finds this forum is what she needs to post her thoughts.  By the way, Diana, there is no such thing as a private conversation here.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sonya - I know exactly what you mean when you say that you appreciate him not making you feel guilty.  There are homeless all over the place here and some who sell what is called "The Big Issue".  I'm assuming it's England's version of "Streetwise", but I've never seen Streetwise.  I went through various modes of thought through the years on my approach to beggars.  I used to to think as I walked through inner city Atlanta to go to school or work, that there is no way I can give out change everyday to all these people with their hands out.  There's just way too many of them.  At that point, I just made it a general rule to ignore them at all times.  I know life must be hard for them to be out there doing that... I never have taken the notion that they were getting a free ride off of society.   Anyway, later in life, I realized that my policy to protect the change in my pockets had become fairly rigid.  Why not hand out change when I can?  The only steadfast rules I follow now on panhandlers is 1. I don't give people change unless I am alone.  2. I don't give change to those who follow me or are anything but humble in their position.  I have various reasons for both of those rules and following them allows me to hand over a couple of quid a week and have a few very, very brief pleasant conversations.  
     

    
</post>

<date>22,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Redesign coming soon.  Hopefully that will encourage me to start posting again.  Happy Foodtalknap Day!  I'm headed over to James' sister's house for Thanksgiving dinner in about an hour.  Can't wait to make a complete pig out of myself.  I won't know everyone there so to avoid awkwardness in conversation, I'll just say when asked any questions, "Hey!  Can't you see I'm eatin' here!"  and then turn my head down and rejoin the pig session.  Hope everyone enjoys the holidays.     
     

    
</post>

<date>14,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
       A monkey blankets an orange mentally with the desire to eat.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Clay  - I just wanted to mention outloud to everyone that your last post about Aubrey's page being a memorial was completely misunderstood by me and probably everyone else.  I thought you were saying that because she hasn't posted that her page was a lonely memorial, but I never noticed what you were actually pointing out.    urlLink And that was the time and date of the post.   Don't know why I didn't catch that, because I was signing her up when I received a phone call from Chris Lea saying that two of the WTC had been hit by planes.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Phil - eh... so I was wrong.  Never met a violet before.  I got the spirituality right...  indigo in color is not that far from violet...and uh... hey, I was drunk when I made the assessment.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's been years since I looked at my aura book.  Mainly because I finally realized I was riding some big ego trip that the book creates from the Indigo color, but I really like the book and if all can take it with a grain of salt then it's a blast.  Just because I'm stoned and really feel like typing I'll write out Blue as an example for Carrie.  This gets very lengthy so be warned.  (if anyone else wants the description for their aura color then I'll try to scan the pages or something and e-mail the info.)  BLUE -   Blues embody the characteristics of nurturing and care-taking.  They are the Personality Spectrums color most concerned with helping other people.  Whereas Nurturing Tans find their life's work in the community, Blues find value in being of service to individuals.  Service is a form of altruism, a giving of oneself.  It is the art of anticipating the needs of other human beings and ministering to those needs while at the same time allowing the individuals to maintain their dignity.  In doing a dindness for a neighbor or performing an act of mercy for a patient, Blues feel fulfilled, valued, and of worth; they find ways to live their lives by giving. The greatest challenge for Blues is to know what they need to be happy and then to ask for it.  Because they are so caught up in service to others, Blues often spend too little time and attention on their own spiritual and emotional growth activities.  They must set limits and boundaries on their emotional, physical, and spiritual resources; they must be able to say no and mean it.  Blues need to emulate the wise cook who returns a portion of the starter dough to the yeast pot for another day.  In this way, Blues can maintain their personal power.  They must learn how to husband their own internal resources by measuring thenm out and using some of their time and energy to renew themselves.  BLUEs Approach to Physical Reality  Blues do not find much to recommend physical reality.  To them it is dirty, harsh, and ugly.  Even an idyllic country scene viewed from a hilltop is, on close inspection, found to be alive with thousands of creepy, crawling bugs.  Blues tend to live in the realm of emotions and feelings, which are more real to them than the external environment. Left to their own devices, Blues do not particularly care for strenuous, sweaty physical activity or exercise.  It makes them hot and sticky, a most unpleasant experience.  However, they do enjoy sports that have a component of camaraderie, such as softball, volleyball, and bowling, or a component of grace and beauty, such as dancing, swimming, and horseback riding.  They enjoy walking as a way of experiencing nature or being with friends out-of-doors.  Exercise classes that incorporate gentle stretching, with a less hectic atmosphere than aerobics, appeal to Blues.  Endurance sports requiring constant physical conditioning generally do not attract Blues, because they perceive that amount of attention to oneself as indulgent and narcissistic. Blues tend  to have an endomorphic body type - the "earth mother" figure.  Tehy put on weight easily, especially after the birth of children.  In an era with so much emphasis on diet, exercise, slender figures, and no hips, Blues are at a disadvantage.  Full-figured, especially after menopause, Blues need to understand that their beauty lies in their ability to nurture and support others and in their pleasing personalities.  BLUEs Mental Attitudes  The Blues' greatest gift is their highly develooped intuition.  They are extremely sensitive to the emotional vibrations of others.  However, it is extremely difficult for them to translate what they know intuitively into useful information.  In the decision-making process, emotions, feelings, and hunches are not usually given equal weight with the facts and figures.  Therefore, Blues feel less adequate than other colors when it comes to making an intellectual contribution.  The ability to collect, sort, and retrieve information is an acquired skill, one that Blues must learn, specifically through training in critical thinking. Like all the Emotional/Spiritual Colors, Blues are holistic thinkers.  They grasp all the parts of a disscussion or decision-making model simultaneously, juggling outcomes and the attendant consequences, assessing and evaluating cause and effect, always holding open the alternative options. If a Green thinks in a binary manner, cutting and paring options at every choice point on the binary tree, a Blue mentally hangs on to the whole tree, never letting go of any of the potential options.  since Blues hold all the alternative solutions simultaneously in mind, it is no wonder they have a difficult time making decisions!  Blues can get bogged down in the details and feel unsure of where they are going or how to proceed.  The most important skill a Blue can learn is how to focus, to cut away all issues and concerns that do not have immediate pertinence to the problem at hand. In school, Blues do well in subjects that place a high degree of emphasis on intuition or feelings:  literature, creative writing, art, and drama.  Those subjects requiring a linear approach, like mathematics or the hard sciences, teach the skills of memorization, organization, and building hierarchies.  These are the subjects that assist Blues in learning to handle real-world data.  It is frustrating for Blues to know the answer to a math problem and not know how they got it. Although they are highly emotional, Blues can do well in businessk, especially those having a service component that allows Blues to work closely with other people.  Blues are capable of making decisions; they are just slower and more deliberate than other colors.  They lack the organizational ability of the Mental Tan or the Green, and the strong  personal ego of a Violet. Blues need to create schedules for coping with business situations, schedules that allow them sufficient time to work at their own speed.  Blues need three to seven days to make a big decision.  Given that time, space, and quiet, Blues make good decisions that are well thought out and to which they are committed.  To be comfortable emotionally, they need to ask that all proposals and complaints be put in writing.  This gives them an opportunity to separate the feelings from the action and to create a solution that they can support. Blues weigh all of the factors that must be taken into consideration in any decision-making process:  previous commitments, needs of family and self, the merits of the project, and the intended outcome.  When confronted with employers and customers who demand instant decisions, Blues must be honest about their motives and requirements before they take any action.  Blues take business setbacks personally.  In the world of the Mental Family colors, everything is first an idea; in the world of the Blues, everything is first an emotion.  Acknowledging their feelings and being willing to keep moving in spite of them allows Blues to function successfully in the world of business. The greatest asset a Blue has is emotional commitment.  This is part of the Blues' mental emotional process -  they see the ptential inherent in good ideas, and they want to help others achieve their goals.  Any idea, project, or individual to whom a Blue is bound is indeed fortunate.  A committed Blue is reliable, dependable, and trustworthy.  BLUEs Emotional Makeup  Blue is the color of female energy and uniquly reflects one aspect of feminine energy - the ability to get in touch with and express one's feelings.  Blues make sense of the world through their emotions rather than through physical sensations, as Yellows and Physical Tans do.  Love, hate, hope, despair - these are everday facts of life for Blues.  Emotions are the data base on which they make decisions and take actions. This ability to act from an emotional center is the Blues' greatest asset, but it can also be their greatest liability.  They want to love and care for others and are perceived as loving, thoughtful, kind, and helpful.  The liability comes when emotional confusion clouds the facts of a situation, preventing the Blues from making the best decisions.  They are unable to discern, for example, the difference between being taken advantage of and being asked to give a little extra effort to achieve success. Because they are so sensitive and pick up nonverbal cues to the moods of others, Blues are not acknowledged for what they know.  Mates and employers, who use a more rational approach, ask what data the Blues have to support their opinion.  Since the data are usually feelings, they are discounted as irrelevant, unspecific, or unscientific.  In our society, the intuitive knowledge of a Blue is sometimes disconcerting and may seem irrelevant to those with a more mental outlook.  However, in those areas of life where their specific gift is necessary, where nurturing and caretaking are essential to the continued well-being of the family and community, Blues are perceived as necessary and valuable.  Blues love people.  To serve others is their life's work.  A Blue's sense of well-being comes from tending to the needs of significant others.  This caretaking can take the form of cooking, cleaningk, and throwing parties, or of listening, accompanying a friend to the doctor, and giving advice.  One of the hazardsfor a Blue is being taken for granted by family and others, Blues open themselves to being used, failing to ask for repayment in kind.  Blues assume that others are as sensitive as they are.  The truth is that others don't see the Blues' needs and even if they do, they will let the Blues bear the burden.  This leaves Blues feeling unappreciated for the effort they have made. To combat this, Blues need to be much more assertive.  They need to learn to set limits on their service, to communicate their expectations clearly (including monetary considerations), and to take action if their requests for gratification are not honored.  In short, they must learn assertive communication skills.  The more they allow themselves to be victimized, the more sorry they feel for themselves, which leads to a resort to a whole cycle of complaint, which sometimes leads to real and imagined illnesses, the most serious of which is the loss of self-esteem and respect. Blues must learn that their needs are as important as the wants and needs of others.  They must learn to nurture themselves, to give to themselves as generously as they give to others. Blues need to nurture the emotional side of their personality.  Activities that support this include keeping a journal, writing, reading, listening to music, enjoying quiet times alone or outdoors, being with friends, and being listened to.  Without an opportunity to sort out their jumble of feelings, Blues find themselves in an endless morass of emotions without resolution. Blues express their emotions through the language of laughter and tears, both of which bubble to the surface easily and quickly, much to the Blues' embarrassment.  This is not an affectation, but rather the spontneous release of pent-up emotion that, if kept inside, would cause physical problems like headaches. Blues know intuitively that language is a poor medium ofexpression for the rich depth and texture of what goes on inside them.  They are touched deeply by sunsets, church music, and being with a loved one.  When they and their partner have mated at the spiritual level, Blues are so overcome with the emotion of that experience that they express their joy and happiness in tears. Blues also cry when they are angry.  Contrary to popular opinion, Blues do not use tears as a manipulative device for getting their own way.  When confronted with an agnry spouse or employer, they should first express the emotion represented by the tears. - anger, rage, frustration, helplessness, or betrayal.  Only then can they move into a more rational discussion of the situation and search for alternative resolutions. Blues understand that htere is an underlying logic to what they are feeling.  They cannot explain it; they can only feel the emotions.  For them to ignore or disparage this aspect of themselves is to abdicate the source of their power.  When in touch with their feelings, Blues are galvanized into action.  For Blues, emotions are the coin of human interaticon, without which there is nothing worthwhile.  well, that enough I suppose... I love the book, but it's like the beatles for me now... already heard it a million times.   The actual book is so much cooler than that web page I found.  "What Color Is Your Aura"  by Barbara Bowers, if anyone is interested... anyway, my trip down aura memory lane is done now.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Phil  - The book I was talking about is "What color is your aura?"  by Barbara Bowers.  There have been many books since that original book using her system  If you really want to dive into the cult that has been created about Indigo's specifically then look up books like "The Indigo Children".   Basically I saw you as Indigo because of your reserved nature, deep spiritual sense, non-conformity, willing to take a non-prestigious career,  direct honesty, etc..   there is alot of stuff about the Indigo that just seemed you.  I've only met two in my life besides myself, so somewhat because you seemed like the other one I met, I threw you in that catagory.    urlLink Here's a brief test I just found for anyone to take.   I'm pretty sure this lady's system is based on Barbara Bowers.  This lady calls some of the auras by different names like nurturing tan is sensitive tan, mental tan is logical tan, etc... Some other auras that I would guess or already know from taking the real book test are:  (some of these are pretty far reaches)  JimS. - Green JimA. - Blue Phil - Indigo John - Lavender Ned - Crystal Heidi - Yellow Dave - Green ChrisH. - Mental Tan Sonya - Magenta Sean - Crystal Shari - Green Clint - Nurturing Tan Becky - Red Hank - Crystal Liz - Magenta? Amos - Mental Tan?  I was going to try to guess everyone, but some people are just too difficult to catagorize.  (Not that anyone wants to be catagorized, but this is all in fun.)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Thank you Sean and Sonya for a cool party.  I was making alot of noise in your basement for how late it was when I finally left.  Hope the neighbors weren't bothered by it.  I woke up extremely disoriented at Ned's with a little help from a wake n' bake n'nap and took a b-line from the couch to the truck without telling anyone good-bye.  It took me about 20 miles of the road before I was actually awake and thinking straight.  It was nice to finally put real people to the blogs.  Thanks to Shari's page I had seen a glimpse of all those people, but meeting them in real life was very enjoyable.  I remember drunkenly telling Phil he was an Indigo.  (just a silly aura book I've had for about 10 or so years that I've showed Ned.  No explanation to Phil at all, just said "Duh, hey you're an Indigo!"  He must have thought I was an idiot.  Anyway, I had tons of fun and hope I get to meet more of the Tanque someday.  Shari got me thinking strongly about going back to school.  My current money situation has to be my priority until I'm financially stable again, but I'm getting dreams of going back to school and getting a masters in Remote Sensing/GIS.  My undergrad degree is in GIS.  I might as well start looking into grants and scholarships and such to see what colleges offer what.  IU would be a great college town to live, but I should probably look around at other schools as well.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      well, it's 3:30 and we're still not off yet.  Jim went to drop his dog off at his sister's and hasn't come back yet.  Hang over still hasn't kicked in yet... I'm putting this miracle up there with me getting my college degree.  What a cool world.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I blew it.  I was very, very, drunk last night.  I'm still not hung over this morning.  I'm still in that morning, still drunk, shock phase.  Terrible, awful... I know the trip down to Bloomington will turn into hell along the way.  Sorry bloggers, you're going to get Zombie Ben instead of Ben.  Jimmy quit drinking an hour before we passed out, but I have a feeling he's not much better.  Just know I'm there somewhere in spirit... I'm sure once the alcohol starts flowing that I'll perk up a bit.  It's 2pm and we're about an hour from heading off.  See y'all soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Within the same week of me deleting  urlLink Hank 's (Chris Hill (for Di)) link because I think he has given up, he goes and writes a huge ass post.  Like I said before... I'll be fixin' up the links this next week sometime.  He's still linked on the main df page.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The links on this page will be corrected whenever I get enough energy to get off my ass, go through my suitcases to find the Flash software, search the net for cheat codes, install the damn thing, then make my corrections.  I think that could happen within a week.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome  urlLink Todd !  I absolutely adored Athens when I went to school there, and even when I didn't go to school at all.  It's a fun town.   I had almost turned into a Townie by the time I left.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      In a slight correction of what Jimmy said about my philosophy on time, I don't think that it's a loop.  Time is just eternal... always has been, always will.  And even if it is not, my point in Jim and I's discussion was that I don't feel it is necessary to create a creator to explain the beginning when we can't explain the creation of a creator.  A view I have expressed since about 12 yrs. old and still feel is pretty valid.  If there was a beginning, then we will just have to wait and be patient in hopes that science will eventually open up our perspective on creation.  Until then, my closest feeling of resolution on the matter is that there is no beginning and no end.  I bought a bed yesterday, a fold out twin.  $25.  What a bargain.  My goals are slowly changing, and I'm feeling like Indy is the place where I need to dig in for now.  I was thinking that I was going to get a quick contract job and then move on to West Palm Beach, but just buying food and paying my student loan and trying to come up with the money to pay for a car/insurance/tags...etc...  Anyway, my goal now is to just try to work contract jobs until I get a permanent one here, get my car, get a 6 month lease on an apartment and work from there to save enough money to move to West Palm Beach safely and securely.  I'm really looking forward to seeing as many of the tanque as possible at Sonya and Sean's on Saturday.  I can't wait.  Tonight I'm headed out to the bars with my bro Clay and two unknown (to me) women for whom my brother said that I need to come along so that he can verify to his wife that nothing happened.  hmmm...  we'll see about that.  I forgot who Clay said they were, but I think it was an ex-co-worker and her sister or something that's in town. I don't plan on getting too crazy, because the thought of showing up to meet the tanquers in a zombie like hang-over from hell, just doesn't seem like a very friendly thing to do.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Made it... that was the worst long ass plane and bus ride of my life.  It's good to finally have arrived, got drunk, and passed out.  I already have a contract job here..  First day! Yeah!!!    I took the religion thingy test... here were my top results. 1.  Theravada Buddhism (100%)    2.  Unitarian Universalism (97%)     3.  Secular Humanism (88%)    4.  Atheists and Agnostics (84%)    5.  Liberal Quakers (82%)    6.  Neo-Pagan (72%)  Post more later... much to do.     
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Shari - I'm sorry we couldn't make the party.  I would have loved to have been there.  I just saw and heard about it too late.   Happy New Year! 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My lame-ass list for 2001  Literature 1.  Dark Life 2. The Case for Mars 3.  Life on Mars 4.  The Tolkien Companion 5.  American Heritage Dictionary 6.  DK Essential World Atlas 7.  What Color Is Your Aura? 8.  Red Mars (reading currently) 9.  Various British Tabloids 10.  John's Blog   Video 1.  Lord of the Rings 2.  Memento 3.  Final Fantasy   4.  The Others (if Sixth Sense never existed) 5.  Blue Planet (documentary) 6.  Shrek 7.  Ass Clowns 2 (just kidding) 7.  Rush Hour 2 (Can't believe I'm putting this one, but I have to admit I smiled a lot during it) 8.  Dune (TV mini-series)  (not a 2001, but that's when I saw it) 9.  E.R.  (got mixed up with Chris Lea's wife Bridget watching that on a regular basis) 10.  The Ninth Gate (saw this one many times for some reason during 2001, I think it was because of the awesome ending)  Music (Non-existent)  Blogs (didn't put much thought into this... just trying to think of the blogs I read most) 1.  Ned 2.  Jim S. 3.  Sean 4.  Liz 5.  Heidi 6.  Dave 7.  Phil 8.  Jim A. 9.  Sonya 10. Amos  Honorable mention - Di-Havana      
     

    
</post>

<date>19,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      For anyone who saw my earlier post about the condo, I'm just going to cancel the reservation because I couldn't get anyone interested with such short notice.  I did already get Saturday off from work though, so hopefully I'll be able to party it up in Indy.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      John - By the way, I never did any redesigns on the main page.  Jim accidently deleted the old drunkenfish and I didn't have a back-up (I'm an idiot), so Jim threw that up so there would at least be something there.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Phil  - No offense but, I don't think knowing who owns the elvish rings is going to destroy the story for anyone other than hardcore fans... and they already know.  But in your defense, the beginning of the movie spells the story of the rings out, but somehow left out the part about who now owns the elvish rings so.... cheers Peter Jackson... and sorry to all if I overstepped my info on that.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Ahhhhhhh....   I finally got my Lord of the Ring fix.  I thought it was great.  I'm wondering if others will be disturbed because it ends in mid-story.  hmmmmm.... a whole year until the next one.  I actually was standing in line to buy two tickets for me and my brother Matt for the eight o'clock showing at 11:30.  I said, "Two tickets for Lord of the Rings at 8pm please.... and uh... um... one for the 12:00 one.   So I couldn't help myself so what... so I am going to see it twice on the opening day.... so what.... I couldn't help myself.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Some paraphrasing on the rings of power -  At the beginning of the Lord of the Rings Trilogy Sauron possessed the 9 rings of men (worn by the Kings and Princes who became the doomed and enslaved Ringwraiths that could never be released from their ghostly lives) and 3 of 7 dwarvish rings (4 of the dwarvish rings had already been consumed by dragons with their owners).   The rings were created by Celebrimbor with the aid of Sauron.   Sauron deceived the master elven craftsman Celebrimbor by enchanting his evil spells into the rings.  His purpose was to have these rings of power distributed among the greatest of men and dwarves while he secretly forged the one ring to rule them all by his own hand.  Celebrimbor also created 3 elvish rings which Sauron never touched or saw.   These rings were, The ring of Airs (Vilya) mightiest of the three, which bore a great blue stone originally possessed by Gil-galad, who gave the ring to Elrond at the end of the second age; The ring of Waters (Nenya) with a single hard white stone of great beauty, which was always in the keeping of the Lady Galadriel; and the ring of Fire, borne by Cirdan the Shipwright until the end of the first millennium of the Third Age, when he surrendered the Ring with its great red stone to the wizard Gandalf the Grey.   Sauron's one ring was taken from him by force from Sauron's own hand at the end of the Second Age by Isildur son of Elendil.  The ring fiercely burned Isildur when he first seized it and abandoned him in his moment of need during an ambush at Gladden Fields, plunging into   the bottom of a river bed for two thousand years in wait for it's master Sauron to slowly awaken into strength once more.  In the 25th century of the Third age, the ring was stirring because of the growth of power emanating from the Dol Guldur (where it was thought that the leader of the Ringwraiths resided and Greenwood forest was renamed Mirkwood; No one knew that it was actually Sauron himself who resided in that fortress).  A simple hobbit fisherman named Deagol found the One Ring and was instantly murdered by his hobbit friend Smeagol (later known as Gollum) who took the ring and hid deep beneath the Misty Mountains with it.  The Ring, realizing that Gollum was not fullfilling its purpose hidden deep in the mountains after 500 years, ensnared a passing hobbit traveller named Bilbo Baggins who later passed it on to his nephew in 3001 of the Third age. With Sauron grown powerful in the land of Mordor and he being in constant search for this Ring, the Lord of the Rings Trilogy begins.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Don't mind me, I'm just mucking about in my own muck.  Well, I thought that maybe it was selfish to keep the drunkenfish thing going when I don't blog or keep up the site, but now I'm thinking it would be selfish of me to get rid of it.  It's going to be ugly for a while because I don't have a pc, but I'll see what I can do everytime I visit JimS.    If any of the DFies get motivated and want to design or add anything to a new look, go for it.  I just got a full time job yesterday as a vet tech.  Very low pay, but I absolutely love the work.  Getting over my cat allergies might prove difficult, but we'll see.  Wow.... tomorrow is the big day.  I can't wait.  Someway, somehow, I am going to go to that movie.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I'm moving out of Jimmy's today so I won't have access to a pc.  I don't want the drunkenfish to die, but I don't know what to do about it.  I'll try to do some redesign by code on my bro's mac.  John or Jim, if you want to do anything with the df, let me know.  I might just turn the df into my own page and domain, like Jolly Jibber, instead of hosting pages.  I just haven't been involved with blog very much lately and thought maybe this is the time to disolve it as we know it.  Those on the df can get hosted with blogger if they choose or you can stay on with the df just knowing I'm not going to be too involved except in maybe keeping up my own blogging page which will become the main df page.  I'll eventually set up links to everyone I've known from both the df and tanque and hope to keep in touch, but I think this is the end of the drunkenfish as a blog community. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Can't get blogger to talk with the df server, but I'm working on it... Maybe in a month or so, I'll have a finished design here.  If your reading this then I'm on my way.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Job!  Job!  I got a job!  I told RCI that I didn't think my job history was good enough to compete for the job offered.  (meaning that I thought maybe it was a ploy to hire the person they really wanted in human resources for the job by putting up the quota of people to interview that weren't qualified to make their pick go through unchallenged; leaving me without a job at all.)  Instead I said that I want the job I came in to interview for:   $13.25 an hour on the phones.   Fine by me.... I've beat the system in my own way and now I have a JOB!!!!!!!    Wooooooooooooooha!  I am so glad to be working.  I start the job on monday (pending a drug test... I'll be sure to make it... ... ...Well, I will... really!)    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Should the federal government fund human cloning?  Not yet.   Should the federal government get out of the way of companies who can prove the value, humane commitment, and security of their cloning research.  Maybe.  I definitely feel that government should investigate and regulate the industry but not draw a line in the sand that research cannot pass.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      John - I'm sorry to hear about your dad's health.  Hang in there buddy.  Your dad probably wanted you to tell the rest of the family because you are such an emotionally strong person who will be able to properly inform those around you.  I really admire your ability to cope with such hardships while still keeping your mind focused on other's emotional security.  You're a great man.     
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Man, I can't win with these interviews.  The last interview before today's was for a Level One help desk job and I failed miserably because they didn't think I'd be able to handle the stress.  The one I went in for today was suppose to be for a low paying, low profile, call support for a Condo trading company; RCI.   I went in thinking, "no way am I going to sell myself short", so I went in with supreme confidence.  What did they do?   They decided I was Supervisor material and now I'm going in for another interview on Wednesday for a job that can make up to 65k a year managing over 80+ employees.   What the fuck?  Am I being set up for a fall?   Probably.  All I can do is go in and try to get the job.  This job hunting business is bizarre.   People are bizarre.  Life is bizarre.  I don't get it, but I'm going for it anyway.   All I want is a fucking job!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I think it would be wise for me to stay out of the God discussion.   I haven't read everything on the Dylan discussion so I'm not sure where I stand in that.  I will say that Dylan has certainly made rock n' roll speak from a much higher conscience than anything that ever floated to the surface of rock in the fifties.  If you look back to popular music before Dylan that wasn't considered Rock n' Roll, there is plenty of meaning.  Who know's how much of the songs Sinatra sang are in Rock n' Roll.  There are so many great lyrical tunes of the 20th century before Rock n' Roll that it's hard to give Dylan Einsteinian status knowing that he certainly didn't pull lyrical quality from a void.     - As far as my finding a career, I've decided to not stress over it and just try my best to stay in jobs that actually make money until I trip over something I enjoy.  My interview for that help desk job is today and although it is certainly not an ideal job, it will really get me out of my financial hole.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Ween Dream - I was hangin' out with Jean and Dean Ween in their house with about 15 other people.  Dean Ween's red-headed girlfriend was sitting in my lap and I was getting smirks from Dean's friends, but Dean himself didn't seem to mind.  Everybody was very drunk and Jean suggested we get more beer.  Jean and Dean and a few of their closest friends were rattling off jokes that everyone seemed to think were funny as hell, but I just didn't get them.  I was always trying to get in the groove, so I could chime in and feel apart of the party, but I only ended up smiling and pretending that I understood the humor.  After awhile of the confusing party I decided to lay down in a back room that happen to have my own bed in it without sheets or covers.  I laid down on the bed and sighed from surviving my awkward party experience when I looked up to see Dean's girlfriend sitting on a bench at the door, closing her eyes looking tired and drunk.  I moved over in the bed to let her know it was alright to crash next to me, but she opened one of her eyes and looked at the bed and said, "I don't think I can sleep with a man who can't take care of his own bed. "  I shruged, turned over, and went to sleep.  I awoke in another dream where I was with a catering crew delivering food to shops around the inskirts of a stadium while some unknown to me event was going on, but I could hear the crowd cheering.  I was leading the group of six or seven caterers around to the different shops asking who ordered food, because we had lost our list of clients.   We came to the end of a hall and I told the group I was going outside to take a break and that I'd be back soon.   I went outside and found an acoustic guitar laying against a wall.  I picked it up and wandered out near a ditch away from the stadium and belted off "Hard Days Night" better than I've ever played it.   When I was done I heard some clapping from a few janitors by a back entrance and I smiled and walked back to my service entrance on the first floor.  The catering crew was on the 3rd floor and I took the elevator up and stepped out of the elevator on the third, barely making it out before it drop back towards the first.  Seeing the crew down the hall I started walking towards them and the dream ended.     
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Some day, I'm going to be sitting in my own chair, in my own house, drinking my own beer, thinking my own thoughts, after working a job I can stand doing for 40 hrs out of my week.  I hope that day comes soon 'cause I'm losing the willpower and drive to survive and make things better for myself and I haven't even accomplished anything yet.  I'm trying to get back into computers because that's where the money is at, but I'm not having much luck yet.  The headhunter that has been getting me jobs just questioned my abilities from the last job I did for him.  4 out of 6 people they hired for that job quit, but I toughed it out to get in better standing with TekSystems and now I learn that those damn 20 yr old unorganized punks that ran my last job said I don't work well without supervision.  Where the hell they got that from is beyond me.  I put up with their unprofessionalism and lack of instruction without complaint and worked my ass off.  I really want to find them and kick their asses.   There's a possible help desk job interview coming up, but it just sucks that abominations like my last gig have to happen with no show for my patience or effort and even fuck up future possibilities.   I really just want to say fuck you to my imaginary person that is somehow responsible for the way this society works.  I wish I could find something that I could do to survive that removes everyone else from any decisions that affect me.   I'm a damn good worker that's smart, easy going, and reliable.   Why is so hard to find a decent job?  I'm currently working at a Vet clinic as a tech, but I cannot stand having to take shit from doctors who think they are gods.  I just keep holding in my rage, smiling, and doing the best that I can do until I can find something better.   My frustration is a big reason I never blog anymore.... afterall, who wants to read whiny crap like this everyday.   
     

    
</post>

<date>05,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
             I am  Kong .   Strong and passionate, I tend to be misunderstood, sometimes even feared. I don't want to fight, I don't want to cause trouble, all I ask is a little love, and a little peace. If I don't get what I want, I get angry, and throw barrels and flaming oil at whatever's stopping me.  What Video Game Character Are You?     
     

    
</post>

<date>25,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink       Like most people, it's hard for you to stop  thinking about your love for Ned.  href="http://tanque.org/shelf/quiz/quiz.html"> How Deep is Your Love for Ned?   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
       I Am A:  Neutral Good Elf Mage Bard    Alignment:   Neutral Good  characters believe in the power of good above all else. They will work to make the world a better place, and will do whatever is necessary to bring that about, whether it goes for or against whatever is considered 'normal'.    Race:   Elves  are the eldest of all races, although they are generally a bit smaller than humans. They are generally well-cultured, artistic, easy-going, and because of their long lives, unconcerned with day-to-day activities that other races frequently conccern themselves with. Elves are, effectively, immortal, although they can be killed. After a thousand years or so, they simply pass on to the next plane of existance.    Primary Class:   Mages  harness the magical energies for their own use. Spells, spell books, and long hours in the library are their loves. While often not physically strong, their mental talents can make up for this.    Secondary Class:   Bards  are the entertainers. They sing, dance, and play instruments to make other people happy, and, frequently, make money. They also tend to dabble in magic a bit.   Find out  urlLink What D&amp;D Character Are You? , courtesy of urlLink     urlLink NeppyMan    urlLink (e-mail)   
     

    
</post>

<date>09,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
      ahhh, the weekend.  I'm heading over to Jibber James' place to relax and be merry and forget about work.  Yes, I know I was very excited to get my job and I still am excited, but work is still work and now it's the weekend.  I'm sorry to those on drunkenfish who cannot get maintenance when they need it on their sites.  I've really let my drunkenfish responsibilities go and I don't see them improving anytime soon.  I can use my brother's mac, but I haven't been inspired to hunt down mac software of any kind.  Basically when I set up drunkenfish accounts I give all admin rights to the user, so I'm hoping most can be solved by the user.  As far as the server in Liverpool that the drunkenfish runs off of...  that's in my cousin Chris' able hands and he will probably keep that running as long as I decide to keep it there.  If there are server problems he usually catches them within the week.  That's about as good as it gets for free hosting so THANK YOU CHRIS!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I guess what I'd really like is to encourage everyone to get their own domain.  I don't mind at all anyone staying with the drunkenfish as long as they would like to, but they would be their own separate entity.  (eg. not drunkenfish/joeblow, but something like bynthere or Di-Havanna).  Jimmy expressed that he would like to keep his JollyJibber page his own thing and not turn it into a community.  Well, I guess I would like that too, but I want to somehow keep everyone involved and still be a community of sorts.  Again, I haven't thought this through very well, but I think the best solution would be to separate into individual pages and then regroup at a time everyone is comfortable with in forming a portal page to keep the community feeling.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'm planning a redesign on Easter whilst recovering from my hangover from Shangri-la on Saturday.  I need all the drunkenfishies to either blog or e-mail their opinions on what we should do about the separate domains.  If they were separated, who would go where?  Should I create a new domain and invite all who wanted into that and then have the drunkenfish as a portal site for all domains created under that?  That way we could all still be drunkenfishies, but would have the freedom to be hosted by whatever domain we want or create and still be a community.  It just seems a little disturbing to have the Jibbers and the Drunkenfishies all under the drunkenfish banner.  Are the drunkenfishies the REAL Drunkenfish.... Am I making way too big a deal out of this?  Jim S. has mentioned that he might want to start another domain all together as the portal site and the Jibber and the DF would just be domains under that... hmmm... I think I would like to just separate the two, but I'm not sure.  I would suppose in that scenario the only ones who would be left as drunkenfishies would be Di-Havana, John, Hank, and myself.  I'd like to know what everyone else thinks before I redesign the site this weekend.  my email is:   urlLink mindevol@hotmail.com  
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      New Computer!!!  I'm back in business.  Once I get all my pirated software back up and going, I think a drunkenfish redesign is in order.  Pentium 4, 1.8 Ghz, 512 MB DDR(?) memory, 21" Sony Multiscan E540 Monitor, 80 GB storage, dvd, cd rw, 10/100 ethernet, 5 USB ports, 64MB nVidia GeForce2MX Graphics Card w/TV out... cool ass sony speakers, I am in heaven.  I really don't want to go to work, but I suppose I have to pay this thing off now.  To test my system, I bought the DVD Apocalypse Now (redux), and the video game Alone in the Dark (the new nightmare), going through my bro's DSL for now.  My brother is so cool to let me buy this thing first and move out of his house later.  Probably a couple months tops.     
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink City Populations   I just think this list is cool to peruse.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Tears filled my eyes when I saw the purple ribbon on Robyn's site saying save the Drunkenfish.  I should be getting a computer in about a month and I vow to redesign the site, find a new host, keep up with maintenance, and recruit more fishies.  I've noticed some of the fishies drifting over to the JollyJibber server, and that's fine and dandy, but for the fishies still on the df server, stability is on the way.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Does anyone know the origin of the phrase; "The whole nine yards"?  My roommates and I all had different stories and when I searched the web I found even more stories.... all different.  A few of the most believable to me are:  1. It takes 9 square yards to make a complete well made man's suit.  If you wanted your suit done right without having to make alterations you would ask the tailor to use the whole nine yards.  2.  Since the phrase didn't seem to pop up until the 40's and later, this one seems plausible to me.  The length of a machine gun belt for a fighter plane was 9 yards.  To use the whole nine yards was to use all your ammo.  3.  The most popularly accepted answer, (one that just doesn't feel right to me though) is that a cement truck holds nine cubic yards of cement.  Thus the whole nine yards was to use the entire truckload of cement for a job.  4. Another popular one that I don't buy is that it is an american football expression designed to be sarcastic since it actually takes 10 yards to accomplish a first down.  There are tons of others, but hearing a quote from a legitimate source would end the brain loop I'm going through on this one.  I suppose I could just make up my own to add to the list.  ** The whole nine yards come from (according to Ben's imagination)  -  the standard length of a shotgun shack.  To get the whole nine yards would to have meant to kill everything in the entire house with one shot.      
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Sean - Still thinking about the convex, concave space thing.  Just to clarify... are you asking if space is convex (meaning the shortest distance between any two points is through space) or concave (meaning the shortest distance between some points is to exit and re-enter space)? 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      What kind of world has this all become when I walk into a bank to start a checking account and they give me a platinum Visa credit card?  Ben Emerson with a Platinum Visa Card.  Danger, Will Rogers!  DANGER!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sean  - My guess (a very undereducated one) is that the universe is filled with several different sized spheres from several big bangs originating at several moments in time.  This perspective is 3D at a frozen point in time and is only dealing with matter, not empty space.  Of course if space itself has a certain shape then those spheres could form a larger pattern expanding and flowing to the shape of that definite space.  I believe personally that space is infinite and that matter that does not have the mass to pull itself back to its source will expand forever.  Taking in all this, the over all shape of the material universe is amorphous.  Yes, this theory could probably get hit hard with dimensional relativity and time distortion and quantum theory and all, but is anyone up to it?  Sorry, if I didn't address what you were actually asking Sean.  I am only slightly familiar with the theory that I think you are referring to about curved space. 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I also dreamed about owning a Rottweiller the other night that was a bit too aggressive.  I was scared of my own dog.  I was ashamed in front of Jim S. that I couldn't control it better, but my main concern in the dream was that I wasn't being very fair to the dog by having me as an emotional guide.  After waking, I wrote Hank (Chris Hill) the next day talking about my fear that I don't have the wisdom to deal with the seriousness of other people's lives.  The dream stirred something in me. (probably the seriousness of seeing the 9-11 stuff on T.V. again had some part of putting these thoughts in my head.)  The feeling was like waking up the next day after a bad acid trip at a family Thanksgiving gathering, thinking who the fuck am I to be screwing with other people's lives.  Serious, serious, serious.... damn, it's not my job to be a reality fixture for others.  I'm wondering why I'm feeling in the spot light when I really don't have anyone that relies on me in this capacity.  Perhaps being around all these new people at work has something to do with it as well.  After all I just came back from working a job that I had no social contact with others to an environment where I am surrounded by people.  Maybe that's it.  Anyway, cheers to all those self-contained floating souls that might have the same feelings of self-doubt and self-worth or perhaps might actually be concerned for the well being of others.  Row, row, row, your boat, gently down the stream...  (I'm not stoned by the way... just a load of caffine.)    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      This morning I'm slowly waking up.  I fixed a huge breakfast of bacon, eggs, and biscuits.  Yesterday I started my 3:30 to midnight work schedule.  Training is over and I am on the phones selling timeshare vacations.  Yuck and yea.  Hate sales, but love that I'm working with cool people and have an income.  I'm very seriously considering joining the Peace Corps in Belize.   There is an assignment there to teach computers and the internet to school kids.  2 years, food and lodging paid, $28k a year on top of that given as a stipend as I understand it.  Ahhhh, Belize, jungle, mountains, 2nd largest barrier reef in the world, Mayan ruins, English as the official language... I'm going to set up an interview with a peace corp recruiter in Chicago before the month is over.  I'm sure I'm over glorifying it, but it's something I'm going to find out everything I can before I sign the dotted line, if I sign the dotted line.  Another option to get to Belize is to just save my damn money up and move there.  I had a dream that my mother died last night and it really upset me.  I cried.  I believe it's a symbol representing my need to let go of my boyhood.  (but I e-mailed my mom to see if she was ok, just in case)  I can generally attach just about every symbol in my dreams to a part of myself or my phyche as oppose to real concern for someone else.  I don't think that is the case for everybody though.  Is the mother who dreams about not being able to find her child, truly concerned in the dream with protecting the child or is she more concerned with her self doubts and self worth?  Not sure on this one.   Might be an impossible question to answer.    
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, wuhbuhduh, ....  it's not working  urlLink Di .  ...but thanks for thinking of me.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, I just can't get enough of these tests...
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink      You are the classic yellow squeeky toy.   urlLink Find your inner rubber ducky.  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'm fairly bored and blanky staring at my brother's computer screen in a bit of silly hazy mind babble.  I've been searching the net tonight in an attempt to explain why the word wuhbuhduh always issues forth from my mouth unconsciously.  I have to admit, I haven't found much.  I went through american indian words and places thinking that's sort of the feel of the word, but didn't find much there.  I did find a town in Somalia named Wabada.  Maybe I lived there in a past life.  hmmm...  actually I just was reading the meaning of the town name and it seems to be the word for "Lion".   Maybe that was my last word in a past life and every life I've had from there out, I've been unconsciously screaming it.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
             Cor blimey, I taste like  Tea .   I am a subtle flavour, quiet and polite, gentle, almost ambient. My presence in crowds will often go unnoticed. Best not to spill me on your clothes though, I can leave a nasty stain.  What Flavour Are You?     
     

    
</post>

<date>30,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I get to watch Clay's dog and house for this week.  Wahhhoooooo!  Party at Clay's!  Well, I can't smoke inside and it's raining out, but I can party in the garage... hmmm... I could have done that at Matt's too.  I think I'm going to stay in Indy for awhile 'cause the money is rollin' in and I'm searching for apartments now.  I'd love to find a house, so I can make lots o' noise, but I'm still only able to look for things around $500 a month, so we'll see.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
           Disorder      Rating        urlLink Paranoid :    Low       urlLink Schizoid :    Very High       urlLink Schizotypal :    Moderate       urlLink Antisocial :    Low       urlLink Borderline :    Low       urlLink Histrionic :    Low       urlLink Narcissistic :    Low       urlLink Avoidant :    High       urlLink Dependent :    Low       urlLink Obsessive-Compulsive :    Low       --  urlLink Click Here To Take The Test  --      
     

    
</post>

<date>22,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Man, Ruidoso sounded so good.  There's just one little thing that makes it difficult to see me living there.  It has less than 5000 people and there's no big cities anywhere near it.  I was thinking it was at least 100,000 because I book alot of vacations there for RCI.  I just can't see living in a town that small.  I suppose I just have to start day dreaming about another location to settle down.  San Diego is still floating around the brain.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Read a couple articles on lucid dreaming today.  The articles weren't that interesting, but I did learn a new technique to keep from waking up when you feel yourself losing the dream.  It's called dream spinning.  In the dream, hold your arms out and spin.  This in itself is a good way to get back into the dream.  Another recommended addition to that is to always have a person, time, and place in mind that you will always go to after spinning.  Say, Bob Dylan, at a smoky club, in the early 70's.  It's apparently a very good way to stay in the dream and regain focus.  I just thought Jim S. might be interested in hearing that technique.  I haven't tried it yet, but I intend to.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the Peace Corps thing fell through because I would have to clear my $15,000 debt before they would let me join and I don't see that occurring anytime soon.  My eyes are starting to focus on becoming a mailman here in Indy for awhile and then doing the same in Ruidoso.  That's my new fantasy (could be reality in a year or so) place to live.  I want to learn to be a top notch spelunker someday and the Carlsbad caves are very near Ruidoso, plus my family owns 50 acres of land in the desert in a nearby Texas county.  Plus it's just gorgeous.  Here's a picture of Ruidoso, Southern New Mexico.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Had a blast with Ned, Shari, Uwe, and Jim out on the boat. If Ned and I had our way, we would have invaded those pathetic old people's homes on the hills, but we didn't want to scare the straights in the boat, so we gave up the idea.  Thanks Jim for the trip.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Wuhbuhduh.org ....   coming soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      The greatest trick I ever learned in dealing with someone you're sleeping with alot and you really like him/her, but you're not quite sure if him/her likes you the same way is to mouth the words "olive oil".  If that person says "I love you too", then you're in.  If that person has a shocked look on his/her face, then you say, "Olive oil, baby.  Let's get the olive oil."  (I know that's an old one, but that's all I could come up with and I felt like posting something)
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      AI was awesome.  It was soooo Kubrik, I loved it.    I am... I was.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Bogus that I have to believe in a Supreme Being to be a Freemason.   I didn't want to be a part of that silly club anyway.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks Ned for having me over for the game party.  Yes, of course I found it my duty to start drinking wine early and as fast as I could.  Someone has to do it.  I went with Sonya and Sean downtown for a brief moment where Sonya and I went off to use a restaurant's restrooms.  Sonya beat me to the rest room and so I thought I could quickly dart over to another restaurant and be back to join the group again.  Well, that didn't happen.  I found the restaurant, but they made me buy a drink to use the restroom and of course I wasn't going to leave a perfectly good drink sitting at the bar without it's buddy Ben.  So I drank it and then took a cab back to Shangri-La.  This brief downtown venture should have been enough to sober me up enough to decide to quit drinking for the night.  I was well aware that I was way over my limit, but I had to play some bad harmonica on the front porch and of course one can't do that properly without a drink.  That's the last thing I remember.  Then I woke up in my clothes (thank goodness for that) on a bed.  I'm picturing me getting up very politely and bidding everyone a good night and then walking to that bed on my own power and bowing out for the night graciously.  If anyone is wanting to tell me the real story, I beg you not to.  Good Luck I.U.!!!!!!  Thanks again for the invite Ned. 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Birthday Ned!!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      John, I'm glad you loved London.  Just wanted to mention that where I was in England, it all shut down at 11:00.  I'm talking "Ghost Town."  After 11pm there was absolutely no one on the street left except drug addicts, vagrants, and Ben.  (was that redundant?) I would suppose that in every major city that the night life continues.  Even Manchester had a night life after 11pm, but it was too much of a pain for me to get there without a car and expect to make it back to my flat.  I so wish that I could have made it down to London while I was in England.  That is probably my biggest regret about my stay there.  By the way, may favorite part about England was seeing so much history still standing and the Indian Food.  Oh yeah, and being so close to Amsterdam was kinda fun too. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well at least I got a start on a new df.  Not too special, but hey, we can work with it.  I didn't include you Ernie because I don't think your log is on the drunkenfish and I wasn't sure if you were going to be a jollyjibber or not.  If you want to be a drunkenfish, let me know and you'll be up there as fast as I can get you there.  That also goes for anyone who would like a blog on drunkenfish.org.  Just let me know and I'll get you up there.  (mindevol@hotmail.com)
     

    
</post>

<date>24,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'm finding I like the Star Wars Jedi Knight II, Jedi Outcast better than I liked Attack of the Clones.  The game is a blast.  It gets about 10x more fun when you finally get your jedi powers and light saber.  I'm still in my in between travel, living out of my suitcase stage and I'm still not goal oriented or focused on anything.  I do finally see the light of where I'm going to settle down for a little while and make a temporary home for myself.  Downtown Indy!  Mainly because I have a job here and until I find something else, I might as well experience downtown Indy.  Move-in date is set for July 1st.  I'm still waiting to be sitting on my own livingroom floor drinking a beer and sighing comfortably that I am home. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Mother's Day all!  I sent my mom a basket of flowers via the internet and she e-mails me back with, "thanks for the two baskets of flowers!"  I'm thinkin'..."two?"  They're 60 bucks a piece.  "Ummm... your welcome mom."  What am I going to do?  Send it back.  Anyhow, it's rare I do anything for me mum, so why not.    Here's some more movie ratings of stuff I've seen lately. Training Day - 15 Ali - 35 (although Will Smith did a great job) Behind Enemy Lines - 25 Another Teen Movie - 36 (yes I paid money to rent this, don't ask) American Pie 2 - 40 (this one too.) Spiderman - 12 Changing Lanes - 22  Also in the video games catagory with the same rating system but how many jack and cokes to be the best video game ever -  American McGee's Alice - 8  (finished it though in two sittings. worst part is the super cool graphically rendered big bad guys take very little strategy to kill except to run like crazy around in circles saving up for another big blast at 'em.) Alone in the Dark (the new nightmare) - 26 (creepy, but I'm always getting stuck on something stupid you have to figure out.) Triple Play - 20 (relaxing... this game has a definite jack and coke bell curve in it's favor because of how easy it is to play.)        
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Man, I would love to work for a video game company,  urlLink Bill .  I've always dreamed of that.  Congrats!  That's so cool.  I wish you happiness, luck, and loads of cash with the job.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Birthday  urlLink Shari  !!!  You're a very easy person to like and be around.  Can't wait to hang out again. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I rented 3 movies last night.  1. Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back - (Teenagerish crap, but that made me smirk about ten times throughout the movie)  2. Zoolander - (Had a smile on my face for most of the movie, but I never seemed to get into it.)   ** by the way, I suppose I'm too intellectually challenged to make any meaningful comments about these movies, but this is what you get on wuhbuhduh. ... and the last movie, which had the same premise as Zoolander, but is in a completely different league was - 3. The Curse of the Jade Scorpion - I absolutely loved this movie.  Granted I was a little drunk, but the banter between Woody and Helen Hunt reminded me of the old Woody Allen flicks.  I laughed and laughed throughout this flick.   On Ben's rating scale - (how many Jack and Cokes do you need before this flick is the best movie you've ever seen.) -  Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back - 32 Zoolander - 24 Curse of the Jade Scorpian - 13  (please note that the above ratings are adjusted by adding the number of jack and cokes I've already had while watching the movie.)
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2002</date>
<post>


       
         urlLink       Which Peanuts Character Are You Quiz      
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Great Party Chris!!!  I still have your shirt.  Sorry.  I forgot.  I'll drop it by after work some time.  Bocce THIS!
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Model (Washburn NV100) of Jim S.'s new guitar...  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Model (Ibanez AR250hs) of my new Guitar...  
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Hey all!  No excuses for not blogging, but anyway...  Never moved into a place of my own yet.  My brother is buying the house next to him and I'll be moving in there before September.  I need to find a roommate before then.  Rent being $325 a piece / a month.  Cool house:  wooden floors, screened front porch, half finished basement, 2 bedrooms.  I'm dreading putting an ad in the paper and then having to interview a bunch of freaks.  I've never really had any problems with complete strangers moving in, so I'm sure this will work out.   A band is slowly forming together here in Indy.  I absolutely cannot calm myself down about it.  I am totally siked.  It's been about 4 years or so for me and I am way looking forward to it.  It's a loose net of people who can come and go as they please, but I'm hoping everyone enjoys it enough to hang out and attend the one practice a week schedule.   urlLink Jim S.  is going to be doing most of the guitar stuff and we have a friend of mine Paul Arnone on the Bass, and a friend of mine's boyfriend from work, named Jeff, who seems to be in the right creative song workshop mode that I consider myself to be in.  Official practice probably won't begin until I can set up the studio in the basement of the new house, but I'm sure we'll get together a few times before that to hammer out details and begin work on learning parts to songs.   I just put in for my vacation down by  urlLink John Shannon  in Palm Beach Shores for the week of Halloween.  If anyone wants to join me, they are welcome.  I've reserved a 1 bedroom for 4 at the Radisson there.  I believe it is Saturday to Saturday, with Halloween in the middle somewhere, but I'll have to check my calender.  It's still beautiful at that time of year there and all water and beach activities are still going on.  It's a mighty spiffy resort too, so there is tons of stuff to do. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,August,2002</date>
<post>


       
      My Uncle Sim finds humor in  that I don't understand Dickenson (I'm sorry if I feel she is a self-loathing slob).... well......  anyway, he has a book that is on sale about a bunch of people on the Mexican border that decide the United States isn't good enough for them and they all move to new exotic lands beyond the border.  Read it after ordering it at  urlLink dreamcatcherpublishing.net    A shameless plug for my uncle, but he's a smart, generous man and he deserves it.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,August,2002</date>
<post>


       
           
</post>

<date>19,August,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink John  - Sorry to hear about your loss.  I regret never getting the chance to meet the man.  Just know that even with your parents gone, you are not alone in the world.  You have your honey, your brothers, and your best friends always with you.  We all love you dearly.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Happy belated Birthday Di-havana!!!      urlLink Jim S.  is trying to get a rise out of me with that DF not existing without John, but dammit... It's just not going to happen.  I mean who is he to.... well, what I mean is that if he had one ounce of... that is to say, his comments do not affect me at all.  hmmph....
     

    
</post>

<date>12,August,2002</date>
<post>


       
      hmmm... DF is back up on it's old server.  I believe Chris Lea moved it from Liverpool to Baton Rouge, but I don't have the details.  Anyway, I purchased a hosting service for a year and will move it over to that when I get the chance.  DF has had a free ride it's entire life, but I believe I told Chris Lea that it would only be a few months when I first set it up on his server.  If Chris Lea reads this.... Thank you so much for giving the DF a home for free.  I'm assuming that I will not be receiving a back dated bill from you in the mail.  I'll be hosting with Your-Site.com in a couple of days for about $5 a month.  Not too bad.  Cheers!
     

    
</post>

<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Maybe I'm misunderstanding, but... is that your place  urlLink Robyn ?  That's sweet!  Wow... that's awesome!  I love it.  If it's not your place, i still love it.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Good explanation of Zero Point Field . Makes me think about a book I read called The Tao of Physics where the author was comparing the flux of molecules with the Dance of Shiva.   Just wanted to also add, that I don't think I believe this zero point field stuff is really usuable even if it does exist.  I may be proven wrong with time, but that's how I feel about it now.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Ode to a woman that didn't give a shit. Well, Shawn Bradford You're leaving to get married tomorrow. You went out drinking with me a few times. I had a few sexual fantasies about you. You're ass is fine. You talked about yourself constantly and would glaze over when I mentioned anything about myself. You made me feel comfortable with you at times. I showed up to every function you invited me to and you did the same for me. It wasn't really friendship, but it was something. anyway, sorry to see you go, and I'm sorry I never tapped that ass.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      *sniffle...*  good-bye Ned's Beard....  you were a strange experiment that turned into a Ned standard.   good-bye Ned's beard.  I remember seeing that beard for the first time and exclaiming, "Wow, that beard looks natural on Ned..."  but it's life is over, and it's just going to be a memory now.... good-bye Ned's beard...
     

    
</post>

<date>19,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Di, I tried to be a sheep and couldn't do it.  I've tried to be a reindeer and they wouldn't let me in their club.  I never tried to be a goose, but I think I'm best at being a squirrel.  I think I'm staying at that.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Welcome Hope!!!   Long time, no see.  I tried to get my brother Clay to blog, but he didn't last very long.  Ned still links to Clay, so maybe he'll bounce back, but I'm kinda thinkin' he's probably done with it.  Anyway, I'm glad you're blogging and I look forward to keeping up with what Hope is thinking and up to.   (I'm in a three exlamation point mode... can I help it if I feel happy and everything I say has to be triple stressed?) I just moved into my own place!!!   I just had my cable internet installed!!!  My first real band practice in five years is tonight!!!  Yahooooo!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink WeenRadio is the shit!!! 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Congrats Di !!!   I hope life is more comfortable for you at Scotty's.    The new guy in the band, "Jeff", is an awesome drummer.  He seems like a real cool dude as well.  I think this basement band is going to work out.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Halloween will be here soon!!!   Still no verification on my holiday request from work yet, John.  I hope I'm still going to be able to get the Radisson near where you live.  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Did I ever mention how much I love The Onion?  Sales Disappointing For First-Ever Hustler Swimsuit Issue LOS ANGELESSpokespersons for Larry Flynt Publications are struggling to explain the poor sales of Hustler magazine's first annual swimsuit issue, crammed from cover to cover with beautiful young women modeling the latest sexy swimwear. "We are utterly baffled," LFP public-relations director Kenneth Micklos said of the issue, which sold 17 newsstand copies nationwide. "Our readership demographic is overwhelmingly heterosexual and male, with a strong interest in looking at beautiful women. It's a mystery."
     

    
</post>

<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      oh ma gawd!  Angel just called about the room. She's a young rock n' roller from Illinois.  She's going to call back about coming to see the house.  C'mon little girl.... everything is cool.... c'mon.....
     

    
</post>

<date>09,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Talked to three perspective roommates.  Two losers in their 40's that have no musical talent, work for themselves, and want to take over the band that hasn't started yet (Rednecks!!!).  Who'd a thunk it living on the east side.  There is one straight forward businessman, but I haven't decided about him yet.  He asked a ton of questions which I suppose is good, but was constantly trying to unveil what was wrong with my offer.  He seemed a little too much Type "A" personality.  I just want a responsible hippie.  Is that too much to ask?
     

    
</post>

<date>04,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      My ad comes out next sunday and wednesday in the paper for a roommate.  This is kind of exciting.  Who is going to call about the room?  I mentioned in the add that the new person would get the master bedroom, but that they would have to put up with a rock band in the basement.  Rent $325.  I'm hoping for a teenage beauty queen who has a thing for alcoholics.  In realistic terms, a really laid back person is all I want.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Here's a plug for my dad's upcoming book as well. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I was searching the internet for the singer I mentioned before and I finally found him.   urlLink Ralph Stanley!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Brad  - I'm not sure if we discussed this before, but I went and saw the "Down from the Mountain" tour when it came to Indy.  I absolutely loved it.  Alot of the focus of the show was the original performers of the music from "O' Brother, Where Art Thou?"  One of the best concerts, I've ever seen.  Just sittin' back with a brewski, listening to awesome and strange vocal harmonies mixed with various mountain string instruments and percussion.  The highlight of the evening was some old guy who everyone praised as the king of Bluegrass.  I wish I could remember his name.  He came out and sang all by himself without any instrumental or vocal backups for his first number.  I don't believe I have ever heard a more soulful voice.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Why does the government always warn of a terrorist attack everytime I'm about to step on a plane?  I can just see it now; some bearded dude grabs a lady and Ben slinks off into the bathroom where he curls up into a fetal position and starts whining like Bernard Shaw.  or maybe I'll get up and tackle the terrorist and wrestle him to the ground saving the whole plane.  or maybe it will just be a long comfortable flight and I'll get some reading done.  *sigh*.  I've got an econo flight to West Palm via a three hour wait in the Dallas/Ft.Worth airport.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, alright!  I'm off of work for 10 days straight.  Got all the RCI stuff worked out.  I'll see ya in West Palm Beach on Friday night, John.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Man!!! I am so sick of not being able to talk to a human being at RCI.  Everything is automated and me being in the peon position that I'm in, I'm not allowed to talk to real people.  I have to fill out forms and wait for days for a response that is usually totally screwy and then I have to fill out forms again to correct the misunderstanding.  I'm trying to get off for vacation.  I asked for the 11th - 14th of October.  My normal days off would be th 8th, 9th, and 10th and then the 15th, 16th and 17th.  That would give me 10 days off!!!  Wahooo.... or at least it would be wahoo if I could get someone to understand my request.  I got an e-mail back saying "ok, you can have the 11th, 13th and 14th off and the 7th.  Where's the fucking 12th?!?!  What, I'm suppose to fly back from Florida so I can work the 12th...  MORONS!!!  What a shity system.  I just filled out another form saying, I don't want the 7th off, please give me the 12th off.  In another week of waiting for a response it's just not going to matter.  I suppose I'll just have to call in sick on the 12th.  I am going to go ahead and buy plane tickets anyway as soon as I here from John.  I somehow forgot to ask him about all this planning.  I did get a room at the Radisson from the 13th to the 20th.  I'm planning on giving the room to John and his wife for the last three days.  I won't go into the trouble I had trying to get that room.  Never what I want at RCI, just what I get.  It's hard to complain about the room though... $125.00 for an entire week at a resort that normally cost $165 per night. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>22,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'm working a new job now at Conseco.  Customer Service Rep... yee haw.  The basement band is going well, but we can't come up with a name.  I wanted to call the band "Booby".  That idea didn't go over well with our Board of Directors (Drummer's girlfriend, Bass player's wife).  The new name is "The Dangerous Kitchen", which I admit, I chuckled and liked at first, but now I think it's a bit like the random generated band names you can do online.  I don't know.  If anyone has any cool band names, pleeeeeeeese, give me some suggestions.  I'm not huge on the importance of a band name, but we do have to put something on the cd cover.  The cd release, (meaning, when we pass them out to friends and family who want them) will probably be around the first of the year instead of the Thanksgiving date we had thought previously.  Our sound is sort of Nirvana/Beatles.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Wow!  What a cool feeling to have people write on your web page.  I somehow missed this whole comments phenomenon until now.  Thanks for welcoming me into this by posting comments.  Anyway, the job frustration built up in my head too much to just cruise along with, so I went ahead and quit.  I've got 2 months worth of savings, so I won't need any income for that amount of time.  I hooked up with a bartending agency for 60 something bucks that sends me a manual and a bartending kit and a test for certification.  I know, it sounds like I just got ripped off, but they guarantee placement in your area within two weeks of certification.  Since I don't really know jack about serving alcohol (it's usually straight from the bottle to the mouth for me), I thought this couldn't hurt me.  I'm going to do alot of searching on my own to find a bar I would be comfortable with.  I figure wherever I get placed probably won't be the bar I'll want to stay at.  So basically, I'll use my first location as a means of learning the trade.  If I like the place, then great.  If I don't, then by then I'll have some experience and I'll seek out a more comfortable working environment.  What I dread most about being a bartender is in going from white collar jobs to blue collar jobs, the character of the boss seems to always change.  I'm almost certain to start off with a redneck asshole for a boss, but that's how that goes.  I'm ready for it.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I feel like Dudley Moore in "Bedazzled" with all the jobs I've had.  If it's not one thing it's another.  Nothing seems to go quite right.  Everytime I get going on a job, there comes a moment when I just look up at the sky, extend my toungue and go Thpppppbbpbpthpbpb!!!  This Conseco Customer Service job sucks!  First off, they have a million different companies they've acquired all with their own 1980's circa computer applications.  No information is easy to obtain.  It's a matter of finding the right program, scrolling through reams of data looking for the code that signifies what type of policy and then the actual info you need is buried in reams of more code.  The whole time the customer thinks you're an idiot for taking so long to get the answer to a simple question.  Also, most every person that gets on the phone with me is stinking mad.  Conseco sold all these Universal life policies in the 80's projecting great things with the policy by estimating the interest rates would stay at 7% or more.  The interest rates now are about 3%, so everyone is getting notices that their policies are out of money and that they need to start paying alot more premiums if they want to keep their policies from lapsing.  Well, thpbpbpbpthpbpbp!!!  I want out of this stupid job.  The pay is great and the benefits are awesome, but I don't want to do this everyday.  I've decided that I want to be a bartender.  Not the safest choice of jobs for me, but I'm going to do it anyway.    
     

    
</post>

<date>27,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Personally, I don't see the big deal about actually going through with making identical clones of a person.  I see alot of the negatives, but I don't see the positives.  I can see that there are many medical advancements that can be made in the field of cloning, but I don't see the purpose of actually going all the way with making the actual clone.  Hmmm... would I want an exact clone of myself.... maybe.  I'd have to involve a woman with the gestation anyway, so I might as well just fuck her and share our genes.  It's evolution baby!!   I'm usually never one to stand in the way of science, but in this case, the potential suffering without (to me) a usuable goal is pointless.  I'm a bit of a sociopath when it comes to my beliefs in what should be sacrificed in the name of science, but with this already overpopulated world, I don't see the significance needed to allow such a human experiment.  ... and how about that Raelian Cult.  Yeah, whatever... to me it's just the same as all religions except they've gone back to the human sacrifice.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'm staying at my brother's house while he's in New Orleans.  Just a good way to get some time to myself and take care of his dog.  I came home on the 23rd to find a business card on his front door.  Kim Dotson of the United States Office of Personnel Management.  This is what the card says word for word. "The U.S. Government is conducting a background investigation on a person you may know.  Please call my office during the business day and leave a message of where and when I may contact you to arrange an interview." Who are they after... could it be me?  Probably not, but this really puts the image of Facism in my head.  Next we'll be having to show our papers in random inspections.  'knock, knock, knock... open up, Homeland  Security!'
     

    
</post>

<date>25,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I've been drunk most of these holidays.  Big surprise.  My thoughts meander around what I might write about, what I might do to express myself, and what's the point.  Sometimes I look at American culture as a society that is chasing shadows.  Do we understand what big purposes we fight for or live for.  I guess all I can talk securely about is what I feel strongly about.  I wish I could pin that down.  I personally just entertain myself by watching VH1 shows on old bands, I play the newest video games to entertain myself and escape from the looming ghostly goal of progressing myself.  We went from the father figures of the 40's and 50's to the rebellious children of the 60's to the recovering ease off of the 70's to the selfishness of the 80's to the fake, but trully felt love of the world to escape ourselves in the 90's to what I hope is clear vision of what the fuck is going on of this decade.   I may be way off, but I find myself wondering what the hell do I really care about in this world.  Stop the war, comes to mind.  Stop killing each other... but what is the real goal.  For me, and I know this doesn't play into much that we can do first hand, but it is to make the human race survive long enough to actually discover a purpose and focus, worthy of humankind.  Survival might be a good start.  Anyway, back to the focus of song lyrics, what the fuck do I write about these days.  I don't have a girlfriend, family, any of the stuff that everyone else around me seems to have.  I do have the anger of the youth, but I'm completely out of touch with what their anger is and am way too in touch with my own personal anger of underacheivement.  (That was just me complementing myself in thinking that I have the ability to be something great, but I just haven't realized what that thing is.)  This is not thinking that's getting anywhere, but I thought I'd share the effort by actually going ahead and posting this ramble.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I just had a chat with my Uncle Sim and he says that the tooth rat thing is a german tradition that my Grammy passed down.  I love that.... the Tooth Rat.   What a wonderful thing that I actually believed in as a child.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Between writing on notebook paper at work like a little kid, stuff like Ben Emerson - Guitar, vocals... etc... and writing my band name in every style imaginable, I am in love with having a band again.  I know it sounds like I'm really into myself, but so what.  I'm very happy to be in a band again.  The name of the band is Penny Strange and the cd will be called Fledgling.  It's all about being 20 something from suburbia and experiencing the city.   We're going to try to write a title song, but the cd is already strong without it.  The new date, now that we have a sound man that has put things in perspective for us, is going to be sometime this summer.  I will throw a huge bash that all will be invited to.  I know it is so much cooler to release good music quietly and just say, "yeah, here it is... whatever."  I'm too egocentric for that.  I want to make a giant event of it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Merry Festivus or Winter Solstice or Christmas or whatever you like to celebrate.  Is Santa Claus God?  Is Santa Claus a saint?  What's the difference between saints and gods.  They both have magical powers and people still believe in them...  That would kinda put a damper on the whole one God belief and how superior this monotheism is to all those ancient belief systems.... but I digress.  Well for me, I guess Santa Claus is the only god I ever knew... oh yeah and the tooth rat.  (We had a bit of a warped family and the tooth fairy was never mentioned.   I think that was my Uncle Sim's doing.... it really sounds like his work.)   Anyway,  I would like to share my love for all the bloggers.  I don't write much, but I very much enjoy reading what everyone has to say in their daily perception of what's going on.  The world is a wonderful place for me.  I absolutely love watching everyone flow past and back again from my choice of a spot to settle.  I've been a driftin' most of my life and for once I am standing still to see what's going on.  I'm really finding I love humanity.  There is so much good in every person I come in contact with.  Either I've picked a very good spot to observe from or I'm getting a good sample of the norm.   In either case, I love you all.  Merry Christmas. 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ...and drunk
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Google is so much fun when you're drunk.  Just make up a word... pull it from the depths of your soul and spell it out.  Then hit the google search button and see what pops up.  It's just a fun way to surf.  Even if the first page that pops up is not interesting.  Sometimes it leads to something.   ok... maybe I'm just really bored.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the job hunt is going awful.  I've sent out over 100 resumes and I've only had one interview so far.  I went through that today and have another with the same company thursday.  Life Insurance again.  Uggghhh.  This time I'd actually be selling and renewing policies.  Since it's my only lead so far, I suppose I have to do my best in the interviews and go for it.  My old job at RCI might be a possibility also.  RCI has a rule that if you quit, which I did, then you can return within a year.  I'll have to go before a review board or something like that to prove I really am worthy of taking back, but I'm willing to do that if it means getting a paycheck.   The band is kind of on the rocks as well.  Paul, the bassist, has alot of family obligations and can't dedicate the time needed to do the project.  We're still trying to work something out, but I'm behind whatever decision he makes.  I hope he stays.  If Paul goes, Jeff and I decided not to get a new bassist, and just try to record everything on our own.  Maybe it might work to just bring Paul back when we play live.  We'll see.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm drunk as usual, but  I can't see losing byn over something stupid.  Come back Byn... I need you.  Please don't forsake us.... You're a huge part of why I still blog.   I want you, I need you.... please come back.  I don't write much, but I read and you're the best personality around for me.  I love reading your blog.   Don't go.  You blog a little like I do.  What's on your mind and very honest.  I love your blogs.  I won't go on and on, so this is it.... my final plea.... it would very much hurt to see you stop blogging.  Please don't.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Random links in my latest web surfing  urlLink http://www.theonion.com/onion3803/judge_orders_god.html   urlLink http://armageddononline.tripod.com/volcano.htm   urlLink http://www.modelrater.com/cgi-bin/intervote/vote.pl   urlLink http://www.theforce.net/episode3/   urlLink http://www.movie-list.com/comingsoon.shtml   
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is a little long for the joke, but I like the idea.  urlLink Office Linebacker. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I thought this page needed a picture.  Here's the lovely Mary Ann just for fun.  ahhhh.... Mary Ann... sweet, sweet, Mary Ann.       some equal billing of Ginger for Paul.   ... and of course that studmuffin, the Professor.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I know anyone who reads this page is sick of hearing about me searching for a job, but today that officially ends.  I got the job at Safeco and start March 10th.  I still have to wait tables for a few weeks though starting tonight to make ends meet.  ok... that's the end of this job search stuff.  Next topics will probably move on to the War.  The most surface thing about the upcoming war to me is that the views of left and right are so far apart, it's scary.  What that means to me is that pretty much most people don't have any real information.  I know that when my roommate talks about it, he is quoting conservative radio, and I know that he knows that when I talk about it, I am quoting liberal journalists.  (mainly articles on commondreams.org)  I read the New York Times online everyday, but they are mainly trying to keep up with the ongoing events instead of answering the questions of why.  Maybe only the privileged decision makers are allowed real information these days.  You might as well ask the guy bagging your groceries as read an editorialist.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I believe I have 3 jobs now.  I do a final interview with the main one Wednesday.  Thanks Chris H. for the job lead at Safeco.  I really hope that one is the one.  Meanwhile, I start work part time at a bookstore tomorrow and I have a job at Lone Star, waiting tables, that starts sometime at the end of the week.  I made it.  Barely.  I didn't even sell anything.  Amazing.  My brother/landlord gave me a bit of a breather on the rent, so I'll have to make it up to him.  Thanks bro.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      After mulling through the potential democratic candidates, I have to say that Kerry looks the best so far.  Sen. Edwards from North Carolina looks fresh and I agree with what I know he has voted for, but I think he lacks accomplishments.  I like Gephardt, but he's actually a little too conservative on some issues if that's believable.  Gephardt is certainly the torch holder for the liberal democrats, but I think he's run enough times to prove he really can't win.  Other names like Dodd, or Biden, I'll have to look into a little more.   Leiberman doesn't have a chance.  I suppose he's more middle of the road, but he doesn't have the charisma to pull the presidency off.  Anyway, those are my initial thoughts on the matter.  I'm sure they'll change as I learn more.
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I've got alot of promises from jobs, but so far no one has locked into a final interview yet.  It seems this snow has put everyone in the frame of mind that it's more important to just get through the day, rather than bother with interviews and such.  I have four jobs all pending an interview and every one of them has told me that they will call me.  I've called every one back, and they tell me someone will call.  I've even gone in person to get the ball rolling, covered in snow, and they tell me.... we need to have a meeting about this.... we'll call you.   I really need an uzi or a sawed off shot gun to make my point understood, I think.  I've had interviews that promised second interviews and those are the ones I am most hopeful for.  Right now waiting tables is the most important job to get because it will give me instant cash from tips.  I have a head hunter looking for jobs that promises to land me a $28,000 a year job within two weeks if I'm good at interviews.  We even practiced some interviews.  I swear, I have lost total respect for the corporate world.  No one ever asks straight interview questions like, " what would you do if this common situation happened in the job you're applying for?"  or "what do you expect out of this job?" ...  or "what are your career goals?"   nope.  they would rather try to build a psychological profile from statistics and corporate passed along methods in determining what kind of worker you will be.  Questions like what type of animal would you be or what would your friends say are your major faults, are questions that elicit learned responses.  They don't give you time to sit and think of a real answer.  What they want is for you to spout the answers they expect to hear straight off the end of your toungue.  A long considerate pause of contemplation makes you tagged as "an idiot."  I do well in interviews as a whole, but I still think corporate psychological tracking and tagging is just plain stupid.  If people answered these questions honestly then maybe it might give them data that they could use.  If they asked me what my friends thought my major flaws were, I should say that's personal information and it's none of your damn business.  Of course that would be telling the truth and that would be the real data they were looking for.  Instead, I'd probably laugh and say something like, "they'd say I can't dance."  I'd get a chuckle from them which lightens the mood and creates the likable atmosphere I wanted, and then I'd say something like, "I guess they might say that I'm too detailed oriented.  I like to wrap every project up into a nice neat package and my friends can find that annoying sometimes."  *smile* (sparkle from teeth)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is a good  urlLink astrobiology and space science site  that is well maintained by an individual instead of an organization or company.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ...that last post was just a bit stupid and insensitive... so *poof*, it's gone
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Strange dream:  I am semi-sick and have the day off so I've been napping most of the day.  I just thought, like spab, I'd share a dream I had.  It was kind of like groundhog's day (the movie) but with only ten minutes to relive.  The first part of it was me talking to an unknown friend walking down a port city street.  I could smell the sea water in the air.  It was just a lovely day and we were walking past shops talking about  various social encounters and the lives of other people we knew, etc...  Then I notice that my friend has an awestruck look of horror in his face and he's looking over my back, above me.  I turned around and wham!  I felt an extreme slam to my left shoulder and everything turned bright yellow-white for less than a second and then I was suddenly down the street and again it was a lovely day, and I was by myself and I realized that I had the same ten minutes to live over again.   I knew that in ten minutes there was going to be that same nuclear bomb that had just happen to hit me square in the shoulder, dropped on the city again, but really for the first time.  I saw a plane landing nearby and thought to myself that if I could get to the airport, maybe I could steal a plane and escape or maybe even fly towards the thing and save some lives by making it blow up in the air.  I knew I probably would never be able to intersect it, but at least I could try and I could have escaped knowing I tried something.  I got to the airport and found the only accessible plane was a fighter jet.  I thought I knew a little bit about planes, enough to perhaps get it off the ground.  I figured if I screwed up and crashed then "oh well", I would have died in the bomb explosion anyway.  I spent the rest of the 10 minutes sitting in the cockpit trying to get the engine started.  I couldn't figure that out even and then I saw the bomb come down and wham!  bright yellow white flash, and then I was sitting in a bar across from a hot woman and I realized I had the same ten minutes to live over again.  (I'll shorten this ten minutes)  Long story short, we went up to her apartment and I got off just as the building began to shake violently and then I was on a boat in the harbor and I realized I had the same ten minutes.  This time I just sat there on the deck and smelled the sea air and looked at the sky and at the people walking on the docks and I just watched my entire ten minutes, not thinking about a whole lot, just trying to appreciate the world.   Wham!  bright yellow-white light and then I woke up from my nap for real.  
     

    
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Is it wrong for a 35 yr old man to like  urlLink Tatu ?  I think it is.  I mean if I loved their music and all, maybe that would be something, but I don't recall ever liking the sound of drum machines and Abba vocals, so.... yes, it is wrong for me to like  urlLink Tatu ... I think. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      um... Happy Birthday Jibber!!!  I forgot that your birthday was in May.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I've never been good at making money, but I've always paid my debts.  It's looking like pretty bleak times here for me money-wise so I'm cutting back on all luxuries.  That includes the internet.  If anyone e-mails me, just know that response time is going to be very slow because I'll be checking e-mail at my bro's house every now and again.  If anyone has any job leads for me, e-mail me at mindevol@hotmail.com.   I haven't done anything with the drunkenfish in some time now, but I think I'm going to let anyone who wants to play with it for awhile do so.  Just to let everyone know, if big changes occur (which they might not at all), I have nothing to do with what is going to happen to the site.  Peace.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      On the warpath again for a job.  If future employers knew how many jobs I have had in my lifetime, they would laugh in my face.  Blogger looks way different than I remember.  I actually accidently came to blogger trying to get my free hoodie for being a bloggerpro member and ended up on this posting screen.  Maybe it's fate that I will start posting again or maybe not, but here's a post.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Song seven 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Song six 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Song five 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Song four 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Song three 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Song two 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Song one 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm moving to New Orleans in the next week or so.  I really wanted to make my album here in Indy before I left, but it never happened.  Our bass player took his recorder when he quit and he had all the tracks on his hard drive.  I had sixteen songs in total for the cd.  I did however receive a cd from a friend of a recording from our third practice.  We had learned 7 of my songs at that point, but the recording is bad and it is recorded through one mike in the middle of the room.  Everything is live and dirty.  Please excuse some of the bad singing notes I produced.  They make me cringe when I hear them, but like I said:  Live and Dirty.  So without further delay.... here is the only recording of Penny Strange.  The cd would have been titled Fledgling.    vocals and guitar - Me drums - Jeff Coyler bass - Paul Arnone  Sorry for all the repeated lyrics... we were just working on structure in this practice and I didn't know all the lyrics to the songs.  Also, the computer I'm putting this on the web from doesn't have sound, so I have no clue what song is titled what, but this is the songlist in no particular order.  Boulevard Crack Whore Nun Playing on the Wabe The Story of Ug Horse and Rider Mother Wickerman  recorded in December of 2002 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Damn this State!!!   Here I was all up for trying to win Louisiana over to the democrats and some bumfuck Republican (I'm just guessing republicans are responsible)  rejects Al Sharptons bid for the State Primary.  I guess his check wasn't certified and his main headquarters address wasn't on the form.  This is the presidential race and we've seen him on every debate!  In a state where most of the African American population doesn't feel it's worth voting anyway because the system is against them, I do believe this will convince at least half to not vote come election day.  The African American vote turn out is the largest factor in getting the Louisiana demo vote in the election.  Jesus, why couldn't we just work it out over the phone with Mr. Sharpton's staff.  What the hell!!!!  I'm so pissed, I could throw this computer through the window.  I may be overblowing this because I have no editorials backing me up on this thought, but it just seems the situation to me.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Damn this Macintosh!!!  I accidentally hit clear as I was writing the last sentence of a very long post.  I'm not going to write all that again.  Here's a brief synopsis. 1. Kerry is still my man, although I like Dean as well.  I'm worried that neither can win a southern state.  I'm prepared to volunteer on the weekends to help get New Orleanians registered and actually voting, because I feel that is the best thing I can do to get this state to swing away from Bush.  2. I start my prison orientation this week.  CPR, how to handcuff prisoners, etc...  I won't be dealing with prisoners directly, but in any prison environment it is always good to be prepared.  3.  I have a possible lead on a place to live in Uptown for May.  It's nothing definite, but I was offered this place last time I lived here and it's a possibility this time.  It's a renovated horse stable behind a large house in a nice section of town near Audubon Park and Tulane University. (the area I lived last time in N.O.) It has a cool brick courtyard and a fountain with beautiful gardens.  I'm not religious, but for this cool of a place and for this cheap of rent, I will pray.  The cheap rent comes from having to keep watch on the larger house.  4.  Being on this Mac makes it difficult for me to change my site much or post.  One thing is that I don't have web tools and software for Mac and I am only able to use it about twice a week, because my brother works from home on it almost 24/7.   I haven't been very good at posting anyway, so no big change there, but I know Jeff wanted me to get rid of all that clown stuff on my site and restart that section with all the new music they're creating in his basement laboratory.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      oh, hell yes.  Thank you Spirit!!!  I was beginning to think that failure after failure would mean unbearable withdrawl of financial support for mars exploration.  More successes mean more money.  I don't have much hope for Beagle, but my fingers are still crossed.  Oh yeah, and GEAUX TIGERS!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I remember going out to a parade with Jason King last time I was in New Orleans and seeing this great big gang of kids walking along following some teenagers.  They were terrorizing people in cars.  Beating on people's windows and screaming at them while not letting them drive on.  Jason wanted to go kick their asses, but I think I talked him out of it.   Anyway, the same type of gang  was walking along the Muses parade yesterday and they ended up shooting 4 people in a scuffle and killing one woman.  If this is a growing trend, Mardi Gras will soon come to an end.  One reason is that no one will want to go out to the parades, but more importantly the parade Krewe's will get sued (because that's where the money is at) and then they'll just quit when it becomes too financially draining.  The police were there in no time and arrested 4 teenagers with guns:  Ages 19,17,17,15.  They have told me at the bars I've been frequenting lately that just about everytime they get robbed, it's by a kid with a gun.  Another thing that scares me about Mardi Gras is that crowd on Bourbon street.  It is so jammed packed with people that if there was a fire or someone caused a panic by shooting off a gun then the death toll would be catastrophic.  Also it scares me that all those unsuspecting drunken tourists who wander away from the French Quarter, away from the river, across St. Claude,  have no idea what they are walking into.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mardi Gras is coming up.  Can't wait.  It's been awhile for me.  Anyone I know who will be in N.O. and will want to hang out, let me know.   The Vieux parade already went by my house.  That's the only parade that's allowed to go through the Quarter.  My bro had a bunch of Louisiana and New Orleans history books lying around when I arrived here and I poured through them all.  I can't remember  when in my life I've actually read 4 books in one month.  No money, with nothing to do, can do that to a person, I suppose.  Common themes throughout Louisiana history: 1. Racism 2. Extreme Political corruption 3. Bad financial ventures 4. Mosquitoes/Yellow fever 5. Slave labor of the Irish for canal building- African Slaves were too valuable a property to have them die so often and there were always new Micks off the boats daily. 6. Biblical Flooding 7. Excessive violence, drinking and drug use 8. Music and Theatric hub of the South 9. Awesome food 10. Cypress Trees, Sugar, Cotton, ...and later Rice then Oil. Today the largest industry is Tourism. 
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Two new bloggers on drunkenfish coming up.   urlLink Andrew Scott  and  urlLink Brad Morrow .  Both Geography majors in college.  Andrew, I knew at University of Georgia and Brad I knew at Georgia State.  Two very different people though.  This should be fun.  I'd link to them now, but I want to give them a chance to set up how they like.  I'm having trouble with my Flash program and I totally screwed my brother's brand new laptop by trying to download a cd key from the internet.  Surprise! Loads of new software was automatically installed.  It's probably what I get for trying to make my tutorial version permanent.  Luckily my bro didn't have anything on the computer, so we wiped the whole thing clean and now it's fine.  Sometimes my impatience makes me stupid.  What can I say?  I went to hear some NPR host (Sarah Vowell) speak at NOCCA.  (New Orleans Center for the Creative Arts.)  She was funny as hell.  One quote of hers that is helping me cope with my letting the porn industry into my brother's laptop is, "Is there a pile of skulls?"  Looking back through history at all the evil people in the world and then looking at my own crime helps my guilt fade away.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hang in there  urlLink Di-Havana .  The ARMY huh...  wow.  One thing good about that is that all the things that seem like problems now, won't make the slightest bit off difference once you have the ARMY as a monkey on your back.  Maybe a whole new life is what you needed.  I wish you the best.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Walter Cronkite warns politicians to  urlLink make Global Warming an issue. 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've looked at a lot of possible VP candidates for Kerry and I think I'm ready to make my prediction.  It came down to two fairly obvious people.  (I really did search around though).  The first is Bob Graham from Florida.  The second is Evan Bayh from Indiana.  Drum roll ......  and the winner is.... Evan Bayh.  You can all start making your Kerry-Bayh signs, bumper stickers, and T-shirts now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Here's an atheist page on Bush. 
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was reading this article  urlLink "Is Military Creeping into Domestic Law Enforcement?"  when one of my bosses came in here at the Sheriff's Office to tell me that we are going to have to go to a meeting tomorrow with Homeland Security.  The article I linked to isn't anything special, but the coincidence was somehow funny to me.  I don't think this is anything to build up into anything, but I haven't posted in a while so...   there's a post.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink TheDialectizer  is fun and easy.  Here's a paragraph of  urlLink John's  in different dialects.  John The diarist on his stomach, sleeping nightmares. Wanting to record Everything. The dream of How. The works of man, the interiors of the cell. Every cell, in every body; every animal, that ever was. Every sub-atomic particle seen in it's divided state; a separate, magnified entity; and in union, communing--the product it composes. Recording the relativity as from every angle; representing each cause per glimpse. From who or what, to then & now. The ultimate diary, the ultimate vision. To behold The Entirety.  Redneck Th' diarist on his stomach, sleepin' nightmares. Wantin' t'reco'd Ev'rythin'. Th' dream of How. Th' wawks of man, th' interio's of th' cell, ah reckon. Ev'ry cell, in ev'ry hide; ev'ry animal, thet evah was. Ev'ry sub-atomic particle see in it's divided state; a separeete, magnified intity; an' in union, communin'--th' produck it composes. Reco'din' th' relativity as fum ev'ry angle; representin' etch cuz per glimpse. Fum who o' whut, t'then & now. Th' ultimate diary, th' ultimate vishun. To behold Th' Entirety.  Jive De diarist on his stomach, sleepin' nightmares. Wantin' t'reco'd Everydin'. De dream uh How, so cut me some slack, Jack. De wo'ks uh man, de interio's uh de cell. Every cell, in every body; every animal, dat eva' wuz. Every sub-atomic particle seen in it's divided state; some separate, magnified entity; and in union, communin'--de product it composes. Reco'din' de relativity as fum every angle; representin' each cause puh' glimpse. From who o' whut, t'den & now, so cut me some slack, Jack. De ultimate diary, de ultimate vision. 'S coo', bro. To behold De Entirety. Slap mah fro!  Cockney The diarist on 'is stomach, sleepin' nightmares. Wantin' ter record Evryfink. The bloody dream of 'ow. The works of man, the interiors of the cell. Evry cell, in evry body; evry animal, that ever were. Evry sub-atomic particle seen in it's divided state; a separate, right, magnified entity; and in union, communin'--the product it composes. Recordin' the relativity as from evry angle; representin' each cause per glimpse. From 'oo or wot, right, to then & now. The bloomin' ultimate diary, the bloody ultimate vision. To behold The bloody Entirety.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here's an article from the Onion for  urlLink Jimmy S.    Study: Owning A Boat Not Worth It  YONKERS, NYAccording to a study published in the April issue of Boating Magazine, owning a boat is not even close to worth it. "Our study proved conclusively that boat-ownership is primarily an inconvenience and a monetary black hole," editor Roger Bernbaum said. "We found little to no reason to keep that thing sitting in a shed all winter just so you can tow it to the lake and pay outrageous docking fees three weekends a year. It'd be much more cost-efficient to don a yachting cap and hang out at the dockhouse." The May issue of Boating promises to explore the financial viability of seaside vacation homes.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Man, those huge monstrosities that work out in the weight room here at the prison really are a pain.  The main trainer is pretty cool.  He might give me a pointer now and again.  But there's this big loud guy that always has to make a giant issue out of me leaving within an hour of me showing up.  I keep telling him, "yeah, well, I've got a schedule to keep."  But everytime, we have to go through the same shit again.  "Where you goin'?  Proud smirk and laughter to his friends,  "You just got here white boy!"  He's white also.  I just nod now with a smirk that whispers, "idiot."  Then there's the guy who always wears his sunglasses to workout indoors.  I wouldn't have a problem with that at all, but he always gets on something right after me and triples the weight.  Don't know why the sunglasses add to that annoyance, but it does.  If they only knew what effort it takes for me even to show up to workout then they probably.... they probably would still be assholes. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
         My new place, if I get it, is in the area of the faubourg marigny dot.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I put in a bid for a new place to live.  She wanted $600 a month plus $50 for off street parking.  I said I'd pay $600 total, parking included.  She said she will use the weekend to think about it.  We'll see.  I really like the place though.  Washer/Dryer hook ups, dishwasher, central a/c and heat, upstairs huge bedroom with windows, (no windows on first floor though.)  It's a converted garage actually, that I have to open a barn-like door to get in.  It's all new and clean and the location is about 6 houses down from my brother Matt's in the Marigny.  Move in date will be May 1st if I get it.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Minor story, I know, but congrats are in order for John Belushi getting his star on the Hollywood walk of fame.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
               I have issues with...        fame  travel  excess  submission  domination        urlLink Take Word Association Test    
     

    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Every now and then I have to just do this.   urlLink Good Vibrations   Oh hell, this one again too I guess.   urlLink I Get Around   I don't know.  Somehow listening to a little innocence just makes me feel better after reading all the hellish news.   Advise:  Don't read the hellish news while you listen to these innocent songs.  It creates a weird sense of derangement and hopelessness.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Thus begins the slow graying of the line between domestic crimes and acts of terrorism.    Will the Patriot Act apply to these types of crimes in the future?  Will the accused be allowed representation?  Even though the Supreme Court betrayed America before by choosing our President, I still have faith that it would step up to the plate if these issues were brought to them and do the right thing.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Kurt Vonnegut writes an article.   
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Dante's Inferno Test has banished you to  the Sixth Level of Hell - The City of Dis!   Here is how you matched up against all the levels:     Level    Score       urlLink Purgatory   (Repenting Believers)   Very Low       urlLink Level 1 - Limbo   (Virtuous Non-Believers)   Very High       urlLink Level 2   (Lustful)   High       urlLink Level 3   (Gluttonous)   Low       urlLink Level 4   (Prodigal and Avaricious)   Very Low       urlLink Level 5   (Wrathful and Gloomy)   Low       urlLink Level 6 - The City of Dis   (Heretics)   Very High       urlLink Level 7   (Violent)   Moderate       urlLink Level 8- the Malebolge   (Fraudulent, Malicious, Panderers)   Moderate       urlLink Level 9 - Cocytus   (Treacherous)   Low      Take the  urlLink Dante's Inferno Hell Test  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Man I screwed this site up.  I don't want to hang around work to fix it so it might be this way for a while.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I love this  urlLink name site .  It generates random names of all nationalities, plus it's just fun to look up name meanings.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I know this is a really simple thing to say, because the Iraq war is a very complex situation, but I want some reporter to just ask Bush point blank again:  "Could you please explain to the American people exactly why you chose to go to war with Iraq?"   It obviously wasn't to help the Iraqi people be rid of a dictator.  Sorry, don't buy that one at all.  It's not because they posed an immediate threat to the United States.  Intellegence reports were found to be contrary to that belief at the time the decision to go to war was made.  I believe Bush pushed us into war for three main reasons.  One - For revenge on the assasination attempt on his father and to show the world that no one can ignore the wishes of the U.S. ( I call this motive "The Cowboy Motive"  Two -  to gain control of Iraqi oil.  (I call this motive "The Family Business Motive.)  Three -  I think we were too blind for our own liking and needed to establish a stronger intellegence link in the Middle East.  (I call this motive "The President of the Country Club Motive.)  There really is no excuse to go into another country that is not a direct threat to us.  National Security may be important to us, but we don't seem to respect that other countries have needs as well and it is not right for us to just walk over them because they annoy our comfort zone.   
     

    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just a Ben update.  I have finally moved in to my new place and set up shop.  I have finally got my washing machine to stop spraying the room by replacing the rubber washers in the hoses and using a shit load of plumbing tape on the threads.  I have finally set up a T.V. with rabbit ears and have been enjoying PBS, CBS, FOX, WB, and a plethora of religious channels.  Maybe enjoying is the wrong word there.  I've been watching PBS the most.   I actually start hating CBS after awhile because I am not a kid or a parent.  I don't think I fit their demographics.  Anyway, as you can tell from my T.V. talk that my life is pretty damn exciting now.  That's all for now. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Published on Wednesday, June 23, 2004 by the Minneapolis Star-Tribune   Bush Team Can't Rise to Responsibilities of World Leadership   by Diplomats and Military Commanders for Change  
     

    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Bill Moyer keynote speech at the Inequality Matters Forum. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There was no article to go along with this Onion headline, but it made me snort out loud to my embarrassment.  Heinz Factory Explosion Looks Worse Than It Is
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          urlLink create your personalized map of europe 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
          urlLink create your own personalized map of the USA   or  urlLink write about it on the open travel guide  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I spent two good work hours on trying to decide who I like best for Kerry's VP.  Thanks  urlLink Amos  for the  urlLink Ontheissues  link.   I still think that a Kerry/Bayh ticket is probably the most electable, but if I am correct in thinking that we can still win this election by choosing the best person for the VP job, it would be Kerrey.  So in summary.  Most Electable -        Kerry/Bayh Best team to govern -   Kerry/Kerrey Most interesting team - Kerry/Nader  Surprisingly, after going through the whole ontheissues site, I agreed more often with Kerry than any other politician.  I'm glad he's our man.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink http://www.newscientist.com  I've actually never heard of this magazine, but after surfin' around their site for awhile I decided to bookmark it.  Then after surfin' around some more I decided, "What the heck! I'm living on the edge of life these days.  I think I like this site enough to link to it. It's just a good science news page. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Higher-Ranking Officer Is Sought to Lead the Abu Ghraib Inquiry   In reference to  urlLink Peptide's  WaPo article.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink My gosh, this trial finally happened?!? 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink An intellegent analysis of President Bush. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Brad - Sorry I haven't linked to your new site yet, but I don't have a working copy of Flash.  The tutorial version of Flash that I have expired and now I'm stuck.  Unless I can crack the version I have, buy Flash, or switch my site to html, the link for your site will be incorrect.  For those who were wondering where Brad has been.  Here is his real site.  urlLink http://www.oliviadrab.com/blog_jbm/blog.html   Andrew - I hope you just haven't had the time to blog, as oppose to me scaring you off with my flaming liberalism.  Anyway, just know you can express your Neo-Nazi views at any time and not lose my friendship. You'll get bashed hard by all the "don't know they're really communists" bloggers on the tanque, but they bash each other all the time as well.  John - Sorry for continuing to call your home "after hours".  Please get your own personal cell phone quickly, before I get drunk and "accidentally" do it again.  Jim - In case you were thinking of sending me a computer, don't.  I appreciate the offer, but my brother gave me an old crappy one, my parents gave me an old crappy one, and my work just made me an offer today to buy the most expensive laptop I could find on the market.  I am set for computers now.  Again, thank you very much for the offer. 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Happy Belated Birthday Ned and Jibber!!!  Totally spaced your birthday Jibber, sorry.  I'm sure I at least tried to drunkenly call you at some point this month.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Bush is a feudal fascist dick.   
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Finally, an informative site on black-outs.  
     

    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sleep has not been good to me lately.  Most of the time, I require at least 7 hours a night to be normal, but I've been going the last 3 and 1/2 weeks with only about 3-4 hours a night.  Not on purpose, but just because I can't seem to sleep.  I can't figure out what it is that keeps me from sleeping.  Here is my list of suspects:(any or all of these may be to blame.)  1. Too much caffeine during the day. 2. Eating too close to when I go to bed. 3. Thinking about various women that I would like to know better. 4. Worried that I won't go to sleep. 5. My stomach stays upset all week from the week-end's drinking. 6. Worried about life direction. 7. My body is just use to 3-4 hours of sleep now. 8. Smoking too close to bedtime. 9. There is something wrong with my brain. 10.I am sleeping. I'm just dreaming that I lie in my bed and stare at the ceiling.    Honorable Mention:  All these damn prison reports I have to read everyday.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Drinking and smoking... Drinking and smoking... Drinking and smoking... I really can't do this anymore. I know it sounds false when a guy with a site called the Drunkenfish says he doesn't want to drink and smoke anymore. I've never made such claims on this site. (I'll have to check the archives on that one) Today I am making a claim and I will hold to it. I am through with Drinking and Smoking. I am simply done. I still want to go to parties and hang out with friends or family at the bar, but I will not personally be drinking or smoking. So there. I think I convinced myself. Anyone else buying this? 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>