<Blog>


<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Sorry I'm posting a day late..... 1. What is one thing you don't like about your body? I have no muscle. 2. What are two things you love about your body? My skin and I don't know 3. What are three things you want to change about your home? Cleaner, bigger, nicer 4. What are four books you want to read this year? Harry Potter 5, and I don't know what else 5. What are five promises you have kept to yourself? If I tell they arn't promises are they?   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I was working on a new site design, but I had to reformat my computer, so the release will be later in February (I think). So for now, the commenting and pictures have gone away, but will return with my new site design.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Where do you currently work? No where 2. How many other jobs have you had and where? 2. IT Support at www.lasvegashomes.com and lawn mower. 3. What do you like best about your job? The pay 4. What do you like least about your job? The stupid people. 5. What is your dream job? To work as a CEO of a multi-billion dollar company   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Ugh. I hate finals week. Thank god it is almost over. I will be so glad when 1136 rolls around tomorrow, lol. I have French and history tomorrow. Those will be easy. Ann is moving to 3rd period French. :'( I might move there, so I can have 5th period history honors. Ugh my dad just walked up and was looking if I was on both computers, which I am, and now he is giving me this whole damn speech about lightening up. DON'T READ WHAT I WRITE! I hate when ppl read over my shoulder on what I write. But moving on................one more day till I can see Quinn. I'm soooooooooooooooooo excited!
     

        
</post>

<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink     What's your sexual appeal?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     

        
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      AWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW! FINALS! lol. I'm ready. I just hope I don't choke, as I normally do. Stefani and I are going to work harder, and get better grades, and help each other on our Aviation work, and stuff. Quinn and I are hanging out again this weekend. He is gonna try and fix my computer. I hope it works. lol. I need to burn cds. :-P
     

        
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Sorry for posting it late.....  1. Where are you right now? At home watching the 49er - Buccaneer game on Fox 2. What time is it? 12:48 3. What are you wearing? Khaki pants and a button down green shirt with blue strips 4. Any people or animals around you? Describe them. Just my dad, do I need to go any farther? 5. What are your plans for the weekend? Hmm, my plans were to hang out with Quinn and go to the mall with Noe. Below is what really happened.   urlLink     MY WEEKEND:  Friday after baseball, I had my dad bring me home, then I went over to Quinn's. I have been spending a lot of time with him. It is great. Friday night we ate Taco Bell, the whole time arguing. I got so mad that I threw 8 cigs out the window. I know, what was I thinking. But yea, we got over that, and then we fell asleep while watching Airplane. That movie is sooooo stupid, lol. But yea, then Saturday morning, I took a shower, then checked email while Quinn took a shower, then we went to Fry's electronics. I thought I had died and gone to heaven. It is sooooo big. lol. Quinn said he messed in his pants, he was so happy. Then Quinn broght me home, and I hung out with Stefani till about 430. Then I came home, and that was that. I woke up Sunday, got ready to go to church (yea tell me about it) and I checked my email. Noe cancelled on going to the mall. :'( His parents said he couldn't go out on a Sunday. OH well, what can you do.   When I got home, Uncle David, who works at Microsoft, had sent us Christmas presents. I got Age of Mythology Collectors Edition. It has a figuring, a DVD on how they made the game, posters, game, music cd, and all sorts of other stuff. It hella kicks ass. But yea. Okay, that is how my life is now. I will post more later.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Due to popular demand, I got rid of the snowflakes.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      My weebend is going good. I'm over at Quinn's (yea I know). I haven't seen hi in like 4 months. It was good to see him. He is my baby. I love him. I spent the day with Jordon. He is cool. We don't really know how we started talking, but all we know is that we are friends now. I have a friend in Miami, lol. I spend the morning helping an agent that works with my mom. Her name is Deb Swann. She wanted me to show her how to make her computer faster, so I showed her and her husband, and I also defraged the computer. That was cool. They have a cat, which reminds me of me, lol. Well, I better go, I don't wanna be rude to Quinn and ignore him.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What is your favorite type of literature to read (magazine, newspaper, novels, nonfiction, poetry, etc.)? Magazines 2. What is your favorite novel? Harry Potter 3. Do you have a favorite poem? (Share it!) No More Fun, No More Love.  As I walk up the jet way, there she is, same place as always, Leaning on the wall in her brown overcoat With the biggest, brightest smile you have ever seen. Her teeth glimmered in the light,  When the sun dances on the water after a storm.  She was my grandma, and I was visiting her, Visiting her on that cold winter day.  It was cold when I went outside and got in her car. We went the same way back home as always,  But something was different, but I didn't know what.  Time passed, and we both got older. We loved each other more than I love chocolate. We would go walking together, and we loved each and every day.  She is gone now. No more fun, no more walking. The house is silent. When I come home, Judge Judy isn't on. No more planning out the week because she couldn't remember. No more fun, no more love.  4. What is one thing you've always wanted to read, or wish you had more time to read?  I don't know! 5. What are you currently reading? The Odyssey   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Mister Rogers: You added a light in my life. You will be missed. Won't you be my neighbor?    PITTSBURGH (Feb. 27) - Fred Rogers, who gently invited millions of children to be his neighbor as host of the public television show ``Mister Rogers' Neighborhood'' for more than 30 years, died of cancer early Thursday. He was 74.  Rogers died at his Pittsburgh home, said family spokesman David Newell, who played Mr. McFeely on the show. Rogers had been diagnosed with stomach cancer sometime after the holidays, Newell said. ``He was so genuinely, genuinely kind, a wonderful person,'' Newell said. ``His mission was to work with families and children for television. ... That was his passion, his mission, and he did it from day one.''  From 1968 to 2000, Rogers, an ordained Presbyterian minister, produced the show at Pittsburgh public television station WQED. The final new episode, which was taped in December 2000, aired in August 2001, though PBS affiliates continued to air back episodes.  Rogers composed his own songs for the show and began each episode in a set made to look like a comfortable living room, singing ``It's a beautiful day in the neighborhood,'' as he donned sneakers and a zip-up cardigan.  ``I have really never considered myself a TV star,'' Rogers said in a 1995 interview. ``I always thought I was a neighbor who just came in for a visit.''  His message remained simple: telling his viewers to love themselves and others. On each show, he would take his audience on a magical trolley ride into the Neighborhood of Make-Believe, where his puppet creations would interact with each other and adults.  Rogers did much of the puppet work and voices himself. He also studied early childhood development at the University of Pittsburgh and consulted with an expert there over the years.  ``He was certainly a perfectionist. There was a lot more to Fred than I think many of us saw,'' said Joe Negri, a guitarist who on the show played the royal handyman in the Neighborhood of Make-Believe and owner of ``Negri's Music Shop.''  Negri said Rogers refused to accept shoddy ad-libbing by guests who may have thought they could slack off during a kid's show.  But Rogers could also enjoy taping as if he were a child himself, Negri recalled. Once, he said, the two of them fell into laughter because of the difficulty they had putting up a tent on the show.  Rogers taught children how to share, deal with anger and even why they shouldn't fear the bathtub by assuring them they'll never go down the drain.  ``He talked directly to children and they listened. He nurtured creativity, self-esteem, curiosity and self-discipline, and his profound contributions will live on, as will the spirit of the man who created them,'' said Pat Mitchell, president of PBS.  During the Persian Gulf War, Rogers told youngsters that ``all children shall be well taken care of in this neighborhood and beyond - in times of war and in times of peace,'' and he asked parents to promise their children they would always be safe.  ``We live in a world in which we need to share responsibility,'' he said in 1994. ``It's easy to say 'It's not my child, not my community, not my world, not my problem.'  ``Then there are those who see the need and respond. I consider those people my heroes.''  Rogers came out of broadcasting retirement last year to record public service announcements for the Public Broadcasting Service telling parents how to help their children deal with the anniversary of the Sept. 11 attacks.  ``If they see the tragedy replayed on television, they might think it's happening at that moment,'' he said.  Rogers' show won four Emmy Awards, plus one for lifetime achievement. He was given a George Foster Peabody Award in 1993, ``in recognition of 25 years of beautiful days in the neighborhood.''  At a ceremony marking the show's 25th anniversary that year, Rogers said, ``It's not the honors and not the titles and not the power that is of ultimate importance. It's what resides inside.''  The show's ratings peaked in 1985-86 when about 8 percent of all U.S. households with televisions tuned in. By the 1999-2000 season, viewership had dropped to about 2.7 percent, or 3.6 million people.  As other children's programming opted for slick action cartoons, Rogers stayed the same and stuck to his soothing message.  Off the set, Rogers was much like his television persona. He swam daily, read voraciously and listened to Beethoven. He once volunteered at a state prison in Pittsburgh and helped set up a playroom there for children visiting their parents.  One of Rogers' red sweaters hangs in the Smithsonian Institution.  Rogers was born in Latrobe, 30 miles southeast of Pittsburgh. Early in his career, Rogers was an unseen puppeteer in ``The Children's Corner,'' a local show he helped launch at WQED in 1954. In seven years of unscripted, live television, he developed many of the puppets used in his later show, including King Friday XIII and Curious X the Owl.  He was ordained in 1963 with a charge to continue his work with children and families through television. That same year, Rogers accepted an offer to develop ``Misterogers,'' his own 15-minute show, for the Canadian Broadcasting Corp.  He brought the show back to Pittsburgh in 1966, incorporating segments of the CBC show into a new series distributed by the Eastern Educational Network to cities including Boston, Philadelphia and Washington.  In 1968, ``Mister Rogers' Neighborhood'' began distribution across the country through National Educational Television, which later became the Public Broadcasting Service.  Rogers' gentle manner was the butt of some comedians. Eddie Murphy parodied him on ``Saturday Night Live'' in the 1980s with his ``Mister Robinson's Neighborhood,'' a routine Rogers found funny and affectionate.  Rogers is survived by his wife, Joanne, a concert pianist; two sons; and two grandsons.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Yesterday I got my baseball uniform! Yea! I'm number 4. I'm sooooooooooo happy, lol. I don't know why. :-P I'm gonna be taking pictures of the unform this weekend I think, so when I take them I will post them to my website. Also, I won a 5 disc cd changer yesterday at the Perfect Attendants assembly yesterday! :-P
     

        
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>23,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
          Your Sexual Energy is Blue!  Blue represents an experimental mindset, and an unpredictability that you are only in touch with. You are not pure, nor are you totally naughty. You are on the borderline. Will you fall into complete kinkiness, or will you back up into being a normal girl?  You're strength is your open-mindedness to try new things. You are confident to follow-through on your lover's fantasies. You often even add your own special edge to them. Do they want to be tied down? Well, how about a massage first, and then tickles to drive them crazy? Blue women know how to mix and match and come out with extraordinary results.  You go about snagging your partners by sneaking up to them and then playing twenty questions. Your targets are often puzzled by your ability to draw out their darkest secrets on a first date. However, you still like to keep your own secrets to yourself.  You could spice your sex life up a bit if you let go of some of your own secrets, and let it all hang out! Tell 'em your desires. You might just surprise yourself! And, for some compatible lovers, look for those who have sexual energies in the colors of red, gray, and brown.   urlLink   What Color is Your Sexual Energy?     urlLink More Great Quizzes from Quiz Diva 
</post>

<date>22,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What is your most prized material possession? I'm not sure, I have so many... 2. What item, that you currently own, have you had the longest? my teddy bear - Mr. Bear 3. Are you a packrat? Hell yea! 4. Do you prefer a spic-and-span clean house? Or is some clutter necessary to avoid the appearance of a museum? some clutter 5. Do the rooms in your house have a theme? Or is it a mixture of knick-knacks here and there? some have themes.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I'm  71% compatible! You're SO in! I mean, this is a match made in heaven. You're in there like swimwear. You've found your match and you better hold on tight, because it don't get no better than this. Congratufreakinlations! But don't blow it, though. Seriously. This is it. The big one. If you screw this up, there's a pretty good chance that you'll probably die homeless and penniless and no one will ever love you. But, hey, buddy, no pressure!   urlLink How Compatible are You? 
     

        
</post>

<date>15,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Explain why you started to journal/blog. I wanted a place to talk about my life. 2. Do people you interact with day to day or family members know about your journal/blog? Why or why not? People yes, family no. I don't know why, lol 3. Do you have a theme for your journal/blog? Not really. 4. What direction would you like to have your journal/blog go in over the next year? I would like to get more people viewing it and maybe move it to its own domain name. 5. Pimp five of your favorite journals/blogs. Um, I don't know.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
        urlLink      For you, kissing is just an appetizer - and a brief one at that. It's not unusual for your hands to wander elsewhere when kissing, even on a first date. Truth be told, you much rather be kissed some where other than your lips!   What Your Kissing Style Says About You:  You're a highly sexual person and not ashamed of it. What's the big deal about sex, anyway? Of all your friends, you're the best in bed... no wonder their lovers are always eyeing you. You're biggest problem in relationships is having too many to choose from. You're in demand, babe!   Your Personal Kissing Matches and Mismatches:  Get together with another Carnal Kisser, and you'll be intwined all night. Not that you'll mind... If you're ready for a wild ride, then search out an Intense Kisser. (Not hard, they're usually obsessed with you anyway.) Kissing an Intense Kisser is... well, mind blowing for you. Word of advice, keep away from Juicy Kissers. They aren't prepared for the amount of lust in your little heart and will be scared away easily. And Romanic Kissers? Please! They want a ring before they'll get down with you!  urlLink  How Do *You* Kiss?  
</post>

<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Here is my new layout! Yea! :-D
     

        
</post>

<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
         Check out  urlLink NASA.gov  for the latest on the Columbia tragedy.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Again...sorry for posting it late.  1. What did you have for breakfast this morning? If you didn't have breakfast, why not? No, because I didn't get up intime for breakfast at Wendy's. 2. What's your favorite cereal? Wheaties 3. How often do you eat out? Do you want that to change? Like 3 times a week. Not really. 4. What do you plan on having for dinner tonight? Got a recipe for that? I honestly don't know. 5. What's your favorite restaurant? Why? Del Taco. Why? They have the BEST frys and burritos   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Emotional Wreck. You are extremely emotional. You feel contentment moreso than happiness and your emotional lows are to the extreme. You need to cheer up and start enjoying your life. Where there is rain there is a rainbow and you need to see it more than others. Do something that makes you happy.    urlLink   How Emotional Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     

        
</post>

<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Quinn and Derek just broke up. The shit hit the fan. OMG. I totally didn't see this coming. Not to get into the details, but Quinn and Derek are no more. I feel awful about it. I feel like it is my fault, even though I know it's not. Or is it? I feel like shit.
     

        
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. As a child, who was your favorite superhero/heroine? Why? The green power ranger, lol 2. What was one thing you always wanted as a child but never got? A play gun 3. What's the furthest from home you've been? England 4. What's one thing you've always wanted to learn but haven't yet? German 5. What are your plans for the weekend? Just to hang out and sleep up for the week to come.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      My heart and prayers are out to those family members of the seven crew members aboard Columbia Space Shuttle, which broke apart over Texas this morning. For the latest details, turn to CNN or check out the article below.     Columbia shuttle breaks up over Texas   Seven astronauts aboard space shuttle   Saturday, February 1, 2003 Posted: 10:36 AM EST (1536 GMT)   JOHNSON SPACE CENTER, Houston, Texas (CNN) -- The space shuttle Columbia, with seven astronauts aboard, broke up as it descended over central Texas Saturday toward a planned landing at Kennedy Space Center in Florida.   Residents as far east as Shreveport, Louisiana, reported seeing and feeling an apparent explosion.   Search-and-rescue teams from the Dallas-Fort Worth, Texas, area were alerted and area residents were urged to stay away from any possible debris from the shuttle, which may be hazardous, said NASA public affairs officer James Hartfield.   President Bush was being briefed at Camp David, Maryland, and was expected to return to the White House by noon. The administration was preparing to convene a "domestic event" conference among all domestic and military agencies that may be involved in the next step.   An administration official said the shuttle's altitude -- over 200,000 feet -- made it "highly unlikely" that the shuttle fell victim to a terrorist act.   NASA officials said they last had contact with the shuttle about 9 a.m. EST, and it had been expected to touch down at about 9:16 a.m. EST.   Video of the shuttle tracking over Dallas showed multiple vapor trails, but NASA spokesman Kyle Herring said it was too early to determine the source.   Steve Petrovich, a police officer in Palestine, Texas, said he heard "a rumble and boom" at about 8 a.m. CDT (9 a.m. EST).     The crew members of STS-107 walked out January 16 for launch aboard Columbia's last mission.   Jim Hubbs of New Boston, Texas, said he heard police discussing over a police scanner "a smoking object going southeast" that disappeared in the Bowie County area near the Arkansas state line.   Amy Townsend of Carthage, said she heard a loud boom that shook her house. She said there were two or three loud noises that lasted about a minute and that she saw a cloud of smoke outside her house.   Don Farmer of Lufkin, outside of Dallas, said he heard loud noises that lasted for 10 to 15 seconds. The noise sounded like dynamite exploding, and he thought it was an aircraft breaking the sound barrier.   Dozens of people, including several officers, reported seeing "a ball of fire," Bowie County Sheriff's office dispatcher Jodine Langford said.   "They saw it go out and then break into pieces," she said.   Officials said no tracking data were available.   Israel's first astronaut, Ilan Ramon, was among the seven-person crew.   There was no official reaction from the Israeli government, but a Defense Ministry spokeswoman said, "Like everyone else, we are feeling terrible, hoping the slightest hope that still remains at this stage will become a reality."   Shuttle commander Rick D. Husband, pilot William C. McCool, payload commander Michael P. Anderson, mission specialists David M. Brown, Kalpana Chawla and Laurel Clark were also on board.   Columbia is the oldest of NASA's shuttle fleet, first launched in 1981. It was on its 28th mission.  
     

        
</post>

<date>30,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>29,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What was your most memorable moment from the last week? The war 2. What one person touched your life this week? Steferoni of course 3. How have you helped someone this week? Yes 4. What one thing do you need to get done by this time next week? My People to People essay 5. What one thing will you do over the next seven days to make your world a better place? try not to litter   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>23,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I got the new Linkin Park cd today! It kicks soooo much ass! If you haven't gotten it, get it! :-D   
     

        
</post>

<date>23,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I have my own domain name! Yea! lol. It is http://www.benssocalledlife.tk :-)
     

        
</post>

<date>21,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. If you had the chance to meet someone you've never met, from the past or present, who would it be? My grandpa 2. If you had to live in a different century, past or future, which would it be? 18th 3. If you had to move anywhere else on Earth, where would it be? Canada 4. If you had to be a fictional character, who would it be? Achilles 5. If you had to live with having someone else's face as your own for the rest of your life, whose would it be? Hmm. Dhani, from A-Teens   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Do you like talking on the phone? Why or why not? Sometimes, yes. 2. Who is the last person you talked to on the phone? Quinn 3. About how many telephones do you have at home? 1 plus my cell 4. Have you encountered anyone who has really bad phone manners? What happened? Yes, I hung up on him. 5. Would you rather pick up the phone and call someone or write them an e-mail or a letter? Why or why not? Email is faster. but sometimes the phone is more important, and you can get your point across.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      You think you know me? Guess again.  Ben Dover would like to invite you to participate in a custom made quiz titled "You think you know me? Guess again.".   The quiz has been setup by Ben Dover, and can be found at this website:    urlLink http://bungkwifa.friendtest.com    To take this quiz, simply click the link above with your mouse.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What was the last song you heard? The finale from Les Miserables 2. What were the last two movies you saw? Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets and 10 Things I Hate About You 3. What were the last three things you purchased? renewed my domain name, Netflix membership, and Poweraide 4. What four things do you need to do this weekend? clean my baseball uniform, talk to Quinn, and talk to Cody 5. Who are the last five people you talked to? Stefani, Cody, Cory, Quinn, and my Mom   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>09,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Happy St. Patrick's Day!  
     

        
</post>

<date>07,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Here is my Uncle in Kuwait. Doesn't he look pissed?     Here he is holding his gun. Damn does he look goofy caring a gun.     Here is his tent. I don't know where he is. 
     

        
</post>

<date>04,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Here is my friend Thomas. Isn't he cute?    
     

        
</post>

<date>02,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Today we had our first game of the year in uniforms. It was actually a scrimage, but yea. It was against Calvary Chapel. We won! 10-2 or something like that. I'm gonna take pictures of me in my uniform soon. When I do, I'm gonna post them to the site. Check back later.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I bought new shoes yesterday. Shocking isn't it?   
     

        
</post>

<date>01,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Check this link out.  urlLink http://bgbg.blogspot.com/2003_02_23_bgbg_archive.html#90394531 .
     

        
</post>

<date>01,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      America Online did this poll with their members in the UK, German, and France. Are the results shocking? Hell no.   
     

        
</post>

<date>26,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What was the last TV show you watched? The Simpsons 2. What was the last thing you complained about? The heat 3. Who was the last person you complimented and what did you say? Thomas; Nice ass!  4. What was the last thing you threw away? My bottle of water from the AIDS walk 5. What was the last website (besides this one) that you visited?  urlLink WeLovetheIraqiInformationMinister.com    urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Who is your favorite celebrity? John Cleese 2. Who is your least favorite? J-Lo 3. Have you ever met or seen any celebrities in real life? Yes, Cal Ripkin, Jr. 4. Would you want to be famous? Why or why not? Yes and no. Yes for the money. No for the damn press! >:o 5. If you had to trade places with a celebrity for a day, who would you choose and why? Justin Berfield. He is hot, and I know he gets a ton all the time. hehe :-P   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
        obsessive compulsive
     

        
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Thug Bear
     

        
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
        Weed. Youre the baby of the drugs, and thats okay, because Im sure, I could do you all day.
     

        
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
        You are the Flame Converse
     

        
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
        You are AIR... You don't want to be tied down. You value your freedom too much. This can be a good thing, but don't cut yourself off from others for fear of being caged in.
     

        
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What was the first band you saw in concert? Ricky Martin 2. Who is your favorite artist/band now? Linkin Park 3. What's your favorite song? Crawling 4. If you could play any instrument, what would it be? Drums 5. If you could meet any musical icon (past or present), who would it be and why? I don't know, lol   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. How many houses/apartments have you lived in throughout your life? 5 2. Which was your favorite and why? Mesa, because I grew up there. 3. Do you find moving house more exciting or stressful? Why? Stressful because you have to leave your friends 4. What's more important, location or price? Location & price, lol 5. What features does your dream house have (pool, spa bath, big yard, etc.)? All.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Guess what? Ben's So Called Life has been around a year! Cool isn't it?  
     

        
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What brand of toothpaste do you use? Aquafresh 2. What brand of toilet paper do you prefer? Charmin 3. What brand(s) of shoes do you wear? Vans and Chucks 4. What brand of soda do you drink? Pepsi and all Pepsi products 5. What brand of gum do you chew? Any kind   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hey all. This is my new site. Do you like it? I know I do. Anywayz.......I went to the RHS Baseball Award's Banquet yesterday night. A ton of food. Very good! I got a plaque for being the manager. When I get my digital camera, I will post a picture of it. No school today! Yes! I love it when teachers have to go to school. So I have a 4 day weekend. :-P
     

        
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What drinking water do you prefer -- tap, bottle, purifier, etc.? Bottled 2. What are your favorite flavor of chips? Sour Cream & Onion 3. Of all the things you can cook, what dish do you like the most? Macoroni and Cheese 4. How do you have your eggs? Sunny side up 5. Who was the last person who cooked you a meal? How did it turn out? My dad. Good. TV dinners can't go wrong, lol :-P   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Would you consider yourself an organized person? Why or why not? No. I'm a packrat... 2. Do you keep some type of planner, organizer, calendar, etc. with you, and do you use it regularly? Yes, my school planner 3. Would you say that your desk is organized right now? Hell no 4. Do you alphabetize CDs, books, and DVDs, or does it not matter? It doesn't matter 5. What's the hardest thing you've ever had to organize? My room! :-|   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>


           
      There is no friday five this week. Check back next week.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      You may know I'm going to England. I leave tomorrow. If you would like   to email me, please email me at  LVSnowboardBoy@hotmail.com . I'm putting an Away Message on all my emails except my Hotmail account. I will talk with you when I get back on July 12.
     

        
</post>

<date>19,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
        i'm indie!    urlLink   How can I label you?     brought to you by Quizilla 
     

        
</post>

<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      My uncle is home. He called us last night. A big sigh of relief from me. I'm so excited. Now I can wear my patriotic swimming shorts.       I wouldn't wear them until he came back in protest to the war. Now he is home, so I can wear them. I'm thinking of taking them with me to England. Good idea? Bad idea? Dunno. We will see. As for the new site, it is in the works. I'm uploading pictures and editting the last few sections. I'm still learning how to use XML, so that is what is taking so long. But the site should be up today or tomorrow. I like the site as it is, but I feel like a new site design is in order, since I'm not gonna be able to update the site when I'm in England. I will try and post what I can when I'm over there, but I don't even know when I'm gonna get time to do that. Plus it would be at an Internet Cafe, and we all know that paying for the internet sucks. lol. 
     

        
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hey all. Just a heads up over the next week I will be working on a new site, along with a new Vacation Journal. Hopefully I can get it up before I leave. I leave in  week. I can't wait! I'm sooooo excited.  
     

        
</post>

<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What's one thing you've always wanted to do, but never have? Dive into a pool 2. When someone asks your opinion about a new haircut/outfit/etc, are you always honest? No 3. Have you ever found out something about a friend and then wished you hadn't? What happened? No 4. If you could live in any fictional world (from a book/movie/game/etc.) which would it be and why? Harry Potter. I would want the magical invisibility cloak! 5. What's one talent/skill you don't have but always wanted? The ability to turn someone gay, lol   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
         China  - Debatably the most ancient and longstanding cultures around, it is nowadays viewed as a heavily populated but impovershed nation.   Positives:  Big. Eclectic History. Communist-Run (Control). Worldwide Manufacturer.   Negatives:  Communist-Run (Bitterness). Technologically Outdated Dissent.   urlLink   Which Country of the World are You?    brought to you by Quizilla 
     

        
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I have recently been inspired by J Fro to write longer blogs. On his blog, he writes like three or four paragraphs. Now, I won't do that, but I understand that a sentence post isn't enough. I have been looking over my past posts, and the longest ones are the friday five. I want to change that, so here I go.  My life sucks right now. My  car  threw a rode, so I don't have a car. When the Land Rover went, my mom went out and bought a  urlLink VW Beetle . It is a nice car, but it is stick. I don't like stick. But this means that in July, August I get a new used car. lol. New used. I get to pick it, but it can't be THAT expensive. I'm thinking on from Thrifty because they have a 6 year, 60,000 miles warrenty, which is hard to beat with other Used Car dealerships. A good thing though, I am going to England in 10 days. I still haven't packed yet. lol. This trip is gonna be soooooooo exciting. I can't wait. When I'm at my homestay in England, I get to stay in a 17th century country mansion, and I get to swim in the indoor pool, and I also get to learn how to play cricket. The lady I'm staying with son is home from "University" and he will teach me how to play. I'm so excited, I can't wait!
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I changed the archives to Weekly. The daily thing was taking up WAY to much space. 
     

        
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Like my new flash opener?   I do! I also changed the archives from Monthly to Daily. A lot arn't there?
     

        
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. How many times have you truly been in love? Never 2. What was/is so great about the person you love(d) the most? See #1 3. What qualities should a significant other have? Smart, funny, I like to spend time with him.  4. Have you ever broken someone's heart? I don't believe so...Have I? 5. If there was one thing you could teach people about love, what would it be? Don't say you love someone when you don't.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Come see my friends in our Last Day Of School. I have two versions.   urlLink Broadband  - For those who have Cable, or DSL (good version)  urlLink Dial Up  - For those who still have 56K modem (shitty version)    Note: To view the movies, you need  urlLink    
     

        
</post>

<date>04,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      School is FINALLY over! Yea!   I'm soooooo happy. Now my parents can't tell me to go to bed. lol. Anywayz. Yea, I'm excited. But yea.
     

        
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What do you most want to be remembered for? My personality 2. What quotation best fits your outlook on life? Don't let life get you down 3. What single achievement are you most proud of in the past year? Coming out to my parents 4. What about the past ten years? Getting into Rancho Academy 5. If you were asked to give a child a single piece of advice to guide them through life, what would you say? Don't let anything scare you.   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I finally got a digital camera. Took me what? A year? lol. Well, last night I took some pictures and I took some more this afternoon. They are in the pictures section. I like the little animated gif feature. hehehe.
     

        
</post>

<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1937-45: Gesellschaft zur Vorbereitung des Deutschen Volkswagens is founded to build the car designed by Ferdinand Porsche. WWII interrupts production as the factory instead produces for the Nazi military  1945-49: VW is transferred to the British Military Government after WWII, Beetle mass production begins in earnest under Major Ivan Hirst  1949-1970: VW is transferred to the German government, VW targets the Americas  1970-1990: The Passat and the Golf are launched, production of the Beetle is shifted to Mexico. The car enjoys a second lease of life in Latin America.  1990-2003: The New Beetle is launched, the Beetle prepares for retirement 
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      By Jorn Madslien  BBC News Online business reporter      The distinctive VW Beetle    The last old-style Volkswagen Beetle is to roll off the production line on Tuesday, 64 years after it was first produced. But the car is refusing to depart in silence.    As the movie star "Herbie" retires, it has become obvious that its heritage will remain vibrant.   The Beetle has achieved an unbelievable cult status across the world, not least because its creation marked the launch of what has since become the largest car company in Europe.   "It was the first product they ever made," said Sanford C. Bernstein's European car analyst, Stephen Cheetham.   "It was the only car Volkswagen made for ages."    Reliance    In fact, although VW made a range of larger vehicles during the 1950s and 1960s, the Beetle was only replaced in the early 1970s.    And not before time.   "Like all companies that discover a money-making machine, they were loath to let the Beetle go," said Jay Nagley, a consultant at Spyder Automotive.   The Beetle was hugely popular in Germany during the 1950s. And when its popularity at home began to fade during the 1960s, it was taken on by the Flower Power generation in the United States.   But by the end of the decade, VW's reliance on the Beetle was bearing heavily on the car maker, Mr Nagley explained.    Golf    VW desperately needed another "people's car", a car for the masses.   And in 1974 it found one, when the Italian designer Giorgetto Giugiaro came to the rescue with the somewhat boxy Golf.   Mr Giugiaro's company Ital Design sold the design to VW, and the golf has been Volkswagen's flagship model ever since, Mr Cheetham said.   "Until a few years ago, VW was effectively the Golf Motor Company," said Mr Nagley.    Tough competition    The Golf has defined the market for mass-produced hatchback cars and has firmly established itself as the leader of the pack in this segment.   Not a bad move, given that this is, in the words of Mr Cheetham, "typically the most profitable segment for car makers".   Recently, Ford's Focus and Opel's or Vauxhall's Astra have seriously challenged the Golf's hegemony. But the German is about to hit back with its fifth generation Golf, due to go on sale next year.   Traditionally, the Golf has managed to stay ahead due to its "unique position as an upmarket massmarket car", said Mr Nagley.    Diversified    But the Golf is no longer everything to VW Group.   In recent years, VW's dependence on one model has been sharply reduced.   As a consequence, new problems have emerged.   "VW as a group now has too many models, and too many overlapping models at that," insisted Mr Nagley, pointing out that VW owns Audi, Skoda and Seat in addition to Volkswagen.   And it owns the somewhat more luxurious brands Bentley, Bugatti and Lamborghini.   Clearly, Volkswagen Group has grown well beyond its origins as the maker of Adolf Hitler's "people's car".   But in the process, the car maker seems to have lost its way, many observers argue.   Even its New Beetle is pooh-poohed by analysts.   "The New Beetle is, I would argue, an awful thing," said Mr Cheetham.   VW's finances have suffered too; on Friday the group reported that its profits have fallen sharply during spring.   VW's operating profits fell to 616m euros ($709m;�436m) during the April to June quarter from 1.4bn euros ($1.6bn; �991m) a year earlier. Pre-tax profits fell 46% to 679m euros.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      A local sports reporter on Channel 3 (NBC) was reporting on Lance Armstrong at the Tour de France, but referred to the Tour de France the Tour de Freedom. This, getting my Political juices flowing, sent off an email. Here it is.  // From: 'Benjamin Tyra' [benjamin@benlogo.com] Sent: Saturday, July 26, 2003 5:51 PM To: 'Rick Strasser' [rstrasser@kvbc.com] Subject: Tour de France, not Freedom  Mr. Strasser,             I have a problem with you calling the Tour de France, the Tour de Freedom. I understand you may not like the French for not supporting the President with the conflict in Iraq, but referring to a bicycling race that has been going on for over 50 years, and is the most popular bicycling race in the world as the Tour de Freedom is unacceptable. You are a news reporter, and you are supposed to be non-biased in your reporting. Yes, you are entitled to your own opinion, but when you are reporting the sports, as you do, you should not voice your political opinion. The French have not done anything wrong to the United States. They only disagreed with us about Iraq, which they are entitled to do. In fact, if it wasn�t for the French, we would have lost the Revolutionary War and not have gotten where we are today in world affairs. This makes it more unacceptable to change the name of a sporting event with as much tradition as the Tour de France.   Thank you for your time,  Benjamin Tyra 16 Years old Rancho Aviation Academy Junior //  He then replyed back with this email:  // From: STRASSER, RICK [RSTRASSER@kvbc.com] Sent: Saturday, July 26, 2003 6:02 PM To: 'Benjamin Tyra' [benjamin@benlogo.com] Subject: RE: Tour de France, not Freedom  Importance: Low  Nicely stated Benjamin.  I don't feel like you calling my work "unacceptable" is acceptable, however.   Thanks for watching,   Rick //  What do you think? Good? Bad?  urlLink Let me know .
     

        
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Check out my new movie!   urlLink http://tinyurl.com/hmsh 
     

        
</post>

<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
            You Should Do Joseph Smith!  Like a Mormon, you are sexually repressed.  You want nothing more than to find a nice husband and start exploring your sexuality in missionary position.  Joseph Smith is your ideal sexual partner because of his voracious appetite for sex and years of experience.   You'll come to love the idea of pleasing a man in any way shape or form.  A threesome is one of those secret fantasies you�ll be able to pursue - maybe even with Joe and your sisters!       urlLink  What Religious Guru Should You Do?  
     

        
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Hey all! I'm back from England. Wow! What a trip! I'm working on getting pictures ready to be posted. More info to follow...
     

        
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Are you going to school this year? Yes, dur 2. If yes, where are you going (high school, college, etc.)? If no, when did you graduate? Rancho Aviation Academy, but you knew that, right? 3. What are/were your favorite school subjects? Aviation, Science, and History 4. What are/were your least favorite school subjects? English and Math 5. Have you ever had a favorite teacher? Why was he/she a favorite? Mr. Rahmani. He was my 8th grade science teacher. Did you ever have one of those teachers that you absolutly loved and you liked going to his or her class? That is what Mr. Rahmani's class was. Mr. Rahmani, you inspired me! :-P   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Today was my first day of school. It was very....interesting. My schedule is as follows:  1)     Office Aide 2)     French II Honors 3)     Aerospace I (Ground School) 4)     American Literature 5)     US History Honors 6)     Algebra II Honors 7)     Physics I  What a load eh? I know, I can't believe it. I have 3 honors classes. I only have one class that isn't that hard, and it is Office Aide, and my parents want to take that away from me, but it is early bird, and not very many teachers teach early bird so.........I dunno. But yea. I'm tired as hell. I start my early bird class tomorrow. I hope all goes well, being that I am in the Deans Office. :-| What am I to expect from the Deans Office? Am I to face the infamous Rancho gang members? Hell no. It is early bird Student Aide. What is the worse that happens? Well, anywayz. I'm tired as hell and the Broncos are loosing, so I'm gonna go. Hopefully the Broncos will get lucky and win. 
     

        
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. When was the last time you laughed? Yesterday night with Jamison 2. Who was the last person you had an argument with? Cassie 3. Who was the last person you emailed? My dad 4. When was the last time you bathed? Yesterday at about 1:15pm 5. What was the last thing you ate? Pickles   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Yesterday evening, my parental units, Jamison, and myself went golfing at Calaway's Devine Nine. It was cool. Damn! Jamison is a good player, except when it comes to putting! So we are gonna go and hit balls on the range and I'm gonna teach him to putt and he is gonna teach me how to hit irons. I'm not very good at irons, but DAMN, I'm good at putting. I got a 51, which is kinda bad for a Par 3 course, but atleast I was consistant. Anywayz. Jamison hasen't posted anything yet, but he might. I wonder how he felt with my parents drinking beer while golfing. I dunno if he felt okay with them doing it. If you wern't Jamison, I apologize, but that is how they are. They are really cool though! :-P I love em! Well, enough from me. I know it isn't a page like my last long one was, but oh well. Close enough, right?
     

        
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Okay.....this is just creepy. I was watching Street Smarts, which is a cool show, and they asked his chick "What fruit does dried banana chips come from?" And she answered "Peaches." How dumb do you have to be? But yea. Anywayz. Another person on the show that they asked questions to was called Naked. And he has a website. It is creepy. His name is the  urlLink Naked Cowboy . Don't worry, he isn't naked. He is just in briefs. It is still creepy. But yea.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      **Yea, I know, what love life! Ha!**    Everyone remembers the 'faked-orgasm-in-a-deli' sequence from your kind of movie When Harry Met Sally. It seems that you're falling for a buddy or have already fallen for them. Uh-oh. You're probably caught between the possibility of having a great relationship and wrecking the one you have now. You know what they say, it's better to regret something you did than something you didn't do.    urlLink   What Romance Movie Best Represents Your Love Life?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
     

        
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I'm diggin' the new dark theme layout. What do you think? Wanna know what I realized? My birthday is in 27 days! Damn. In 27 days I will be 17 years old, with two years of high school to go. Shit. How time flies. I remember when I entered middle school, and how I was scared at the fact that I would have to go to 6 classes and have 6 DIFFERENT teachers. I'm glad I got over it though!  My life, as you can tell by my new layout, has turned dark and sinister. Why? I cannot tell, because I don't know. And Meghan, don't try cheering me up. This is just my overall feeling, and I like the picture. Sad, but in a way, happy. Know what I mean? Probably not, most people don't get what I am saying, but oh well. Life sucks and then you die, or at least that is what Nicole says. I dunno if this is true. Sure my life sucks now, but it could be worse. I'm the leader of a group of teenagers helping build a house with Habitat for Humanity called the Teensters. If you don't know, Habitat for Humanity builds homes for low income families. Wanna know something sad? Teachers qualify to live in a Habitat house. How goddamn sad is that? Someone who I learn from makes less than $50,000. Damn. What has this world come too?  School starts in 7 days. Scary to think that I will be starting my 3rd year at Rancho. I wonder how this year will be different. How I will change Rancho in my own special way. How I will pass Mr. Hale's Ground School. How I will grow the balls to talk to Josef about how I feel. How this year's football team is gonna be different from last years. How Stefani and I will continue to be friends. But I can't dwell on things forever. I'm reading a book, entitled " The Art of Happiness, a Handbook for Living ." It is by the Dali Lama. I was just gonna read it and tell my mom, yea I read it, to make her happy, but as I continued reading, I realized that it was good. Shocking! I read! lol.   Anywayz.......I have been having dreams lately. About Josef. What do they mean? I'm desperate. lol. But yea. Seriously, could Josef be gay? And if he is gay, how do I know if he likes me? Do I just go up and ask him? These are the questions that I don't have the answers for.  I was talking with Meghan tonight, and I said...If I had the magical power to turn one person gay, and make him call in love with me for the rest of my life and we live happily ever after, it would have to be   JOSEF  . If you had this power, to turn someone you liked in love with you, who would you pick?  God I'm hungry for a smoothie from Smoothie King. Damnit Dez, you got me addicted to Smoothie King! lol. If you want a GREAT smoothie, go to the Smoothie King at the corner of Lake Mead and Rampart and look for the short girl whose name is Dez. She is great. She is dating Jamison. He is the one in the friends section with the big pink sign, 'Over here big boy.' He wants me to take it off. I will.....when I get a new one. Dez, Jamison, Jamie, and myself went bowling and minigolfing, so I will upload pictures when Jamie gets off her ASS AND SENDS THEM TO ME!  It is hard to believe, but I graduate high school in 2 years. I will be out on my own in 2 years! Holy crap! =-0 What am I gonna do? Where am I gonna go to college? What do I wanna major in? Do I wanna get my bachelors or masters? Ugh. Decisions, decisions. Oh well. It is 12:30 and this is by far my longest post, so I'm gonna go. Later y'all.  **UPDATED 10:51 AM** It has come to my attention that Smoothie King has some "issues." I won't post them here, because it could get some people into trouble. Needless to say, the smoothies are good, whether or not you agree with the business practice.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      God I am bored........................................................and tired. I think I'm gonna go to sleep early today.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I finally got my new shoes! Yea!   
     

        
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. What's the last place you traveled to, outside your own home state/country? Ireland, Wales, Scotland, and England 2. What's the most bizarre/unusual thing that's ever happened to you while traveling? I had pigeons eat bird seed out of my hair (London) 3. If you could take off to anywhere, money and time being no object, where would you go? Cruise through the Bahamas 4. Do you prefer traveling by plane, train or car? Plane 5. What's the next place on your list to visit? San Diego   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Did you know....  *47% of the people who have been to Ben's So Called Life have done something with the same sex. *50% of the people who have been to BSCL are straight, and 50% are gay. *89% of the people have had sex, and 11% wonder if their hands count. *57% of the people like green, 29% like red, and 14% like purple *67% of the people like the new website and 33% of the people don't like it.  I have also added a new poll. Will Arnold Schwarzenegger be elected governor of California? Vote. The other polls have now been archived.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I am thinking these two for school. What do you think?    Green Chucks        Geoff Rowley XLT    
     

        
</post>

<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Ben [11:39 PM]:  I'm gonna mud wrestle you for Jamison, ok?  Dez [11:39 PM]:  NO! HE'S MINE! Ben [11:39 PM]:  first person to pin for 3 seconds wins  Dez [11:39 PM]:  lol Dez [11:40 PM]:  ok, bitch, you're on! Ben [11:40 PM]:  LOL   Should I go for it?
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>


           
      By Jonathan Kent  BBC correspondent in Kuala Lumpur   The Malaysian cabinet has promised to change the country's laws to discourage men from divorcing their wives by means of electronic messages.     An Islamic court in the country declared last week that a Muslim man had legally ended his marriage by sending his wife a mobile telephone text message.   That ruling had been endorsed by the prime minister's religious affairs adviser.   Now, however, the government says it will consider increasing the fines and jail sentences for men who pronounce the talak - or declaration of divorce - by electronic means, such as e-mail, fax or text message.   Men who declare divorce outside a court already face up to three years in jail.    Condemnation    Malaysians love high technology - just over half the population own mobile phones.   But just over half of Malaysians are also Muslims and bound by Islamic sharia law, rooted in scriptures 1,400 years old.   Even the country's Prime Minister, Doctor Mahathir Mohamad, accepts that this can occasionally cause problems.   Last week, a sharia court declared that a text message sent by a man to his wife reading "if you don't leave your parents house, you'll be divorced", had legal force.   While it may be correct from other angles, it is not the way to get a divorce, Doctor Mahathir told reporters.   Last week's court ruling was condemned by women's groups and Malaysia's minister for women, who accused a small minority of Muslim men of damaging the reputation of Islam.   Sharia law requires a man to tell his wife three times that he divorces her. At least one declaration must be before a religious official.   Women wishing to end their marriages are subject to a far more arduous procedure under Islamic law.    Story from BBC NEWS:  urlLink http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/pr/fr/-/2/hi/asia-pacific/3112151.stm   Published: 2003/07/31 04:02:39 GMT  � BBC MMIII
     

        
</post>

<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Who is your favorite singer/musician? Why? Dashboard Confessionals. Why? I don't know honestly, I guess it is because I like their music. Emo music is soo cool, lol.  2. What one singer/musician can you not stand? Why? Eminem. Why? Because he is a white man trying to live in a black man's world. I'm not racist, but come on. You arn't black, act your god damn color! 3. If your favorite singer wasn't in the music business, do you think you would still like him/her as a person? I dunno. Probably not. 4. Have you been to any concerts? If yes, who put on the best show? Yes, I would have to say Ray Charles, just because he is like a music legond. 5. What are your thoughts on downloading free music online vs. purchasing albums? Do you feel the RIAA is right in its pursuit to stop people from dowloading free music? I think if you download a song or two from a cd, to preview the cd is fine. I mean, if I have never heard of an artist before, am I gonna go out and pay $20 - $40 for a new cd? Hell no. I'm gonna download the music first to preview the cd. I think the RIAA can go to hell. If it wasn't for KaZaA and other P2P Networks, some little known artists wouldn't have become well known, like Jason Mraz. Look at him now. How did he get his start? KaZaA. So, RIAA, suck my left boob.   
     

        
</post>

<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
       Ben:  dez and i made comments about you on my website   Jamison:  i know, i saw and i added my own  Jamison:  listen i dont want to make this  a big thing man, can't we just have different views on this? or does this mean a lot to you  Ben:  yes we can have different views, but when you tell me i'm wrong is fucked up. no one can be wrong, unless it is a factual statement.   Jamison:  no, when i told you you were wrong, was you were wrong in wanting me to agree with you  Jamison:  you cant tell me that i should agree with you just because  Ben:  No, you said I was wrong because I didn't like girls, which, you think I should.   Jamison:  oh, im sorry i did say that  Ben:  I'm not saying that, but you said I was wrong for being gay   Jamison:  listen i wasnt entirely serious with that statement,.. i dont think you are wrong about not liking girls  Ben:  Well, it hurt   Jamison:  im sorry that i wasnt more careful with what i said  Jamison:  i was wrong, can you forgive me  Ben:  I don't care if you were joking around. I take my sexuality very serously. I get enough shit at school from my "Republican aviation teachers", I don't need it from so called friends   Ben:  Yes, I forgive you, but I might not if it happens again   Jamison:  ill be more careful on the subject, i promise, and i can understand how it is to have different views when the majority has the rule  Ben:  Thanks 
     

        
</post>

<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      My Ken is gone. He has be grounded for a month. Why you ask? For DITCHING! I'm so angry with him now. I told him not to ditch, but did he listen to me? HELL NO! Oh well. I miss my Kenneth. I want him back.                                            time left until my Ken can talk to me again.
     

        
</post>

<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Happy Birthday to me! Oh yea! 17. lol. Yea.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      My mom got my a webcam for my birthday! Yea! Go me!
     

        
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. Is the name you have now the same name that's on your birth certificate? If not, what's changed? Yes, Benjamin Edward Tyra 2. If you could change your name (first, middle and/or last), what would it be? Ben Jessie Tyra 3. Why were you named what you were? (Is there a story behind it? Who specifically was responsible for naming you?) Named after no body. lol. My grandpas, both of their middle names were Edward. 4. Are there any names you really hate or love? What are they and why? Not really, most names are normal, but some are silly, like Shaniqwa 5. Is the analysis of your name at kabalarians.com / triggur.org /  astroexpert accurate? How or how isn't it? Well, here are the analysis' (in order as listed in the question):  Kabalarians.com: The name of Benjamin creates a quick, analytical, and clever mind; you are creative, versatile, original, and independent. You have large ambitions, and it is difficult for you to be tolerant and understanding of those who desire less in life or who are more slow and methodical by nature. Patience is not your forte. You do, however, have leadership ability and would never be happy in a subservient position. You are ambitious and aggressive by nature. You would be happiest in positions where you are free to express individually and creatively and where opportunities are not restricted; you desire freedom, and do not tolerate being possessed by others. You appreciate change and travel, and the opportunity to meet and mix with others, and to influence them with your creative ideas. You are very self-confident and feel you can accomplish anything you set out to do, and you can, although, this name does not allow proper completion of undertakings, and forced changes cause financial losses and bitter experiences. This name also creates caustic expression and moods which prevent harmony and happiness in close association.  Triggur.org: BENJAMIN    From the Greek root meaning "Licker of Toads"    Expression Benjamin is blunt and insensitive.  Personality Benjamin is a shivering ball of rage waiting to explode.  Natural Benjamin likes animals-- perhaps too much.  Emotional Benjamin uses and abuses friendships.  Character Benjamin tends to get others down.  Physical Benjamin has breath that could drop buffalo.  Mental Benjamin isn't rowing with both oars.  Motivation Benjamin has an oedipal complex.  AstroExpert.com: Unable to access website.  The Triguur one is NOT right. lol. Anywayz. Yea.      Quinn - You will not be forgotten - 1983-2003  
     

        
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I'm deeply sadden by the news that Quinn, my first boyfriend, and extremely close friend has committed suicide. It was sometime this morning. I got the email from Derek at 1:40 this morning saying that he had gotten a call from a detective in Pahrump, NV. The detective had said that Quinn had died from self inflicted gunshot wound. When I heard the news I was devastated. I still am. I have lost someone that was extremely close to me, that I loved. Quinn is gone now, I can't bring that back, but he will always live in my memory.       Quinn Dyer - 1983 - 2003    But on a happier note......I got my permit! Yea! Go me!
     

        
</post>

<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      My fun Sunday started off with me going to Road Runner's Bar & Grill to watch the Broncos - Bengals. The Broncos won, of course. Anywayz. Then I came home and sat around for a little bit, but then we decided to wash Lucky's ass. That was, how should I say it? Interesting? After that, I walked Lucky around for a little bit to dry him off. Then my mom let me practice my parralel parking. That was awsome!  I have pictures!     Driving 1   Driving 2   Driving 3   I had such a great weekend!
     

        
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      It's all about the love people! Two great things happened tonight.  One....Rancho beat Cheyenne in Football. Yes, that is big because Rancho's football team hasen't been very good, but we are now 2-0! Oh yea! We beat Cheyenne in overtime, 18-12 at Cheyenne. I went to the game, and I am gonna try and make it to every game. I'm buying a Rancho Football T-shirt on Monday.   and two...Ken told me he loved me! Isn't it great? I feel loved. I am loved. Could like getting any better? hehe. I love Ken. He loves me. hehe. :-P Okay, I'm gonna go before I get all giddy. Nite all!  PS - I'M LOVED! hehehe
     

        
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      This is the coolest song. It is by  urlLink Josh Groban .      Josh Groban    This is dedicated to the sexiest man alive, Ken. I love you.   I close my eyes And there in the shadows I see your light You come to me out of my dreams across... the night You take my hand, though you maybe so many stars away I know that our spirits& souls are one We've circled the moon and we've touched the sun So here... we'll stay  For always, forever Beyond here and unto eternity For always, forever For us there's no time and no space No burial our love won't erase Where ever you go I still know in my heart You will be with me  From this day on I'm certain that I'll never be alone I know what my heart must've always known That love has a power that's all its own  And for always, forever Now we can fly And for always, and always We will go on beyond goodbye.  For Always, forever Beyond here and unto eternity For always and ever You'll be a part of me And for always, forever A thousand tomorrows may cross the sky And for always, and always We'll go on beyond goodbye  
     

        
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I find this weeks questions funny, being that I hardly ever clean, but when I do, I tend to get into it, lol.  1. What housekeeping chore(s) do you hate doing the most? All of them, lol 2. Are there any that you like or don't mind doing? Cleaning my room is always fun. I always seem to find something I was looking for like a week before and then I found it, and it is like a four year old with a ballon, you are the happiest person alive! 3. Do you have a routine throughout the week or just clean as it's needed? Just clean as it is needed 4. Do you have any odd cleaning/housekeeping quirks or rules? I always have to be listening to music. 5. What was the last thing you cleaned? The computer screen   
     

        
</post>

<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser ...and now my post... Nine Monsters Rated: Which is Scariest? by Tamim Ansary Every year the community center down the block from my house sets up a "haunted house" at Halloween. For a couple bucks, you can stick your hand into a bucket of warm fettuccini and pretend they're entrails. If you try you might even feel a twitch of fear. Why some people want to feel frightened, I don't know, but we do. Lots of us do.  It isn't real-life menace we crave, of course; it's fictional horror. Alas, in my opinion, our scariest creatures have been overexposed. When I see "ghost" I think Ghostbusters. Goblins? Casper's uncles. Witches? Sabrina. Vampires? Buffy the Vampire Slayer.  The chill is gone.  So what's a member of Fright Club to do? I've been thinking that we might need to look beyond the tired, traditional, mainstream scary creatures to less familiar monsters. I looked into it, and I found a number of worthwhile candidates from cultures around the globe. How many of these monsters do you know?   Creature  |  Culture Hai-uru  |  African Raktabija  |  Indian Chindis  |  Navajo Golem  |  Jewish Chupacabra  |  Puerto Rican, Mexican Jinn  |  Islamic Banshees  |  Irish Ghouls  |  Arabic Windigo  |  Cree and Ojibwa   I've rated each creature from 1 to 10 on my own private scare-o-meter, on which 10 means total terror. See what you think.   Hai-uru  African folklore is rife with legends of a frightening fellow who hunts human prey. He'll kill you if he can, but he'll give you magic powers if you beat him. He's Hai-uru to the Khoikhoi of southern and western Africa, Tikdoshe to the Zulu of southern Africa, and Adroa in Democratic Republic of the Congo (formerly Zaire).  Details differ, but all these creatures share one feature: They have only half a body--one eye, one arm, one leg, etc. What's up with that? I think this thing may be aimed at some nerve that I don't have.  Scare-o-meter rating: 3   Raktabija  Topping the terror charts of Indian mythology is Raktabija, the demon's demon. The gods couldn't kill him because every drop of his blood that touched the ground turned into a new demon.   Then the god Shiva's sweet wife Parvati went into action. She turned into Kali, goddess of death and destruction. She stuck out her tongue till it covered the world and then chopped off Rakbatija's head: all the spilled blood fell on her tongue and she drank it down.    If you've seen a typical sculpture of Kali, you've seen Raktabija. He's the severed head she's holding at arm's length. What a monster! On the other hand, he's dead--a definite detriment to his power.  Scare-o-meter rating: 3 (All we have to worry about now is Kali.)   Chindis  According to Navajo beliefs, when people die, the evil in them lingers on. These spirits, known as chindis, account for the Navajos' particular dread of corpses. When someone dies among the Navajo, tradition calls for the house to be burned to the ground and the person's name never to be spoken again.  Here's the thing about chindis: If you do evil, a chindi can attach itself to you and no one can detach it except the person you have wronged. So yes, be afraid of chindis if you're evil--be very afraid. If you're good, relax.  Me, I'm not worried. Whistle whistle.  Scare-o-meter rating: 6   Golem  Frankenstein's monster was scary till he got a gig as Fred Munster and later moved to Nick at Night.  The underlying story, however, tapped our modern anxiety about technology: know-it-all builds artificial servant out of lifeless matter but loses control of it. That idea still scares us, especially when we think about how nanotechnology is about to meet genetic engineering.... Yet the archetypal story isn't new at all.  The granddaddy of the type might be the Jewish legend of the golem. Sometime around 1500, it seems, a certain Rabbi Löw of Prague decided to build a tireless servant. He shaped a heap of clay into a crude humanoid, muttered a spell and--say hello to the golem, a powerful pile of mindless matter that follows its master's orders relentlessly.  Needless to say, it didn't work out as hoped.  Scare-o-meter rating: 4   Chupacabra  We think of vampires as suave fellows in black tuxedos and silk capes. But that's only our common Transylvanian vampire, Dracula, invented by 19th-century novelist Bram Stoker. (Dracula, incidentally, has some historical basis in a 15th-century count known as Vlad the Impaler. His name says it all.)  But the vampire myth is both older and younger than Vlad. The Chinese were telling stories about a vampire called giang shi as early as 600 BC. And in Puerto Rico, Chile, and Mexico, there have been recent stories of a new vampire called the chupacabra.  The chupacabra kills goats and cattle by sucking the blood out of them. Nothing else is known about it--that's what makes it scary. You can imagine anything. So ... for all I know the chupacabra might be a two-legged tree-stump with a beak and a cape. Come to think of it, the scare-o-meter reading just dropped.  Final score: 1 1/2 (10 if you're a goat)   Jinn  In Afghanistan, where I grew up, we didn't have witches or ghosts. The fearsome spooks of my own childhood were jinn.  These creatures are mentioned in the Qur'an, the scriptures of Islam; if you're a good Muslim, you have to believe in them. The Qur'an says jinn are made of smokeless fire, so you can't see them, but they're everywhere, everywhere, especially in old, abandoned buildings ... rural cemeteries ... dank basements--places like that.  When the back of your neck prickles for no reason, jinn are near. Sometimes they get inside you. To me, the Blair Witch Project was about jinn.  Scare-o-meter rating: 8   Banshees  There's only one thing most of us know about banshees: They scream. But what are they?  I'll tell you. Banshees ("women of the hills" in Gaelic) come out of Irish folklore. They're women who died in childbirth and are doomed to spend the remaining years of their allotted span near deserted streams, washing blood from the grave garments of those who are about to die.  The banshee's scream is more of a wail. If you hear it, someone in your family is about to die.  Sad-scary.  Scare-o-meter rating: 7   Ghouls  We come now to ghouls, creatures out of ancient Islamic folklore. The word ghoul comes from an Arabic term meaning "the grabber"--as in a hand bursting out of the earth and grabbing your ankle!  Seems that in ancient days, Arabian nomads would upon occasion run across a plundered grave. Sometimes the corpse was missing. Sometimes, they'd find half-eaten remains nearby. How to make sense of this?  Two possibilities spring to mind. One: wild dogs. Two--equally plausible: some corpses come back to life after burial and feed on their fellow dead. Islamic folklore did not choose "wild dogs."  Scare-o-meter rating: 8 (The grossness factor may be distorting this reading.)   Windigo  The windigo is a Native American nightmare, invented in the subarctic by the Cree and Ojibwa peoples.  Let's set the scene: The subarctic is about 5 million sq km (2 million sq mi) of forest and tundra inhabited by fewer than 60,000 people. We're talking lonely. Winters last forever up there, and winter nights are long, cold, and dark.  In times past, the people who lived in this region spent winters holed up in their shelters, rationing out their dwindling food supplies, and telling tales. The most dreadful of these stories featured the windigo, a friendless creature that lives alone in the forest. It's 6 to 9 m (20 to 30 ft) tall and has a lipless mouth and jagged teeth. Its footprints in the snow are full of blood and you can hear its hissing breath for miles.  It eats people. And that's the good news.  The bad news is, if a windigo catches you alone in the forest, it can possess you. Then you turn into a windigo yourself--a mindless cannibal.  I think I see the underlying fear that glimmers through this story. Survival in the subarctic was a desperate struggle. Often, food ran out before winter did. Sometimes, well.... Cannibalism happens.  There you have the real horror of the windigo legend. Ask not what some monster might do to you; ask what you might do to someone should you become a monster.  Scare-o-meter rating: 11
     

        
</post>

<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Voulez Vous by The A-Teens ...and now my post... Oh yea! On Tuesday night, at the North Las Vegas, I met the one, the only, HOWARD DEAN! He is just like he is at HowardDean.tv. He was right to the point and said that as President he wouldn't send Nuclear Waste to Nevada if the science wasn't right. Oh yea! Anywho. Sorry, I'm just a little happy at the fact that I could have just met the future President of the United States and shook his hand!
     

        
</post>

<date>27,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser! ...and now my post...    Donald Rumsfeld     It's been a rough couple of weeks for the Rumster. First George W. Bush went behind his back and put Condoleezza Rice in charge of rebuilding Iraq (poor Don didn't see THAT one coming!), and then last week a morose Rumsfeld memo ended up in the hands of the press, causing the administration to look rather foolish. And when your boss is sneaking around divvying up your work to your colleagues, the last thing you want to do is make him look foolish. Well... more foolish. In the memo, Rumsfeld questioned whether the US is winning the war on terrorism, writing, "Is our current situation such that 'the harder we work, the behinder we get?'" (yes, he used the word 'behinder') and suggested that winning the war would be a "long, hard slog." Fortunately for Don, it's not like Our Great Leader is, oh, I dunno, in the middle of a PR campaign to convince Americans how great everything is going in Iraq or something. And it's not like Bush would have had the nuts to stand up in front of the troops and say stuff like, "We're rolling back the terrorist threat, not on the fringes of its influence but at the heart of its power," if his defense secretary had completely the opposite opinion, surely? But anyway, back to the memo. Rumsfeld appeared at a news briefing soon after the leak, armed with a dictionary definition of the word "slog" which he told reporters meant, "to hit or strike hard, to drive with blows, to assail violently." Right... so just to clear that up, he didn't mean, "To walk or progress with a slow heavy pace; plod." It just, um, came across that way.   George W. Bush      What's worse than a bumbling idiot? Why, a bumbling idiot who surrounds himself with bumbling idiot advisors, of course. Our Great Leader must have been privately seething after Rumsfeld's memo was leaked, but not merely because it completely undermined his "Everything's Just Fine In Iraq" PR campaign. Wasn't it only a few weeks ago that Dubya was coming over all macho about cracking down on leaks? Well yes, it was: "There's leaks in the executive branch, there's leaks in the legislative branch, there's just too many leaks. And if there is a leak out of my administration, I want to know who it is," said Bush at the end of September. Tough words - and now here's his chance to back them up! See, the Rumsfeld memo was only sent to four people - General Richard Myers, General Peter Pace, Paul Wolfowitz and Douglas Feith. So in theory, it shouldn't be too hard to figure out where the leak came from. In fact, you might say that the odds are really quite good! Unless of course Our Great Leader has completely forgotten the bold pronouncements he made less than four weeks ago, which, let's face it, would not exactly be unusual.    George W. Bush (again) But despite the occasional bump in the road, Bush's "Everything's Just Fine In Iraq" PR campaign is going ahead full steam. And one of the methods the administration is using to convince people that, indeed, everything is just fine in Iraq, is simply covering up the coffins of dead American soldiers. According to the Washington Post, the administration is "banning news coverage and photography of dead soldiers' homecomings on all military bases" - because hey, if you can't see it, it isn't happening, right?! Brilliant. Unfortunately Bush may need to revisit his "head in the sand" policy, because the very, very bad news is that on average, more coalition soldiers are now being killed per day than were being killed per day when George declared "mission accomplished" back on May 1, and attacks on coalition soldiers have increased markedly in recent weeks. But I guess it doesn't matter as long as we keep covering up their coffins when they arrive back in the US. Way to support the troops, George.   Fox News For some reason Fox News seems to be on a constant crusade to prove how stupid its viewers are. First they tried to sue Al Franken because they claimed that the front cover of his book could be confused for a Fox News product (hey, considering the word "lies" appears on it in big letters, maybe they had a point). But apparently this isn't the first time that Fox News honchos have demonstrated their complete inability to understand satire by threatening a frivolous lawsuit - they once hilariously threatened to sue another Rupert Murdoch-owned enterprise, "The Simpsons." "Simpsons" creator Matt Groening revealed this tidbit on NPR's "Fresh Air" program last week, telling interviewer Terry Gross that Fox News threatened to sue if an episode spoofing the news channel was aired. The episode featured, among other digs at Fox News, a ticker scrolling across the bottom of the screen displaying vehemently anti-Democratic party slogans. Groening called their bluff and went ahead with the show because he assumed that Rupert Murdoch wouldn't be stupid enough to sue himself, but apparently there is now a rule at Fox which says that "The Simpsons" isn't allowed to spoof Fox News anymore. Why? Because they don't want Fox News viewers to get confused. Now, we've known for a long time that Fox News viewers can't tell the difference between real life and a cartoon, but to hear Fox News themselves admit it is really quite fascinating.   Arnold Schwarzenegger So the heady days of California's bizarre recall election are over, and now it's time to get down to business. Unfortunately it looks like Governor Groping Austrian Beefcake is about to take a shot in the gut from the phased plasma rifle of reality. According to the L.A. Times, Schwarzenegger got "a grim briefing on California's budget Thursday, and emerged appearing sobered." That's right - suddenly Arnold has realized that now he's the governor, he actually has to run the state. Bummer. "The problem was created over the last five years," said Arnie, "and so you can't expect that - even though I've played very, very heroic characters in the movies, but you can't expect me to walk into his office and all of a sudden come out with the answers." What? But surely during the campaign, Arnold kept going on and on about how he was going to swoop in and fix California's problems in the blink of an eye. I mean, I know he didn't explain how he was going to do it, but I got the impression that the fact he played "very, very heroic characters in the movies" was going to be an integral part of his governing technique. Does this mean that we can no longer expect him to pump up Sacramento? What a letdown. I was looking forward to that.   Talking Presidents If you can't get enough of Ann Coulter - and I know you can't - then have I got a product for you! Talking Presidents, manufacturers of such presidential action figures as George W. Bush, Bill Clinton, and, um, George H.W. Bush, is breaking new ground with its Ann Coulter action figure. The figure comes complete with a series of pithy catchphrases apparently recorded by Coulter herself, such as, "Liberals can't just come out and say they want to take more of our money, kill babies, and discriminate on the basis of race," and, "Liberals hate America, they hate flag-wavers, they hate abortion opponents, they hate all religions except Islam, post 9/11. Even Islamic terrorists don't hate America like Liberals do. They don't have the energy. If they had that much energy, they'd have indoor plumbing by now." Hilarious stuff, huh? The figure itself looks remarkably like Coulter, right down to the plastic skin and bleached flyaway mane. And if you're a collector of tasteless pieces of crap, you'll also want to check out Talking Presidents' George W. Bush fine art print, a remarkable value at $11.99 plus S&H. Hang it on your front porch this Halloween and give the neighborhood children a real fright.   The Pentagon The Top Ten wouldn't be the Top Ten these days without a report on how the Department of Defense is screwing the troops. Here's the latest. The recent bombing of an American diplomatic convoy in the Gaza Strip left three security specialists dead, but the way the Pentagon has treated at least one of the relatives of the deceased is quite remarkable. Courtney Linde, whose husband John was killed in the attack, was diagnosed with bone cancer while going through Air Force Tech School, but the Air Force refused to give her any medical benefits to help pay for surgery and chemotherapy because they claimed it was a pre-existing condition. Funny that, because when Courtney signed up she passed her medical with flying colors. So what does this have to do with John Linde? Well, the reason he took the dangerous assignment in the Gaza Strip in the first place was because he and his wife were so desperate to cover the cost of their medical bills, they needed the extra money. Hats off to the Pentagon for yet another great example of how to support the troops.   Dennis Miller How times have changed. It seems like only yesterday that conservatives were deriding liberal celebrities for criticizing the war on Iraq, and telling them to shut up about politics. But the critics seem to have gone strangely silent on the issue of Arnold Schwarzenegger, a man who, by his own admission, "played very, very heroic characters in the movies," and is now governor of California. And now, suddenly, it seems that being a celebrity is in fact absolutely fine with conservatives - as long as they know which side their bread is buttered on, if you know what I mean. Take Dennis Miller for example, whose fabulous locks once awed the nation every Saturday night from the Weekend Update desk. But the career of the post-mulletectomy Miller has taken a turn for the worse - first being booted from Monday Night Football for being, well, crap, then appearing every other week on The Tonight Show to stick his tongue up George W. Bush's arse, and finally coming to rest as a decidedly non-hilarious political commentator on the Fox News network. So what's next for Miller? Well, the word on the street is that he may be considering a run for Senate in California, and some conservatives are - surprise - absolutely thrilled. Radio host Hugh Hewitt gushed, "A Miller candidacy guarantees the ability to get a message past gatekeepers like the Los Angeles Times. That's a huge plus." And National Republican Senatorial Committee spokesman Dan Allen was enthusiastic, citing the Schwarzenegger campaign which "energized" Republicans in California. To be fair, there are Republicans who think that Miller wouldn't be such a great candidate, but not because he's a celebrity - because they think he doesn't stand a chance in hell of winning. And anyway, it would be a "great loss to comedy," according to David Horowitz, who apparently hasn't noticed that the last time Miller said something funny was in 1987.   Eric Cantor Of all the conservatives who've gotten their panties in a bunch over CBS's forthcoming Ronald Reagan movie, Rep. Eric Cantor (R-VA) is surely sitting the most uncomfortably. During an appearance on Buchanan & Press last week, Cantor made not-so-veiled suggestions that CBS should have its license revoked if it went ahead with the movie. "I'm just saying I think as a representative of the people of the Commonwealth of Virginia and as a member of Congress we have a duty to make sure that licenses at the federal level are not abused...and abuse means using those licenses to advance a political agenda." said Cantor. Riiiiight. So CBS should have their license revoked for airing one movie, but "Fair and Balanced" Fox News should, don't tell me, be applauded for their evenhanded and unbiased approach to news reporting. Interesting that Saint Ronnie of Reagan is considered so untouchable that members of Congress will threaten to shut down TV stations for besmirching him. In fact, why not just go the whole hog? Perhaps Eric Cantor could simply a introduce a Constitutional amendment which says that any station caught broadcasting material unfavorable to the GOP will have their licenses revoked, their offices burned down, and their CEO's hung in the public square. That should put a stop to the evil liberal media once and for all.   Rush Limbaugh And finally, an update on Rush Limbaugh's pill-popping problem. It appears that the Ditto King's treatment is going spectacularly well, and the word on the street is that he will be back on the air as promised, fresh as a daisy and clean as a whistle. Remarkable how effective treatment can be for rehabilitating drug addicts back into society, isn't it? Such a shame that Republicans think drug treatment is an evil waste of taxpayer money. Of course, that doesn't apply to Rush - he can afford the very best. Real treatment. The kind of treatment which can only be afforded by drug addicts who have pulled themselves up by the bootstraps. But Rush's listeners may be in for a shock - it turns out that his rehab clinic may be the epitome of everything Rush has railed against throughout his career. Limbaugh is rumored to be receiving treatment at Sierra Tucson, which apparently "utilizes many different types of therapeutic modalities to access underlying issues." Picture Rush partaking in "psychodynamic role-playing and yoga" and "adventure therapy," not to mention hauling his bulk up the Sierra Tuscon climbing wall (which apparently serves as an "important therapeutic metaphor.") Or will he be more comfortable with "the desert experience" and "equine-assisted therapy?" Personally I can picture Rush bonding with a horse. So will we see a kinder, gentler Limbaugh emerge from rehab? Only time will tell!
     

        
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser. ...and now my post... Don't you feel so bad for this cat? I know I do.     
     

        
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Violin Sonata in G Presto by Bach ...and now my post...   Oh yea! The Yankees lose! Bought damn time!  The Yankees lose, (quoting Monty Python) "and there was much rejoicing!"
     

        
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Our Last Summer by The A-Teens ...and now my post... Sorry, no Friday Five this week!  Oh yea! It's Friday! I love Friday's! Why? I dunno why. I just do. Tomorrow I have a Habitat for Humanity thing.  urlLink The Teensters . We are building homes with Habitat for Humanity. We start tomorrow. Then I will be going to the  urlLink Bite of Las Vegas . It should be fun. Then on Sunday I'm gonna enjoy my day off, and do some Physics homework. That is my weekend. Oh yea!  
     

        
</post>

<date>19,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Oh yea! lol 100 visitors!   
     

        
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: I Want More by Chumbawamba ...and now my post... My weekend has been great! On Friday I went to the Bone Game. The game started at 7:00, and at 7:05 they wouldn't let anyone else into the game. It was pretty gay. I thought it was dumb. But hey, it is CCSD. LOL. Talk about ghetto. Anywayz. So at half-time I got into the game. The white ccsd police officer let me in. I guess he felt sorry for me or something. So I enjoyed the rest of the game. Rancho lost, but I had fun. Then we (parental units and myself) went to In-n-Out. Guess who I saw? CHAD! I hadn't seen him in forever. He was too busy working, but he is still oh-so-hot. But yea. Then I went home and showered and went to bed. Dreamt about Sean, but that is another story.  Then I woke up on Saturday and messed around on the computer. I invited Michaela to the show at Smoothie King, so we went Saturday night. I had a blast. I'm beginning to like her. Shocking, I know, being that I'm GAY. But moving on....We saw Ann the Man and Natalie there. They are soo cool! So we guawked over guys and listened to bands, and discussed gay guys at school. Then I took Michaela home and went to bed. And had yet another dream about Sean.  Then I woke up today and just got online, and watched my dad's fantasy football team get its ass kicked. Needless to say, we lost. LOL. Then I watched the Bronco - Vikings game. We lost. :'( It is a sad day. Oh well. Then I got called ugly by Tim and Tyler. Oh well, fuck them. They are assholes. Then I went to the store with my mom. We got dog food, and LICORICE! LOL. I love that shit. Anywho. Yea. Tomorrow will be busy. I have French Club, and Thursday I have ESU!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! LOL!   ...till next time...
     

        
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: nothing, I know I'm a loser ...and now my post...  urlLink     The Bush Administration  So apparently the Bush administration has decided that it's time to ease restrictions on the killing, capturing and importing of endangered species. And why would they want to do this? The answer, to anyone who's been following the antics of the Bush administration over the last couple of years, should be quite familiar - they believe that killing and capturing endangered species is the best way to protect them. Isn't it obvious? Here's how it works: part of the money spent by U.S. zoos and circuses to import endangered animals would be simply be funneled back to the animals' country of origin to support conservation projects. Clever, huh? The more endangered animals we import, the more money goes overseas to help protect them. In fact, if you think about it, the more animals we remove from their natural habitat, the more money will go back into their conservation, and the more animals there will be to capture or hunt! It's brilliant! Reopen the ivory trade - soon there will be wild elephants teeming across the Serengeti! Build more whaling ships - before long the oceans will be crammed full of whales! Put a price on Pandas' heads - and you'll have Pandas as far as the eye can see! I can't understand why nobody but the circus, zoo, pet industry, and hunting lobbies thought of this before now...   The Pentagon  Last week Our Great Leader kept up his push to explain to America that everything is going just fine in Iraq, while U.S. soldiers continue to die on an almost daily basis. But Bush's optimistic proclamations of great success were given a healthy boost by Republican lawmakers who were recently taken on carefully-planned guided tours of Baghdad and returned from Iraq bearing - surprise - good news. Take Rep. George Nethercutt, for example, who said, "The story of what we've done in the postwar period is remarkable. It is a better and more important story than losing a couple of soldiers every day." Well I guess that depends on whether you're related to one of those soldiers or not. But if you think you might not be getting the whole picture here - you're right. Last week Senator Chris Dodd and other top Democrats were denied entry to Iraq by the Pentagon. Why? Because according to the Pentagon, "no planes were available to ferry the group from Jordan to Iraq." Yeah, right. So the next time you see George W. Bush complaining about how the news coming out of Iraq isn't fair and balanced you'll know that he's right - only Republicans are allowed to see what's going on over there.   Leaders of The War On Terror  Last week the International Institute for Strategic Studies released a report called "The Military Balance" which, according to the UK Guardian, says that "War in Iraq has swollen the ranks of al-Qaida and 'galvanised its will' by increasing radical passions among Muslims." Are you shocked? Perhaps if you'd been given the same information as the prime movers behind the war in Iraq, you wouldn't be. The Guardian article goes on to note that "The parliamentary intelligence and security committee reported last month that Tony Blair was warned by his intelligence chiefs on the eve of war that an invasion of Iraq would increase the danger of terrorist attacks." Funny... I thought that the whole point of the war was to reduce the danger of terrorist attacks. Or was it to find weapons of mass destruction? Or free the Iraqi people? It all seems so fuzzy these days.    George W. Bush  Looks like Our Great Leader is really getting a handle on this White House leak thing. Two weeks ago he simultaneously promised to catch the senior administration official who revealed Valerie Plame's identity as a CIA agent, and said that he had "no idea" if the person would be caught (see Idiots 130), which is pretty impressive. But last week he really put his foot down, telling top officials to "stop the leaks" - or else. The Philadelphia Inquirer reported that Bush "'didn't want to see any stories' quoting unnamed administration officials in the media anymore, and that if he did, there would be consequences." And how do we know all this? Because it was told to the Inquirer by "a senior administration official who asked that his name not be used." Good job, George. You'll have those pesky leaks under control before you can say "The Floccinaucinihilipilification Administration."   Colin Powell  It was time for Colin Powell to be taken down a peg or two last week when former chief State Department intelligence analyst Greg Thielmann appeared on the PBS documentary "Truth, War and Consequences." Thielmann described how the Bush administration were "cherry-picking the information that we provided to use whatever pieces of it fit their overall interpretation," and said that Powell's speech to the UN was "probably one of the low points in his long distinguished service to the nation." "They knew what they wanted the intelligence to show," said Thielmann. "They were really blind and deaf to any kind of countervailing information the intelligence community would produce." Which would probably explain why the only weapons of mass destruction that have turned up in Iraq so far are a couple of trucks used for blowing up balloons, a metal tube buried under a rose bush, half a jar of botulism toxin which is probably just some three-year-old mayonnaise, and a pair of Qusay's old socks.   Halliburton  What a surprise - Iraq is becoming a major cash cow for Dick Cheney's former company. And now Democrats are charging that Halliburton is screwing the U.S. taxpayer while importing gas into Iraq. Importing gas into Iraq? That's right - the invasion that was supposed to pay for itself through Iraqi oil revenues has ended with the U.S. importing oil into Iraq. Brilliant. But as if that wasn't bad enough, Halliburton is charging the Army between $1.62 and $1.70 per gallon - the average price for gas in the Middle East is 71 cents - while Iraqis are charged between 4 cents and 15 cents at the pump. Halliburton has already received $1.4 billion of the U.S. taxpayer's money through September and seems intent on continuing to gouge Joe Sixpack for every cent they get. Of course, the fact that Dick Cheney still holds Halliburton stock options and continues to receive deferred payments from his former company has nothing to do with the fact that they've been allowed to get away with this daylight robbery.   George W. Bush (again)  It's compassionate conservatism gone mad! The Washington Post revealed last week that the Bush administration "has been studying whether a private contractor should take over the custodial and food services provided by 21 federal employees at the National Naval Medical Center in Bethesda." As part of Bush's "competitive sourcing" initiative, civil servants working in all areas of government have to "prove they can do their work better and more cheaply than a private contractor, or risk seeing the work outsourced." Sounds like a good idea in principle, but here's the catch: the 21 federal employees providing custodial and food services at the National Naval Medical Center are all mentally retarded - "beneficiaries of federal policies that promote the employment of people with disabilities." See how this works? Bush is perfectly happy to throw $87 billion at Iraq, but then turns round and decides that he wants to shave a couple dollars off the budget by firing government workers with disabilities. That's compassionate conservatism in a nutshell, folks: more money for Halliburton in Iraq, more disabled Americans out of a job and out on the streets. Disgraceful.   Saudi Arabia  I hope Laura Bush is paying attention to this: last week 17 schoolgirls were suspended from their school in eastern Saudi Arabia for the heinous crime of uncovering their faces on a school bus. The girls were caught during a surprise inspection. As expatriates they're probably lucky to get away with a suspension, as opposed to being suspended from the rafters - I mean, it's not as if the Saudis are particularly well known for their excellent treatment of schoolgirls (see Idiots 59). Still, despite being the home country of Osama bin Laden and most of the 9/11 hijackers, the Saudis are still our great allies. So we should probably ignore this kind of behavior and instead give them a big round of applause for all the support they've given us while we invaded Iraq, which, as you know, was not about weapons of mass destruction at all, but was instead about freeing the Iraqi people from the tyrannical dictates of their leaders. Hey, wait a minute...   Clear Channel DJs  With the war on terror all but over - if you discount the fact that our soldiers are dying every day in Iraq, al Qaeda's membership is on the rise, and we can't find Osama bin Laden, Saddam Hussein, or any weapons of mass destruction - Clear Channel DJs are looking for another group of evildoers to spew venom at. And they seem to have found a worthy target - cyclists! It appears that at least three Clear Channel stations - in Cleveland, Houston, and Raleigh, NC - have been instructing their listeners to run cyclists off the road or pelt them with bottles. And not only that, but they've been instructing them in the best way to do it; even getting advice from callers. Surprise - cyclists are pissed. Email campaigns and boycotts have forced at least one station to issue a formal apology, but the fact that this anti-cyclist campaign seems to be spreading across the Clear Channel airwaves concerns some people. "When you incite people to violence, you've crossed the line," said Houston cyclist Frank Karbarz, who helped organize against the station. "They did it almost like a tutorial. It wasn't humorous. It was how to hurt someone." Of course, I don't imagine that this has anything to do with the fact that most Clear Channel listeners associate cycling with liberalism - get off the road, you stupid environmentalist hippie! - and I'm sure that this isn't just an underhanded way of suggesting that red-blooded, pickup driving American patriots should get out there and start running down the scum-sucking liberal treehuggers - but I'm certainly interested to see where they go with this next...   Lt. Gen. William "Jerry" Boykin  And finally, you'll be glad to learn that we have responsible, sane, diplomatic people in charge of finding Saddam Hussein and Osama bin Laden. Take Lt. Gen. William "Jerry" Boykin, for example. Boykin is the newly promoted deputy undersecretary of state of defense for intelligence, and is at the forefront of the hunt for Saddam and bin Laden. Unfortunately it was revealed last week that he's made some rather dubious comments in the past which make him look less like a top terrorist-hunter and more like a... well, not to put too fine a point on it - a religious nutcase. Boykin has apparently told religious groups that George W. Bush was "chosen by God" to lead the "global fight against Satan" - at one gathering he said, "Why is this man in the White House? The majority of Americans did not vote for him. He's in the White House because God put him there for a time such as this." Silly me - I could have sworn it was because of a bunch of Republican aides "rioting" in Florida followed by a hopelessly partisan Supreme Court decision. I guess God really does work in mysterious ways. Boykin has also said that his God is "bigger" than Allah, and that Muslims worship an "idol," which is exactly the kind of attitude you need when you're trying to recruit Muslims to help you track down Saddam and Osama. The good news though is that Boykin has decided to cut down on his public speaking while he's working for Bush, saying "I don't want to come across as a Right-wing radical." Goodness, no! That would never do!
     

        
</post>

<date>17,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Memphis Soul Song by Uncle Kracker ...and now my post... I'm all giddy now. lol. Rancho High School has a Eurpean Student Union! Oh yea! I'm Vice President, and Joe is the President. So leps recap: I'm VP of French Club, Junior Class Rep of Aviation Club, member of Pride Alliance, and VP of ESU. Hell yea! :-P hehe.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Memphis Soul Song by Uncle Kracker ...and now my post... 1. Name five things in your refrigerator. milk, jelly, meat, cheese, taco from Tacobell 2. Name five things in your freezer. ice cream, pot pies, bread, ice, TV dinners 3. Name five things under your kitchen sink. plates, forks, spoons, sporks (they kick ass!), glass 4. Name five things around your computer. phone, cds, speakers, money, books 5. Name five things in your medicine cabinet. tooth brush, deodorant, after shave, shaving lotion, razor   
     

        
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currentling Listening to: Nothing...I know I'm sad. ...and now my post...  I'm adding a new weekly thing to my website. The Top 10 Conservative Idiots (thanks to DemocraticUnderground.com). Enjoy!   urlLink      Rush Limbaugh    Look, if Rush Limbaugh wants to spend each day stuffing two grams of Oxycontin down his throat or half a pound of Bolivian marching powder up his nose, that's his business. It's a private, personal matter and it should be of no consequence to anyone, especially liberals, especially the tolerant, compassionate liberals that Sean Hannity was commanding to forgive Rush last week. But you know, this kinda reminds me of, say, that time Bill Clinton had a consenting relationship with a woman who wasn't his wife. It was his personal, private business and had nothing to do with anyone else, and thank goodness Rush treated it as such and didn't make a big fuss about it. Because now Rush has admitted that he too is a mere human being with feelings and flaws just like everyone else, we can all just say, "Oh, that poor guy, how awful," instead of calling him a fat, hypocritical crackhead. To his credit, Rush doesn't actually want to be treated like a victim: "I am no victim and do not portray myself as such. I take full responsibility for my problem," said he on his radio show last week. Got that, dittoheads? Next time you feel a pang of sympathy for Rush, remember that he takes full responsibility for his actions. Then re-read this old quote of his: "Drug use destroys societies. Drug use, some might say, is destroying this country. And we have laws against selling drugs, pushing drugs, using drugs, importing drugs. And the laws are good because we know what happens to people in societies and neighborhoods which become consumed by them. And so if people are violating the law by doing drugs, they ought to be accused and they ought to be convicted and they ought to be sent up." Don't forget, dittoheads - Rush is always right.   Rush Limbaugh (again)     But you have to take pity on Rush, really. I mean, the guy has a serious back problem which surgery failed to correct. He got addicted to painkillers six years ago when they were prescribed for the severe pain he was experiencing. As he said on his radio show, "Unfortunately the surgery was unsuccessful, and I continued to have severe pain in my lower back and also in my neck now, due to two hernated disks (sic) - pain which I'm experiencing because of that." Hmm, interesting. Apparently those two herniated discs didn't put Rush off his golf game. According to golfserv.com, Rush Limbaugh is "no slouch with the sticks himself after only playing for the past six years." "'I felt like an absolute dork,' Limbaugh said after practice rounds on Tuesday and Wednesday with the long hitters. 'These guys are hitting the ball 330 yards up here in this air. I'm lucky to hit it 240 and they are kind of snickering behind their backs, while to my face, 'Thatta boy, Rush, you can do it.''" Good grief, he can hit 240-yard drives with two herniated discs and constant neck pain? Impressive!   Rush Limbaugh (yet again)  But that's enough about Lardbottom's pill problem. Let's rewind a little: it's the day after Arnold Schwarzenegger's victory, and Rush Limbaugh is live on air, in full flow, talking about... Democratic Underground. What? It's the day after an unprecedented recall election, the Republicans won, and Rush is bashing our little website? Man, that guy must be on dru... uh, never mind. I know what you're thinking - didn't he have some gloating to do, or bloating, or whatever it is he gets up to on his show? Nope, apparently Rush had more important things on his mind than Arnold Schwarzenegger, and those things included getting back at people who've given him a taste of his own medicine. No, no, not Wilma Cline - your friendly hosts, Democratic Underground. Rush spent some time last Wednesday crying to his listeners about how mean nasty liberals are saying bad things on the Internet, and according to Mr. Factchecker himself, we want American troops in Iraq to get killed. Now just to set the record straight here, I can categorically state on behalf of the Adminstrators of Democratic Underground that - and this may be a surprise to some of you conservatives out there - we actually don't want American troops to get killed! See, like a lot of his material, Rush simply made that up. Believe it or not, we're extremely keen to see the troops come home unharmed. But then, we weren't the ones rallying out there last March demanding that our boys and girls be shipped off to the Middle East to die ASAP. That was, uh, fans of Rush Limbaugh. Name-calling? Yes, we do that. Immature needling of big-cheese conservatives? Check. Wishing for American troops to be killed? Uh-uh, sorry - we wish them all a safe and speedy return. But thanks anyway for the free advertising, Mr. Limbaugh! Oh, and just so you know - the following Friday, when Rush told his listeners that Democratic Underground had been shut down because of all the extra traffic he sent our way? Yeah, he made that up too.   Pat Robertson  Here's a follow-up to the recent Rush Limbaugh/Donovan McNabb story which was too late to make it into the Top Ten last week. It turns out that - guess what? - Pat Robertson has come out with a staunch defense of Rush's comments (Rush said that quarterback Donovan McNabb was overrated because he's black - see Idiots 129). So what's Pat's angle? Unsurprisingly, he's taken Rush's ball and run with it into an even uglier area. The Racist Reverend tried to demonstrate that black people do benefit from "social concern" by comparing McNabb to actor Morgan Freeman: "He started off playing a chauffeur in 'Driving Miss Daisy,' and then they elevated him to head of the CIA and then they elevated him to President and in his last role they made him God. I just wonder, isn't Rush Limbaugh right to question the fact, is he that good an actor or not?" Um, reality check, Pat. Morgan Freeman is an actor. He's hasn't actually been promoted from chauffeur to God. You know? It's all, like, an illusion. Of course, the implication here is that as far as Pat Robertson is concerned, black people should stick to playing chauffeurs and let white people deal with the business of playing God. Incidentally, in between playing a chauffeur and God, Morgan Freeman also played, among other things, the roles of a slave ("Amistad"), a slave ("Glory"), a murderer ("The Shawshank Redemption"), and, oh look, a murderer ("Nurse Betty"). Presumably Pat considers these to be more appropriate roles for the three-time-Oscar-nominated actor.   Bill O'Reilly  Bill O'Reilly retained the title of "Most Thin-Skinned Conservative in America" last week when he appeared on NPR's "Fresh Air" program last week to promote his book Who's Looking Out For You? (Bill's answer: me, me, me, it's all about me!). O'Reilly was given free time to refute the recent criticisms of Al Franken and others, talk about his TV show, discuss his childhood, background and spirituality, blast liberals, and plug his book in a debate-free atmosphere. But being the paranoid blowhard he is, O'Reilly couldn't even handle interviewer Terry Gross's relatively softball questions and instead tried to make out that he was being personally defamed. (Defamation seems to be a hot topic in the world of Bill O'Reilly - he mentioned the word about two hundred times in the first fifteen minutes). Eventually Gross's gentle probing became too much for the supposedly tough TV personality to handle - so he blew up, ranting about NPR's liberal bias and how all the questions were designed to make him look foolish (actually he managed to do a pretty good job of that all by himself). Bill then topped off his little tantrum by hanging up. Amazing - he can cut people off when they're not even on his show! Now that's talent.    The Bush Administration  You may have read recently that the Bush administration is on the offensive over the Iraq situation, and plan to push the message to Americans that everything is just fine and dandy over there. I don't know about on the offensive, but they certainly are offensive. Conveniently for the administration, letters from soldiers stationed in Iraq detailing the great progress of the rebuilding process have been showing up in local newspapers all over the country recently. But here's a funny thing - they're all identical. Oh, sure, they're signed by different soldiers, but strangely the wording of each letter is exactly the same. And not only that, but when Gannett News Service contacted several of the soldiers who supposedly authored the letters, none of them had any idea who wrote them. Gee, that's weird. I wonder how these optimistic missives, all identical, all apparently signed by soldiers currently serving in Iraq, managed to end up in the mailbags of American newspapers? I mean, surely the Department of Defense wouldn't go around forging soldiers' signatures on fake letters, would they? Would they?   George W. Bush  Somehow George W. Bush didn't manage to make it onto the list last week - I guess we have to give him a break from time to time - but he's back with a vengeance this week, and he's on top form as usual. Last week Our Great Leader demonstrated his can-do approach to cracking down on "appearances of impropriety" within his adminstration, forcefully asserting that he has literally "no idea" if the White House leaker will be caught. Uh, what? Why not? According to Bush, it's tricky because "This is a large administration." Well... okay - but surely you've stated with confidence that you're going to find Osama bin Laden and Saddam Hussein, and they could be anywhere in the world at this point. I mean, this guy might work in the office next door to yours. What's the problem here? Apparently there's no problem - a confused Bush went on to contradict himself by stating that "We'll find out" who it is, and with the assistance of John Ashcroft we'll "come to the bottom of this." Well it shouldn't take long then. I think George and his administration are going to hit rock bottom any day now.   Kendel Ehrlich  Okay, this is just bizarre. Maryland's first lady Kendel Ehrlich was speaking at a domestic violence prevention conference in Frederick, MD, last week, and got onto the subject of young women needing to become independent, and the dangers of becoming too dependent on others. To illustrate her point, Ehrlich said, "If I had an opportunity to shoot Britney Spears, I think I would." Whoa, hold on a second there... she'd shoot Britney Spears? Damn, that's harsh! I'm not sure where Ehrlich got the idea that the best way for young women to become independent is to go out and murder celebrities (question: only given the opportunity, or is stalking optional?) but my goodness, that sounds like a comment in need of a clarification. And here comes the clarification! Comedically, a spokeswoman said later that Ehrlich used an "inadvertent figure of speech." Ah yes, the old "inadvertent figure of speech" ploy. That's always a good one.   Pat Robertson (again)  One appearance on the list just wasn't good enough for Mad Pat Roberston this week. Not long after his Morgan Freeman comments, Pat was back on the 700 Club bemoaning those awful traitors over at the State Department. What the State Department has done to incur the wrath of Pat isn't entirely clear (it's run by a black person, perhaps?) but whatever it is, he's not messing around. While interviewing Joel Mowbray, author of the new book, Dangerous Diplomacy: How the State Department Endangers America's Security, Pat said, "When you get through, you say, 'If I could just get a nuclear device inside Foggy Bottom, I think that's the answer,' and you say, 'We've got to blow that thing up.'" Oddly enough, Mowbray never actually says that in his book. But Pat may be projecting here - back in June the Rabid Reverend suggested that "Maybe we need a very small nuke thrown off on Foggy Bottom to shake things up like Newt Gingrich wants to do." Now, I'm not sure where in the teachings of Jesus it says that the way to deal with one's enemies is to blow them up with a nuclear bomb - not only that, but nuking the State Department sounds awfully un-American to me. Perhaps if Pat is serious about this plan he should get in touch with someone who shares his beliefs but has more experience in this kind of work, someone like, I dunno, Osama bin Laden.   The Pentagon  And finally, whatever happened to "Don't Ask Don't Tell?" It was reported last week that Lockheed Martin have scrapped the planned name for their futuristic new combat ship "The Sea Blade" because - wait for it - the word "blade" is too gay. Lockheed have denied the claim that the name change was requested by the Pentagon, although it was apparently "dropped shortly after the Navy awarded the defense conglomerate a $10 million contract for a preliminary design." It turns out that "gay blade" is an old slang term for someone suspected of being a homosexual - a term which was later satirically adopted by the gay movement, and introduced to the masses through newspapers such as the Washington Blade. And so the Pentagon, in their infinite wisdom, apparently decided that it wasn't a good idea to have all those sailors, stuck at sea for weeks in cramped quarters, living it up aboard the old Sea Blade. Incidentally, has anybody told Wesley Snipes about this?
     

        
</post>

<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currentling Listening to: Toccata and Fugue in A Minor by Johann Sebastian Back ...and now my post... 1. Do you watch sports? If so, which ones? Yes, hockey (eh?), baseball (damn Yankees), and football (Broncos!) 2. What/who are your favorite sports teams and/or favorite athletes? Broncos, Avalanche, and Rockie 3. Are there any sports you hate? RAIDERS (shuttup Cory) 4. Have you ever been to a sports event? Yes, Rancho games all the time 5. Do/did you play any sports (in school or other)? How long did you play? Yes. Baseball, Bowling, and hockey. I played hockey for two years, baseball for two, and bowling for one.   
     

        
</post>

<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currentling Listening to: NPR Hourly News ...and now my post... Are we really winning in Iraq? What the Bush administration may have you think, we arn't. Before sending me hate mail, please let me explain. We are losing about 2 US soldiers a day. And for what cause? To get the Bush Administration more money from the Oil Industry. Now here is a nice graph.     This graph sure makes on think, doesn't it? The Bush Administration is leading the US into something we can't undo. We will be stuck in Iraq forever. We have yet to win the War of Terror. No bin Laden. No Saddam. No WMD. Who are you voting for? Bush and his lies? Or Democratic? Me? I'm voting for Clark, Dean, or Gephardt. I'm undecided at the moment. Why? I'm still looking into the education packages each candidate offers. And where they stand on Iraq, the War on Terror, and Foreigh Realations (yes this includes mending the hole with the French).
     

        
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Well Crap. This was the banner this morning:     Well, he won. Damnit Damnit Damnit! Oh well. California will have to deal with this for a LONG time. Oh well. Sorry if you live in California. Sorry in advance, if you voted for Schwarzenegger.
     

        
</post>

<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currentling Listening to: Tocatta and Fuge in A Minor by Johann Sebastian Bach ...and now my post...  Was searching the web, and I found this picture. Thought I would post it. I know I'm gonna vote November 5th. Are you?    urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>04,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currentling Listening to: Violin Sonata in G, BWV 1021 - Largo by Johann Sebastian Back ...and now my post... 1. What vehicle do you drive? VW 2003 Bug 2. How long have you had it? It is my mom's, since April 3. What is the coolest feature on your vehicle? The flowers 4. What is the most annoying thing about your vehicle? Stick 5. If money were no object, what vehicle would you be driving right now? Nissan Z3   
     

        
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currentling Listening to: Gira con Me by Josh Groban ...and now my post...  Hey all. Like the new look? I like the leaves. hehe. Anywayz. I'm back. Sorry for not posting any lately, I have been hella busy with school. I moved into Physics Honors, so now I have Physics, US History, Alg II, and French Honors. What a load. Plus add Ground School and American Lit. Anywayz. Well, lets see. The US passes a Homeland Security bill worth $30 billion. What the hell? Why not pass $30 billion towards education. Oh yea, thats right, we don't care about the future of American schools. Just about the damn military and our fake war in Iraq. Well, enough political venting. I will post more later.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: I Don't Wanna Spend One More Christmas Without You by N'Sync ....and now my post.... Why is it Wednesday's are always so boring. Why is it that they are the slowest days of the week? With that I begin my post for today. Today was your typical Wednesday. Sloooow moving. Don't you just hate days like that? So I go to school and I leave home without my Blogger Hoodie. Why you ask? I don't know. So I'm standing at the bus stop freezing my ass off, and well it sucked. So Kenny (my bus driver) shows up late as usual, and I warm up. Then I get to school and head straight to the locker. I pull out my trusty leather airman jacket. Man do I love that jacket. It is soo warm. Then Stefani, Jenkins, and I head off to the Cafeteria, and as we are walking past the old gym I notice I got mud on my Dickies. "Craaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaap!" I hate it when I get mud on my CLEAN Dickies. So we get into the Cafeteria and do that thang. Stefani gets me some paper towels because our lazy janitors don't fill up the guy’s paper towel thing. Why? I dunno. So anywayz. I wash them off best I could, and then the bell rang so off I go to Early Bird. Ms. Nelson was there. Her son was shot in the neck. So she wasn't having the best time. We just went over the study guides. Fun stuff!  After that I went to French and watched Joan of Arc. The movie is cheesy, but hey, it is a movie right? Then I go to aviation and watch this boring ass movie about weather. The whole class was falling asleep so Mr. Kelly told us to all stand up. "Reach for the air. Bend over, grab your ankles."   Riight. I did get to see Oscar's happy trail and belly button, twice actually. So I guess that is good. He smiled at me too, so I dunno. But yea. Then I went to American Lit and took that test. Easy as pie. Then lunch, and history. Following that was Algebra II. Boring as normal, but hey! It is math; it is supposed to be boring, right?  Well, that is my day. Maybe tonight will be better. Chinese food. Mmmmmm. *drools*. And then tomorrow is TURKEY DAY! Fun fun fun! I love Thanksgiving. If I don't get a chance to post tomorrow, I'm wishing you a happy thanksgiving, and hope everyone is safe.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: American Idol Christmas on FOX ...and now my post... So today I attended the Sun Youth Forum at the Las Vegas Convention Center. It was fun. I got to debate about Nevada topics, such as the schools, Yucca Mountain, water, and growth in the Valley. The only bad thing was this guy named Ryan who attends Chap (and is an ass if you ask me) asked if I carried heat to Rancho because Rancho is "unsafe". Why does everyone and their uncle thinks Rancho is unsafe? Since when has Rancho been unsafe? Is it because we have a larger Hispanic population? I don't know the answer, but Ryan goes to Chap. Come on here people. We all know Chap is more dangerous then Rancho. Rancho is one of the safest schools in Clark County. Chap isn't. So he has no where to talk. Rancho has a bad rap which needs to end. But moving on...  We talked about many topics, but I liked the topic about the school district. We never really went back to it, but I liked it. I wanted to see how other students felt about the over crowding in the schools, and while we are suffering our lovely superintendent, Carlos Garcia drives a Lexus and gets a gas card. Why? Oh great School Gods, why?  Other then the Sun Youth Forum, my life has been relatively quiet. I bleached my hair on Friday. Boy did I get some weird looks and comments at school on Monday. I only got two nice comments from Desiree and Stefani. I know Stefani wouldn't diss on my hair, but come on people. It isn't THAT bad. See what I mean?     Is it honestly that bad? Keep in mind it is 8:30 at night, so my gel isn't THAT good, but still. Cut me some slack here people.  I apologize for not updating the website with my stuff lately. Hopefully it won't happen much anymore. Tomorrow is Wednesday. Fun fun fun. Then TURKEY DAY! I'm going to be spending it with family friends. I was gonna go to El Paso and visit Mike, but he is going to officer training school then going to Korea. Why do you ask? Because the DAMN military is saying he has to. God I hate the government right now. Why is it so corrupt? Absolute power corrupts absolutely. Well I'm done ranting. I will post more this week. I will have pictures from Thanksgiving too!  
     

        
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: The Little Drummer Boy by Stevan Pasero ...and now my post...       Senate Republicans      Okay, hands up - who watched the 39-hour judicial nominations wankathon last week? I know I didn't. Well, okay - I did tune in once or twice. The entire colossal waste of time was perpetrated by Republicans who, pissed off that Democrats wouldn't roll over and nominate four of Bush's nutjob justices, were trying to score political points by holding a multi-day cry-fest. Never mind the fact that the Democrats have already approved 168 of Bush's judicial nominees - nooo, that's not good enough for the power-mad Republicans who are for some reason laboring under the misapprehension they have a huge mandate for this kind of nonsense. Here's a thought guys - if you want the Democrats to approve every single one of Bush's justices, how about getting him to nominate some folks that are acceptable to everyone, not just to crackpot wingnuts? Gee, there's a thought. Meanwhile, let's not forget that one of Bush's most important campaign promises in 2000 was his pledge to "change the tone" in Congress and bring the two sides together in a bipartisan explosion of good will and compromise - not that he's managed to keep any of his other campaign promises, mind you (except the one about shoveling fat piles of cash to his multimillionaire buddies).   Senate Republicans and Fox News  The odor of hypocrisy surrounding George W. Bush grew even more repugnant last week when he pulled out his favorite chestnut and accused Democrats of "playing politics" with his judicial nominations. Wow, I haven't heard him use that one for, ooh, about five minutes. But who's really playing politics here? Last week a leaked memo from Elizabeth Keys, a senior communications advisor for the Senate Republican Conference, revealed that Senate Republicans were in cahoots with Fox News over the theatrical aspects of this colossal waste of time, uh, I mean, very important debate. The memo to Republican staffers said, "It is important to double efforts to get your boss to S-230 on time ... Fox News Channel is really excited about this marathon and Brit Hume at 6 would love to open with all our 51 senators walking onto the floor - the producer wants to know will we walk in exactly at 6:02 when the show starts so they get it live to open Brit Hume's show? Or if not, can we give them an exact time for the walk-in start?" So let me get this straight - Fox News isn't just spinning the news any more, they're actually working directly with Republicans to stage-manage the news. My word, is there no end to the impartiality of the Fox News Network?    George W. Bush  Our Great Leader could be in for a shock when he visits the UK this week - massive protests are being planned, and London's Metropolitan Police appear to be decidedly uninterested in recreating Dubya's infamous "First Amendment Zones" in the capital. It appears that Team Bush arrogantly attempted to get the Met to shut down the city center for three days, but Ken Livingstone, the Mayor of London, is making sure that Bush won't be protected from the indignity of actually having to see protesters, as he is at home. Bush has taken all this in stride, of course, saying last week that, "I'm so pleased to be going to a country which says that people are allowed to express their minds." Yes - that'll certainly make a change from being in the US these days. But Bush added, "But certainly they should agree with the goals of the United States, which is [sic] peace and freedom." Now wait - hold on a second here. So if people turn out in huge numbers to yell at the Chump-in-Chief, they're not actually doing it because they disagree with him and his murderous policies - they're doing it because they disagree with the benign and benevolent goals of the United States? Uh, so despite the fact that Bush has been president for less than three years and has already managed to invade two countries, not to mention piss off the entire world community, everyone who shows up to protest him actually hates peace and freedom? What year is this, 1984?   Roy Moore  We've been commenting on the Roy Moore story for a long time now (see Idiots passim) but we're pleased to report that he finally got his just desserts last week when an Alabama state judicial ethics panel booted him out of office. Moore's rabid tendency to shove his beliefs down everybody's throats, not to mention his unhealthy obsession with a large chunk of granite (funny, I thought the First Commandment says something about not having any other gods) led to his downfall - not to mention the fact that chief justices really ought to be able to follow the law themselves. Moore was - surprise - unrepentant (funny, I thought Jesus said... oh, never mind) and vowed, "You will hear from me again when it comes to the right to acknowledge God." Newsflash - everyone's already got the right to acknowledge God, dude. You just need to learn the difference between "acknowledge" and "illegally shove down everyone's throats." Incidentally, Roy Moore's attorney was apparently heard on CNN last week favorably comparing the ex-chief justice to George Wallace. For those of you who are unfamiliar with George Wallace, he was a staunch segregationist who became famous in 1963 when he attempted to prevent federal authorities from enrolling two black students at the University of Alabama. So, uh, I guess if that's the kind of hero Roy Moore wants to be compared to then, um, right. Ooooo-kay.    Bill O'Reilly  Oh please let this be true... oh please oh please oh please. It was revealed last week that the blowhard who blows harder than anyone else, Bill O'Reilly, may be considering a run for president. "Certainly the option is open if I want it," said Bill, although he also acknowledged that he wouldn't stand a chance in hell of winning. However, I have to say I'd be thrilled at the prospect of an O'Reilly candidacy. How awesome would it be to watch the thin-skinned jerk self-destruct every time he was put in a tough spot by a reporter? I'm getting goosebumps just thinking about it! To be fair, Bill wants to make sure that everyone knows he would be a serious candidate: "I'm not a vanity player, I'm not gonna go out like Al Sharpton, to get on 'Saturday Night Live' to run for president," he said. Heh heh, yeah right. Not a vanity player. Nice one, Bill. That's pretty funny coming from a guy who manages to turn every single segment on his TV show into a commentary on himself. So please, Bill, if you're reading this, please run for president. I'll even send you a donation! Ten bucks, and a handkerchief to blow your nose into while you're having your nightly bout of self-loathing.   Arnold Schwarzenegger  In a bizarrely OJ Simpson-style turn of events, Arnold Schwarzenegger has hired a private investigator to uh, investigate himself. The Groping Austrian Beefcake made a campaign promise to look into the allegations made against him and to be fair, unlike OJ Simpson, Arnold actually appears to be keeping his promise. But I can't help feeling that this is all a little odd. I mean, the dude just got elected and now he's investigating himself for sexual harassment? Can't he just ask himself whether he did it or not? What does he need the PI for? Tell you what though, I'm going to go out on a limb here and predict that the private investigator will clear Arnold of all the charges. "I've interrogated Governor Schwarzenegger thoroughly and determined that there was absolutely no wrongdoing involved in any of these incidents. It appears that the breasts and buttocks of the alleged victims actually flung themselves at Governor Schwarznegger's hands. Case closed. Nothing to see here. Terminator 3 is now available on DVD. Check stores for details."   Ken Conroy  Conservatives are always keen to demonstrate how much they respect veterans - providing that they approve of those veterans' opinions, of course. A group of veterans were forcibly removed from a Veterans' Day parade in Tallahassee last week by the parade organizer Ken Conroy, because they were "offensive." Their crime? Disagreeing with the current war in Iraq. "They can have their free speech, just not in the parade," Conroy said. "They belong on the sidewalk." Meanwhile, the parade - which, according to the Florida Times-Union contained "several high school marching bands and even a group of young women from the local Hooters restaurant" - continued. Without the veterans. I guess in future Veterans' Day should be appended to Approved Veterans' Day, where we're only allowed to honor those who don't have some kind of controversial opinion. Ah, the land of the free.   Jeb Bush  While we're on the subject of Florida, it's nice to see the return of Governor Jeb Bush to this list after a long absence. What's Jeb been up to? Well, last week he was having a bit of a "joke" with the good people of San Francisco, suggesting that they may be an endangered species. Bush was holding a cabinet meeting when the subject of environmental land came up. While viewing a map of the US which showed the locations of endangered wildlife, Bush said "It looks like the people of San Francisco are an endangered species, which may not be a bad thing. That's probably good news for the country." Uh, ha ha - I guess? I'm not entirely sure why Governor Bush thinks it's a good thing that "the people of San Francisco are an endangered species," unless it's got something to do with the fact that one thing San Francisco is famous for is its large population of homosexuals, and therefore it would be good if they were all wiped out. But I'm sure that's not what Jeb Bush was getting at. California's new governor Arnold Schwarzenegger immediately made a statement defending San Francisco... actually, nah, he didn't say anything at all. I guess he was too busy investigating himself.   Tom Delay  Just when you thought this guy couldn't get any more irritating, he comes up with a scheme that is so desperately annoying it makes being stabbed repeatedly in the buttocks seem like relaxing in a meadow on a pleasant summer's day. Here's the deal: Tom Delay has been sending recorded phone messages to people telling them that they've won a "national leadership award" and they should return his call ASAP. When the unsuspecting "award recipient" calls back - gotcha! A telemarketer comes on the line and hits you up for cash. Get it? If you give $300 or $500, you win the "national leadership award!" According to MSNBC, "Past awardees include a convicted sex offender and a maker of drug paraphernalia," although apparently, "both awards were later rescinded." Why, did their checks bounce? But seriously - thanks again, Tom. Every time we think you've hit rock bottom you manage to surprise us.   The RNC  And finally, the RNC managed to stop CBS from airing "The Reagans" (see Idiots 134) but they're not stopping there. No sir, the RNC isn't content with merely setting the record straight - they want to take the record off the record player, polish it, replace the stylus, add a new pair of top-of-the-line speakers and some of those Monster sound cables, then take the record and... (enough with the record player metaphor already - Ed). Ahem, anyway, the RNC has announced tentative plans to produce their own Ronald Reagan story, titled, um, "The Real Reagans." If it's anything like that epitome of unbiased truth, "DC 9/11" (see Idiots 126) then we could be in for a real treat. Picture the scene:  a muscle-bound, shirtless Ronald Reagan has Mikhail Gorbachev in a headlock and is using Gorbachev's own hand to punch him in the head. Reagan: "Mr. Gorbachev, stop hitting yourself and tear down this wall." Gorbachev: "Alright, I admit it, you have won the cold war!" Reagan gives Gorbachev a wedgie, then uses his laser eyes to carve his own head into Mount Rushmore.  Hell yeah, I'd watch the shit out of that.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: A Soal'n by Stevan Pasero (I'm in a Christmas kind of mood right now) ...and now my post... 1. List five things you'd like to accomplish by the end of the year. Get ESU off the ground, build more on the Teensters house, take more to Trystin, get to know Scott better, and drive on the freeway more 2. List five people you've lost contact with that you'd like to hear from again. Um, I dunno. Maybe Josh and Justin from Arizona. 3. List five things you'd like to learn how to do. Oh, there are to many. I dunno. 4. List five things you'd do if you won the lottery (no limit). Buy a Mazda RX-8, Lincoln LS, a house in Summerlin, a new Toshiba laptop, the $3000 ones, and buy a plane, maybe a Cessna Citation or something. 5. List five things you do that help you relax. get online, chat with friends, listen to celtic music, sit in my room, light candles.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
        I did it in 24   seconds. I deserved a B+!! Take the  urlLink How Dexterous Are You? Quiz !!
     

        
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: All You Wanted by Michelle Branch ...and now my post... 1. Using one adjective, describe your current living space. messy 2. Using two adjectives, describe your current employer. I don't have one 3. Using three adjectives, describe your favorite hobby/pasttime. fun, exciting, rush 4. Using four adjectives, describe your typical day. boring, fun, boooooooooooooooooring, sleepy 5. Using five adjectives, describe your ideal life. fun, Trystin, fun, Trystin, fun. I know, but hey, I'm like in love. Oh well, right?
     

        
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: I'm In Love With The Girl On A Certain Manchester Megastore Checkout Desk by The Freshies ...and now my post...    Ed Gillespie  These days it's hard to believe just how far conservatives have shoved their noses up St. Ronnie of Reagan's ass. Take RNC chief Ed Gillespie for example, who, upon learning that the CBS miniseries "The Reagans" may - gasp - take some dramatic liberties (I mean, it's not like it's a, uh, drama or anything) that he fired off an angry letter to CBS execs. According to CNN, Gillespie insisted that CBS "allow a team of historians and friends of former President Ronald Reagan and his wife" to check out the drama and approve it before airing it. And if CBS refused, Gillespie would - get this - "ask the network to run a note across the bottom of the screen every 10 minutes during the program's presentation informing viewers that the miniseries is not accurate." I mean, fer crissakes, what next? If viewers now need to be told that what they're watching on TV may not be 100% accurate, there are plenty of other shows I can think of that could do with a clarifying message. How about a crawl along the bottom of the screen during "The Bachelor" informing viewers that "while Bachelor Bob insists that he is in love with all of the remaining contestants, in fact he may have already decided who he is going to pick." Or how about during "Threat Matrix" - now there's a show that needs a clarifiying message every ten minutes - "while this program depicts the Office of Homeland Security as a team of hip twenty-somethings who talk cool-sounding cyberbabble and watch live satellite feeds in dimly-lit bunkers before heading off to some exotic location and busting terrorist ass, the real Office of Homeland Security is actually comprised of a lot of fat old white men sitting around conference tables discussing their golf swings." Not that any of this really matters any more since chickenshit CBS bowed to the right-wing pressure and shuffled "The Reagans" over to Showtime where it will be seen by approximately nobody. Cowards.   George W. Bush  No weapons of mass destruction - check. No connection to al-Qaeda or 9/11 - check. Looks like Our Great Leader is seriously starting to run out of excuses for invading Iraq and getting us into this ridiculous quagmire. But at least he can still bask in the glory of having removed Saddam Hussein from power and liberated the Iraqi people from his tyrannical regime. The remnants still persist, of course - Bush was heard last week suggesting that "Saddam loyalists, those are the people, the torturers and murderers and thugs that used to benefit from Saddam Husseins regime" being behind the recent attack on an American Chinook which killed 16 of our soldiers. Funnily enough, on the same day Our Great Leader was making this statement, it was announced that "The U.S. administrator of Iraq has decided to conditionally support the creation of an Iraqi-led paramilitary force composed of former employees of the country's security services and members of political party militias." Uh, okay - so that's no weapons of mass destruction, no connection to al-Qaeda or 9/11, and now we're re-hiring "the torturers and murderers and thugs that used to benefit from Saddam Husseins regime" to help run the country. Right... so I guess all we need to do now is withdraw from Iraq, allow Saddam return to power, and we'll be right back where we started. Minus the lives of hundreds of American soldiers and billions of taxpayer dollars of course. Good job, George. (note: kudos to Democrats.com for spotting this connection).    George W. Bush (again)  Did you know that last March, Gray Davis declared a state of emergency in California because of the threat of wildfires? And did you know that in April, he asked George W. Bush for $430 million from the Federal Emergency Management Agency to try to prevent a major fire disaster in Southern California? He sure did. And do you know what Our Great Leader told Gray Davis? Yup - screw you, dude. See, apparently FEMA's job is to clean up after emergencies, not do anything to prevent them. Although funnily enough, $500 million for the rebuilding of fire-ravaged areas was tacked on to the recent $87 billion Iraq request - which I'm sure will make George look good when he tours all the rebuilt areas next year with Governor Groping Austrian Beefcake. Look at all the money I've given California to recover from this disaster! Sure, sure, I could have given it to you earlier when Gray Davis asked for it - but that might have made him look good. Oh, and, yeah, sorry if you lost your house and all your belongings and stuff, but I've got an election campaign coming up, so, uh, America thanks you for your sacrifice.   The Bush Administration  How to not support the troops, episode #1837: it turns out that while the Bush administration has managed to appropriate $87 billion for, among other things, building new schools in Iraq, they're cutting costs at home by closing schools for the children of American servicepeople. According to the Army Times, "Defense officials notified the services in mid-October that they intend to close 19 commissaries and may close 19 more, mostly in remote areas. At the same time, the Pentagon is finishing a study to determine whether to close or transfer control of the 58 schools it operates on 14 military installations in the continental United States." Why? Well apparently "The two initiatives are the latest in a string of actions by the Bush administration to cut or hold down growth in pay and benefits, including basic pay, combat pay, health-care benefits and the death gratuity paid to survivors of troops who die on active duty." For the administration to make these cuts in the first place is awful (so much for Republicans supporting the military) but to make them during a time of war, while American soldiers are fighting and dying on a daily basis, is simply disgraceful.   Fox News  Fox News has always tried to maintain that it merely appears conservative and Republican, simply because all the rest of the media is - gosh - so damn liberal. But a former Fox News employee - a "veteran producer" no less - recently summed that claim up in a single word: bull. Charles Reina, who recently left the Fox News network after six years, published a letter on the Internet last week in which he explains exactly how the Fox newsroom works. According to Reina, "Not once in the 20+ years I had worked in broadcast journalism prior to Fox - including lengthy stays at The Associated Press, CBS Radio and ABC/Good Morning America - did I feel any pressure to toe a management line. But at Fox, if my boss wasn't warning me to 'be careful' how I handled the writing of a special about Ronald Reagan ('You know how Roger [Fox News Chairman Ailes] feels about him.'), he was telling me how the environmental special I was to produce should lean ('You can give both sides, but make sure the pro-environmentalists don't get the last word.')" Hmm... that doesn't sound very Fair and Balanced does it? But Reina goes on: "Editorially, the FNC newsroom is under the constant control and vigilance of management... the roots of FNC's day-to-day on-air bias are actual and direct. They come in the form of an executive memo distributed electronically each morning, addressing what stories will be covered and, often, suggesting how they should be covered." What? You mean management gives daily instructions on how to spin the news? But I thought Fox was a no-spin zone? Wrong! According to Reina, "The Memo was born with the Bush administration, early in 2001, and, intentionally or not, has ensured that the administration's point of view consistently comes across on [Fox]." So there you have it, folks - only this time it's official: Fox News is merely a lying, spinning tool of the Bush propaganda machine.   D. Nick Rerras  Here's another conservative Republican who wants to take us back to the Fifties. No, not the Nineteen Fifties - the Thirteen Fifties! D. Nick Rerras, who won re-election as a Virginia state senator last week, came under fire recently for suggesting that mental illnesses are caused by, um, demons. According to the Virginian-Pilot, a member of the Norfolk Community Services Board was present during a conversation with Rerras which turned to the topic of mental illness, during which Rerras said "he believed mental illness was caused by demons," and, "God may be punishing families by giving children mental illnesses." Our sources tell us that Rerras went on to inform his rapt audience that "thunder and lightning mean God is mad at you," and, "for those of you who think the Medicare crisis cannot be solved, I have one word: leeches."   An Unidentified Bus Driver  Let's see, according to Republicans these days we didn't go over to Iraq because of weapons of mass destruction; we went to liberate the Iraqis from their tyrannical dictator. Which we did! And now we're spending billions of dollars of American taxpayers' money to rebuild the place and, um, send them gasoline. It's just odd how so many conservatives seem to be of the opinion that rescuing the Iraqis from Saddam Hussein was the right thing to do (because that's what Dubya told them), except when it comes to the crunch, they still hate the damn brown people. Take this incident in Jacksonville, Florida, last week - an unidentified bus driver allegedly told 10-20 children to get off the school bus, forcing them to walk five miles home. Why? Because the children were Muslim, and many of them were wearing traditional Muslim dress. Nice, huh? You know, it kinda makes me wonder whether the real reason conservatives are so keen to liberate the oppressed Muslim populations of the Middle East is because they're jealous. Hey, if anyone's gonna be oppressing these people, it's gonna be ME!    Arnold Schwarzenegger  After saturating California with campaign ads claiming that when it comes to taking money from special interests, "I don't play that game," Governor Groping Austrian Beefcake has started mailing out invitations for his first fundraiser. The fundraiser will be held a mere two weeks after his swearing in, and is "aimed at tapping contributions from Capitol insiders," according to the L.A. Times. See, despite being a multi-millionaire, Arnold got a sweet deal on a loan from City National Bank of Beverly Hills to pay for his campaign, and now he needs to pay it back. And what better way to pay it back than to ask for up to $21,000 a pop from "Capitol insiders?" But according to Schwarzenegger spokesman Rob Stutzman, this isn't politics as usual. "What's different is that our fund-raising policy is different than other elected [officials] in Sacramento. What's different is that this governor will not play the special interest game…. Voters know they have sent a man to Sacramento who cannot be bought." Uh, right - so I guess all those "Capitol insiders" just really liked "Jingle All The Way" or something.   David Horowitz  Hey, there's nothing wrong with a spot of shoddy journalism. I'm one of the shoddiest journalists around! But then, I'm not all high-profile and respected like, say, David Horowitz. Surprising then that Horowitz published this on his blog recently: "The email below is making the rounds and is something that defenders of the President and this country ought to know to be better able to deal with them... a.. Enron's chairman did meet with the president and the vice President in the Oval Office. b.. Enron gave $420,000 to the president's party over three years. c.. It donated $100,000 to the president's inauguration festivities. d.. The Enron chairman stayed at the White House 11 times. e. The corporation had access to the administration at its highest levels and even enlisted the Commerce and State Departments to grease deals for it. f.. The taxpayer-supported Export-Import Bank subsidized Enron for more than $600 million in just one transaction. Scandalous!! g.. BUT...the president under whom all this happened WASN'T George W. Bush. h.. SURPRISE ........ It was Bill Clinton!" Sadly, anyone who is even vaguely familiar with the Internet knows that this is nothing but a well-worn email hoax that's been doing the rounds for a long time. Shame the high-profile and respected David Horowitz didn't bother to check before he published it. Even more of a shame that he had to publish an embarrassing retraction. Chortle.   Steve LaTourette  And finally: during the Clinton impeachment, Rep. Steve LaTourette (R-Ohio) was clearly torn about his vote, although he finally decided that America's moral values were at stake and decided to vote "yes." Perhaps one of the reasons that LaTourette had a hard time making up his mind was because he was busy boinking a Washington lobbyist behind his wife's back. But it's okay, because according to LaTourette, this is "a private matter" so there's no need for everyone to make a big brouhaha over it. Hmm. I guess his wife doesn't think it's a private matter since she's now blabbing to anyone and everyone about what an asshole he is. "He was a wonderful husband and father, the best I ever saw, until he went there [Washington]. I told him I was trying to get him out of the dark side, all that power and greed and people kissing up to them all time. Now he’s one of them. All they care about is getting reelected. I hate them all." Ah, chalk up another one for the party of morals and family values.
     

        
</post>

<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser ...and now my post... It isn't everyday you see an Oxymoron. This is thanks to  urlLink bitter pill .   
     

        
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser ...and now my post...    George W. Bush    White House communications director Dan Bartlett appeared on this list back in September (see Idiots 128) for trying to pretend that the White House had nothing to do with the "Mission Accomplished" banner hung behind George W. Bush on the aircraft carrier Abraham Lincoln. As if the White House - which went so far as to color-coordinate the uniforms of the sailors standing behind Bush during his speech - would allow a gigantic banner to hang in the frame if they didn't want it to be there. But it was George W. Bush himself who was most recently perpetuating this myth, disavowing any connection to the banner at a press conference last week, saying, "The 'Mission Accomplished' sign, of course, was put up by the members of the USS Abraham Lincoln, saying that their mission was accomplished. I know it was attributed somehow to some ingenious advance man from my staff - they weren't that ingenious, by the way." Whoops. The White House released a statement hours later, which, according to the Associated Press, said, "the Lincoln's crew asked the White House to have the sign made. The White House asked a private vendor to produce the sign, and the crew put it up." I guess that would explain why the banner looks exactly the same as other banners which have appeared deliberately behind Our Great Leader at various campaign stops - um, I mean, speeches of vital national importance:            Wow, look at that. Not only did they use the same flag graphic, they used the same typeface. Lazy bastards! Mind you, the fact that the White House created the banner seems to have been common knowledge immediately after the carrier appearance - the Washington Post reported back in May that, "Aides say the slogan was chosen in part to mark a presidential turn toward domestic affairs as his campaign for reelection approaches." So I guess Bush was more than happy to be associated with "Mission Accomplished" - right up until the shit started hitting the fan in Iraq. Typical really - as soon as things start going wrong President Personal Responsibility looks around for somebody else to hide behind. The CIA, MI6, his own advisors - now it's the Navy's turn.  Point of interest: Dan Bartlett had previously claimed that George W. Bush never said "mission accomplished" (although the banner was a bit of a giveaway) - unfortunately it didn't take long for the White House to change its tune, because that's exactly what Bush did say to the troops a month later in Qatar: "America sent you on a mission to remove a grave threat and to liberate an oppressed people, and that mission has been accomplished." A second point of interest: last week the number of American soldiers killed by hostile fire in Iraq after Bush stood in front of his "Mission Accomplished" banner jumped past the number of soldiers killed by hostile fire during the initial invasion. This is getting ridiculous.    George W. Bush (again)  It's not exactly the throwing of flowers that we were promised by Bush and Cheney pre-war, but, you know... flowers... car bombs... it's close enough for Dubya. Yes, if George W. Bush's lame attempt to pass the buck on "Mission Accomplished" left you confused, his take on the recent spate of car bombings and attacks on U.S. troops in Iraq will make your head spin. According to Our Great Leader, the increase in attacks on American soldiers and international aid agencies is actually a sign of progress. "The more successful we are on the ground, the more these killers will react," said President Brainiac last week. Oh really? So following this logic, at what point can we declare total success on the ground? Hundreds of attacks per day? Thousands? I mean, seriously, I'd like to know, because frankly this whole thing just seems to be getting kinda ass-backwards. First George W. Bush declares Mission Accomplished at the beginning of the conflict, and now he's of the opinion that the more American troops are blown up and shot at, the better we're doing? How bizarre.   Zell Miller  In case you hadn't noticed, we're a partisan website, so we've made a point in the past of excluding Democrats from this list. But it's finally time to tell Sen. Zell Miller to go jump in a lake. Miller announced last week that he would be endorsing George W. Bush for president in 2004 because he is "the right man at the right time" to govern the country. How a serial liar who has put 3 million people out of a job, killed hundreds of American soldiers, and destroyed a foreign country at the behest of his corporate donors by feeding the world a line of bullshit translates to "the right man at the right time" is anyone's guess. But clearly Miller has his reasons - one of them presumably being that he enjoys seeing America thrown into a world of hurt. So if Zell Miller decides that he's going to spearhead a "Democrats for Bush" group going into election season, call him and tell him where to get off. Because as far as we're concerned, Zell Miller is no longer a Democrat.   The Bush Administration  Surprise, surprise - Halliburton is going to be sucking at the teat of Iraq a little while longer. It was announced last week that the Bush Administration is extending Halliburton's no-bid contract to rehabilitate Iraq's oil fields because saboteurs keep blowing up the pipelines. The Army Corps of Engineers hoped to announce the winners of new contracts this month (and yes, Halliburton is in the running) but decided to extend Halliburton's current no-bid contract into next year. Amazing really - the worse things get in Iraq, they better they get for Halliburton. The company just released figures showing its third-quarter revenues up to $4.14 billion from $2.98 billion last year. So I guess making money from the misery of millions is a decent business to be in these days - especially if your ex-CEO is the guy who gets to create the misery in the first place.   L. Dennis Kozlowski  What do you do when your company is on the verge of bankruptcy? If you're L. Dennis Kozlowski, former head of Tyco, you spend two million dollars on a gigantic week-long birthday party for your wife in the middle of the Mediterranean. Jurors in Kozlowski's grand larceny trial saw 21 minutes of a four hour videotape last week, which featured Kozlowski welcoming partygoers to the island of Sardinia, along with "five young women in scanty, diaphanous frocks cavorting around a swimming pool, half-naked male models posing in snapshots with female guests and a performance from a pop star [Jimmy Buffett]." What the jurors didn't get to see apparently included "an anatomically correct ice sculpture of Michelangelo's 'David' urinating vodka," and, "two men dressed as ancient Romans carrying Kozlowski's wife over their heads." The clever part, see, is that Kozlowski managed to get Tyco to cover half the cost of the party because "Tyco business was taken care of as well." Presumably that was done while everyone was taking a break from cavorting and gang-banging. But you know, if there's one thing that makes me feel good about corporate America it's got to be the knowledge that while millions of Americans are losing their jobs, the top 1% are drinking vodka out of ice penises.   Jon Matthews  Has another staunch promoter of "family values" been caught with his pants down? It was revealed last week that conservative talk show host Jon Matthews is under investigation by the Sugarland Police Department for allegations of indecency with a child, according to ABC 13 in Houston, Texas. Matthews has been pulled off the air by KSEV while the investigation is under way, although he is already being defended by Republican congressman John Culbertson: "I just can't even imagine… I refuse to believe it… It must be a mistake..." I mean, a conservative child molester - why, that's unheard of! Preposterous. I know of no conservative in the history of mankind who has preached family values while groping children. It's disgraceful to even think that someone could be that hypocritical.   Hewart Lee Bennett & Stephen White  Meanwhile, two preachers who were previously known for "fire and brimstone" sermons denouncing "fornicators," "whores" and "sodomites" are now better known as, well... fornicators, whores and sodomites up to their nuts in fire and brimstone. Rev. Hewart Lee Bennett and Rev. Stephen White were arrested recently for "soliciting sex with boys under the age of 16," according to gfn.com. Bennett apparently talked dirty to young boys online, but - get this - says he "only described sex acts to gain their trust and tell them about the love of Jesus." White, on the other hand, "approached an unidentified teen boy and asked if he knew of any adult shops in the area selling pornographic videos or magazines. After the boy told him he did not, White told the boy he could 'make some money' by letting White perform oral sex on him." Must be another one of those parables from that weird secret version of the Bible nutcase fundies carry around. By the way, at this point I'd like to say on behalf of Congressman John Culbertson that I just can't even imagine... I refuse to believe it... It must be a mistake.    Raj Patel  Conservatives always seem to be in the process of attempting to roll the clock back to the 1950s, but there's a small town in Florida that's tired of all the talk and is actually doing something about it. Perry, Florida, made the news back in 2001 when a black lawmaker from Maryland was told at a local bar that he would only be served if he sat in back. And last week Perry made the news again when another black man was allegedly told by motel owner Raj Patel that "coloreds aren't allowed in the pool." Patel, who is Indian, said, "Everybody is welcome who pays me. I'm not against any color. My skin is not white, I'm brown." But according to the Associated Press, "The attorney general said he doubted Patel's version, saying the investigation was based on 'multiple witnesses.'" Can somebody please give Florida a call and let them know that this is the 21st Century?   Two Congressional Staffers  There was uproar at the Cannon House Office Building in Washington DC last week when two of Republican congressman John Shimkus's staffers brought a toy gun through a security check point. The staffers had the gun as part of a Halloween costume, and a security officer - demonstrating just how tight security is on Capitol Hill - didn't notice the gun's image on the x-ray machine monitor until the staffers had collected their bags and left. Panic ensued as the building was evacuated and the House of Representatives was forced into recess while security officers attempted to track down the gun-toting "terrorist" and SWAT teams were summoned. The drama lasted about 90 minutes before the red-faced staffers realized what was going on. Just to put this in perspective, if you live in Washington DC you know that you can't get into any government building without passing through a metal detector. So why two people who work in a government building would be so dumb as to try and bring a plastic gun through in a bag is kinda beyond me.   The NRA  And finally: do you want to know who the real enemies of freedom are? Then just head on over to the NRA's website and check out their 19-page list of un-American gun grabbers. The blacklist was discovered recently by gun-control advocates, and boy, if you're a member of the NRA then stand by to get those panties in a bunch because there are some damn scary people on there. Like who? Figure-skater Tara Lipinski, for one. Still not scared? Then you've reckoned without Jerry Seinfeld, who, unless the NRA can stop him, will be coming round to collect your guns any day now along with Catherine Zeta-Jones, Boyz II Men, and the Kansas City Chiefs. Yes, it's a law-abiding gun owner's nightmare come true. Picture waking up in the middle of the night to find Leonard Nimoy sitting on your chest while Doug Flutie and the Central Conference of American Rabbis cart off your prized AK. Makes me break out in a cold sweat just thinking about it.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Uninvited (Acoustic) by Alanis Morrisette ...and now my post... 1. What food do you like that most people hate? coleslaw 2. What food do you hate that most people love? shushi 3. What famous person, whom many people may find attractive, is most unappealing to you? I dunno, I guess I haven't really thought about it. I guess off hand it would be Leo Dicaprio, but I dunno. 4. What famous person, whom many people may find unappealing, do you find attractive? Justin Berfield from Malcolm in the Middle. He plays Reese 5. What popular trend baffles you? Slipper wearing. Why would you wear them to school? I don't get it
     

        
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently Listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser ...and now my post... A new poll from Marist College's Institute for Public Opinion showed that 44 percent of Americans definitely plan to vote against President Bush in 2004, while only 38 percent support his reelection.  
     

        
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: For You to Notice by Dashboard Confessional ....and now my post....  It snowed in Vegas! WOW! LOL. I'm a loser, I know! :-P   
     

        
</post>

<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: When You Say You Love Me by Clay Aiken ....and now my post....    Do you ever feel like your life is like trying to push a fat man off a cliff? Well that is how mine feels right now.  Here is how my Winter Break is going:  All last week was okay, I guess. Christmas was good. I got a lot of cool stuff, including a $50 gift card to Best Buy, which I used today. I also got a $20 gift card to Barnes and Noble from Greg the Goat (loooooooong story for another time). I also went ATVing. The picture of me with all the stuff is in the Pictures section. Other then that, my week went by slowly.  Now onto today:  Okay, so today I woke up about 9:45 and I couldn't breathe, so I sat up and I magically could breathe. Amazing how noses work, isn't it? So then I got up and took a shower. Then I called Stefani but I got the answering machine so I waited like 5 minutes and called her back. It was busy, so I was all UGH! BUSY! Lol. So then I hang up, and she calls right back. So we decide to hang out. She wants to use her Wal-Mart Gift Card (don't even get me started! I didn't buy anything - I'm morally against Wal-Mart. I will explain later if you want). OH! But before that we went to the bank so Stefani could get some money out then we went to Taco Bell. Stefani told me that I might get the job at Taco Bell! She saw her manager looking at my application. She also told me the shim isn't working. She thinks it either got fired or quit. Phew! Now I can work there and not worry about a thing looking at me, lol.   Then we called my mom and I wanted to go to Best Buy. So she comes and gets us and we go to Best Buy. I bought a computer game, which of course won't work on my F-ing computer! Don’t ever buy an HP. They suck! I also bought two Dashboard Confessional CDs and the Clay Aiken CD. All are VERY good. Then we went to DSW and I saw these really cool shoes in the sales rack. They are goofy, but cool. They are brown and Rancho green. I think they are cool. If I get the job at Taco Bell I will go back and get them. Then we went to Barnes and Noble. I didn't find anything, so we went home. I stayed over at Stefani's for a bit and then went home.  My mom picks me up and tells me we are going to the office. I looked at her like WTF? And I asked why and she said because she got a really big bonus. I was like so I can get my car now? And she said no. UGH!  So that was my day. Now can you see why my life is like pushing a fat man off a cliff?  Until next time...
     

        
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Hotel California by Pennywise ....and now my post....    I hope everyone had a Merry Christmas or Hanukkah or whatever you celebrate this time of year. I have a very good Christmas. I got a lot of good stuff. Here is a short list:  Pirates of the Caribbean DVD 505 Stupid Websites (this book is really funny) a Civil War book candy a Sponge Bob Square Pants pillow (which I left in my locker at school). Sorry Stef!   But yea. How was your Christmas/Hanukkah/other? Good? Bad? I hope everyone has a good New Year!
     

        
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Nothing, I know I'm a loser. ....and now my post....   1. Key the first 3 digits of your phone number (not the area code) into a calculator 2. Multiply by 80 3. Add 1 4. Multiply by 250 5. Add the last 4 digits of your phone number 6. Add the last 4 digits of your phone number again 7. Subtract 250 8. Divide by 2 Is this your phone number?  This is cool. It works for me, does it work for you? I'm done posting for the year. I hope everyone has a Happy Christmas and a great New Year.   
     

        
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: What's My Age Again? by Blink 182 ....and now my post....   Why does life have to be a roller coaster ride? Why are there mean people and why do they suck? I got some new hair gel, pomade actually, and it will be WAY easier on my hair. So I put it in and people think that I just got out of bed and didn't do my hair. WTF? It isn't hard like gel, but does the same thing as gel. It is like I can't change ANYTHING about my look or people freak out. This same thing happened when I bleached my hair. Hello people! I did this how many times last year! Please. But moving on to today's events:  Today was interesting. Slow, but interesting. So let's start in French. We played Bloody Fingers, as we normally do, and I was picked like 4 from the end. Why? I dunno. People suck. Are you beginning to see a pattern?   Then I went to Ground School. The one time I actually did the homework, by like reading the book; does Mr. Kelly ask us questions? NO! Ugh! Okay, then I went to American Literature where I forgot my book, AGAIN! Ugh. So we went over Rapaccini's Daughter by Nathaniel Hawthorne. What a BORING story. We ended up talking about how Ms. Nickels (my teacher) got her family stoned at Thanksgiving and action figures. How? I don’t know.  Then Lunch. Lunch was alright I guess, except Kim kept stealing my chicken from my salad!  Then I went to History. We are doing projects. We have been since last Monday. I went last Tuesday. I was so nervous. Joe told me that I stuttered. Oh well, I got an A.  So I had to go to bank from Brummett for CloseUp (the program I'm in for going to Washington DC. More info soon!). So he told me to go to the bank. So I do. Is the banker there? No. Where is she? How the hell should I know? That racist bitch is NEVER there. So I did that then went back to history.  Then I go to Math, and this is when the day gets interesting. I moved up because the dumb beaner who thinks she is black keeps telling us to "BE QUIET!" and stuff like that. So I move up, and does that bitch shut up? Hell no. Grrr.  . But anywayz, we get to the end of class, so I go to the back of the room to shoot the shit with Joe and Asian Sean. So we are standing there talking, and I reach over and grabbed Sean's ass. So what does Sean do? I was thinking he would do it back, thus proving my point that he is gay, but NOOOOOOOOOOOO he reaches over and does the same thing to Joe. Joe is VERY straight. I have never seen Joe that pissed before. Not even when Justin called Meghan a whore. I was like HOLY SHIT! I hope Sean is gay, I would date him. And by date I mean corrupt, lol.   Yea, then I go to French Aide and Leland asks me for my Verb book but I don't have it. I think he likes me, but my opinion doesn't count because I think "everyone is gay." At least that is what Meghan says. Well. I'm gonna go.  Now you know why I say people suck.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Nothing, I know I'm a loser. ....and now my post....  Well, good news from Iraq I guess. We got Saddam. After DNA testing I guess we proved to the world that it was him. But this isn't the end of the war. We are far from it. We all know that we will be there for at least 3 years, if not more. We will also be there with NO ally help i.e.: Russia, Germany, France, etc. I like the ad from my previous post. If there is money for Iraq, where is the money for domestic problems and Afghanistan? Insurgents are rising in Afghanistan. Why? Because the US pulled troops for Iraq. Iraq was dumb. We need to get our priorities straight.  I just noticed a few minutes ago that the war in Iraq is now at $90 Billion +. Wow! Why can't that money be spent on say like SCHOOLS?!?!?!?
     

        
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      While searching the Anti-Bush web, as I always do, I came across MoveOn.org. They have a very powerful message. Check out two of their ads. You will need Windows Media Player to view these.    urlLink      urlLink     Makes you think doesn't it?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Lucky Love by Ace of Base ....and now my post.... So it is Tuesday. Wonderful, wonderful uniform day. Why do they make us wear these? It doesn't signify anything anymore. There are 1200 of us now, why not make the non magnet kids wear a big pink shirt that says: "I'm to stupid to be a magnet student, I attend RHS." I like those. But yea. Lets move onto my day, shall we?  Okay, so the day starts with French. Bloody fingers was fun. We got 65 points or something like that. Then I toddle off to Aviation and take a short quiz on weather. BORING! Then Mr. Kelly puts in yet ANOTHER weather movie. When was this made? 1979. You know those bad movies you watch in science with the bad music and crappy graphics? Yea, this was it. And tomorrow we are gonna watch yet ANOTHER movie made in 1969. Why? Does it teach me aviation? NO. Moving on...  American Literature. Wonderful American Literature. We are learning about Poe and Hawthorne. Oh yea. Fun! But yea. So moving on.... HISTORY. I love history. Why? I don't know why. It is just ....cool..... I guess. lol. Then Math. Boring, as normal. Well, that was just my day.
     

        
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: This Is The Night by Clay Aiken ....and now my post....    Do you have nasty habits that you want to kick?   Life sucks. Why does life have to be so hard? Why can't like be easy? And why can't boys be smart, instead of dumb? Why are boys so dumb? That is the unanswerable question. Boys are dumb, let's face it. I mean, think about it. They always want what is right for them, and damn, why do they have to be so protective of there money? God, just open the damn wallet.  Anywho......moving on to today's events. No much happened. I'm glad it was Friday. We watched Charlotte Grey in French. That is the most boring movie you will EVER watch. It moves to slow, and not enough people die. Lol. I know. I'm bad and evil.   Dez and I were talking about 'Why boys are dumb.':  Ben (9:46:51 PM): Why are boys so dumb? Dez (9:46:54 PM): ok   Dez (9:46:56 PM): i dont know   Dez (9:47:30 PM): you're a boy   Ben (9:48:21 PM): Ah yes. But I'm a boy who wants to be a girl (mentally, not physically, lol) Dez (9:48:21 PM): but your not dumb... but dont you know why they are   Dez (9:48:25 PM): yeah   Dez (9:48:45 PM): i dont know... i guess boys just think irrationally becuz of their wieners   Ben (9:49:08 PM): always thinking with there dicks......typical! Dez (9:49:16 PM): yeah!  Why does life suck?
     

        
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: I Survived You by Clay Aiken ....and now my post....      Do you ever feel like you don't mean anything to anybody? I guess this is my mood and feeling at the moment I guess. I dunno though.  Today was long and boring. In French we did a play about going to Ireland and the Guinness factory. Ann Marie is a little alcoholic. Lol. Then in Aviation, we took a quiz on section B. It was easy, since Mr. Kelly gave us all the answers. Anywho. I guess that is all.   OH! Funny story. Carmen Lee came over to me, and asked: "Do you like Matt Malsteade?" and I said no, but I use to and then she said "Are you gay?!?!?" and I said "Yeah, you are like 9 months behind." Peter then said "You are?" lol. Then she asked who I liked, and I didn't tell her, and Sean is grateful I didn't tell her, or it would be around school that Sean was gay, and he doesn't want that. I do though!    Updated: January 30, 2004 @ 5:50 AM.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Pick up the Phone by Evan & Jaron ....and now my post....    So this weekend I helped at the Habitat site again. We knocked down a concrete wall with sledge hammers. It was fun! Just imagine someone you hate and BINGO! There ya go! Lol. I met Mr. T's son, Karl. He is HOT! Not as hot as Sean, but almost as hot. I was like, DAMN! But then Meghan said he might turn out to look like Mr. T. lol. Oh well. Oh! And he kept like looking at me. It was weird. Meghan thinks he is gay. Oh don't I wish.    So today at school, it was your typical Monday. It went by slow today. I guess because Joe and Meghan weren't there. Meghan's grandpa died, so she went to the funeral. I don't know where Joe was. He might have gone with her. But yea.   So Chesto (principal) took out ALL the soda machines from the cafeteria, and now when we order food we have to give them our student number. Why? I don't know. It will have affects though. Where is the school supposed to get $1500 per month? Not from juice and water sales, I can tell you that. I give Chesto about a month before things are back how they should be. He thought the Student Body got mad when he raised soda's to $1.25. Wait until we relize there is no soda for us to buy. Oh well. Anywho. I suppose I should go. My parental units are home, and my mom will want the computer to write up an offer or something.   OH! Valentine's Day is coming soon. I hate Valentine's Day. Want to know why? I never get anything, nor have anyone to give things to. It is the WORST holiday ever! Everyone is like, OH! I LOVE IT! I hate it. It sucks.
     

        
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Shine by Clay Aiken ....and now my post....    Ever feel like you are being controlled? Do you ever just want to scream, and have it all go away?  Well, my life lately hasn't been great. My dad has the flu, and could have to go to the hospital.   The second semester has started at school. When I get a 4.0 GPA, my parents will pay me $500 cash, and I also get an unlimited gas card.   I can't wait! Stefani doesn't feel that it is right for my parents to pay for gas. I don't know why. I'm going to school, which they help pay for, so I don't know why it makes a difference.  So Monday night, I picked up my car! I'm so happy! Here is a picture of it:     Isn't it purdy? Lol.   Anywho. I guess I am outta things to say. I probably won't write more till Friday. But I dunno.
     

        
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Swords Cross from Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl ....and now my post....    So today we have no school. Today is going to be sooooooo boring! I'm gonna hang out with Stefani, and maybe Jerry, if they want me there. If not, I will just come home. I might watch Pirates of the Caribbean in French or something. Lol. But I dunno. I know I will write more later. Isn't this picture wrong?        
     

        
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Hold You So by Kilt ....and now my post....    Do you ever feel like breaking a window for fun? Have you ever been THAT bored? Well, I'm that bored right now. It is so boring at my house. My mom is at a conference, and my dad is sick.  Today has been, needless to say, BORING. I went to the store with my dad about 9:30 to get three things: shampoo, trash bags, and cough medicine for my dad. It took us like 15 minutes to find the stupid trash bags. They were down the aisle with canned soup. Why? I don't know. Leave it to Food 4 Less to amaze us all.   No one is online. Everyone is out of town. Stefani is working, and I have no license to take the car anywhere. I get to go pick up my car on Monday though, which is good. Stefani is gonna come over and help me move the fountain, which is concrete, to the backyard so we can make room in the garage for my car. I want these accessories for my car. What do you think?       All green of course. What else? Lol. Well I'm gonna go for now. I may write more today.  Please save me from my boredom!
     

        
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Invisible by Clay Aiken ....and now my post....    Finals are over! Thank god! I did my math one today. It was kinda easy I guess. And in 6th, I have Trystin his Dictionary. He thanked me for it, although I would like a different kinda of thanks, but that is another story. Oh, funny story:  I have my TI-83 in my back pocket, because I didn't want to carry it, and I was too lazy to go to my locker, so I went into French before the testing started, and Leland was in there, and he walked up behind me, and he reached out for my calculator, and Mr. Hill said "Don’t grabbed his butt!" and Leland responded with "But I.....I....." and he turned bright red. LOL. And I said "Yea! Don't grab my butt!" Secretly saying in my mind "Please grab my butt!"  Okay, sorry. I love to get side tracked. Now onto today's events. I took my math final, and that was it. I slept most of 6th. It felt good to sleep. And I woke up and Leland was staring at me. Trystin was also playing footsie with me too! Oh yea! I never thought I would get over Quinn, and in a way I never will, but I think I'm coming out of my shell and beginning to move on. I'm flirting again, which is good. I'm so bored. No one is online, and everyone has plans for tonight, except me. Stefani is hanging out with Jerry. Dez is going to California. Nat is going to a party. Jacquie is going to hang out with friends, and then to California. Will is going over to Mike's tomorrow. Ryan is going over to his boyfriend's house tomorrow. So I guess I will just spend it with my mom. I might convince her to go to the AT&T store, so I can get a new cell phone. My current phone:     can't hold a charge to save its life. So I might get one of these:      Like it? I do. But I don't know if she will go for it, or if the store will have it.  Well, I'm outta things to say, so I'm gonna go. I will post more tonight.   NO SCHOOL TOMORROW! OH YEA!  
     

        
</post>

<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Addicted by Simple Plan ....and now my post....    Finals are in the final lap. I have Algebra tomorrow, and that is IT! I will be so happy when this semester and quarter is OVER! Ugh! I found out today that I got an A on my French test. I'm so happy! Shocking that I got an A, since I didn't do like the last 30. But moving on.  Yesterday I had Aviation, Physics Part I, and French. They all went great. Since Physics is my Early Bird, I had two days to do it. I finished today.  Today I had US History, American Literature, and Physics Part II. They all went great. I will be so happy tomorrow though when they are all done.  I can't stop thinking about Will. I don't know why. I know he is with Mike, but still. He is so cute. I haven't felt this way about anyone since Quinn died. Does it mean something? I hope so.  I may write more tonight.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Shine by Clay Aiken ....and now my post....    Ever feel like your life is a wreck? I don't know if mine is, but that is how I feel at the moment. I told Stefani I was gonna do the questions for History and I never did. She got hella pissed off at me. Then I had to carry at least 90+ pounds home with all of my notebooks.   My final in Physics will be difficult, but easy, since we can use our study guides. French is worth 380 points, which is a lot. Keep in mind that each question is worth 4 - 6 points.  But yea. I better go study, so I will write more tonight, before I go to bed.        
     

        
</post>

<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
       The Champion of Mushrooms!  Currently listening to: Blue and Yellow by The Used ....and now my post....    I have come to the amazing conclusion, that life is funny. Why is life funny? Because it has it's ups and downs, but you always end up having fun in the end. I'm out of my depressed mood I have been in all week. Maybe it is because it is Friday or maybe because I have realized that I am trying to hard to find someone. Let that someone come to me. And if they don't, then oh well. I will find someone eventually, right? Right.   Now onto today's events:  Today we were on assembly schedule. Why they schedule an assembly in the same week as the week before finals is way beyond me. Well, that is Rancho's wonderful administration. That or someone forgot to look at the calendar. We just reviewed in mainly all my classes. I actually understand what is going on in Physics. We are working with heat and when stuff vaporizes and whatnot. It is fun! And I know how to do it, which is a plus. We watched Charlotte Grey in French. Thank god it isn't in French. I like to watch movies in French, but I don't like to be tested on them with only knowing them in French, lol.   Then in Aviation, we just reviewed. Shamara (the cheerleader that sounds like a man) puked. Kinda the same way Mr. Kelly did. It was funny. American Lit was just review, and in History we watched Andersonville some more. Math we reviewed and in French Aide I watched the Count of Monte Cristo. That is a good movie. If you haven't seen it, you should. That was my day. I will probably be going to happy hour tonight with the parental units, and study, study, study this weekend. Fun!
     

        
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: First Date by Blink 182 ....and now my post....    Why does life have to be hard? I know it would suck if it was easy, but come on people. Why does life have to be THIS hard? Think about it. Last year sucked. My dad lost his job in 2002, and was unemployed for about 6 months. Quinn killed himself, and the friends I thought I had left me when they found out I was gay. WTF? Sometimes I just hate life. Ever know what I mean?  I now find out Dez has a bf. Good job Dez! I'm happy for you! I hope you love Nathan as much as you love me! But what about Tony?  As for my day: Today was slow. Nothing exciting happened, except Mr. Kelly wasn't here, so we had Mr. Hale teach us. We were supposed to review Chapters 1-3, but he talked ALL PERIOD! Non stop! I was like, "Was this class THAT boring freshman year?!?!?!" Nothing grand to talk about I guess. Nothing interesting happened today. But oh well.  I guess I will go. I'm chatting with Stefani and Ken, so I guess I don't want to keep them waiting long. I might write more later.
     

        
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Jesu, Joy of Man's Desiring by Josh Groban ....and now my post....    Today was my first day back at school. Ever feel like you just need a break? Ever feel like you could just go AGH! And just yell at the world? Well that is how I currently feel, and I'm not quite sure why. I don't know if it is Ryan, or people in general or the stress with school or what. This weekend I was so happy, and then it just went downhill.   So today was my first day back at school since two weeks ago. It was good to be back in the routine I guess. I missed seeing people I hadn't seen in a while, but mostly everyone was just ....there.... I don't know why either. I don't know if this new year was different or what. It just seemed different I guess. Anyway. In Physics we started a chapter on heat. FINALLY! A chapter with a subject I know! And it starts next semester, when grades go back to A's again. French comes next. In French I find out we have a test. JOY! How I love tests...... NOT! All we had to do was explain passe compose and translate sentences from French to English and conjugate verbs, like finir and aller. Wasn't it fun?   Then I went to Aviation. We had to finish our test we started before break. Chapter 5 I think. So we started passing them out and Mr. Kelly went outside and came back in and told one of the other Ben's to go get a janitor, because someone had thrown up. It was him. Mr. Kelly blew chunks, well, not really chunks. More like acid and water. It was gross, and after 2nd people was WALKING in it! Ewww!  Moving on......  Then I went to American Lit. Miss Nickels got a hair cut. It looks nice. We just talked about our review, and we gossiped mostly all period. It was fun. I love it when teachers talk and we get NOTHING done! It is great. Then I went to lunch. Lunch seemed, kinda ....off.... and I don't know why. I guess because Cripple wasn't there. But maybe it was just because it was cold. It was cold WITH my bomber jacket on. Then I went to history and watched yet more presentations. Vince's project sucked. He didn't even stay on the topic. Come on people. Then Joe did his. He did well. Would have done better with Power Point, but he chose not to use it. Oh well, I made my $20. Then was math and French Aide. Trystin wasn't here today. It sucked. But Leland was, but the ass didn't say hi to me.    Well that is all for tonight. Oh and keep a look out for audio blogs. I will be posting soon.    Oh, Nat, don't worry about the Vinni thing. Just call him, and everything will be alright. I promise!   
     

        
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Saints and Sailors by Dashboard Confessional ....and now my post....    Have you ever done anything for money? Would you do anything for money? That's how I feel right now. I feel like I could just scream. I feel so alone. I don't know why either. It is frustrating sometimes. Know what I mean?  Now onto my day: Today was quite boring and depressing. I woke up about 10:15. Cleaning the garage yesterday took more out of me then I thought. Wow! So then my mom asks me if I want to go to the mall with her, and I said sure, so I got in the shower. Then we head off to the mall. My mom took her suit I got her for Christmas back. It didn't fit. Damn! But I was close. She said she will go back. The lady at Macy's was a bitch. She was rude when she found out we didn't have our tag from the suit. Not that we needed it, since we had the dress. What is it? Sales people are rude to customer week?  Then we went to Mervyn's so my mom could find shoes. She found some cool ones on sale for $25. That is always good.  Then we went to the Big Inning to watch the Broncos - Colts game. Damn did the Broncos suck. They lost, big time. And Neal was playing like a damn Raider. Oh well, baseball starts soon. Baseball starts in 7 weeks. Well pitchers and catchers report then. I can't wait till Spring Training.  I'm losing my bet to Tiffany. My bet: The Avalanche will have a better season then the Redwings. The Redwings are 4 games ahead of the Avalanche. But it is a long season.  God, I can't wait to go back to school. I'm so bored, and I miss seeing Trystin.  This is how I feel about Ryan:  . Oh well, maybe he will come around. I'm tired, and the Simpson's are on, so I will write more tomorrow.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Take Me Away by Lifehouse ....and now my post....    Do you ever feel like you are on top of the world? Ever have that feeling like if you jump off of a building, you could fly? Well that is how I feel right now!  I get my car! My parents are getting me a 1990 Honda Accord. It is gold, with a brown interior. It is soo cool! It has less then 75,000 miles too! As a comparison: Our 1988 Subaru Wagon has 180,000+ miles on it, as apposed to my 1990 Honda Accord with less than 75,000 miles. It is owned by a little old lady who drives it to and from the store. I'm sooooooooooooooooooo in love!  So I spent the day cleaning out the garage with my mom. We are making room in our garage, so we can park all three cars. My dad was like:  "I don't know how we can fit three cars in here."  Um, it is a THREE car garage.    "I don't know people that park three cars in their three car garage."  Um, most people don't have as much crap as us.    Come on people. Do your parents collect papers? We have news papers from like last year in a stack in our garage. Does my dad read them? No. Why keep them? It is old news. Anything news worthy, you already know, and has passes. WTF? Why do people have to be so thick? Well, that was my day. OH, Blockbuster.  I hate Blockbuster. Why do I hate Blockbuster? I hate Blockbuster because they lie. They advertise, we will have it in stock or it is free. This is what I thought, so I go and want to rent American Wedding, because I'm a movie nerd and never get to see movies in the theater. But I’m getting better at that. So I yell at the lady at the counter about false advertising, and she said    "Well, it isn't a guaranteed movie." "Why advertise a guarantee if it isn't good on anything?"  She just stood there dumbfounded. Ugh. I hate Blockbuster. I will NEVER go there again. I will add it to my Don't Shop at List. Wal-Mart is also on that list.  Well, that is my day. Tomorrow I think I'm gonna finish my room. You can see the floor now!    Why doesn't Ryan get that I like him?  
     

        
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: The Best Deceptions by Dashboard Confessional ....and now my post....    I'm wishing everyone a happy new year! Lets all hope we can keep out New Years Resolutions! Ha!         
     

        
</post>

<date>17,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Sancta Maria by Charlotte Church ....and now my post....  666, lol...    
     

        
</post>

<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, this is just DUMB! My friend Thomas was kicked off of Centennial's campus for talking about HIV and AIDS. Check out this story and let CCSD know that they were wrong.   urlLink http://www.kvbc.com/Global/story.asp?S=1643567&nav=8H3dKnmN .
     

        
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: NBC Nightly News ....and now my post....    So yesterday I went to the LV Caucus. It was GREAT! Here are some pictures I took.    urlLink LV CAUCUS    More info about my weekend later.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Amici ....and now my post....    Ever feel like we are just pawns and life is a chess board? Do you ever feel like a doll and you don't want to play dress up with your best friend Ken? Well that is how I feel.  I did Habitat stuff Saturday morning, and then I hung out with Josh and Meghan. We were gonna go job hunt but we never quite got around to it, lol. We went to the swap meet to exchange some cheap luggage Meghan got from this Chinese man. His wife got pissed when Meghan took the bags back, lol. Oh well. Then Josh wanted flags, so we headed out east for the outdoor swap meet. We spend an hour looking for it, and when we got there, no one was there. It was hella windy, so we left and went to dinner at Green Valley Rancho, at the buffet. It was good, although we stood in line for an hour. I don't know why, but I guess it was worth it. I didn't want to tell them this, but I kinda had too. Josh is embarrassing in public. He is loud, obnoxious, and yea. But he is still a great guy. I'm just different then he is I guess. Oh well. Meghan and Josh are happy with each other (as apparent with the sounds coming from her room as I get out of the shower at her place.) Oh well.  Then today my parental units and I went to the outlet mall on Charleston and shopped. I need pants. Only two pairs of my jeans fit, but sadly, I didn't find any. Oh well.  We then went to DSW, for shoes. I didn't find any. After that, we went to Borders and got some books. I got a book titled 'Project X', 'The Pleasure of My Company', and 'The Art of War.' 'The Art of War' is for my math project and 'Project X' and 'The Pleasure of My Company' are for my English project. Then I came home, and I am getting ready to call Aunt Mary about her coming to town for my Uncle's Elvis wedding.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Nothing, I know I'm a loser ....and now my post....    got milk?  So this week has been different. Stefani and I are planning our Prom. I know it is in May, but think about it. That is only two months away. We need to get our dresses and tuxes and stuff. And of course, the BLUE limo. Lol  But other then that, this week has gone normal. In Physics we are working on waves. In French we are working on, well French, lol. In Aviation, we are working on weather depiction charts. In American Literature we are doing poetry. In History we are doing the 19th century. In math we are working, on well math. Dur! Well. I'm outta things to say. I'm watching American Idol.     
     

        
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Me (10:35:23 AM): are you gonna watch the superbowl? Brandon (10:35:34 AM): that's today? Me (10:35:43 AM): uh, yea Brandon (10:35:50 AM): oh Me (10:35:55 AM): lol
     

        
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Story of a Girl by Nine Days ....and now my post....  I'm so sorry for not posting lately. I have had so much crap going on it isn't even funny. I spent a week in Washington DC last week. It was sooo fun! I will be uploading pictures later this week. 
     

        
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: All My Life by K-Ci and JoJo ....and now my post....    Bush is such a dumbass. First he said he wasn't going to use September 11th for political gain, and now he is? Why? God he is dumb.  Second of all, here is a poll I saw on his website (why I was there, I don't know).     Um. How about none? God he is dumb. 
     

        
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Standard Lines by Dashboard Confessional ....and now my post....    Isn't that a trippy picture of that cat! It is like HOLY SHIT! THAT CAT CAN READ! Lol.  Me: Hey Dez Pez! Me:  HANSON? [her buddy icon is of Hanson] Dez: hey Dez: yah Dez: haha Me: lol Me: They kick ass Dez: haha hell yeah!  So that has basically been my morning. Oh, I am talking to Matt! Hehe. He is such a cool guy. I want to get to know him better, but I dunno what he wants. He is cool. Not much else is going on in my life. Prom is Sat. I am going with Corinn. I got my tux yesterday for like $102, which was WAY cheaper than Gingiss for Homecoming last year. The limo will be here at 5, dinner is at 6 at the Eiffel Tower Restaurant at Paris. It should be fun. I hope I enjoy Prom. Tickets are $80/couple. It better be good. Lol. Well I am outta things to say now. I may voicepost later today.  UPDATED at 6PM: So today I went to the mall with my mom. She got two pairs of shoes. Today has gone by SO SLOWLY! I think I am getting sick too, which sucks because Prom is Saturday. That reminds me, I have to buy my tickets tomorrow at school. Corinn said something nice. She offered to buy the flowers. That is cool. I am leaving the flowers to my mom, since she was in the floral industry for 20+ years. I am tired, so I am going to eat, then call Matt, and then go to bed. Sorry for not posting lately, I have just been swamped at work.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      We always hear "the rules" from the female side. Now here are the rules from the male side. These are our rules! Please note... these are all numbered "1" ON PURPOSE!   1. Learn to work the toilet seat. You're a big girl. If it's up, put it down. We need it up, you need it down. You don't hear us complaining about you leaving it down.  1. Sunday sports. It's like the full moon or the changing of the tides. Let it be.  1. Shopping is NOT a sport. And no, we are never going to think of it that way.  1. Crying is blackmail.  1. Ask for what you want. Let us be clear on this one: Subtle hints do not work! Strong hints do not work! Obvious hints do not work!  Just say it!  1. Yes and No are perfectly acceptable answers to almost every question.  1. Come to us with a problem only if you want help solving it. That's what we do. Sympathy is what your girlfriends are for.  1. A headache that lasts for 17 months is a problem. See a doctor.  1. Anything we said 6 months ago is inadmissible in an argument. In fact, all comments become null and void after 7 days.  1. If you won't dress like the Victoria's Secret girls, don't expect us to act like soap opera guys.  1. If you think you're fat, you probably are.  Don't ask us.  1. If something we said can be interpreted two ways and one of the ways makes you sad or angry, we meant the other one.  1. You can either ask us to do something or tell us how you want it done. Not both. If you already know best how to do it, just do it yourself.  1. Whenever possible, please say whatever you have to say during commercials.  1. Christopher Columbus did not need directions and neither do we.  1. ALL men see in only 16 colors, like Windows default settings. Peach, for example, is a fruit, not a color. Pumpkin is also a fruit. We have no idea what mauve is.  1. If it itches, it will be scratched. We do that.  1. If we ask what is wrong and you say nothing," we will act like nothing's wrong. We know you are lying, but it is just not worth the hassle.  1. If you ask a question you don't want an answer to, expect an answer you don't want to hear.  1. When we have to go somewhere, absolutely anything you wear is fine...Really.  1. Don't ask us what we're thinking about unless you are prepared to discuss such topics as baseball, the shotgun formation, or monster trucks.  1. You have enough clothes.  1. You have too many shoes.  1. I am in shape. Round is a shape.  1. Thank you for reading this. Yes, I know, I have to sleep on the couch tonight; but did you know men really don't mind that? It's like camping. 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: The Reason by Hoobastank ....and now my post....    Spring Break ’04 kicked ass! I worked Monday – Thursday morning, and then on Friday, we drove to KNOTTS BERRY FARM! It was so fun! Then Saturday we went to the beach (pictures coming soon), and Saturday night we went to the Dodger – Rockies game at Dodger Stadium. It sucked, the Rockies lost. Oh well. No biggy. They won last night, so it is all good. Then we drove back last night. I got to drive from Baker to Home. We ate lunch at Bun Boy in Baker, home of the world’s tallest thermometer. It was cool I guess. Between Baker and Vegas we saw a car on fire, and no, not just the engine, THE WHOLE DAMN CAR! It was cool! Anywho. That was my Spring Break.
     

        
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Isn't this a strange world? I don't know why I say this, I just do. I wonder how long it will be until I change my perspective of the world. My current perspective is that this world is great, with a few bad evils aka: al Qaida, and the Bush Regime. What is it about the Bush Regime anyway? I mean, he wasn't really voted into office, and now he thinks that his shit don't stank, when in fact it does. Why does he think he is hot shit? I don't get it. Oh well, maybe it isn't for me to know anyways. But it you know, why does he think that? I hard earlier posted an audblog, but I deleted it. I will be posting another one soon. I think they are cool. I can post a 4 minute post on my website simple by calling a number, logging in, and creating a voice message. It is really cool, so look for that in the near future.  My life at the moment couldn't be better. I have a great job - data entry at LasVegasHomes.com. It pays really well too. I'm single, which in a way sucks, but think of it this way: I'm not being dragged down by an over controlling person. School is going good, and life is just great. Well, I better get back to work. I will post more later this week. I hope you like the new website layout. I know I do.  
     

        
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: The Reason by Hoobastank ....and now my post....  New post! Yea!
     

        
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Dashboard Confessional ....and now my post....    A jet carrying 308 passengers was forced to make an emergency landing in Ireland on Sunday, after fruit fumes set off its fire alarm system.   urlLink Full story 
     

        
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Yellowcard (thanks Dez Pez!) ....and now my post....    So the government said today that the "credible" threat to the US was a hoax. LOL. The FBI got there intelligent from a WEBSITE. WOW! I'm happy to know that my hard earned money is going to pay for some geek at the FBI going to Google and typing in al Qaeda and calling the first website they find "credible." Why can't they get anything right? I think the directors of the National Security Council, FBI, CIA, and Homeland Security should resign. Save us from more humiliation.         Okay, I'm done. LOL
     

        
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: my mom cry about something stupid at work ....and now my post....    I'M FREE! I'm free from school! Today was my last day at school. Finals start Tuesday. Tomorrow the teachers have to go to class on how to give a test, lol. On Tuesday I have my Physics, French, and Aviation final. Wednesday I have Physics, American Lit, and History, and Thursday I have Algebra II. God I can’t wait for next Thursday at noon. I will be FREE!    Side note: GOD! My mom is being dumb and CRYING about WORK! It is fucking stupid, but anyways...   Today was kinda sad. I mean, they are tearing down Rancho. I know it is for the good, but still. It is Rancho, and it is 50 years old. I guess you would have to go to Rancho to know what I'm talking about. But the new school is going to be pretty cool.   Another side note: God I hate when my dad says "Don't get so defensive" when you get an edge in your voice. He is a fucking joke. My parents are fucking jokes. I can’t wait to go to college, or turn 18 when I can go out till god knows when. But yeah.   I dunno what to talk about. I guess I am just tired of school and stuff. I can't wait to be free.
     

        
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: my mom play the piano ....and now my post....  So I got bored and went online to the construction site of the new Rancho High School ( urlLink www.tatesnyderkimsey.com ) and I found some pictures and a really cool video of what the new school is designed to look like. The movie is below. You have to have Quicktime to view it.   urlLink     Enjoy!
     

        
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
             VOTE RESULTS
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Air America ....and now my post....    I got this email from Amanda from school who got it from her grandma:   Subject: Kerry enterprises  Shortly after reading the following e-mail content, I happened to look at the label of a jar of Heinz sandwich slice pickles. Yep...."Made in Mexico" Check some of your Heinz products.  "Sen. John Kerry keeps talking about U.S. corporations leaving this country and setting up shop in foreign countries, taking thousands of jobs with them. He is right, because that has happened. However, he is trying to blame it on George W. Bush.  As far as I know, Bush has not moved one factory out of this country because he is not the owner of a single factory.  That cannot be said about Kerry and his wife, Teresa Heinz-Kerry. According to the Wall Street Journal, the Kerrey’s own 32 factories in Europe and 18 in Asia and the Pacific. In addition, their company, the Heinz Company, leases four factories in Europe and four in Asia. Also, they own 27 factories in North America, some of which are in Mexico and the Caribbean.  I wonder how many hundreds of American workers lost their jobs when these plants relocated in foreign countries. I also wonder if the workers in Mexico and Asia are paid the same wages and benefits as workers in the United States.  Of course they're not. However, Kerry demands that other companies that relocate should pay the same benefits they did in the U.S. Why does he not demand this of the Heinz Company, since he is married to the owner?  If Kerry is elected, will he and his wife close all those foreign factories and bring all those jobs back to America? Of course they won't. They're making millions off that cheap labor.   So, doing the Democratic thing I do, and started to prove this email wrong. I started by going to Yahoo! Finance and looking up the Heinz stock stuff. Then I clicked on Major Holders. After pulling up this webpage I shocking found the Teresa Heinz-Kerry is NOT a major holder. Here is what I found:    JOHNSON, WILLIAM R. holds 550,086 shares as reported on 22-Sep-03 JOHNSON, WILLIAM R. holds 342,639 shares as reported on 20-Jun-03 BERTASSO, MICHAEL J. holds 97,817 shares as reported on 22-Sep-03 JIMENEZ, JOSEPH holds 74,951 shares as reported on 19-Mar-04 MILONE, MICHAEL D. holds 66,603 shares as reported on 20-Jan-04    Thus proving that Teresa Heinz-Kerry doesn’t own a majority of the company, I then went to the Heinz Company’s website, and pulling up the About Us page, I found that William R Johnson, who owns 550,086 shares of stock, is the Chairmen, President, and Chief Executive Officer of the Heinz Corporation. This proves that Teresa Heinz-Kerry doesn’t run the day to day, or even the company in general.   Ahh. I’m happy! LOL.
     

        
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
        You're a Garbage Pail Kid!!  You're dirty, foul, disgusting, and wrong.  But you're still funny as hell.   urlLink  What childhood toy from the 80s are you?   
     

        
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
        You are a School Boy Kiss!! you're a deprived catholic school boy who needs some action... don't get caught in the locker room!   urlLink  What kind of Hot Boy Kiss are you??  
     

        
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Nothing, I know I’m a loser. ....and now my post....    So I saw Shrek 2. It was FUNNY! "I am Puss......in boots!" LoL. Anyways. Today I just worked and went to see Shrek. It was funny! You really need to see it. I think it was personally better than the first. Oh, and when the credits start, DON'T LEAVE. There is a surprise at the end.  To You Know Who: Congratulations on Graduation. I love you so much, and I hope you take your graduation and do great things with it. I can't wait to see you in August!    Limerick  One very long, boring day,  Jimmy was tickling Ray,  It got out of hand As they rolled in the sand,  And it all got decidedly gay.
     

        
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Am I Missing by Dashboard Confessional ....and now my post....  I wonder how the Bush Administration likes these numbers?      Name    KERRY    Bush    Date      Time/CNN   51%  46%  5/13/04     CNN/UST/Gallup   50%  46%  5/9/04     ARG    46%  44%  5/6/04     AP/Ipsos   41%  44%  5/5/04     Fox/OD   43%  46%  5/5/04     Gallup   49%  47%  5/4/04     Quinnipiac   43%  44%  5/3/04     NBC/WSJ   42%  46%  5/3/04      Interesting isn't it? I now have a limerick. I will be posting a new limerick with every post.  There was a young plumber of Leigh Who was plumbing a girl by the sea. 	She said, "Stop your plumbing, 	There's somebody coming!" Said the plumber, still plumbing, "It's me."  LOL. Any hooters. Today was boring. We didn't do much, except we talked about fellatio. It was funny. For those of you who don't know what it means:  fellatio, fellation -- (oral stimulation of the penis)  I hope this helps. Well I am going to go. I may post more later.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Ben's So Called Radio ....and now my post....   One afternoon when the President is returning from a trip to his Texas ranch, he gets off the helicopter in front of the White House with a baby pig under each arm.  The Marine guard snaps to attention, salutes, and says: "Nice pigs, sir!"  The President smirks and says, "Well, that's where you're wrong, soldier. These are not pigs. These are authentic Texan Razorback Hogs. I got one for VP Cheney, and I got one for Defense Secretary Rumsfeld."  The Marine again snaps to attention, salutes, and replies, "Nice trade, sir!"
     

        
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: XM Radio!!!!! ....and now my post....    I got XM Radio today! It kicks ass! I love it. I especially love America Left, which plays Al Franken and such. Any hooters, I guess that is all. I will post more this week, I promise.
     

        
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
              
     

        
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Billy S. by Skye Sweetnam ....and now my post....    Today was just like any other day. I dunno what made it different. Maybe it was that tomorrow is Ms. Nelson’s last day. She is my Physics teacher. I think she did a good job teaching Physics. She has a prosthetic hip and it slipped, so she is going to take medical leave for the rest of the year.  As you can see, I have changed the layout of the site. I'm working on understanding the new Blogger code implemented, and as soon as I do, I will add my pictures pages with this layout. Until then, there are still at the old address,  urlLink www.bungkwifa.com/bendover/photos.html . I can't wait for this weekend to be here! Tomorrow is pay day! Yeah!  As I was surfing BBC News, Berg's dad blames Bush for his son's death. I also read an article on Aljazeera ( link ) that says that Bloggers think that the video is a hoax. I don't know if you have seen the video, but I have, and it is kinda gross. But Bloggers make the point that no blood drops from his head when it is raised up, which could mean he was already dead. I have included a link to the article. Aljazeera is now in English, lol.  That is all for now I suppose. I may post more later, depending on my mood.
     

        
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Okay, this story is just dumb. How stupid can the Baptist Church get? I don't hate all Baptists, but god damn. Pull your head out of your ASS and move on with your life. The world doesn't revolve around you, or religion.        (May 12) -- Several hundred people showed up Wednesday morning to show support for a local high school in the face of a protest over a play the school put on.  Half a dozen members of a controversial Kansas church were protesting the Las Vegas Academy's production of the play -- The Laramie Project. The play is about the life of Matthew Shepard, a Wyoming college student who was brutally beaten to death for being gay.  Students and demonstrators supported the school while church members held fast to their beliefs that the play promotes a gay agenda.  Shirley Phelps-Roper, anti-gay protester, said, "It's not okay to be gay. There is a God and a day of judgment. You may not live like the devil and expect to die and go to heaven."  The protest ended before classes started Wednesday morning. The last performance of the play was last weekend.        (May 6) -- Students and staff at Las Vegas Academy are responding to flyers being distributed by a church group that says everyone associated with the school will "go to hell."  The Kansas-based church is upset because they say the school is performing a play that promotes homosexuality. Eyewitness News  spoke to an actor in the play and the school's principal.  "It's basically about hatred and not to hate," said Leland Smith. Leland is a student and actor in the Las Vegas Academy's production of The Laramie Project.  Leland Smith: "I feel bad for them. That's their ignorance, not really knowing about our school."  Leland feels bad for members of the Westboro Baptist Church -- a group that's passing out flyers protesting the performance of the play. The flyer says everyone associated with Las Vegas Academy and the Laramie Project will eventually join Matt Shepard in hell. The play is based on Shepard -- a gay man who was beaten to death five years ago in Laramie, Wyoming.  The flyer from Westboro Baptist Church berates and insults the students and staff of Las Vegas Academy: "God hates Las Vegas Academy, the school board and all responsible for leading the kids to lives of sin, shame, and death in inculcating them that it's okay to be gay!"  The church-goers plan on staging a protest at the school next Wednesday. They say the school is performing a play that promotes homosexuality propoganda. The letter says the school is wrong for performing a play about Matthew Shepard.  Leaving this teen questioning -- Ryan Boylan: "How could they be so ignorant?"  Patrick Boylan: "First thing I thought was God, this is religious terrorism."  Patrick Boylan is Ryan's father, but he is also a member of the Nevada Board of Education: "Sure, they have a right to do what they want on public streets and all that stuff. It just doesn't seem right to scare the children."  Voice of Shirley Phelps-Roper: "Those children don't have any fear of God. What's to be imitated. They think they're infallible and invincible."  Stephen Clark, Las Vegas Academy: "One thing I'm communicating across to them is, 'I don't want to validate what they're doing.'"  Stephen Clark is the school's principal and he's been fielding calls from parents and counseling students. "Some of the values we hold dear -- integrity, compassion, respect," he said.  Clark is asking students and parents to stick to what they're doing and ignore the protestors when they arrive next Wednesday.  Principal Stephen Clark: "Of course I'll have all my administrative staff, my support staff, we'll have teachers out there, school police has been notified, Metro has been notified."  Leland Smith: "I also feel that being part of The Laramie Project, that we have to show others in the school how to deal with this."  The actors say they have been getting good crowds at their performances and they now expect even more people to show up, which they say will only increase the message of tolerance.  So now the school waits until next Wednesday.  Patrick Boylan, father and member of the Nevada Board of Education: "I'm going to be there. Others shouldn't be afraid, I'm going to be outside that school."  The school's principal says this experience can be viewed as educational. He says the children have learned about bigotry in the classroom, now they'll see what it looks like in action.  Westboro Church says it will contact authorities to make them aware of the protest. Eyewitness News tried contacting the school district and school district police for their reaction -- they did not return our phone calls. 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is just sick. Can't the Bush Administration get ANYTHING right?   urlLink http://www.drudgereport.com/iiraq3.htm 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Hey! Look at this! New site layout. I hope you like it. My pictures are coming soon!
     

        
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Alla Luce Dal Sole by Josh Groban ....and now my post....  So Prom went good. Corinn looked nice, as did Stefani and Gordon. We had dinner at the Eiffel Tower Resturant, which was excelent as always. Then we headed off to Prom. It was cool inside the LV Villa. It was kinda small though. Damn did Liberace know how to live. His bathtub was HUGE! Well, I have posted pictures online. I hope you like them. Another post is coming soon after I get the pictures off the dig. cam. I GOT MY BUNGKWIFA license plates!?!?!?!?!?!?!   urlLink  PROM 2004  
     

        
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Sky Harbor   urlLink Live ATC Feeds  
     

        
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
          How to make a Ben        Ingredients:   1 part competetiveness  3 parts crazyiness  5 parts leadership        Method:  Add to a cocktail shaker and mix vigorously. Top it off with a sprinkle of emotion and enjoy!       urlLink Personality cocktail  From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com 
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
       
     

        
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Meet Virginia by Train ....and now my post....   I found this at  urlLink BizStone.com . It is hella funny!  One sunny day in 2005 an old man approached the White House from across Pennsylvania Avenue, where he'd been sitting on a park bench. He spoke to the U.S. Marine standing guard and said, "I would like to go in and meet with President Bush." The Marine looked at the man and said, "Sir, Mr. Bush is no longer president and no longer resides here." The old man said, "Okay" and walked away.  The following day, the same man approached the White House and said to the same Marine, "I would like to go in and meet with President Bush." The Marine again told the man, "Sir, as I said yesterday, Mr. Bush is no longer president and no longer resides here." The man thanked him and, again, just walked away.  The third day, the same man approached the White House and spoke to the very same U.S. Marine, saying "I would like to go in and meet with President Bush." The Marine, understandably agitated at this point, looked at the man and said, "Sir, this is the third day in a row you have been here asking to speak to Mr. Bush. I've told you already that Mr. Bush is no longer the president and no longer resides here. Don't you understand?" The old man looked at the Marine and said, "Oh, I understand. I just love hearing it." The Marine snapped to attention, saluted, and said, "Yes Sir. See you tomorrow."   
     

        
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: 99 Luftballons by Nena ....and now my post....   So yeah. I turned in my time sheet today. Pay day is Wednesday! Yeah! I’m so excited. LOL. I’m a dork. Zen and I are going to hang out on Wednesday. That should be fun. Um, what else. Oh, Lena is gonna help me install speakers I am going to buy at Fry’s on Wednesday or Thursday, then on Friday it is off to Montana for a week. I have heard Montana is quite boring. What is the worst that happens? I’m bored? LOL. But yeah. I am outta things to say so I am going to go. I may post later.
     

        
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      BeingKenny (8:24:15 PM): I would call your cell but it's a waste, you never want to talk really, and you NEVER call me back. You are the king of all those who are flakes. (sometimes) I just wish you wouldn't tell me something and never hold to it. trifidpath (8:24:41 PM): Um, okay. Fine I'm a flake trifidpath (8:25:40 PM): oh, my mistake the King of all Flakes BeingKenny (8:26:12 PM): HEHEE! BeingKenny (8:26:17 PM): Admiting it is the first step.  And this is a so called "friend".
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser ....and now my post....   I just saw Fahrenheit 9/11, and HOLY SHIT! It is a GREAT MOVIE! It fires you up! It is super! If you haven't seen it yet, you should, and I just read a thing that says its first day it made an estimated $5 million!!!!! Take that George! Hahahahahaha! But yeah! I am probably going to see it again with Anton and maybe Leffner. Now my fav quote from the movie:   "If you fool me once, it's on ......................................... you. You can't fool me again!" 
     

        
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
        The Bush Administration thinks is okay to compare the Democratic Party to ADOLF FUCKING HITLER! WTF? Check out his new web ad, and then call him and let him know it is wrong!   urlLink Click here to watch - Windows Media Player   Call him - 202.456.1111 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Somewhere I Belong by Linkin Park ....and now my post....   Isn’t that a scary ass picture of her? LOL. She is scary anyway. “Monica called the former president's account of their relationship dishonest and said he is a "revisionist of history" who has missed an opportunity to undo some of the damage their entanglement caused her.” *as reported from the Daily Mail, London*  I find that funny. LOL. Anywho. I worked today, set up a printer, then I came home and found out I have a potential job for another artist. That is cool! LOL. Well I am outta things to say. Zen and I may hang out, but I dunno.
     

        
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Is there happy hour tomorrow? No, theres sad minute.
     

        
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      As another long week has ended, this question was asked to you:  "Are you Democrat or Republican?"  and you voted like this:  Democrat = 42% Republican = 50% Other (Libertarian) = 8%  Why is it, me being a Dem, I have more Republicans reading my site? LOL. I have archives this poll, and I now have a new one! Please vote. I will try and keep this one on a weekly basis from now on (but no promises).
     

        
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Only One by Yellowcard ....and now my post....   So I have done nothing but drive, and drive that endless road of boredom. I am so bored. No one wants to hang out, or can't hang out. And when I do drive across town, nothing ever happens, and I ended up wasting gas and time for nothing. Let's take last night for example. I drove to the god damn strip to hang out with Will, and his best friend, who was meeting up with this dyke. That was okay, but then they had this cross dresser, which just grossed me out. I don't mind guys doing that, it is just weird. You have a penis, why not act like it! If you want to be a girl, get a freaking sex change for god's sake. Damn! Then today I hung out with Nat and her friend, and Nat was going to hook me up with this bi kid she knows, but NO! He wasn't there. Oh well. No big deal. I just will deal with the fact that I am doomed to be single until god knows when. Oh well. Good news though: I saved a bunch of money on my car insurance by switching to Geico. *I like the sarcasm in there. Don't you?*
     

        
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      God I am bored!!! Someone come rescue me!!!!!!
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This was a headline on Google News:  Rumsfeld OKd harsh treatment of suspects in U.S. war on terror  Here is the story: urlLink  http://www.thedesertsun.com/news/stories2004/national/20040623010000.shtml   Can the Bush Administration get ANYTHING right? I think it is time Rumsfeld RESIGNS!!!
     

        
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Feeling This by Blink 182 ....and now my post....  Isn’t it funny how when people say to call them, they are never there? I love shit like that. It is great. So I uploaded all of my pictures from Texas to Snapfish. I will post that Album online soon. I want to hang out today with somebody, lol. But NO one is online, or can do anything, and it is really bugging me. Oh well. Good news on the work side though, I get to set me own hours! That is good. Meghan is trying to hook me up with this guy at her work, and yeah. Well that is all for now. I might Voice Post later.\
     

        
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Last Comic Standing on NBC ....and now my post....    so I am back from Texas. The funeral went okay, and we also go to attend my dad's aunt Becky, who died in the 70s, daughters wedding. It was cool. She had a great wedding. I took a ton of pictures, so look for those on  urlLink DeviantArt  soon. I dunno what else to say so I am going to go. I might post later tonight, or I will Voice Post tomorrow.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Come Around Again by Jet ....and now my post....    So my dad's Aunt died on Tuesday. We are heading out to Texas today. It is kind of sad, but we knew it was coming. She was fighting cancer for 5 years. But on a happy note I got my license! I hung out with Joe, Meghan, and their friend Erik till like 1 in the morning. I slept in till about 9:30, which is a long time for me, lol. Well that is about it. If I get to a computer at all this weekend I will post, if not, I will voice post. So until then, I am out like a fat kid in dodgeball.
     

        
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: My Girl by The Temptations ....and now my post....  I have changed the site design, and have purged most of the 2002 posts. They are all online, if you want to read them at www.bungkwifa.com/bendover/old/2002
     

        
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Hold You So by Kilt ....and now my post....    Look at these numbers! It is great! Let’s just hope Kerry can hold onto them until November.  Poll -- Date -- Kerry -- Bush  Fox News -- June 9 -- 45 -- 43 LA Times -- June 9 -- 51 -- 44 Gallup -- June 8 -- 50 -- 44 Zogby -- June 7 -- 44 -- 42 ARG -- June 3 -- 48 -- 46
     

        
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Nothing, I know I'm a loser ....and now my post....    I just got back from Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban. It was hella good! If you haven’t seen it yet, you should. I LOVED it. I liked this one way more than the other two, maybe because it was funnier or something. I dunno. But it wasn’t as true to the book as the first two, but that is what you get with another director. Anywho, I give this movie  , which is what it deserves!
     

        
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
        German MPs are furious that a flag from the Reichstag parliament building has been sold... to a brothel.   The madam of the bordello said she was delighted to have acquired the national symbol and would be flying it over her place of business.   The flag had been put up for sale by the government in an internet auction to help it raise funds.   Only after the winning bid had been accepted did the organisers find out who had paid the 3,350 euros ($4,020).   Christine Schmittroth, 42, made the highest offer of the 29,636 received.    The German newspaper Bild ran the headline "Should the Reichstag flag be allowed to wave above a whorehouse?"   It showed a photo of two of the brothel's prostitutes - in just their knickers - saluting the flag on the roof of the establishment.   But the new owner said her building in the eastern city of Halle was a fitting home for the 6.5 by 4.5 m (21ft by 15 ft) emblem.   "The guests think it's a great idea," Ms Schmittroth said. "It's obviously an honour to have this kind of flag."   She said the new acquisition would not only lend dignity to her business, it was a patriotic gesture.   'Scandal'   "I know that the country is massively in debt," she said.   "It's obviously a way of helping the state back on its feet, even if it's just a drop in the ocean."   But parliamentarians were not amused.   "The Bundestag flag does not belong above this establishment," Christine Scheel of the Green party told Bild.   "It is a scandal for Germany," added an unnamed MP from the conservative opposition Christian Democratic Union.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: It's All Because of You by 98 Degrees ....and now my post....    So I am back from Denver. It was alright, except it was HOT! I went to the mountains to get cool, not HOT. It was gross. Anywho…I am back now. I went to Wet n’ Wild yesterday. It was fun. I got hella sunburned though. That kinda sucks. Anywho… I guess that is all. I might be doing voice posts more, now that they are free. Those thingies are hella cool. But yeah.  Ronald Regan was laid to rest today. That was sad. It is my first, but not last, Presidential death and funeral. Mrs. Reagan looked sad and drained. I would be too if I had to mourn for a week. Gov. Arnold was at the burial in Cali. That was cool. Well I'm done.
     

        
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      If you could vote, who would you vote for?  Kerry (4) - 66% Bush (2) - 33% Undecided (0) - 0%  Total Votes: 6
     

        
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Broken Vow by Josh Groban ....and now my post....   urlLink    
     

        
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Nothing, I know, I'm a loser ....and now my post....  I have spent $250.55 since 6/13 on gas and my car gets an average of 22.25 mpg, and I spend an average of $2.01 on gas. I have had a total of 11 fill ups equaling 124.4 gallons of gas. That means I have driven over 2600 miles since the 13th of June. Holy shit! There ya go Mr. President! I hope this makes your friends at Big Oil and OPEC happy! 
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: The Best of Me by The Starting Line ....and now my post....  49 days until I turn 18! God I can't wait. It is kind of scary to think about it. I mean, in 49 days I will no longer be a child, but an adult. I can legally buy cigarettes. I can vote (John Kerry for President!). I can stay out past cerfew (not that I will, lol). Wow! How time flies!  
     

        
</post>

<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Broken Vow by Josh Groban   ...Who is by the way, going to be playing at Mandalay Bay August 21st ... ....and now my post....  So I just got back from a Air/Helicoptor/Boat Tour of the Grand Canyon. It was so cool. I loved it. I will post pictures later. 
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Alejate by Josh Groban ....and now my post....  Ugh! Sometimes I just want to scream, I HATE MY PARENTS! Last night is one of those nights. My mom was drinking more than normal, which is okay, because she is about to become the new Managing Broker of Coldwell Banker, which is big news! So after the bar, they went to the baseball game and drank, yet more beer. So I go to leave and I'm driving down Washington and she is like "How fast are you going?" and I said "45" and she said "Um, its 35" and I said "Okay?" Then I get to a light, and slow because it is red, and then it turns green so I accelerate to 45 again, and she said "It is STILL 35!" Then I get home and I just want to sleep because I'm tired, and the bitch has to odasisty to tell me that I am a bad driver and then she goes into this 30 minute speech about me and accidents and shit, and how I have no respect for her and all this bull shit. God I hate my parents. They are so dumb. I wish I was 18 so bad!   
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Cold Hard Bitch by Jet ....and now my post....  Sorry I haven't posted in forever. I have been really busy with work, and friends, and college searches, and what not. I am back though! I am working on a new poll and a new site design among other things. I am working on getting my car fixed up, but adding a new sound system from Meghan's friend Samik (I think that is how you spell his name) for like $200. I just hope I don't fuck it up or something. LOL. I didn't know owning a car would be so expensive. I have spent $230.75 on gas for my car alone since June 13. That is a lot of money, but my car does get 23.43 mpg, or atleast that is the latest one. I use VegasGasPrices.com to keep track of how much I spend and stuff like that. It is pretty cool when you think about it.    Anton and I went to First Flight yesterday to look at stuff we are going to need to by for flight lessons next year, and we met a really cool guy (and hot at that) named Shawn. He went to Rancho and graduated in 2002. He took us out to their new Diamond Star. It has an all glass cockpit. It only has 38 hours on it, TOTAL! It smells like a brand new car. It was so cool. I am going to go there and have Shawn be my instructor or my IR (Instrument Rating) training.  Speaking of which, I need to go get my physical, and take my FAA written test. That should be an adventure. Well I am going to go. I will post more often, I promise, even if it is a Voice Post here and there.  
     

        
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Back Home by Yellowcard ....and now my post....  Hell yeah! Marriage is protected! Bush and his stupid ass man/women marriage shit didn't pass the Senate. That teaches him to make it a fucking re-election thing. He is such a dumb ass. Yes Mr. Ashcroft, I called him a FUCKING DUMB ASS! Go suck eggs you dumbshit! LOL
     

        
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: You're a God by Vertical Horizon ....and now my post....  So summer is blowing by. I don't know what I am going to do. I can't wait to go Back-to-School shopping. I'm a dork, I know. But I love the smell of new backpacks, and paper and new folders. LOL. I have a feeling my feelings for someone arn't going noticed. They are, but I don't think this person believes me. I dunno if he is going to come visit me, but I know I am going to visit him in March. I hope he comes visit me. Anywho. My July 4th was FUN! I almost blew myself up! We had artillery shells, and the guy whose house we were over at had one to many beers, ok, about 4 too many beers, and he was putting the wrong artillery shell in the wrong tube, which caused the tube to explode, out towards us. LOL. It was fun though. I love Montana. I am going to apply to MSU and the University of Montana. Well I am outta things to say, so I might voice post last today. I wish Noe would called me though. Him and I haven't seen each other in FOREVER and he won't return my phone calls.  
     

        
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Question: Are you going to see Fahrenheit 9/11?  Answers:  Hell yes - 17% No! - 33% Already have! - 50%  New poll is online. Check it out.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      DaKine Band Geek (3:13:43 PM): wanna get diz shyt over wit trifidpath (3:13:47 PM): oh please trifidpath (3:13:51 PM): and stop talking like an asian DaKine Band Geek (3:14:02 PM): omfg DaKine Band Geek (3:14:13 PM): i type lyke dis now DaKine Band Geek (3:14:15 PM): i just do DaKine Band Geek (3:14:16 PM): lo DaKine Band Geek (3:14:17 PM): lol trifidpath (3:14:19 PM): it is gay and dumb trifidpath (3:14:23 PM): and it is hard to read trifidpath (3:14:33 PM): JuSt LiKe ThIs ShIt DaKine Band Geek (3:14:33 PM): im sorri DaKine Band Geek (3:14:37 PM): i can read it trifidpath (3:14:44 PM): it is fucking dumb trifidpath (3:14:58 PM): Is it that hard to type normal?
     

        
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
        urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Currently listening to: Lasting Impressions by The Starting Line ....and now my post....  That, alone, is a weird ass combination. The SS and Harry Potter, LOL. I got a couple new books on Saturday. I got  JackBoot: A History of the German Soldier 1713 - 1945  and  The Order of the Death's Head, The Story of Hitler's SS . They both seem quite interesting. I have read so much of  Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix . I am on Chapter 23, which is good for me, being that it took me 4 months to read  The Presence of My Own Company  which is only like 150 pages.  But yeah. I should be finishing Harry Potter sometime this week then I can start  JackBoot  or  The Order of the Death's Head . I wonder how big my file is with the FBI or Homeland Security. Think about it. How much have I dissed Bush, Ashcroft, the US Government, plus I support Kerry, and I have just posted online that I am reading books about Nazi Germany. Oh well. Who knows. That is all for now. 
     

        
</post>


</Blog>