<Blog>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Entry originally posted on 8 August 2003 .  This is not a journal in the traditional sense of the word. This is an exploration, a new beginning mapped out through language and metaphor. There are a great many changes that are taking place in my life. Tommorrow, I will become a mother to a tuxedo cat named Demeter. In two weeks, I will be starting graduate school, embarking on a life-long journey into the world of academia. My friend, Julius has joined the Navy and will be shipped off to basic training next week. Lots of changes.  So, this space is a reflection of those changes, the need to write and think beyond the traditional weblog, livejournal, or daily journal. This space will be composed of ideas, broad themes, academic pursuits, and the occasional antedote about graduate school and life, in general.  There will not be an archive section, because the purpose of this space is to write and live in the present and not rehash the past nor to dwell on the future.   Right now, I am walking in darkness.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "For the love of God is broader that the measure of the mind &nbsp;And the heart of the Eternal is most wonderfully kind." &nbsp;-&nbsp;Our Lady of Mount Carmel Hymn  Michael was the first openly gay man that I met in life. Every day after World Literature we would walk to the college cafeteria and eat lunch together, sometimes studying for a test, but mostly we discussed his sexuality and his faith. I was curious about him, about how he could be both gay and Christian. I grew up in a Southern Baptist tradition that labeled homosexuals as deviants who were out to corrupt Godde-fearing people. Listening and learning about life through the eyes of scared adults, anything and everything can be painted as black or white, right or wrong, and good or evil. When you are a child, it is hard to see the that the world is comprised of multiple shades of grey. Therefore, it is easy, too easy, to judge others for their differences, because you are not yet comfortable in your own skin.  At a time when I was advocating at the top of my lungs against institutionalized Christianity, Michael was advocating in favor of the church. It baffled me that he did not consider it a paradox, a contradiction, or an oxy-moron to be a gay man and a Christian. I did not understand how he could support and participate in an institution that stated that Godde hated him for who he loved. Michael told me that he believed that Godde is merciful, kind, and loving, rather than a vindictive deity that is pissed at the world. "Sometimes the people in charge of the religion," he said, "get so wrapped up in the rules that they forget about the message. The message of Godde, of Christ, is ultimately about love for your fellow man." A few weeks later, Michael broke down another barrier of prejuidice that resided inside me. He told me that he was HIV positive. I remember that we had been sharing a basket of french fries and I was paralyzed with fear at the thought of contracting the disease. Now, I realize that it was a naive and foolish fear, but at that time it was a life-altering experience, because it showed me that who you sleep with is insignificant in the grand scheme of life.  I never saw Michael after that semester. I tried to track him down several times, but never succeeded and I have moments when I wonder if he is even still walking among us. I am convinced that he was an angel, a messenger sent to me by Godde to teach me about compassion, honesty, and love. In light of recent events that have taken place within my community of faith, I have thought about my friendship with Michael more and more and I often wonder what he would think of all this controversy surrounding a gay man that wants to bring people closer to Godde. To me it is clear that Godde places people in our lives to teach, inspire, and make us better human beings. Godde does not discriminate and I am very proud of the Episcopal church for recognizing that truth by ordaining Gene Robinson. I will stand by my church and my faith, regardless of the political ramifications that come from this decision. It is my firm belief that, eventually, we will all have to answer for our actions. To the individuals that are quick to suggest that Gene Robinson will be punished by Godde for his relationship with a man, may I remind you all that casting judgement is also considered to be a sin. Instead of pointing fingers, learn from this man. Open your hearts and embrace the message that is being sent to you.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A couple of years ago, I wrote a short story entitled, "Faith is a Funny Thing." I wrote this story at a time in my life when my quest for spiritual direction was beginning to resemble a fruitless search for a needle in a haystack. In the story, a young woman find solace in a dusty cathedral, the very institution that she spent years denouncing. It was a piece that would foreshadow my return to the church in the years to come.  I was a spiritual pilgrim for the span of a decade, researching and practicing a variety of religions. I attended a service at a Jewish synagogue, read Thich Nhat Hanh's  Living Buddha, Living Christ , held a full moon ritual in my living room, and attended Catholic Mass on a Sunday afternoon. In Yann Martel's  The Life of Pi , the main character, Pi, practices a multiplicity of religions and sees no conflict in his syncretism. Halfway through the book, Pi and his family are walking through town and are approached by the leaders of the local temple, church, and mosque. Each leader tells Pi that he must chose a religion to practice. He can be a devout Hindu, Christian, or Muslim, but he can not practice all three faiths at the same time. Pi remarks that all he wants to do is love God. The church leaders are speechless at the simplicity of that statement.  I love to tell people the story of my return to the church. I tell them that I am a Christian because of a conversation that I had with a Pagan. My good friend, Loria, listened to me rant on and on about my spiritual crisis until finally she told me that there was no shame in being Christian. She reminded me that there are a lot of interpretations of what it means to be a Christian, that Jesus was a profound teacher and prophet, and that a great deal of beauty remains in the Christian tradition. You just have to find a community that you feel comfortable attending. I did.  I am an Episcopalian. I am an open-minded, syncretic, goddess-loving, liberal, Celtic Christian-Buddhist. I believe that Jesus was sent to the Earth to teach and inspire humankind. I believe that Godde is both masculine and feminine and that He/She resides in every single heart that beats on this planet. I am addicted to Sufi poetry, Buddhist philosophy, and Celtic rituals. Religion, faith, is not about the rules, but what road the heart travels. If our motive in life is to love Godde, regardless of the form that being/spirit takes, then does it really matter how we go about expressing that love? My answer is no, it does not matter. Rituals, words, and theology are wonderful things until they begin to place limitations on a person's soul. In the end, what matters the most is how that person uses their faith in the world. Their actions towards other human beings are a reflection of their interpretation of Godde.  The rest is just ashes and dust.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I believe in eating. I think women especially have this fear of eating, and I think there is a whole euphoric plane you can rise to when you have a good meal. You sit down and with every bite you honestly just say thank you. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;(Tori Amos)  I was eight years old when I went on my first diet. I have this memory of standing on the scales in the pediatrician's office and hearing the doctor tell my mother that I was fat. As an adult, I look at pictures taken of me during that time and I often wonder what the doctor was thinking. I looked like a healthy, active eight year old girl. My mother immediately put me on a diet. She gave my grandmother the strictest orders not to let me eat anything other than cantaloupe for a snack. Nan took pity on me after the second week of scarfing down cantaloupe; she gave me cookies and ate the fruit herself. I have not eaten cantaloupe since that summer.  My weight haunts me. It speaks to me, nit-picks me in the guise of voices from the past; Lance Crane telling our fifth grade classmates that there would be no more ice cream left once I went through the serving line, the constant pressure of being stick thin in high school, and my best guy friend from college telling me that men did not like girls with guts and if I wanted a boyfriend then I would have to lose weight, because no guy would want me otherwise. These are the things that I think about when I am in the presence of a man, even if that man is my lover. I know that it does not do well to dwell on the past, but when you spend your life hearing that you are less because you are more, it is hard to believe that beauty resides within your body.  I do not blame my mother for her obsession with my weight. It seems that she too was contantly struggling with her self-esteem in that realm. In her mind big was a simple translation for ugly and so I can not hold her actions against her, because she was suffering from the same societal ideals of beauty. She was struggling to feel beautiful and she wanted me to not have that struggle. It amazes me how many beautiful women, who I am surrounded by on a daily basis, think that they are hiddeous. I read my livejournal, talk to my co-workers, listen to my friends; all of them think that they are less than wonderful, because this world, this culture tells them that they are worthless unless they have Sarah Jessica Parker's body, a body that has no curves, very little cleavage, and is nothing but skin drawn taunt over bone. How is that beautiful?  I stand in front of the mirror naked and I like what I see. I walk around my apartment without clothes, because I am, finally, learning to be comfortable in my own skin. It has nothing to do with being sexy, although if you ask me I will tell you that I am sexy, and everything to do with feeling at ease with the woman that I have become. Yes, I want to lose a few more pounds, for health reasons. Next week, I am going back to the pool and swimming laps, because I miss the feel of the water between my thighs and the burning in my lungs when I am holding my breathe. I want to, once again, be addicted to the feel of gliding through the water. I used to swim two miles non-stop, the equivalent of 72 laps in an Olympic-size pool, and I want that to happen again.  Until then, I will continue to stand in front of the mirror and celebrate my hips that could bring children into this world with great ease, my breasts that are full and lovely and tinted at the tips with a shade of pink, and my back, which is smooth and, in my opinion, flawless. I am a work of art, because Godde made me. As women, we must learn to embrace ourselves and not fall victim to the societal contructs of beauty. If society had its way, I would be the size of my letter-opener, quiet, docile, and submissive.  No. Fucking. Thank You.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This one is for you, Dad.   I want to talk about censorship. I want to talk about what happens when you get home after a hard day and find that you father has left a message on your machine, telling you that he read your website and that he thinks that using the "f-word" to make a point is very inappropriate. If it were any other person, I would launch into a lecture about my right to free speech, free assembly, and the academic concept of language reclamation. However, when it is with my father, confrontation seems more difficult, because I was daddy's little girl long before I was a feminist.  When you plant your feet, heart, mind, and soul under the banner of feminism, loving men reaches a level of frustration that is unparallel to any other experience. There are a great number of men who continue to identify feminism as an anti-male campaign. This is a lie. The complexity with feminism and my relationship with my father is that it is difficult to play out simultaneous roles. I can no longer play the role of dutiful daughter, because the woman inside me is demanding justice. I can no longer pretend that my father is a paragon of perfection, because humans are flawed. For any woman who once thought that her father walked on water, it is a hard lesson to learn when you discover that you are a disappointment to the man who gave you life.  I am sorry that I disappointed you, Dad. I am sorry that you think there is hypocrisy in my lifestyle because I use vulgar language and then call myself a Christian, but I will not censor myself for anyone, especially not for you. You were the person who taught me to be strong, to never settle, to always be true to myself, and to believe that I could do anything that I put my mind to. Now, you are telling me that the way that I conduct myself is inappropriate and even though you do not verbalize it, the insinuation in your message is this;  the man who I adore most in the world is ashamed of me.   That is a bitter pill to swallow, even for the most ardent feminist. I still remember what it felt like to be the pride and joy in your life and thought it sounds selfish -even to my own ears- it hurts to even consider the possibility that those feelings are no longer present in your heart when you think of me.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday evening, I went to church for the first time since my confirmation in June. It is pathetic and sad, how distracted I became this past summer. Lust overcame my heart and I pulled away from Godde, deserting my faith for the simple pleasures of the skin. Yet, when the inevitable happened and that man disappeared from my life, I found myself clinging to my faith like a life-raft. Godde became my glue and she held me together during that horrible time, when I felt him slip through my fingers. Godde continues to hold me together as I am writing these words.  It felt like coming home when I received communion. I could feel this overwhelming sense of purpose and direction flood through my body, melting into my soul. When I tasted the bread, for the first time in months, it had a dry bitter flavor, but it connected me with the others in the church. When I drank the wine, I could feel the blood of Christ renewing me, strenghtening me, preparing me for the road ahead. Catholics believe that the Eucharist involves the process of transubstantiation, where the bread and wine are, literally, the body and blood of Christ. Episcopalians recognize this belief, but tend to view the Eucharist as a symbolic act, rather than a literal one.  In my opinion, Christianity is about the blessing of this sacrament. Long before there were numerous denominations, the early Christians were meeting in secret to receive bread and wine. They risked persecution, even became martyrs, for this simple act. The Eucharist is an invisible rope that, through this acknowledgement of the sacrifice of Christ, binds Christians to one another.  Growing up in a Southern Baptist tradition, I received communion during two services a year, Christmas and Easter. I never considered communion to be an active part of the faith and when I started attending services at the Episcopal church, I thought it strange that Episcopalians received the Eucharist every single Sunday without fail. Now, I can no longer imagine going to church and not receiving communion before I go out into the world. It is the ultimate business card,  please, take our Savior with you. His body and blood are yours, if you wish to carry it inside of you . It is an incredible gift.  This is the reason that I am a Christian. The Eucharist brought me comfort when my relationship with Gene was falling apart. I know that there are a number of theological interpretations within the world-wide Christian community, so many that at times it seems as if that community will fall apart. The Eucharist is what binds us together in the face of adversity and change. It is an integral part of the faith. It is what brings Christians back into the church, even after they have been gone for days, weeks, months, and even years.  It is a blessing. It is home.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fortune cookies are beautiful things. I get excited, like a school-girl in a candy shop, at the very thought of what the Fates are contemplating sending in my direction. I hold on to my fortunes, those little paper notes that following in the wake of a simple cracking of a cookie.  I have it taped to my computer monitor, this one fortune that reminds me to savor life and live for the moment.  You will discover the truth in time . I meditate on these words every single day, searching for a better understanding of what they mean in relation to my life. At first, I thought the note was a message from Godde about my ex-boyfriend, putting me at ease about our troubled relationship, letting me know that we would overcome our differences and move forward together. How naive was I, to think that I knew the meaning of truth, the meaning of time?  There are moments in my life, where I feel like I am in a rush to learn everything at once. I worry that I will run out of time and that I will never discover the truth about myself, this world, and Godde. I obsess over the fear that I will never find a safe, comfortable, loving relationship with a man. There are so many items that occupy my mind, that drive me to distraction. It is only my faith, my love for Godde, that allows me to take a deep breath and force these thoughts out of my mind. I remind myself that there is a plan, a purpose.  Despite the presence of my fears, I feel more grounded now than I have at any other point in my life. I have a wonderful job and my career goals for the future have come full circle in the wake of my return to school. I am surrounded by the most incredible support network of family and friends. I go to an incredible church, a place where I am encouraged to think about my faith instead of blindly accepting doctrine. I have a cat who adores me. Truly, I am a blessed woman.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came here, once or twice since I last wrote, with no topic in my mind. I came here with a voice, but no words to give that voice a contextual meaning. What should I write about in this space? Should I tell you about my ex-boyfriend, how his memory continues to break me, even after he abdicated from my love? Should I discuss the weather, the change of colors and climate? Perhaps, I could write about my indecisiveness regarding the future; professional and personal?  With each passing day, I am becoming more of an introvert, more shy with the world. I enjoy my new-found solitude, but I would be lying if I did not admit that there are times when the loneliness hits me hard. There are times when I wish for a companion, preferably of the male variety. I want a man in my life, not for sex or romantic love, but for friendship, for those times when I need strong arms to hold me.  I am fully aware of my faults. I am stubborn, tempermental, loud, obsessive compulsive, and a hopeless romantic. I am passionate, almost to the point of being militant, about certain issues. I have no problem with expressing my opinion, to an individual or a crowd of people. I am an emotional eater. I have a vulgar sense of humor and a tendency to use excessive amounts of profanity in any given situation.  I am picky about spelling, punctuation, and style.  For all of my faults, I have just as many good qualities. I am intelligent. I write a mean research paper. I try to see beauty in everything. I have strong faith. I like to give back to my community. I want to make the world a better place to live, especially for women and children. I want to be a role model for young girls who are searching for an idenity in this crazy messed-up world. I am compassionate and giving. I put my all into my friendships and relationships. I love sex. (Of course there are some individuals who would argue that this is a negative quality. Screw them.) I am honest. Also, while I may never win the Miss America pagent and I know that I have some weight to lose, I do not believe that I am hard on the eyes. I can look myself in the mirror and see a valuable woman who posesses beauty, even if it is of the inward variety.  I am not perfect, but I have worth.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      October is a difficult month for me. Three years ago, Nan died on Friday the thirteenth.  She died in her sleep; she had sat down to take a nap during the middle of the day and when her daughter came home from work, she discovered that her mother was no longer among the living.  The funeral took place on what would have been an otherwise gorgeous autumn afternoon. As I watched her casket being lowered into the ground, I could not help but ponder the irony of burying my grandmother, my spiritual rock, on such a day as that one.  A couple of years later, my family buried our beloved pet, Freckles, after he lost a brief, yet painful, battle with liver disease, an ailment that is very common amongst male cocker spaniels. It happened so fast and I will never forget my mother calling me and tearfully telling me about his passing. She loved that dog.  It seems that there is so much pain in life. Sometimes, I want to wail against Godde, because I know that she has the power to cease the world's suffering and sadness. Then, there are moments that I know I am growing stronger, because of the suffering that I have had to endure at times. The fall is the perfect time of year to reflect on that strength. In the tradition of the Celts, the autumn season has become my personal New Year's celebration. I use this time to re-focus my goals, especially since I have a habit of getting distracted over the summer. This is the time of year that I pay homage to those individuals who have passed through the veil.  I miss her. There are still days where I feel an overwhelming need to hear her voice over the phone or to hold her hand. When I realize that this is no longer a possibility, there is a sharp pain that runs straight through my heart. It takes my breath away and I start to leak silent tears.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I watch the students in this college town. You would think they're carefree, I have seen their trials, Frowning into Shakespeare and practicing their smiles, With every new idea, wondering if they've changed at all, Then they turn away, it happens every day.  - Dar Williams,  The Green World    I want to talk about responsibility. Oftentimes, I feel that pressure of responsibility, the higher moral obligation to make the world a better place for us to live. There are those individuals who mock my idealistic desires, but for me, being an optimist is the only way to survive in this crazy place. My faith in Godde prevents me from becoming the World's Greatest Cynic. I am a natural optimist, always wanting to see the good in people and their motivations, and I feel absolutely no shame about that fact.  Mother Teresa stated that, "In this life we cannot do great things. We can only do small things with great love." Indeed, it is the small things that make the most difference. The environment is a good example of this point and I have made it a part of said higher obligation to protect the space in which I live. I drive a car that gets good gas-mileage and has the lowest emissions rating in the country. I car-pool to places when it is possible. I recycle paper, plastic, aluminium, and glass products. I take my own shopping bags, made out of thick cloth, to the grocery store and if I am forced to use the plastic bags, I keep and re-use them to carry my lunch to work during the week.  Perhaps it is naive of me to be so sure that my actions, alone, can change the world. Certainly, other people think in such terms. On more than one occasion, I have been labeled as a  bleeding heart , a  touchy-feely liberal , and a  hippie tree hugger . I have grown immune to such attempts at attacking my desire, my need, to keep this place clean. I refuse to believe that it is a bad thing to want to leave something beautiful for those who, years after I am gone, will walk this land. Godde did not give us this land to plunder with shameless abandon. When you rape the land, you are, for all intents and purposes, raping Godde, because  She is the land . This type of language, this violent metaphor, is harsh, but true. I am a firm believer in honesty, a trait which far too many individuals have lost sight of and no longer value. We are tied to this place. We are tied to Her. If we, as a society, destroy our planet, then we will be destroying the gift that Godde gave to us. We will be destroying our own lives, the lives of our children, and Godde Herself.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was never one of those girls. I never planned my wedding, most of my Barbie dolls eloped rather than having a frou-frou ceremony. I did not keep a scrapbook full of pictures of rings, dresses, and cakes. In college, when I first discovered feminism, I proclaimed at the top of my lungs that marriage was a patriarchal institution and there was no way that I was going to willingly participate in the ultimate downfall of women. Yet, the entire time that I went through that militant phase I had a dirty little secret.  I wanted to be married. I wanted to fall in love with a man.  Now, I am older and a bit wiser. I recognize that I can be both, a feminist and a wife. In the last few weeks, I have been contemplating this topic, mostly because I have a great number of friends who either are married or are engaged to be married. I find myself turning into one of those women; clipping dresses and rings out of magazines, thinking about ceremonies, but most of all looking for the ever elusive  Mr. Right . My feminist self knows that such a creature does not exist. I am too cynical to believe, truly, in faerytales. I am no longer viewing the world through child-like eyes. However, the hopeless romantic in me will not stop looking for this individual.  I would be lying if I said that I was not ready for love. I would love to be in a relationship with a man, a committed union with someone who wanted to spend his life with me. The problem is that I am not ready to give up all of the things that I would, most likely, need to sacrifice in order to be with this person; traveling abroad, working in Washington D.C., getting my doctorate. I am not sure if I am ready to be that unselfish with my time and energy.  What is problematic about this situation is that I give my heart away with too much ease. I am a hopeless romantic and caring for other people is second nature to me, not because I am a woman, but because I am me. It is a seamless part of my identity that I can not divorce from other parts of my life. I crave a partner, a companion, like most of the world. I want to fall in love with a man who would be willing to move to another city/state/country for my career. I want to be involved with a man who is my best friend and loves me because of my flaws and not in spite of them.  The hard part about contemplating issues, such as this one, over which I have no control is that I am afraid of the hard, realistic possibility that I may never find this individual. However, I have faith that things will follow the path that they are meant to travel. In the meantime, I am going to take a deep breath and focus on taking life one day at a time.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are days when I feel as new to the experience of living as a newborn child. Those moments often seem so simple that I am certain that I am missing a bigger lesson. Like a speeding car, it passes me by and leaves me standing, searching, on some lonely dirt road called life.  Introspection, as wonderful as it is, can be a dangerous thing. Thinking too much and too hard about a particular topic will wear you down, emotionally and mentally, and leave you more confused than when you began your ponderings. I think that Pooh had it right all along; life, and all the tiny moments that comprise it, just  is , not this insatiable push for progress that the human race seems hell bent on completing.  Right now, I am studying for a final exam, writing a paper, and trying not to pull out every single strand of my hair. Right now, I am learning to sit back, relax, and breathe. The world may not revolve around me, but it will wait on me for a little while.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think that men, when they are first introduced to me, forget that I am a woman. It is easy for them to see me as the embodiment of a label, a definition. They think that they know everything there is to know about my life, because I call myself a feminist. Assumptions get made at the drop of a hat; I am most definately a man-hater, I am probably a lesbian, and it is incredibly suspect that I have a good, healthy relationship with my father.  If I were to place an open advertisement for a life-partner, it would read  single, open-minded, slightly-dorky, academic-type woman seeks single, open-minded, funny man for a life-long commitment, which will include evenings of intellectual ramblings on feminist theory, very bad cooking, obsessive devotion to the art of shagging, cat hair that covers every conceivable surface, eventual birth of children, a house by the sea, and a woman who will stand by your side, no matter what life throws at you.   I am too honest for my own good. Most women hide those dark parts, waiting for the moment to reveal thier true nature. I do not live my life in such a manipulative fashion, chosing instead to be completely honest and open about who I am as a woman, for better and for worse. I do not believe in the artificial and it is that dislike for artifice that creates my disdain for dating. In my mind, in my experience, dating is fake.  I do not want a romantic illusion, I want a real person in my life, to share my life. I want someone who forgets to leave the toilet seat down and can laugh at his own mistakes and weaknesses. I want a man who thinks that I am beautiful without make-up and who understands that kissing is not a prelude to sex, but a pleasure that is to be explored and enjoyed on its own merit. I want someone who will not run out the door, but will chose to stay by my side the morning after we have made love.  I want passion, truth, and someone who is not afraid to love me. Most of all, I want a man who understands that I am a strong-willed, take-charge, opinionated, refuse-to-be-a-doormate type of person; however, at the end of the day, I want to come home and have someone take care of me.  In a word, I want  acceptance .
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I believe in things that I cannot see with my eyes. I hold stock, importance and prominence, in the rest of the senses; touch, taste, hear, and smell. Yesterday, I celebrated the birth of a miraculous man. I cannot prove that he was the son of Godde, but I feel that particular truth down in the depths of my bones. However, he is not the only truth in which I believe nor does my belief in him negate or make impossible the existence of other esteemable tenants.  I consider myself a Celtic-Christo-Episco-Pagan, who follows the teachings of Jesus and pays homage to the Goddess. I believe in the existence of faeries, Santa Claus, elves, unicorns; all forms of magic that can only be found by paying attention, by listening to that child-like voice that lives inside of me, a voice that has the potential to disappear if we, human beings, do not guard it with care and love. I hold the words of Buddha close to my heart and I have a penchant for Islamic spiritual poetry. I follow the religious path of the ancient Celtic Church. I use my rosary for prayer and meditation.  I believe that evil exists, but I also believe in the overwhelming nature of Good, of Godde. Godde speaks to every man and woman, through every race, religion, and creed. Godde is not reserved for one nation or one brand of theology, but embraces and can be embraced by all who walk this planet. Beauty, happiness and fulfillment, can be found in every tradition.  Regardless of your path, I wish you a Blessed Christmas and a Happy New Year.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are some occasions for which Hallmark has no appropriate card to give to another human being. There is no card that expresses a proper sentiment for the friend who has been laid off from work for the second time in three years, for the woman who choses to have an abortion and struggles with that decision for the rest of her life, or for the man who is diagnosed with HIV and is forced to reconcile himself with the fact that he is dying.  There is no card for my friend, and co-worker, Nancy who was diagnosed with cancer and has spent the last three years battling this disease. Last week, I discovered that her doctor found four tumors in Nancy's brain and that her chances of living to see another year are very slim. I am struggling with the injustice of this revelation. It is times like these that cause me to question Godde's purpose for people. Is this kind of action the definition of mercy? Is it right for a woman, an individual who has never been anything but wonderful to her co-workers and friends, to suffer in such a manner? How does a person live out the remainder of their life, knowing that with each rotation of the sun they are one day closer to leaving behind all that they have ever known?  Sometimes, there are simply no words for the moment, no words to describe the shock you feel at learning that a person in your life will no longer be there to grace you with their smile. There are no words for the sadness, the frustration, and the anger that is felt when good people are forced to suffer and carry an unbearable burden, while the dregs of humanity walk the world and feel no consequences for their actions.  This is the hardest part about being a person of faith, not the theology that you adhere to nor the manner in which you daily practice the rituals of your religion, but the need to keep your hand tight around the tenuous thread of hope. The most difficult thing in the world is to have faith when the entire world tries to pull you away from it.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wait for the Red, red - the flow that marks me as a woman.   Crimson guilt Of sins once done, Committed In a brazen act Of passion.   Once more, I pay the price Of using my body To speak the language of liberation.   When did the faerie dust disappear? Did my mother Put Away My favorite doll?   I remember a simpler time, Before the Red Sea (with all its glorious might) Swept away my body Leaving my soul in her wake.   This is a moment That belongs to Every Woman.   A scare, A lunar flow unshed, A potential choice that devastates, And a false line that burns Bright pink.   Hope lies in a cardboard box.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Feminism is like any other ideology. It shifts, morphs, over time and different people interpret the ideology in a plethora of ways.  For me, feminism is mother's milk, a liquid that runs through my veins and becomes one with my life's blood.  I am unable to separate my affiliation with feminism from the rest of my life.  It is part of my DNA to be a strong woman, but every now and then I forget that I have that strength and fortitude.  I neglect that part of myself that can conquer the world, that will be an individual.  I am having a revival of my political alignment.  In the last few weeks, I have struggled with what it means to be a Christian and a feminist, my weight and self-worth issues, and sexual harrassment in the workplace.  Yesterday, I realized that I had been living my life in a vacuum, head buried under sand, letting events and opportunities pass me by without second glance.  Ani DiFranco sings that,  us people are just poems / we're 90% metaphor / with a leanness of meaning / approaching hyper-distillation / and once upon a time / we were moonshine .  Once upon a time, we were pure, rid of societal impurity.  I want to reclaim that fierceness, that independence of mind and self once more.  I want to recover my strength from the terror that I experienced on the morning of yesterday.  No longer will I be claustrophobic, held back from the world for fear of making mistakes and disappointing other people in my life.  I want to eat, sleep, drink, fuck and breathe feminism through my pores.  This may no make sense to you, those individuals in cyberspace who know nothing about me but for the words that I write.  This may seem a jumble, a hodge-podge of vernacular guaranteed to confuse the mind and cause the heart to twist and turn.  It is none of these things and all of these things at once.  This is a statement.  This is a manifesto.  I am a woman who believes, who lives her life under the concept, that feminism can and will free men and women.  I am a white, anglophile, heterosexual, woman-loving, socially-liberal, fiscally-responsible, pro-choice, veggie-tree-hugger, rockin' mama, intellectual, believer in fae feminist.  No longer will I feel as if I am less of a woman, because I expect more from men; more being equality, respect, love, friendship, lust, and decency.  After all, would you expect any less of a poem?
 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Procrastination, to be sure, is an artform.&nbsp; It is one that I have cultivated through many years of school, secondary and post-secondary education.&nbsp; There are days when it seems that I will never be motivated enough to pursue academia and then there are moments where it feels as though I am meant to be nothing but an academic, that scholarship and research will be my life.   The hard part about going to graduate school on a part-time basis is finding the time to live.&nbsp; When you are an undergraduate student, your job is school and your life is a separate entity.&nbsp; When you work for a living and go to school at night, school, suddenly, becomes your life.&nbsp; All other aspects of daily living fall by the wayside and you are plunged into a monotonous routine of work and school, work and school, work and school.   Procrastination, as a result, becomes more than an artform.&nbsp; It becomes as essential to life and breathing air and drinking water.&nbsp; It becomes sex, something that we do not need to survive, but is something that we cannot imagine living without.   Therefore, one could conclude, procrastination is nothing short of fucking with our own self.  

     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am having a hard time making decisions lately.&nbsp; This summer semester has been really difficult for me to get through.&nbsp; For some reason, I am not liking school as much as I thought I would.&nbsp; Truth be told, I hate writing papers and sitting through hours of class lectures.&nbsp; I am not sure if this is a phase, but more and more I am beginning to believe that I am not cut out for academia.&nbsp; I want to teach.&nbsp; I want a classroom.&nbsp; I want a life outside of publishing and research.&nbsp; I am so bloody sick of writing about women, gender, and feminism.&nbsp; To think that I wanted, thought that I wanted, to study this material for the rest of my life.&nbsp; I love being a feminist, but I hate writing about it.&nbsp; I hate the theory behind it.&nbsp; I want to be a practicing feminist, not a stuff academic one.  There are times where it seems that I am not meant to be anything but an academic, then I start thinking about all the years of school that I have left in store for me.&nbsp; At best, I will complete school by thirty-three.&nbsp; Not old at all, but do I want to be in school for that long?&nbsp; I am not sure.&nbsp; Right now, I just want to get through this fucking semester.

     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So small and fearless My fickle heart,  My brave path, My one true love.  A list of sins Follow in&nbsp;my wake, Trailing after&nbsp;me.  Give me amnesty, Sophia. Protect my mourning soul And comfort my love-starved self.  I cling to you. I pine for your presence, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Godde. Waiting anxiously for the taste &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;of your salvation &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;upon my lips.  I imagine salvation tastes &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;- like honey. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;- like green tea and jasmine. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; -like salt licked from a man's &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;post-coital, sweat-soaked back. I imagine salvation tastes Wonderful.  Who do I have to fear In this colourful (colour-stained) world?  What pagan soul have I unravelled With my Jesus-freak sensibilities?  In a woman's arms, Your arms, I wish to lie.  You seem like grace incarnate to me.  Godde is manifest. Not unreachable. Eager to be traced.  The small of a woman's back, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;(the gateway to the womb) The curve of her neck &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;(the matching pulse point of life) Laying shallow into the valley Of her breasts &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;(the center of her heart).  Godde &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;pulses, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;sweats, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;and breathes Alive in us all. 

     

    
</post>


</Blog>