<Blog>

<date>13,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink The Sun News | 03/13/2003 | Tricks Prevail in S.C. House  says it as well as anything I've seen.  Fuzzy math and funny money from the alleged leadership of the S.C. House of Representatives.  

     



    
</post>

<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink House panel rejects cigarette tax, supporters rally at Statehouse   Kinda figures, huh?

     



    
</post>

<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink Jimmy Moore  at Common Voice raises some interesting points concerning the debate over the cigarette tax, and I suppose yesterday's action by the alleged Republican leadership meets his definition of "creative revenue-generating ideas."  But some of this crap still sticks in my craw.  Mossback Democrat Herb Kirsh laments the fact that retailers in his area will be hurt by those going across state lines to buy cheaper cigarettes - where was this concern for retailers and their employees when the issue was shutting down video poker?  The Employment Security Commission says that of the approximately 3,000 workers left unemployed when the anti-gambling jihad took hold,  urlLink just 212 have found work  since.

     



    
</post>

<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

      Republicans claim their plan to refinance tobacco bonds to fund Medicaid is designed to stop spending non-recurring dollars to pay for recurring needs - but the proposed Medicaid budget still relies on at least  urlLink $45 million  and maybe up to  urlLink $70 million  in one-time money.  While claiming to follow their governor's lead in funding Medicaid without raising taxes, the alleged House leadership seems to be ignoring something else Governor Moonbeam said in his  urlLink  State of the State address:  "Let this also be the year that we curb the annualization problem. No sensible family would use a one-time bonus to finance a new car - if they didn't have some other source for payments - not just this year's - but also each following year's payments. This principle should also hold true for our state."     

     



    
</post>

<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink Tax smokers or everyone pays, study says   Private health insurance premiums could increase 4 to 9 percent if the state does not fully fund the state-federal Medicaid partnership, a study by the Grant Thornton accounting firm states. 

     



    
</post>

<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

      Proposed State Budget Underfunds Health Care By $95 Million, No wait, $51 Million, No, Um, It's Funded Completely!  Thanks to  urlLink creative financing  by the alleged leadership of the S.C. House of Representatives, South Carolina's woefully inadequate Medicaid system is now fully funded!  Except, of course, they are proposing to continue the practice of funding recurring needs with non-recurring money - the kind of irresponsible action that has created the budget crisis we're now in.  By refinancing the state's tobacco settlement funds, House leaders Wilkins, Harrell and Quinn say they can fill the roughly $51 million hole in the Ways & Means Committee's Medicaid budget.  They say it will raise approximately $45 million - though that still doesn't equal $51 million, but who's counting - and that this is all good, solid, recurring money that we can count on for years to come.  No, wait a minute, upon further review, they admit that it  does  include $15 million in non-recurring funds, maybe.  The fact is, the alleged House leadership continues to play with funny money.  Under their revised proposal, Medicaid would be funded with $10 million in unspecified eligibility changes (read: kicking people off the rolls), at least $45 million in one-time money (including $30 million they admitted to last week and $15 million from tobacco settlement refinancing), a $20 million tax increase on hospitals and by taking $20 million out of an underfunded Department of Education.  The time for Bandaids is over.  This temporary, one-time solution will leave us with an even bigger problem next year.  It is time for a stable, recurring, dedicated source of funding for health care, not more creative financing.  The cigarette tax is the only solution that works, and the alleged leadership knows it.   

     



    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink The State | 03/18/2003 | Legislators who oppose cigarette tax happy to raise other taxes  points out the hypocrisy of the alleged leadership of the S.C. House of Representatives quite well.  A tax is a tax is a fee just doesn't wash.

     



    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink The State | 03/18/2003 | Treasurer spurns bond proposal  but I'm sure it won't stop the smoke and mirrors approach preferred by the alleged leadership of the S.C. House of Representatives.

     



    
</post>

<date>18,March,2003</date>
<post>




       

      On war with Iraq...  Personally, I don't really know what else those who oppose war would have the President do.  "Give diplomacy a chance?" It's failed for twelve years, not just since last November.  While I'm a p.r. hack, not an attorney or law student like many of my friends, my own reading of  urlLink U.N. Security Council Resolution 1441,  in citing Resolution 678, seems to give us the authority to use force:  "Recalling that its resolution 678 (1990) authorized Member States to use all necessary means to uphold and implement its resolution 660 (1990) of 2 August 1990 and all relevant resolutions subsequent to Resolution 660 (1990) and to restore international peace and security in the area,"  I would definitely be interested in hearing someone on the wire versed in international law to share their opinion.  Even without UN authority, however, I'm still convinced that we are justified in going into Iraq, even if it means embracing the doctrine of preemptive war.  Can anyone honestly debate that Adolf Hitler was evil? Would the world not have been a better place had someone, anyone, taken a preemptive strike against him?  We can have a philosophical debate on the existence of evil if you want.  But I was raised a Southern Baptist and converted to Catholicism, so I believe that some things, some people are, in fact, evil.  In my view, Saddam has demonstrated his nature, and stopping him is justified.  But philosophy aside, in my mind practicality justifies preemptive action in the world in which we now live.  Sitting around waiting for Saddam - or anyone else - to attack before we act is suicide. 

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>




       

        Pentagon Abandons Terrorism Betting Plan   Dang! There's goes my chance!   urlLink Guardian Unlimited | World Latest | Pentagon Abandons Terrorism Betting Plan  

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>




       

       Profiting on Death and War is No Longer limited to the military-industrial complex!  Now you can play too, thanks to PAM!   urlLink Policy Analysis Market - PAM  

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>




       

      Kill a Middle East head of state, win prizes! - Pentagon shows how By Andrew Orlowski in San Francisco  "Poor people aren't necessarily killers," the current President of the United States tells us. "Just because you happen not to be rich, doesn't mean you're willing to kill."   Phew! However, the poor now have an additional incentive to take up arms, thanks to an extraordinary initiative from the Pentagon-funded research agency DARPA. Long ago DARPA brought you the Internet, although its more recent windfall has gone on projects that range from the sinister to the whimsical, from Admiral Poindexter's Total Information Awareness surveillance research, to invisible body suits, and a self-healing minefield, complete with winking knight.    urlLink The Register 

     



    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

       A Recommended Read  I haven't read  urlLink Down and Out in the Magic Kingdom  yet, but Cory Doctorow, who also brings us  urlLink Boing Boing , is giving away his first novel.  It's getting great reviews, including a plug from Amazon.com founder and CEO Jeff Bezos on the  urlLink NPR : Weekend Edition Sunday, Summer Reading 2003 list .

     



    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

       Track PACs and Contracts    urlLink Correspondences.org  has a great concept on its hands - a daily look at Department of Defense contracts awarded, cross-referenced with political contributions made by the winning companies.  The site bills itself as a "newspaper out of the box" covering world events.  Highly recommended. 

     



    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink  Tell Bush to recall himself    Interesting logic behind this one, and I like it.  Bush's sins are far greater than those of Gray Davis.  I hope this one catches on.  Brought to you by one of my other favorite sites  urlLink the Bushwackers , as well as  urlLink Progressive Majority .

     



    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

      Thanks to SC Hotline for tracking down the original Roll Call article where Kevin Geddings again proves to be an ass:   urlLink Roll Call   Tenenbaum outpolled Geddings's candidate for governor by more than 120,000 votes.  She got 45,000 more votes than Lindsay Graham in his Senate race.  Granted, she was up against weak competition.  But, going back to 1998, she outpolled Hodges by 37,000 votes and beat a decent Republican candidate, David Eckstrom, by 161,000 votes.  She even beat Eckstrom in his home county, Lexington (you remember Lexington, don't you), albeit by a little over 200 votes.   

     



    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink TIME.com: High On Gals In Good-Ole-Boy Country -- Aug. 25, 2003   Inez gets some more national press.

     



    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

       From the Guys Who Brought Us The Disaster of '04   "Keep your noses out of our business," Dick Harpootlian was quoted as saying to DSCC in an interview with Roll Call, a Capitol Hill newspaper. He told The Greenville News: "These are the guys who brought us the disaster of '02."  Interesting that this story was ginned up by Dick and Kevin Geddings, who closer to home brought South Carolina the disaster of '04.  I love Mayor Bob - but he ain't going to get elected statewide.  Personally, I'm glad to see a primary.  I think our eventual candidate Inez will emerge stronger because of it.  But Geddings is the guy who ought to get out of South Carolina after his last masterful performance.   urlLink GreenvilleOnline.com - GOP gleeful at possible Dem strife 

     



    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

       Draft Clark   Is Wesley Clark the Great White Hope of the Democratic Party?  I don't know, but I am very intrigued by the possibility.  The Draft Clark movement seems to be picking up steam, going so far as to commission a Zogby poll that says  urlLink In Blind Bio Match-Up, Wesley Clark Tops All Current Dems, Beats Bush 49 Pct. to 40 Pct.   How would Clark fare in a South Carolina primary?  Depends on the crossover factor.  Clark might be a guy that draws a lot of independent and even Republican voters into that primary, and his military credentials will appeal to many.  Stay tuned.

     



    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>




       

       Ouch!   Governor Moonbeam's people still have to be smarting from yesterday's Augusta Chronicle saying that the  urlLink Governor's tactics resemble Clinton's 08/25/03 .  I'm not sure Sanford is consciously pursing a strategy of triangulation - in fact, I'm not competely sure this is conciously pursuing any strategy at all.  I do know that he has been a disappointment to many (including this Democrat) who thought he was the breath of fresh air South Carolina needed.  So far, though, he seems to be giving us more of the same (see  urlLink The State | 08/24/2003 | Sanford campaign donors land almost half of his appointments ) except with fewer results to show for it.  As I read the news that  urlLink Blue Cross Blue Shield could be forced to be cut up to 800 jobs  in Florence and Myrtle Beach, it occurred to me that I don't recall this governor making a single "job announcement" since he took office.  I guess Sanford really is doing things differently, since these little press events are usually a staple of gubernatorial politics.  Instead, this governor has spent 8 months looking at a real estate deal,  urlLink even at the expense of his own Commerce Secretary. 

     



    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

       South Carolina Draft Clark   I've started a new blog,  urlLink South Carolina Draft Clark,  to share news about the Draft Clark movement in our state. Call me crazy, but the more I know about this guy, the more I like him.  

     



    
</post>

<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

       urlLink Zogby shows wide open race    "No candidate has the edge, and it looks like South Carolina will be shaped by Iowa and New Hampshire.  In this kind of vacuum, Clark may seize the moderate mantle." 

     



    
</post>

<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

        urlLink CNN.com - Wesley Clark may announce for presidency next week - Sep. 11, 2003     WASHINGTON (CNN) --  urlLink Wesley Clark  has begun building a campaign organization and several people close to the retired general told CNN Thursday they expect him to announce next week that he is running for president.   Clark has discussed his potential campaign with presidential candidate Howard Dean, the liberal antiwar former Vermont governor who, according to Dean campaign officials, asked Clark for his support.   According to one source familiar with the conversations, the two men discussed the vice presidency. But Dean campaign officials said such talk is premature and those close to Clark expect him to run for president, not vice president.   "I think he's going to run," said Skip Rutherford, a Clark friend and the executive director of the Clinton Presidential Library in Little Rock. "Impressive people are coming forward offering to work on his campaign, run his campaign and consult his campaign."   Several Democratic sources said Clark -- Supreme NATO commander during the war in Kosovo -- has begun the process of putting together a campaign team, including talking to potential campaign managers.   "There is a lot of momentum here," said one former high-level Clinton administration official who has talked to Clark about a campaign. "It's 90-10 that he runs, but he has not pulled the trigger in his own mind."   Gore campaign veteran Mark Fabiani, who is advising Clark on the possible presidential campaign, cautions that Clark has not yet made a final decision.   "He's doing the kind of things you'd do if you are going to run. He's doing what he needs to do to put himself in a position to run," Fabiani said. "He'd be a great candidate, but at this point it's theoretical."   Clark is returning home to Arkansas Friday to talk to his family. Clark has said that his wife, Gertrude, has reservations about a presidential campaign but will support him in whatever decision he makes.     urlLink  

     



    
</post>

<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

        Destroying the Village?     urlLink Rumsfeld: Criticism Harms War on Terror  reminds me of that old saw about "it was necessary to destroy the village in order to save it."  We're supposedly fighting this war on terror - in the "centerpiece" of Iraq - at least in some fashion to lift our Arab brethren out of oppression.  But in order to do so, we have to suspend our right to point out that we think Donald Rumsfeld is full of crap.  

     



    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

      Link Via  urlLink Suburban Blight       My inner child is sixteen years old!    Life's not fair! It's never been fair, but while adults might just accept that, I know something's gotta change. And it's gonna change, just as soon as I become an adult and get some power of my own.    urlLink   How Old is Your Inner Child?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   

     



    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

        Bush Bumper Stickers    I'd credit the original creators if I knew who it was, but this just came to my email box from my friend Zach.  Choose your favorite re-election theme from those below:  Bush/Cheney '04: Apocalypse Now! Bush/Cheney '04: Because the truth just isn't good enough.  Bush/Cheney '04: Compassionate Colonialism  Bush/Cheney '04: Deja-voodoo all over again!  Bush/Cheney '04: Four More Wars!  Bush/Cheney '04: Leave no billionaire behind  Bush/Cheney '04: Lies and videotape but no sex!  Bush/Cheney '04: Or else.  Bush/Cheney '04: Over a billion Whoppers served.  Bush/Cheney '04: Putting the "con" in conservatism  Bush/Cheney '04: Thanks for not paying attention.  Bush/Cheney '04: The economy's stupid!  Bush/Cheney '04: The last vote you'll ever have to cast.  Bush/Cheney '04: This time, elect us!  Bush/Cheney '04: We're Gooder! Bush/Cheney: 1984 Now George W. Bush: A brainwave away from the presidency George W. Bush: It takes a village idiot George W. Bush: The buck stops Over There George W. Bush: Let them eat yellowcake! Vote Bush! George W. Bush: Peace & Prosperity Suck -- Big-Time Vote Bush in '04: "I Has Incumbentory Advantitude" Vote Bush in '04: "Because every vote counts -- for me!" Vote Bush in '04: "Because I'm the President, that's why!" Vote Bush in '04: Because dictatorship is easier. Vote Bush in '04: Who would Jesus Bomb?  

     



    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

        A Little Football News    Couldn't resist a break from politics for a little football.  Good news for Clemson fans.  Auburn has replaced the Tiger Cubs in the (un)coveted No. 5 spot on  urlLink ESPN.com's Bottom 10 .  Just goes to show you what a strong win over Furman can do for you (insert evil grin here).

     



    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

       From Palmetto Journal: Fox guarding the hen house    urlLink Palmetto Journal  reports:  "The toothless ethics laws and the political fiefdom known as the State Ethics Commission are about to be exposed in the coming weeks and months.  We understand that a legal action is in the works against the Ethics Commission. The suit will be based upon federal civil rights law and relate to freedom of speech and due process, among other things. "   This should interesting!

     



    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

       Welcome Back To Common Voice    urlLink Common Voice  is one of the best South Carolina blogs around, for the simple reason that Jonathan Pait provides a forum for a wide diversity of opinion on the issues.  I'm glad to see that he's put the site back up, and I look forward to the return of some of the lively discussion that has been a hallmark of the site.

     



    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>




       

        On Tommy Windsor's second chance    The news that Tommy Windsor is back at the AG's office rankles some people  urlLink ( The State | 09/07/2003 | Writer of offensive e-mails rehired ) , and while his politics rankle me, I say he deserves a second chance.  I've known Tommy for quite a while, I can tell you that his past transgressions really were a rather lame attempt at humor.  Yeah, yeah, he shouldn't have used his state computer to send those messages to anyone, but you can bet he won't make that mistake again.  Besides that, I continue to maintain that the Constitution of the United States does not include a right not to be offended.  Offensive speech is the very speech that needs to be protected by 1st Amendment, and I'd be sorry if I didn't piss off a few of you every time I put pen to paper.  

     



    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>




       

        Enough to make me a fiscal conservative    Complaints over "pork barrel" politics have become so commonplace as to border on cliche.  In fact, after reading  urlLink Cindi Scoppe's column  this morning, I now realize that South Carolina's General Assembly has moved well beyond the barrel and planted its snout firmly in the trough.  I'll try harder to get worked up over the perks of local elected officials later, but right now I am entirely too pissed off at state officials to comment.  The fact that a legislator who "retires" after 30 years draws a pension nearly $10,000 higher than the current salary - while state employees at the same pay level who actually work during those 30 years draw down about $20,000 less annually than the morons who make our laws - is too outrageous for words, even for me.  I used to feel that while their were certainly a few people who ran for state office to feed their own egos, enhance their business prospects or simply line their own pockets, the vast majority of our public servants were just that - people who were giving something back to their state or community.  What a naive freakin' idiot I was.  Every one of these people - some of whom are personal friends of mine - have hoodwinked us all.  No matter their intentions, the news of this pension plan convinces me that the S.C. General Assembly is absolutely committed to one thing: greed.  My only hope is that voters who think they are sending fiscal conservatives to the General Assembly will realize what a joke that is.  Alas, I doubt it will happen, because it is increasingly apparent that the only life form less intelligent than the average South Carolina legislator is the average South Carolina voter.

     



    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>




       

       Lovely Day For A Guinness!   Someone recently pointed out to me that I haven't ranted for a while on here, so before I lose my reputation as budding curmudgeon, I thought I better do a little blogging.   urlLink Guinness  has long marketed its great product with the slogan "Guinness is good for you."  Turns out they're right, with word of a study presented at the American Heart Association's Scientific Sessions 2003 that finds  urlLink Dark Beer May Be Better for the Heart .    Low-carb beers have become all the rage - the problem being that most of them taste like water with a drop or two of water added.  But the true connoisseur knows that  urlLink Guinness offers great taste and low carbs.   I've dropped a lot of lb's myself in the last few months, through a combination of a controlled - not necessarily low - carb diet and increased exercise.  Guinness is a vital and fulfilling part of my diet.  I urge each of you to hoist a pint tonight!

     



    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>




       

        Links      South Carolina    urlLink Wyeth Wire    urlLink Common Voice    urlLink Backcountry Conservative    urlLink S.C. Hotline     National    Taegan Goddard's Political Wire   urlLink Instapundit   urlLink Talking Points Memo   urlLink Political Animal   urlLink Electablog   urlLink Donkey Rising   urlLink Outside the Beltway   urlLink Power Line       

     



    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       What I'm Reading This Week     urlLink The Princes of Ireland   is a Micheneresqe look at several hundred years of Irish history and the first of a projected two-parter dubbed The Dublin Saga. It's an easy read and touches on all the big themes in Irish myth, legend and history, from the Celts to St. Patrick and Brian Boru to Henry VIII's treachery.     Rating: 3 Pints on the 5-pint Guiness Scale 
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

        It's A Mini-Bounce...     ...but John Kerry still goes over 50 percent in a two-way matchup with President Bush coming out of the Democratic National Convention.   urlLink The NEWSWEEK POLL  conducted Thursday and Friday, shows Kerry/Edwards leads Bush/Cheney 52 to 44 Percent, a two-point bounce.  The bounce is four points in a three-way race between Kerry (49%), Bush (42%) and Ralph Nader (3 percent).  In the two-way heat in the July 8-9 Newsweek Poll, Kerry led Bush by six points, 51 to 45 percent. In the three-way heat from that week, Kerry led Bush by 3 points, 47 to 44 percent, and Nader received 3 percent of the vote.  In polling before Kerry's speech on Thursday, he led Bush 47-45, with Nader at 2 percent.  On Friday, Kerry received 50 percent to 40 for Bush and 3 for Nader.

     



    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Gallup Analysis    urlLink Political Wire  points to a  urlLink Gallup analysis  that argues five character traits drive voters' presidential preference:   Shares your values  Can manage the government effectively  Is honest and trustworthy  Party affiliation (of respondents)  Is a person you admire   The analysis goes on to point out that on four of the five (party affiliation being the exception), voter opinions of Bush and Kerry are virtually identical.  The least important trait in this analysis? "Has an optimistic vision for the country's future." Does this mean Kerry's call for optimism last night - and his running mate's famous sunny disposition - don't matter?  Not necessarily. In fact, in the next few weeks, it's Bush who's most likely to be touting his optimism about the future of the country - naturally so, since he's by default advocating the status quo. If voters aren't moved by the optimism argument, Kerry/Edwards might ironically be the beneficiaries of pessimism. 

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

      In an effort to get more involved in the whole blogging community,  Haloscan  commenting and trackback have been added to this blog. 

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Others on Kerry     urlLink Outside The Beltway  has a roundup other opinions on the speech.   While I don't agree with James's assessment, I do enjoy this comment:   "...while I get that he's apparently basing his entire campaign on the facts that 1) he went to Vietnam and 2) he's not George W. Bush, I'm constantly bemused that a man who has been in the public spotlight for thirty-odd years wants us to think that he left Vietnam and suddenly emerged last week wanting to be president. "&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;  urlLink Kevin Drum  at Washington Monthly says..."Overall, though, it was at the high end of workmanlike and did what it had to do."&nbsp; He also has an open forum for other thoughts.  Thanks to  urlLink Backcountry Conservative  for the heads up.     

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Dissent in the Ranks    A Republican-near-and-dear-to-my-heart-to-remain-anonymous took issue with my praise of John Edward's speech and the theme of the Democratic Convention in general.&nbsp; To wit:   "This two Americas stuff is bull. &nbsp;Consider that for eight of the last twelve years,&nbsp;we had a Democrat president and supposedly this wonderful economic growth, and I'll give you that. I thought the middle class was doing okay.&nbsp;   "The problem with the middle class is that we buy really big houses that our parents would have neverthought to buy because interest rates are so low that we can afford the 'payments.' We buy expensive cars for the same reason, so when things do go bad, and, God forbid, someone loses a job or has a major health problem, we're so strapped in debt that we have to file bankruptcy. That is the greed of the middle class,&nbsp; not the fault of the politicians.   "On other issues,&nbsp;the USDOE under Bush spends more on education than ever before - &nbsp;so what is this "two American schools" issue? &nbsp;No Child Left Behind&nbsp;is addressing the issue and giving parents and kids the knowledge and choice to control their educational decisions, and that is what&nbsp;the establishment hates.&nbsp;   "I&nbsp;can't argue too much&nbsp;with raising the minimum wage for certain people, although I suspect&nbsp;it will hurt small business and cost jobs in the long run. I think they should exempt people under 18, although that probably raises legal issues.   "Finally,&nbsp;what is that mole or bump on Edwards' lip. It was very distracting.&nbsp; :)"&nbsp; 

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       From the For What It's Worth File...    Zogby was polling during the Democratic Convention, and the results show that Democrats have at least (temporarily) achieved one&nbsp;of their objectives.&nbsp;  Bush's&nbsp; urlLink job rating  is at 44 percent, the lowest since mid-May.&nbsp; Poll was conducted July 26-29, so impact of Kerry's speech isn't reflected.&nbsp;  In the  urlLink head-to-head , Kerry leads 46-41, increasing his spread from 47-44 in early July.&nbsp; Not much "bounce" but again, no reaction to the speech yet.   

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Kerry Reaction     On Wednesday John Edwards promised us hope was on the way, and last night John Kerry reassured us that help is coming, too.&nbsp; I'm certainly not the first to point out that this was a clever slap at Dick Cheney, who used the same line in appealing to military families four years ago in his own acceptance speech.   Kerry also appropriated a Bush theme from four years ago - promising to restore trust and integrity to the White House.   Overall, I think Kerry delivered last night.&nbsp; He showed passion and&nbsp;drew a clear distinction between himself and the idiot currently holding the office of president - damn, I forgot that civility thing already.   Everyone knows I'm more of a political junkie&nbsp;than a policy wonk, so I stayed up way past my bedtime to watch Frank Luntz with his focus group in Cincinnati.&nbsp; I just love the instant dial doohickeys and try to talk every client I meet with into spending way more money than they need to just to use the dial thingies.   Anyway, Kerry's biggest jump in the testing came here:     "We value an America that controls its own destiny because it's finally and forever independent of Mideast oil.&nbsp;What does it mean for our economy and our national security when we have only 3 percent of the world's oil reserves, yet we rely on foreign countries for 53 percent of what we consume?   "I want an America that relies on its ingenuity and innovation, not the Saudi royal family."  When he hit that line about the Saudis, the measurements went off the charts.&nbsp; And Michael Moore's movie isn't making a difference?   Personally, my favorite part of the speech was this:      "You see that flag up there.&nbsp;We call her Old Glory, the stars and stripes forever.&nbsp;I fought under that flag, as did so many of those people who were here tonight and all across the country.&nbsp;That flag flew from the gun turret right behind my head and it was shot through and through and tattered, but it never ceased to wave in the wind.&nbsp;It draped the caskets of men that I served with and friends I grew up with."  &nbsp;  "For us, that flag is the most powerful symbol of who we are and what we believe in:&nbsp;our strength, our diversity, our love of country, all that makes America both great and good.&nbsp; That flag doesn't belong to any president.&nbsp;It doesn't belong to any ideology.&nbsp;&nbsp;It doesn't belong to any party.&nbsp;It belongs to all the American people. "   I'm damn tired of being looked at as some sort of subversive who hates America because I dare to disagree with George II and Prime Minister Cheney, and Kerry articulated my resentment at Republicans who impugn our patriotism as well as anyone ever has.    urlLink Full text is here  for those who want to begin the critique.   

     



    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

        Only In South Carolina Can You Find The Words "Extortion" and "Cockfighting" In the Same Sentence    From the state where the governor brought livestock into the State House comes word that the Commission of Agriculture, Republican Charles Sharpe, has been  urlLink indicted  for his involvement with a cockfighting ring.  According to the AP, Sharpe is accused of accepting at least $20,000 from an organization involved in breeding and raising birds for cockfighting in exchange for helping the group avoid legal trouble.&nbsp; He was allegedlly working on behalf of the South Carolina Gamefowl Management Association.  The Augusta Chronicle reported on a law enforcement raid on the same facility last fall, and printed the names of  urlLink 118 people arrested  at the time.  

     



    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Demint, Sex & The City     The state GOP is quite alarmed that Senate candidate Inez Tenenbaum has received a campaign contribution from Barbara Streisand. But a review of Republican candidate  urlLink Jim Demint's SEC filings  points out something that should be much more alarming to GOPpers the world over: Jim Demint has received financial support from  urlLink a company that has previously employed Sarah Jessica Parker  (of Sex &amp; The City), Madonna (author of the best-selling book Sex) and  urlLink dope smoker  and  urlLink anti-war activist  Lenny Kravitz, among others.   More to come on this important developing story...    

     



    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Hope Is On The Way   John Edwards gave a  urlLink rousing speech  tonight.&nbsp; Yeah, I'm a Democrat, and yeah, my family knows a thing or two about lintheads and the mill hill, so I'm predisposed to like the guy.&nbsp; But he did a remarkable job putting forth a Democratic vision for middle class America.  Other random thoughts:   The guys on MSNBC were just talking about the fact that Edwards failed to mention God - well, damn.  Joe Scarborough, of all people, just had a great observation about watching trial lawyers going head to head with CEOs - a pretty good image to keep in mind when Edwards and Cheney square off in a fall debate or two.  I know people don't base their vote on vice presidential candidates - and that's a damn shame when you compare Edwards with the guy who spends most of his time in a secure, undislosed location.  &nbsp; 

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Blogging From Boston    Bloggers have actually been credentialled at the Democratic National Convention.&nbsp; Here's a pretty good&nbsp;overview of some of the  urlLink Boston blogging .&nbsp; Why didn't I think of getting a press pass? 

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

        Speaking of Razors...       urlLink According to PRWeek  Gillette and convention organizers are denying rumors that all of the razors Gillette placed in the gift bags handed out to Democratic National Convention attendees were confiscated by convention security in an ill-advised product placement move.   But I gotta tell you - believe the hype about the  urlLink Gillette M3 Power Razor . I plopped down $13.98 for one of these suckers and two blades, and it absolutely delivers the best shave ever.    

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Hogzilla   No truth to the rumors that Mark Sanford is negotiating to dig up this beast in his next effort to hogtie the General Assembly:  urlLink CNN.com - Hogzilla, the?legend grows - Jul 28, 2004 

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Backcountry Conservative    urlLink Backcountry Conservative  takes note of Harvey Gantt's appearance at the Democratic National Convention tonight on behalf of John Edwards.  Includes some interesting observations about Edwards attempt to play football at Clemson.  As a Carolina fan and the husband of an N.C. State grad, I say it proves how smart Edwards is that he got out of Pickens County Tech after just one semester.

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Obama Transcript    As previously promised, the full transcript of Barack Obama's fantastic keynote speech from the Democratic Convention:    urlLink CNN.com - Obama: Time to reclaim America's promise - Jul 27, 2004  

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

        Follow the Money     urlLink Cindy Scoppe's column on South Carolina's weak campaign disclosure system  is right on target.  It's nearly impossible for the average voter to find out who actually bought and paid for our elected officials.  Scoppe points out that according to the  urlLink Campaign Disclosure Project , the Palmetto $tate ranks right where we're used to when it comes the things that make our state better - the bottom: 50th in accessibility to information and Internet usability, 37th (or tied for last with 13 others) on electronic filing by candidates.  The State Ethics Commission does provide a link to some Internet information at  urlLink Follow the Money .  While there's very little information about the current election cycle, the 2002 data is fairly comprehensive.  Some interesting facts gleaned from that information:  The State Democratic Party gave $207,000 dollars to its candidates - far less than the approximately $384,000 contributed to Republican candidates by three GOP party committees.  One of those GOP committees is the Speaker's Politically Active Citizens Committee, through which (presumably) David Wilkins doled out $84,000 to his party's House candidates - guess that explains how thoroughly he's able to "lock down" the House to beat back the cigarette tax and other stuff he opposes.  Blue Cross Blue Shield was the top giver among South Carolina businesses, handing out $115,150. Forty-four Democrats got $35,900 of that, with the remaining $79,250 going to 96 Republicans.  

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

        Random thoughts on Democratic convention   OK, I admit:   I'm watching Teresa Heinz Kerry now, just hoping she'll say something outrageous.   I loved watching Ted Kennedy while my Republican wife cringed across the room.   I switched over to Fox for a few minutes, and Newt Gingrich still makes me want to puke.   Seeing a guy like Obama serving in the  state  Senate in Illinois really shows how bad things are in South Carolina.     

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Is this guy great or what?    I've heard hundreds - probably thousands - of political speeches. Hell, I've written plenty, including a whole bunch as a volunteer speechwriter at the 2000 Democratic National Convention. But I've never heard one I've actually been moved by until tonight.  urlLink Obama's keynote  was simply fantastic. I can't wait to get the transcript, and I'll post that, too. 

     



    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Blogging Hits Convention   Everybody has a blog these days - here's an official one from the Democratic National Convention:   urlLink bostonDparty - 2004 Democratic National Convention Blog 

     



    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>




       

      Andy Brack of  urlLink South Carolina Statehouse Report  weighs in on the likelihood of South Carolina using new electronic voting machines in several counties this November.

     



    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>




       

       Something Different    I'm trying out an alternative system for Die Tryin'.  Check out the   urlLink Squarespace version  of the site and let me know what you think.

     



    
</post>


<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Famous activist Brett Bursey weighs in on behalf of the  urlLink S.C. Progressive Network  on the growing controversy over South Carolina's  urlLink voting system.   Bursey argues that an improved optical-scan system is the better option, as long as those systems provide "voter-verified paper ballots."  According to Bursey's op-ed, such a system would mean having ballots scanned at the polling place - rather than election headquarters - so that if a ballot is kicked out for some reason the voter has a chance to correct it.  Sounds reasonable to me.  Questions continue to mount over the security and reliability of touch-screen systems that are being implemented across the country.   urlLink Move On  is also leading efforts to ensure that electronic voting systems provide voter-verified paper ballots. urlLink  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Official Kerry-Edwards Blog  gives you an inside look at the current post-convention trip across America.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Politics & Whatnot - Blog 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>