<Blog>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 22. October. 1999              Vestigion Darkness crowds in against the warm, living parts of me.  Pushes against the wet, hot, hidden places I keep secret from even myself. Red and wet, like my probing tongue against your ear, like my lips sliding over your tongue- teasing you with what I'd like to do to you.  But later, much later, after the Darkness smothers us, makes us cling to each other- as seductive as black lace on sweat.   Pain is pleasure, sublime torture Sometime in the night the music died, the Darkness crowded in again, oblivion in the bottom of a bottomless cup. Living information and I draw it in with each breath, strip mining and raping it for all the pertinent details before exhaling the waste- filled with meaning.    And there's you, rubbing, sighing, wooing, coaxing the secret from me, breathing in what I  breath out, asking me to come again when its over, to call and hang and share all the warm, wet, living information of Vestigion Darkness- with you- And shall I feel afraid?  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 11. January. 2000          I have this body of work something to behold, to see, to read its bulky, jagged in places, but its mine.  I definitive cross section of who I am- indelible proof of my need for therapy or drugs. Bi-polar, split personality, borderline schizophrenia- all of these things are in my head. The order of things was never in question. How was that order broken? Pre-thought thoughts microcosms in your eyes. I can't live like this. I can't go on not knowing, any longer. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 14. October. 1999                        Somewhere  Somewhere in the Darkness lost- a girl child cried out for her Mother. No one answered.  Somewhere in the light of day a Mother left her girl to fend for herself. She never looked back.  Death comes as an end Sublime peace for a  chaotic life.  Somewhere in the Darkness lost a girl child cried out. Silence answered with no answer.  Lost inside the dead of night, near the hour of the wolf, a love starved woman gave birth to pain, bitterness, and hate. Trapped inside the suffering of life a girl child screamed in mute need, letting go of trust,  hope, and love.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 7. September. 1999            I would like to state for the proverbial record, that the events that have taken place these last months here in San Antonio are by no means morally, legally, or justifiably correct.  I took part in them firstly because I wanted to, and secondly because they were a means to an end for me in a time of my life that needed extreme means to reasonable, rational ends.  I took part in these acts because they were exciting, they were wrong, and because to me, they played to that dark fiendish side of myself that I keep so well hidden;  of course, I could've done them simply for their arrogance.  ( Again, I never finished this either. ) 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 8. August. 1999     I'm dying, did you know?  And I'm trying so hard to pretend I'm not, to fool myself and everyone else.  There are all these words locked inside of me, and they won't come out.  I just want someone to hold me. PLEASE!  I feel so alone, and lost, and it hurts just to breath. Please, somebody help me!  I sleep all the time because that's the only time when it doesn't hurt, when I don't exhaust myself by trying to double think myself into happiness.        I just want to be able to talk to someone.  About anything. I feel so completely locked inside myself and no one seems to want to listen.  I just want some attention.  I sit on this bed day after day and I watch them-         ( I never got to finish this ) 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 21. October. 1999                Mehe Nihil Soom- Though Everything            I used to be a very shy, lonely girl. I say girl because I was over 18, but not yet a woman within myself.  I was 18, but still clinging to all my childhood pain and anger, still embracing my teen angst and rebellion; it was all I had to keep me alive.  To keep me from gathering the courage to see what was on the Other Side.  For a year there had been a man who'd been training me, preparing me for things to come, teaching me, forcing me to become more than the sum of my broken parts.  Broken parts- the means were there, but all my foundations were in ruins, and this man, my man, was trying to build on top of rubble.                          I had a restless spirit and a bad home life, so I left.  Proverbially to sow my wild oats.  2 years and my first criminal record later I came home, only different.  Before, I had been nothing, though everything was there for me to be something.  It took countless miles, terrible prices and soul searing agonies to become what I am.  Rape, near homelessness, jail, even a conversation with death, but I'm here.  It took 2 years to realize that I had it all, I just needed to lift it up, clear out the rubble and lay solid groundwork.         Formulas were never my forte. I went about it all backwards. Built the tower before I poured the foundation.  Grew into the woman before I knew she was me.  No one wants to suffer, to know pain and sorrow.  Especially not me, and for so long I thought that was my purpose in life, to live in pain.  It wasn't that.  I was learning. From each new horror and crisis and fire to walk through there was a lesson, a boundary of myself to break through.  Last month I realized that for the first time.  In everything learn something.  Be it good or bad, carry it with you always, for you'll have need of it again.  Last month I became a woman at the age of 21.             Remember that, when you're happiest, and when you're saddest, but especially when you're simply feeling fine.  From eveything, learn something.  From joy learn to smile.  From pain know that joy will follow.  But perhaps most importantly- never leave the house without clean underwear.  You never know when that bus won't stop just because its a red light. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 20. October. 1999                      The One You Want To Be  Calm but unbroken, Tame but unbridled Fettered but free So you smirk my way tell me I'm headstrong and I laugh in your face. I know the soft parts of me, the womanly needs in me, I know how to cross my ankles when I sit. I know the pains of love and the scars of hate. I know ridicule and jest and maliciousness. I know my limits I know how to break them. I know what turns me on, what keeps me going- I know the ending to my own story- know the price I pay for this knowledge, feel the shackles of responsibility... But I know how to rattle my chains and still get what I want. You'll never break me. You'll never bridle me. And I'll always be free. So go on and and smirk and think you know me better- I know me, the soft and the hard, the gentle and the strong, delicate and steely. I know me. I'm the one you want to be.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written.20. October. 1999               Without my Warrior Heart   It is said home is where the heart is, How can that be? Tattered, frayed, bloody, scarred heart that stubbornly continues to beat, to Love, to Hope- Despite Fate itself. How can Home be there, on that already Sundered battlefield?  Home is where you take your heart, Here, there, geography matters not Mountains or oceans, forests or deserts- Home is where you take your heart.  Without my Warrior heart- Nothing would be Home, even heaven. Without my Warrior heart, I would not be what I am, Alive, strong, wise and naive, Without my Warrior heart-  I would not be Home-Within myself.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written 22. March. 2000       You are Me.      You're cool, when I'm hot. You're subtle, when I'm bold. You're tactful, when I'm brash. You're smooth, when I'm rough. You're suave, when I'm uncouth.  You are everything I'm not when I need you to be.  You are all that I am when I'm not myself. You are the sun and the moon and the stars when I am Darkness and Nothing and Void. You are my worst nemesis, you are my dearest lover, my harshest critic, my tragic seer. You are me, when I look in the mirror,  and see my reflection... from your eyes.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written 9. October. 1999              Taunting   Taunting,         in the vague     shiftlessness of Darkness, a teasing laugh, a tender smile- What am I seeing? Truth- my own wishes, simply what I want to see, or something more... Something deeper, hints of longing.    A delusion for a love       starved heart, a bittersweet dream for touch starved skin- flushed and heated beneath my fingers- wet and sticky agaunst my tongue.    Legs, long and tone- arms wrapped tight A blood filled heart beathing rythym with mine- For the Blood is the Life. . .  And shall I feel afraid?    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written 1. March. 2000                  Merely Sleep  Its soft here, Behind my eyes, sensuous,  neither dark nor light, A moment of just Being. Feel my breath Float on sound, Exist in the rythym. Turning and flowing Notes caress my face the way a breeze would Cooling me, fooling me, Such sweet repose Drifting over Mind's Landscapes.   And  There  is Serenity, There is Peace Feel me breath Rising higher, wanting more nestled among worlds Sure of everything, everywhere, every when  Absolute Bliss To be behind my eyes in the right moment. The rest is merely sleep.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written 5. February. 2000                  Down In the Jungle        Down in the jungle Where the hard ones and the horrors play,  in a thorny grove of decadent decay lies the heart of the matter.  The seat of the soul at the base of madness' origin. Down in the jungle, sickly sweet and humid with fright.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm trying to make this page more reader friendly.  And I'm gathering up the energy to transcribe some more stuff.    So bear with me, please.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Well.  So far so good.  I've got an awful case of acid reflux at the moment, so this will be short and sweet.  If anyone would like to comment on the poems or writings here, feel free to do so at witchylass@hotmail.com. Anyway, I need to get rid of this feeling of being eaten by acid, so ttfn.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Written 10. October. 1999            I swear there's a certain ennui trickling within me.  A languid sort of viewing, perception of the world that worries me almost more than the situation from which it originates.  I took a breath, and my whole world fell away when I exhaled, and I was forced to look at all the foundations on which I'd built the city of me.  What I found was less than solid construction.      So I razed all the old foundations and in record time rebuilt using all new, indestructable materials.  Solid as the oak, but with the power to bend as the willow, and offer shelter to others in the storms.  Perhaps its just a fanciful metaphor for saying that I changed my life's values and perceptions in the space of a week.  o maybe I like verbosity. But even that irreverence is part of who I am.      I thought my time in Atlanta was hell. It was everything a tearjerking, anger inciting, heart anguishing Lifetime movie of the week should be.  I nearly died in Atlanta.  And so I thought Atlanta was my hell.  It turns out San Antonio was.  For the first time I knew true, paralyzing, fork against your fillings tasting terror.  And in the three days I lost contact with the outside world, my life shattered around me.  I was homeless, friendless, penniless, and had nothing but the phone numbers in my head and the clothes on my back.  In the month since that time I have had to push the limits of who I am and what I was capable of to the breaking point- and beyond.  I've swallowed all my pride and given up every spark of dignity. But by doing so, I broke all my own boundaries and rebuilt all my crumbling foundations- I renovated who I was.  Became who I am.  Its only in the last month that I finally gave up all my childish trappings and become a woman.        I'm not preaching.  Gods know I had enough of that from my Mother last week.  I guess what I'm saying is never give up.  I know how it can be so tempting to drop your head onto the pillow of eternal sleep.  But its not as fun as seeing just how strong you are.  It sucks while its happening, but when its all over- Gods it feels almost better than sex.  I couldn't begin to tell you what's on the other side of life, but for me- its infinitely more fun to see how far I can go, how much of my own potential I can fulfill.        No matter what though, be true to you.  Because its not really worth it if you're not.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     written 2. November. 2000        Flip your hair and take a walk- on the not so wild side. Breakdown in a break up ruined life in a ruined date and what do you know of true pain? Of silent screams and bleeding wounds that will never be seen, never be healed.      Do you nails and jog around the block of your upper middle class suburbia. Never mind the wrong side of the tracks where the down trodden struggle to feed children who dodge bullets on the way to school.      Don't you worry about a thing, dear. But don't expect anything from me except gleeful laughter when the inevitable happens- and you tumble from your slick little pedestal- into my dementia.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						           First written 22. December. 2000                 Sovereignty of my Soul.    There is but one Mistress here, and no master.     I hold the key, and the lock, and the Universe resides in my soul.      Made of star stuff and filled with light, and I alone hold control of its destiny.    An eternity of knowledge fused into flesh and sinew, blood and bone.   By Divine right I sit upon my Throne of Scone and royal fiant alone bind my commands.   I am High Queen, and Master Sorceress and kin to the dragon of my heart.   Gods alone know the razor edge I walk on the verge of continual disaster.   But I alone am Sovereign of my Soul, and I alone pay for my mistakes.   I alone bring about my fate; I alone must face it straight.   So there will never be master here, and only myself mistress, for I am the Sovereign of my Soul.        Would that I did not have to rule... alone.         

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Forewarned is forearmed.  So they say.  The saying sometimes is easier than the doing, a thing we already know.  The majority of the postings here will be transcriptions.  Journals, essays, poems, snatches of short stories.  In short, all that which make sme who I am.  Writing comes more naturally to me than breathing oftentimes.  But I need a permanent residence for those scribbling and bibblings as Mozart put them, and so here is where I choose to do so.  And here they can not be tarnished, nor used, nor stolen from me and destroyed in a fit of adolescent temper.  my goal in this is two fold.  Firstly I wish to have a chronological record of my life, or at least all I was able to save from the Hell and go on to do.  Secondly I want to be remembered.  My greatest fear is being forgotten, that after my death my life, my mind, my heart will simply fade away, like the dust of the earth I return to.  In this medium I can assuage myself of that fear somewhat.  So I begin with a poem written little less than a month ago, though some entries will date back years.  Be assured that I will preface each one with the original date beforehand.  And now I bid you adieu for this evening, and welcome.... to the world of me.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        This is MY letter to the world. A detailing of all the slings and arrows this  outrageous fortune of a life has chosen to throw at me thus far. As it was, as it is, as  it shall ever be. Each moment is a learning experience. And each lesson is an  opportunity to grow, to change, to become more fully what we truly are. So read as  you will, learn if you want. But if you walk away from my pontifications with one  thing, walk away knowing that this is just one perception in a Universe of  perceptions. And it may never write to me.... but this Is my letter to the world. This  lifetime, anyway 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 31. January. 2001  (This was comissioned by a very dear friend of many lifetimes.  Working on revisions, to be posted. ) Dreams past  When we are able, not to look beyond- but beneath. When dreams past fade, spins into shadow-  becomes lessons learned. When time slips not away, but spins outward into infinity and back again. When the faces we wear no longer are masks, but facets of ourselves  Only then will we see the whole, see the Universe in the blinding light of truth. But not blind for the we shall SEE the soul beneath- know the spirit true heart that makes up our existence.  Linger not in the shadows, in the realm of dreams past. Move into the light of truth, the gravity of love. Look beneath. Look to the Soul. Only then- will we know peace.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 4. November. 2000   A blank sheet of lined paper, like this, is intimidating to me.  I feel compelled to write, but when I open the notebook, and the blank page is before me- I clam up.  Its like some twisted version of performance anxiety.  Time and again this happens and it never fails to leave me frustrated and unfulfilled.  As though I'm taking some cosmic test of merit, intelligence, and inevitably I think I'm going to fail.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 4. November. 2000   A blank sheet of lined paper, like this, is intimidating to me.  I feel compelled to write, but when I open the notebook, and the blank page is before me- I clam up.  Its like some twisted version of performance anxiety.  Time and again this happens and it never fails to leave me frustrated and unfulfilled.  As though I'm taking some cosmic test of merit, intelligence, and inevitably I think I'm going to fail.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 11. January. 2000   There's something about a roast beef sandwich at 5 in the morning that's just bliss.  Absolutely wonderful.  Too bad I don't have the energy for another one.  One should be enough.  Nobody's been in anyone else's shoes.  We all have our own private pains.  Its how we deal with them, integrate them into our shared lives that defines who we are individually.  I have this frustrating feeling like everything I write has been written before, like the same perception has been explained by someone else, and so I'm just copying.  There is nothing new under the sun and Gods how finely I feel it, how precisely, how keenly.   How many variations on the same can there truly be?   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 11. January. 2000   sitting in the tub, head bent- the spray showering down on me; its silent, except for the water And its a small thing, but I love it, you can't take it from me.    the lines in a hand, tendons flexing, veins bubbling to the surface- such aesthetic beauty to me- such wonder in a hand, you can't take it from me.  I'm running away from the change. From the knowledge.  From the being.  From the doing.  I don't know how to break through I don't know how to get anyone to listen to me.  I wrap myself in silence, blanket my world with denial, so that I don't have to face it.  I'll never get what I want that way.  I don't know what I want.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   (No date on this on, but done late Sept.-Oct. 2000)  Tell me what it means to be one of the chosen ones And maybe I'll choose you. Show me what it is to know arms around me, and maybe I'll wrap mine around you. Give me access to just one hour of your love, your reason for living, and maybe I'll let myself fall in love with you. Teach me to feel the fullness of life and death, And maybe I'll learn to revere you.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 11. August. 2000   Precious Gems  All the glitters is gold, But not all gold is worthwile. Fool's gold, thieving deceiver, Tightropes treacherously walked over pipe dreams, Phantom Hopes, Glittering brightly, waiting to be snatched Away.  Diamonds are forever, But hope soon whithers, sundered.  Flashing in the harsh sun, Dangling happiness like prisms- Rainbow colours on the walls Icy talons eager to rip, shred, Tear me from myself.   Sapphires sparkle, Flowing like tears, mine And deepen into obsidian flakes- Chipping at my heart- Until my blood runs like rubies Fevered attempts at self preservation A treasure chest of pain.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 16. August. 2000       ( The original is of course, in pencil )   God damn, pencil  I can't stand using pencil.  Nor can I abide erasing with it.  I need the permanence of ink, the starkness of jelly roll styling.  I needs PENS!  I'm a writer, I write.  I am attempting to catch every moment of my life on paper.  Do I want to go back later and change it?  Edit and rework it until it is no longer a moment I captured as it happened?   Do I want to erase the life I'm trying to encapsulate in indelible grammar?  So how the bloody, buggery hell am I supposed to use pencil?!?!?!?! Pencil implies fleeting, temporary, not meant to linger.  It feels faded and inconstant, easily marred and taken away.  Its like taking back something I did, or said, or thought, or wanted.  Oh, I'll just erase it and it will never have happened.  Its like saying I can move ahead without looking back.    Then, THEN!, there's the physical.  Two paragraphs from the top and I'm nearly on my third pencil- they wear down so easily!  Too fast!  First the line starts out thin, distinct, sharp and crisp.  But then as you continue the thinness flattens, becomes fat, lazy.  You find yourself pushing harder, holding the damn thing at wierd angles to get more readable letters.  Your fingers hurt, your penmanship falters and your level of frustration grows exponentially with each fat lazy, indistinct letter until-  you change to a new, sharp, clean lined pencil.  At least for a little while.    And after all that bullshit, if you're very lucky, in a week it won't be so faded you can't read it.  More often than not, though, it will be nearly gone, lost forever to the redundancy of smudging graphite.    God damn, pencil  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   (Again, no date, though I know this was written at least 4 or more years ago. Please note:  As with a number of other poems, this one is meant to be centered down the page.  Unfortunately, either blogger doesn't have that feature, or I haven't figured out how to access it...yet. )   Wicca   Phallus.  Womb. Fertility religion. Invoke the Goddess in her earthly form.   Earth.  Water.  Fire.  Air. Strength of Stone. Power of Light. The circle opens.  The coven unites.   Heated tantric dance. Fearless. Careless. The invocation is completed. The praise is given. The spells are cast. The beauty seen. The wonder awed. The gods thanked. Phallus and womb become one. The seeds are offered. The circle closes.  The Persecution. The Burning. The Hanging. The Ignorance. The Hatred Reigns. The Rape of the magic. The Loss of the Truth.  Dispersion. Secrecy. Solitary Practices. The Fear of Discovery. The Careful Steps. Silent Offerings. Hidden Desires. Coupling in the darkness of ignorance. Praises given under the veil of disguise. The magic remains alive.  The Darkness lifts. The Bold step into the Light. The Courageous reunite. The Coven forms again. A new Age begins. Ignorance is smothered in wonder. Left festering in the blackened hearts. To be reborn as the Wheel begins to turn again.  The Darkness will fall anew. The Hatred will rule again. But the Magic will remain sacred. The Truth will remain hidden. The Practices will continue. The Covens formed.  The circles cast. Wicca will remain alive. Blessed be the Gods. So Mote it be.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 22. September. 1995   Cigarette.  The young woman sat on the dock in her jeans and her NIN shirt.  She wasn't really looking at the water as much as she was looking through it.  Clear through to the murky depths of her psyche.  Anyone seeing her there would've thought her to be a statue.  Although the guys who drove past thought she was a pretty good looking statue with her knee pulled up so her arm could rest on it while her other leg dangled over the side of the dock.      But she doesn't notice her surroundings.  She's too preoccupied with her own mental introspection to care about anything else.  'This has got to stop. I can't live like this anymore.  Never again. Someone help me.  Never again.  Quoth the raven, Nevermore.'  Why does she always get off track?  The young woman slowly lets her eyes focus on the water around her.  Its green and colorfully murky, with an oily covering.   She delicately reaches into her shirt pocket and draws out a long, slender cigarette and a lighter.  Carefully, she lights the cigarette, takes a large, nicotine filled drag, and replaces her lighter.  She watches the smoke as she blows it out, noticing the swirls and inconsistencies of its patterns.           She languidly flicks an ash into the water and watches it try to stay afloat.  Her life is a paradox.  She can't think.  She can't cry.  She can't feel.  She simply focuses all her remaining energy on smoking her cigarette.  She lays back, enjoying the feel of the wooden planks under her back.  She takes another addiction guaranteeing drag and exhales sensuously, as if she were in a deep, long term relationship with her cigarette.  In a sense she is.  The cigarete has her undivided attention, her absolute focus to the act of sucking in and blowing out.  The art of french inhaling is like a long lost lover's kiss.  At least to the woman.  Briefly, her attention leaves her cigarette and refocuses on the calming polluted waters around her.  Hindsight is always 20-20.  But she can't go back now.  The bridge was burned.  Along with the rest of her heart.  The young woman closes her eyes and lets a barely audible sigh escae her slightly parted lips.  One small, clear, delicate tear seeps out of the corner of her eye and leaves a salty, sorrowful track down her face.  She takes another drag.  She is determined to finish her cigarette.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 27. November, 2000   I feel like Madame Bovary, only without the opportunity to take on lovers and thereby spill passion everywhere.  Any real feeling I have for this world or the people in it is so  far gone from me as to never have existed.  I AM comfortably numb.          

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 18. May. 2000   What's it like to write, to really write?  To start with a single word on a blank, virginal page and add to it?  To watch this child, grow and mature, page after page, until at last you look before you and you've borne a work, purely from the bits and pieces in your head.  What's it like to look upon this body of work and know that you created it, breathed life into it?   And how do you then offer it up for the world to tear apart or elevate to godhood as it chooses?  Once I know the answers to these questions- do I dare to create?  Or leave those creations inside of myself where they'll be protected and nurtured and never subject to the persecution and torment and lamentation of existence?   Do I even have time to worry about any of this? 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 13. February. 2001  ( Yes, this is the most recent poem I've written.  And its silly, but its kind of cute, too. )  Sleepy Nap Time  Its raining soft, light, the kind that makes you want to curl up- take a nap.  The sky is gray, but not oppressing. just shadowy enough that you can throw the curtains open, and sleep comfortably in the light.  Bed's warm, dark sheets, fluffy blankets, perfect with the egg crate foam underneath cozy and inviting me, a doorway to dream land.  The cat is resting, lolling, luxuriating, fitting her soft body next to mine- one eye cracked open, then close- purring next to me as we drift off into Morpheus' Lair-  Floating off to Sleepy Nap Time.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 14. November. 2000   I had the oddest dream last night.  Or rather a series of dreams.  A family with a secret who was forced to destroy its home- and the one that sits more uneasily with me:  Alison who had powers, a dragon ability, fell in love with the devil.  And how he was attractive.  I think I fell in love with him, too.  After losing her head, she gave up her powers in order to live with him in Hell.  They left, and I was to await either his return, or David's.  Mother actually came, and there was a huge fight.  A school type function, and then I called Him- and he was so wonderful- so alluring and captivating.  He and Alison had broken up and I pleaded my case- he agreed.  Then the alarm woke me up.    I can never describe it well enough afterwards, can never get all the little details.  Was I dreaming about Keith and this upcoming date symbolically?  I wish I could find the meaning of it.  Was it a warning?  A test of some kind to be passed?  Gods, I wish I knew.  I nearly called in so I could go back to it.  I'm here at work, however.  And still very much affected by it.  I imagine I will be for quite awhile.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 17. November. 2000     Keenly  Time passes so slowly when You're so keenly aware of it. Its not like you killed someone Except perhaps yourself Choking on tedious time Gagging on inconsequential inertia Counting the seconds as your will Slithers away Leaving an empty time- So keenly aware of Its passing so slowly.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 30. March. 2000   Personal Observations.  So it goes.  I'm trying very hard not to let the shadows over take me.  Even if the shadows are in my own mind.  They say you're not going insane if you can question your own sanity.  I'm not so sure.  But I'm trying.  Trying very hard.  If I'm truly unable to face up to my own past, will I finally be consumed by it?  Can I stand up to my own shadows, or will I have to admit defeat and go on the 'happy' drugs?    And so it goes.  And I'm still trying very hard not to let the shadows overtake me.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 9. October. 2000    fly away if I could- Soar above it all and watch as it fell away to nothing. Let the current take me, blow me, flow me, twist and mold me, clean me- of all the dirt. I'd land, fresh, almost new, anonymous- And I'd start over.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 15. October. 2000      I tried.  I tried to love you- and you turned me away. I tried to live for you- and you told me I was better off dead. I tried to fight for you- and you shunned my blade. I tried to defend you- and you led yourself to slaughter.  I gave you all of me, life love, soul, blood, sweat, and tears.   All my sorrow, all my pain. My shame. Every ounce of control. All my joy was yours.  I held the world back for you. And you just walked away.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ( This one isn't dated, but it can't have been written more than 2 months ago. )  Gentle fingers through my hair- am I consoling myself? Heated bubble bath, Am I soothing myself? Sherry sipped before a warming fire- Am I indulging myself?  I'm refusing, certainly- but what I'm not sure. Give in, give up, resign myself to melancholy? To solitude and pain? Solitude maybe, but not pain I'm happy in my aloneness. I am peaceful in my silence. I win.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ( Here's a haiku I wrote for my sister because she couldn't come up with one for class.  Written in the last 3 weeks. )  Autumnal wind blows gently through my raven locks Fall is nearing fast. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 12. September. 2000      I think today  I think I said farewell today to all the haunts of my past Wolfie's Death Mass presided- in apropos solemnity. But I think I mourned for today all the ashen dreams, crumbled hopes Silence hovered in that sky, pregnant with accusation.  And I wonder how much fight is left within me I wonder how much further I can go- Alone. If I keep breathing is it the same as fighting, or admission of laziness. If I don't have the strength to fight, am I too weak to end it?  I think I said farewell today- But I'm not sure to what.      

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 2. October. 2000      Will It?  My life My love My joy, my hate My shame, my pride- I gave it all to you. And it still wasn't enough. I've been such a very good friend Held back the world for you Carried your reality on my shoulders- So it wouldn't crumble in your face- And still it wasn't enough. It was never enough. And it never will be... Will it?   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 30. August. 2000   Its time for me to stop and take a breath- to look around and see what I can see.  Not that I'm going too fast, But I'm too deep, too mired down in the mundane, slowly drowning without even knowing it.  I have to take a step back and look at the whole of it- at least that which I can See.    Perhaps I'm so deeply embedded in the little things that I've really become detached from Spirit and so yearn for adventure, for change I know I don't need.  I wish I could meld the two, so I could function smoothly between, ins tead of having to flip back and forth, using energy and resources that are limited to begin with.  This is my goal, to achieve fluidity; as I grow and learn I believe it can happen.      Through it all there is this lethargy, a weariness that grows every day, an increasing desire for true silence.  I fight myself even as I am resigning myself to the care of Spirit, and it is exhausting me.    I've begun to wonder how much further I can go alone.  I wonder if I even want to.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 10. January. 2000      Nothing Really.    New century, new pen, new paper. Nothing really changes. Its not right, this year, it started to well, won't stop.  Each night I lay me down to sleep Each morning I wake up just the same. Nothing really changes. I breath the same breath, think the same thoughts. Go through the same motions.  I want to rip holes in all my shirts to see if anything looks different on the other side. I want to see through someone else's eyes. I want to make amends for my wrongs.  Each night I lay me down Each breath I wonder what changed In me- Nothing, really.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 7. July. 2000   So you read a poem in front of a group and you got a goodly amount of applause- maybe not the biggest, nor yet the most- but enough. To make you smile, to make you proud, to make you think maybe you're not so gawky and ungainly as you thought. Maybe, just maybe, you have some worth. Maybe. But its early yet, and there's so much more of your soul you want to expose, to lay open like a living autopsy for the eyes of others.   Maybe its not time, maybe your not ready- Maybe they're not. You think you could, if the time was right, if all the facets fell into place- if the planets aligned and the Dark Crystal were healed- if Ogra knew, if Jareth made his maze easier to solve.  If Hercules became a God and Xena begged to be your love slave forever- if Ares learned compassion.    If all these things happen- and if I can know true love- Then what the hell, I'll let them all see... All of me.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 21. February. 2000   Work  At this moment I'm sincerely wondering if we're going home early.  I don't think I'd complain.  I'd like to sleep, but the Ginseng is keeping me from nodding off at work.   And just for the record, I think the missing link is sitting next to me.  Not that it really matters, I'll take my break and with any luck be out of here by 9.  I've taken to hanging up on my calls. The ones I do take always kick out in the screener.  Still though, there are worse jobs than this.  Its amazing the assumptions people make on sight alone.  And how easily they disregard the truth if presented with it- We really are just lambs eagerly being led to the slaughter.  The Bible teaching us to be better herd animals, Republicans helping us to to sodomize ourselves gleefully, and the government urging us to kill ourselves in the most painful and torturous way we can- by slowly polluting, raping, and destroying our own world around us.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 10. January. 2000     I dreamed about Death last night- and it came on a pale horse to take me away. And I dreamed about God the night before. He talked and gesticulated, and said, 'Suffer the children', but didn't give me peace. Last week I dreamt of blood- imagine that. Hot and thick, flowing in my veins nectar of the Lost Gods. Someone died in my dream two months ago. And soon after two uncles died,  and I stopped to take a breath.  Maybe later I'll dream about you.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 22. February. 2000   ( Here's a tiny phrase that I always wanted to construct into a more in depth poem.  )  Fire walk with me Because sometimes My arms bend back. Perfection is the dream of those with no imagination. We can't all be heroes, Can we? 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 2. January. 2000   ( This was written about a man who I gave 5 long years to.  And to whom I am still enternally bonded.  We may never speak to each other again, and ours is a long, long story, but we'll always be each others.  And no, it was never a romantic relationship. )  There's a feeling of justification as I sit here writing, a feeling that I did what needed to be done.  Ours paths are ultimately seperate, but forever intertwined; in that respect we'll always be friends.  But I need to embark on a personal journey, I need to go forward and carve my own niche, and he can't be there for that. Its the same feeling from San Antonio, and this time I HAVE to act on it- I have to heed the calling.  Its time for my spark to flare to brilliant life.        He heard his calling long ago.  And I'm sorry if these actions and decisions hurt him, but its my turn to shine.  I know how selfish that sounds, and that's not how its meant.  I want him to understand, but its not necessary for me to keep going if he doesn't.    Its almost as though I'm standing outside of myself watching the drama.  I don't need him anymore, though I'll always want him near me.  There's a transcendance here, of all the things small and material, and he knows it.  The move was a catalyst only.  I'm happy where I am.  I'm safe.  I'm excited about my future.  I'm free.  I'm challenged, and esteemed, and centered within myself.  I'm ready.  I'm not forsaking the past, nor ignoring the present.  I'm finally learning all my lessons.  I'm doing it without him.  No bad blood, no ill will.  I'm coming into my own, on my own.  I feel justified.  I feel right.  I feel whole.  I feel love.      I feel alive.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 25. March. 2000   5 years ago on this day I was writing the blackest poetry of my life. Only then I didn't know what true blackness really was.  I'd had a nice, healthy taste of it, no denying that, but I hadn't been beyond it, to the light, only to make the stupidest mistake and be plunged back into that darkness.  Now, here, 5 years later, I've seen that light, that happiness, been able to walk that path-and yet I still made a stupid mistake.  But the funny thing is it feels more like a slap on the wrist. As if the Universe has said, 'Hey now, we didn't help you achieve your freedom from the Dark so you could turn your back on it. Straighten up, now, you have a destiny to attend to.'       I do have a destiny to fulfill.  I will be known, remembered.  So this mistake of mine won't end up amounting to much.  My karma here will be short and swift and generally painless.  There will be a few snags, a few tangles to work out, but in the end it won't keep me from what's ahead.  And so long as I heed this slap on the wrist and go about paying my karma, I won't be any worse off than if I'd never done it.  I grew complacent, and careless, and while the hidden irony of it is shaded blue- its still no one's fault but mine.  So be it.  I will pay, and continue on my path, and never once look back.    I want to tell you a wonderous story, filled with love and happiness and dreams coming true.  I want to tell you this glorious tale, but I can't.  What I can tell you is a tale of unwavering devotion, of true friendship.  A tale of heartbreak and tragedy, of trial and sacrifice.  What I can tell you is a tale of life, and of one life in particular, and how there may not be true happy endings, but there is survival, and in the midst of darkness- there can be life.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 3. December. 1999    Been out of reach and Seperatist feeling the coming of the new age as keenly as the icy steel of the razor-against my wrist pressing in, a thin line of blood welling up- Red and wet, as tempting as any Biblical apple.  Washed in the blood, And shall I feel afraid. Hell at one dark window, Death at my back, breathing down my neck Caressing my Dark side, my Isis. You're leading me astray. And I almost begged you to on my knees, giving you everything you demanded.  Undeniably jealous, watching others go before me But shall I feel afraid? Or wake up- from this bittersweet nightmare?  Do I want to? 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 1. April. 2000   ( This was something that popped into my head one night at work. No real context, just.. this. )    It was filled with a wonderous sound that flowed over me and through me until I thought surely I would be swept away by it.  It was as though I was going to die and find before me the Elysium Fields.      I stood there transfixed, seeing colors bloom behind my closed eyes in time with the music and I knew I would have this played at my passing over.  The music faded finally, and slowly I opened my eyes, letting the real world take shape around me once more.  I drew in a long, heart felt sigh of peacefulness and reached down to pluck a sprig of mint from the ground before setting off.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 9. October. 1999          Who.  I lusted for you, I wanted you, I loved you with all that I am. You turned it away. In anger I cursed you, in pain I bled for you. You turned it away. I loved you.  I needed you. You turned me away.  But who is the stronger now?   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Written. 21. November. 1999      In the shadowed darkness of moonless night- I search for you. In the cries of a new dying infant, I yearn for you. In the screams of lost innocence, I moan for you. In the heated core of my sex, I come for you. In the suffering of our existence, I live for you. In the bloodlust of timeless feedings I call to you. In the death, in the life, I will find you, I will love you, To Death.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   (Unsure when this was written, as I didn't date it. Grr.)     Desperate in my questing vigil lonely in my waking hour restless in the dark corners. Not quite comfortable- in this  new skin. Loose threads in the raveled parts. I'm not quite- whole. Something missing, undefined. Some small stitch- in the design; I'm questing to find it. A silent, watchful vigil. Lonely when I think to be. restless as it lays undiscovered, as time flows by. Lonely, when I lay down at night,  when I can't think of anything else. And I'm still searching For this elusive link, this small thing to make me- whole. Still keeping vigil, still questing- still lonely when I think to be. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 2. March. 2000         How like Me      I fell away from you as you reached for me. And I reached out, too, How futile of me.     I thought I wanted you, when you didn't need me. And I longed to need, too, How foolish of me.  I searched to find you, as you tried not to hide. And I lost you completely, how naive of me.  I screamed for your release as you proved not to be captive. And in so doing shut myself away, how misguided of me.  I fought to make you a dream come true And all the while you were there before me, How like me, to miss the forest for the trees.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 9. June. 2000          Failure  Strength of Stone Be in My Bone Power of Light Sustain my Fight In this my Darkest Hour Help me find within myself the Power When dawn afire crests the horizon Let this icy heart be no more frozen  In the passage of time, the winds of change did blow This war is over, Bury me low In that my darkest hour, no Light came saving No Gallant Knight, no Gods a-waving And nothing from within my soul All was slience, Lifeless and cold. Stone as water, Light was as ink- Take off my sword, Carry me slow This war is over- And I failed.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 16. August. 1999                  Just Now    I am  a pretty piece of flesh I am, a neatly coded set of numbers I am, A convergance of Molecular structures I am, A thought, an action, a deed I am, A sentence, a knowing, a consciousness I am,  A mind, a heart, a soul I am, A sense, a touch, a taste I am, A smell, a sight, a sound I am A need, a yearning, a hunger I am, A current of running electricity I am, A nexus within my own resistance I am, A safe harbor within my own stormy seas I am, A consoler of my own cries I am, A romantic buried in cynicism I am, A quester buried in complacency I am, Watching the audience for any hint of approval I am, Slowly exposing my secrets for perusal I am, Living proof that pain can suffer I am, But half complete without my darkness I am, There always, should you have need of me I am, Just now Learning to understand who  I am.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 7. January. 2000               Dive    Poison flowing through my veins, exploding into the chambers, of my heart. A willing overdose. Treacherous ground to walk, these legs beg run and I stand- Firmly grounded head thrown back as the wave crests over me, eyes wide to take in what I can. Teeth, shivering in my jaw from the excstasy. A poison in my body, in  my blood, But Gods I love it, fall into it.  Dive headfirst, Into Crysania.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Acid Steel... Conclusion.   Its not possible. You can't be stalked by a figment of your own imagination. Never the less she's there. Maybe half a block behind me. I can't think straight. I'm still seeing trailers, flashes, visuals all over the place. She's amused by this. Enjoying my discomfort, my confusion, my... arousal. I AM aroused, I can feel it now, my nipples hard, warmth between my legs as I speed up, trying to put some space between us. I close my eyes to focus internally. I could walk these streets blind I know them so well. I think I want her to catch me. I'm sure I can hear her chuckle from behind me. The chase is on.  I walk even faster, turning corners, feeling the hunter, reveling in being the prey. How did I get here? Oh yes, the acid. Of course. I've never been hunted by my trip before. Interesting take on things. I'm almost running now, buildings and people and colours streaking past. I can feel the wetness between my legs now, nipples so hard, aching; they could cut glass. How is this possible? Don't think, just look for- yes, there. turn down that alley. I stop, catching my breath, one hand on the wall for support. In a heartbeat she's there before me. Sweet Jesus I'm caught. Trapped. Right where I want to be. I am so thoroughly enjoying this, even if it isn't real and I'm chasing shadows.  Her hands are on my shoulders; I hear the notebook slip from my fingers, fall to the damp ground with a thud. I catch a flash of white teeth, a triumphant smile, and then her lips are on mine and they're ice cold. I think I groaned, tried to exert power over my own hallucination- yank her roughly against me. She pins my arms above my head and laughs and open my eyes, knowing, realizing, seeing. She's completely real, always was. And she was always in control of this... encounter. Fear mixes with desire and my knees feel weak, but I'm paralyzed. I've never wanted anything more. She kisses me again, roughly this time, her tongue pushing past the barrier of my clenched teeth, twining with my steel studded tongue, so eager. There's danger here. I can feel it throbbing through me and it spurs me on and on; how I've been searching for this.  She releases my arms and immediately I cup her breasts, firm, ripe, tracing the outline of her nipple rings through her shirt. She's got one hand in my crotch, torturing me through my jeans as our tongues war. I want to feel her, taste her, penetrate her with my tongue and fingers- see her writhe beneath me, begging for release. With an effort I pull away from her damnable tongue and drop to my knees, pushing her legs farther apart as I flip up her plaid skirt. Now I can smell her wetness, slick bliss. My hands travel up her legs, fingers peeling apart her labia and I thrust my tongue into her tight, wet hole, then dart quickly up, flicking over her clit, all swollen and pink. I hear her moan and now there's a heartbeat pounding in my head but I can't tell whose it is. I've never tasted anyone like her, so sweet, with a tang- but she's pulling me up, away from her sex and I whimper, a child whose toy's ben taken away. She's staring at me, drowning in those eyes again, so green, like a meadow I saw as a child...and we were running through it, laughing and kissing...  The same wall where I first saw her. Some of the same people milling about. The same quasi punk rock music overhead. Only this time no one talks to me. No one wants to. I don't mind. I smile to myself, remembering- her lips on my neck, the sharp sting of her fangs, and then- ecstasy. My lips on her wrist, the font opened for me to drink of, fountain of youth, and death. The blood flowing hot and thick and coppery, ambrosia of the Lost Gods, the Dark Ones. Better than any acid trip. Forevermore. She was real. I remember how warm her lips were when she kissed me afterward, how cool mine had become. She was gone when I awoke that night. She was gone and I was a vampire and we'd never even spoken a word.  Now I'm the one against the wall, letting the hunger build,looking for dinner amidst all the heated teen age rebellion. Perfect hunting ground. I'm melancholy suddenly. Never again do I get the option of joining in. Forever on the edge, watching, observing. What the hell though, I wanted this, and the sex is great, but the blood... the blood is always better. Another smile- dinner just walked past in a black leather trench and pony tailed blond hair. Pushing off the wall I follow dinner, and the soft clink of steel against my fangs sounds natural amidst the roar of pulsing, throbbing hearts, flowing blood, all around me.   (NOTE: THis and all works of mine are CopyRighted. All right Reserved.)  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 3. March. 2001    Acid Steel   ( WARNING: This is pure fiction, scraped from the leftovers of my psyche.  Part 2 to follow soon.)  The soft clink of steel against my teeth sounds natural amidst the back drop of raucous teens in various stages of rebellious rantings. Ski caps and wallet chains, and mohawks in abundance. I sit quiet, alone, dressed almost somberly in untucked button down shirt and jeans; I'm watching. Occasionally someone will come up to me, someone I know, to see how I am- mingle- before moving on to more enjoyable company. I'm not very good company tonight, would rather watch than talk, feeling the ebb and flow of anger laced angst. I never did quite fit in here, though it was fun to pretend. But tonight is different somehow, things are vaguely distorted. I feel eyes on me even as I'm eyeing everyone else. And then I catch a glimpse of her at the corner of my vision, little snatches as people walk past. She's leaning against the wall on the far side of the room, a wallflower against a mural of clouds.  I think at first she's not real She looks exactly as I'd always imagined someone like her might look. I think maybe the acid I took earlier is starting to kick in. She's tall but not lanky, tone and lithe- inhuman is the word that slips into my mind. Thinking her a figment of my hallucinogenically enhanced mind I don't bother to not stare. The crowd things and I have an unobstructed view of her; I'm drinking her in with my eyes. She's pale, but so are most of the people here, under this lighting, would be Goths and creatures of the night, or simply malnourished. A heart shaped face, full lips, she reminds me of the actress Angelina Jolie. Her hair is dark and short, but in this light its hard to determine what color. High cheekbones, small ears; I'm avoiding looking at her eyes. Finally, I bring mine to hers, impossibly deep, impossibly green, impossibly alive. Inhuman. There it is again, a warning? The floor drops out from under me and suddenly I'm falling, drowning in her eyes. I never knew what they meant by that until now.   I can't be here. I must be starting to peak to feel this intensely, to dream up someone so real, so Alive. But I can't take my eyes from hers, can't stop this free fall, can't breathe even- and like that someone walks past, and I jerk my eyes away, the connection broken. I stand, grabbing up my notebook and cigarettes. Keeping my head down I slip out the back door and into the cool autumnal evening air. Already I feel better. More grounded, though I can feel the acid coursing through me and I shake off my hallucination, a bad trip avoided.  I hear again the clink of the tongue bar against my teeth as I walk away, down the street, letting the LSD skewed world tilt and tumble around me, getting lost in mundane sights and sounds turned hazy, abstract. I've gone from Teen angst to being part of a Salvador Dali painting. I'm strolling down the sidewalk, notebook in one hand, lit cigarette in the other. I've always had a talent for acting perfectly sober in public, no matter my mental state. No one pays me any mind. There's an accident up ahead, squad cars everywhere, their flashing blue and reds drawing me like a moth to a flame. I look like all the other rubberneckers milling about, but its those lights I'm looking at. The colours are swirling and blending, exploding into prisms of trippy enlightenment. But I've gawked long enough, my interest is waning and I move on with a sigh. Nothing really holds my interest anymore. Such a wasted, jaded life is mine.   She's following me.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 10. November. 2000   My second day at yet another new job.  Will I ever settle in one place and be happy?  Somehow I highly doubt it.  The closest I've ever come is TCIM in Oklahoma and that was due to a lack of options and transportation.  And what of the position promised me if I move to Longview?  TCIM, yes.  But won't I suffer the same ennui, the same burn out for its being on the phones?  I truly did enjoy working at Waldenbooks and at Priscilla's.  Variety, the chance to meet new people- but in both cases my physical limitations played a major role.  So back to the phones, back to the doldrums.  And why am I complaining when there are still starving children in Africa and Hitler's reincarnation ready to take office here in America?   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 27. February. 1993  ( This is one of the very first poems I ever wrote. )  Some people  Some people can't even believe that there are others unlike them.  Some people can't figure out that the First Amendment goes both ways like the split in a dress' hem.  Some people are just so ignorant that they can't believe they aren't god!  Some people are just too stupid to realize that there is a real life, especially the death squad.  Well some people will never, ever learn, and they will never, ever earn in mind as well as social and soulful knowledge.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 9. April. 2000  (This was a person I'd met and Really wanted to develop a relationship with.)  A chance  Hes mesmerizing.  I'm fascinated by him.  He intimidates me.  Someone so good looking, so handsome, so witty and intelligent.  I feel I don't deserve him and I don't even have him, yet.  Perhaps I never will.  But don't I deserve?  Haven't I struggled and fought for exactly this?   I've let my hopes rocket into space.  Why shouldn't I?  I'm so frightened I've scared him off.  I pray he calls.  It would be such a validation of all my past pains if he calls.  A validation that I'm just as real, just as worth something so good.  Even just in friendship, gods.  I could spend hours looking at him.  I could spend years being thrilled, challenged by his intellect.  I'm not fooling anyone.  I want much more than friendship, I know.  I want passion and seduction, hot kisses and fevered caresses, whispered words.  I want to make out in dark theatres and flirt with our eyes in public.  More than that I want to be able to touch him, to put my arms around him, to feel his arms around me.  I want him to put an end to my lonliness that night after night leaves me frustrated and pained.  I want to be able to call him my boyfriend to other people and know its true.  I want a full fledged relationship, even if its not for love or forever.  And I want it to be with him.     Kevin Patrick Dougherty.  Mulder in a ball cap and sexy black coat.  Oh gods, I hope he calls.  I want it so much.  A chance: Conclusion  I'm surrounded by shadows even though I'm trying to live as much in the light as I can.  And he never called.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 21. February. 2000   I smile  He told me I had a good voice, pretty eyes, but then claimed allerigies when I tried to repay with a kiss. Is it my inexperience? My naivete that keeps them away.   You make the best friend they say. And its always just me alone  at the end of the day. Mentally I went beyond the physical, emotionally I moved beyond the mental. But there's still the emptiness, there's still the physical, and so my lonliness begins to feel simply logical. In that moment I began to make my masks, hiding from myself even, anything even remotely resembling human contact.  And the cobwebs form, the dust settles, the shadows move in to claim their domain and I pretend that I like them, that I love the dark.  I pretend to enjoy only what I can see in the light.  I tend to my hidden places because even I know that to shed light on them would destroy my logical existence.  I smile when love blossoms in the world around me.  I smile and step down on another thorm from my hidden places, my savage garden.  I smile and shed another drop of blood to my pain.    I smile- and you say I'm the best friend you could ever have. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 21. February. 2000   It happened so suddenly I almost didn't see.  One heartbeat I was one person, and the next heartbeat another.  And it didn't happen with bells ringing or pumkins into carriages or great melodramatic wailings and hair pulling.   I breathed in- and I was myself, with the same pains and sorrows, firefly sparks of joy and searing longings.  But when I breathed out- it was as though I was standing in a ring of me's, each one carrying one trait or mannerism orbelief that made up the whole of me at that moment.  It was as though all of my parts had seperated and then presented themselves before me for inspection.   I knew of self analysis,just never expected to bring it upon myself this truly, this- palpably.  If frowning were an emotion, then this is what I felt at that moment, looking around at all the different parts that made up the sum of me.  Funny though, if these parts make up my sum- then how is it I haven't fragmented just as they did?  How could I look at each of these parts seperately if it took all of them to make me to be able to look at them?    Have I then erred in my deductions, or am I simply an innocent bystander in the acute and quite permanent fracturing of my psyche into millions of not so easy to assemble shards?  But I shouldn't use shard there, it makes me think of the Crystal Shard from 'The Dark Crystal', and gets my thoughts roaming completely from the moment at hand.  Another facet of me, one I'm quite good at.  So let us say pieces instead of shards, for pieces is a banal word, and only flickers in my memory association with Tori Amos' singing voice.  Tori being a topic very easy to push aside for later, I gatherd myself together, such as it were, and had a look at this ring of me's.    To my immediate right was the part of me that worked tirelessly to construct my many, many masks.  She had a sort of harried look to her, as if she'd just been interrupted from the most all consuming task, which I suppose she was.  For perhaps the absolute first time in her existence she didn't have to be creating a new mask to put on, to present to the outside world, to keep the whole me hidden so completely that standing there, on my right, she was only just realizing that there was a vast universe beyond her mask making that she was too self contained to see or even know existed.  Until now.  And with the simple act of turning inside and looking at myself, getting my own attention, I had touched the first domino in a labryinth of intricate and subtle changes, changes that would take years to fully manifest and mature.  All I did was draw air into my lungs, and in that heartbeat, in that breath, I began to change.  By tapping the part of myself that generates my masks on the shoulder to say hello, I had set into motion a series of thoughts and actions, realizations and epiphanies, that would finally, completely, and wholly allow me to tear down my own self made prison, brick by brick, bar by bar.    Just one breath, one heartbeat, one blink of an eye and I knew I was meant for greatness, in some form, even if it was only in the conquering of who I was, to become who I am.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 25. May. 2000   Benefits  I may be lonely, but I can't say, truly, that I am alone. Friends with benefits? Dave in Atlanta. Desperation for human contact. I need to sleep on it. No pun intended.  Warned by everyone, no strings attached But oh, go slowly, be gentle- I could break- so easily. Can I take this at face value?  Am I lonely enough? But are my standards too high? Would it be settling- Because he's not a fairly tale knight in shining melancholy? Do I aim too high? Can I live with myself if I say no? Can I if I say yes? Friends with benefits, eh... I wish I knew, wish I could see- The fork in the road, and the right path for me.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 23. May. 2001    Something In Me   Something in me... brewing, building... frothing red and wet.. just under the surface. A volcano of passion, desire, hot and sticky melting my icy heart  Give me back my will to live So I might die in peace- and know- Whatever is there to know But it simmers, churns,  bubbles, and never crests.  To course through me, Surge in my veins, A hurricane in my mind Tornadic soul. A tidal wave of rage, of love, of hate, joy, sorrow of everything that nothing did first create.  Be me Walk in my shoes know the wrath- and the pain of me. Know your history. Know Me.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 30. April. 2001    So. You think you know me. But you've never been in my shoes. Think you can control me. But you don't know what's in my head. You try to mold me. But I don't fit into any of your forms. How is it then you think you'll hold me To the lies you take for truth?  And who said I would let you try, anyway? 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 21. April. 2001    Its time for me to go I think, Curtain call is here. And I have run my course- a bit part, cameo, at most.  Its time for me to say goodbye, the shadows leading me away. And I never did anything , really- My ember never sparked to life.  I never saw another  butterfly. I never really wanted to.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 20. April. 2001   Would That  Within, without As I breath, As I feel, As I am. A pretty piece of flesh, within- But without, Nothing, everything, too much. Flesh upon flesh, always alone- enough for two In one. The sounding board, the confidant- And never the lover.  Would that I was without, the woman within.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 16. April. 2001   Goth  We have dark, withered things with in us. Eerie, fetid, festering secrets, down in the jungle Where the nightmares and the hororrs play, clambering about with malicious glee.  Whispers in our ears, of sweet repose and roses decayed. Gloomy dusk and sorrowful mourning and the fantasy of black lace... on sweat. Erotic funerals, for witch we dress. Musty scent of burning leaves, and clove cigarettes.  A twilit world of aching grief, sublime in its crystal coldness. pale faces and black veils, all the trappings of mourning. Passion, thick, and red, and explosive- down in the darkness, the early Autumnal evening of Goth. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 16. April. 2001   Handle Me  Head bent, defenses up, charging bull like through the world to keep from getting hurt. Casual off hand remark, Savage self deprecation to others, When in Rome, they say. Self poison in jest, to warm smiles that never reach my eyes How dare you think I'm not lonely.  What made you think I'd want your sympathy? Who told you I only wanted to be friends? Why do you assume I have no feelings?  Because I'm fat.  Not like the others.  I'm fat. But I'm sick of your hipocrasy.  Fuck you all, you just can't handle me.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Written. 20. April. 2001   And its the little things that make me smile, make it easier to breath, to live, to BE. The sights, the sounds, the tiny gestures the Universe makes in its infinity of finding itself. The questing to KNOW. The doing, seeing, touching, smelling, searching. Every moment, every thought, every second a journey of infinite possibilities. And we'll never learn it all, never know ourselves completely, never come to the end, ad infinitum.   But is that really so bad? A journey without an end, a quest without a holy grail. If there were an end, and we found it, What then? On to greater things, higher levels? Implies a continuation merely. Do you see? There can not be an end. The end would be absolute darkness, utter void, complete null. Who are we to call that down upon the Universe?   Thus, the journey. To see how the proverbial cookie crumbles, over, and over, and over, into eternity...   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Contemplation    ( Written about 8 Am this morning.)  27.July.2001  My dream, whatever it was, sits very heavy with me this morning. The feel and shape and tone of it. There was a message in it, a meaning, but I'm not sure what. I know it had shades of yesterday's thoughts, but the complete content is gone. I think it had water, and a hazy kind of drug numbed pain.  Sometimes I think I'm beginning to understand the nature of Death, of what it means to Be dead. Or maybe once the fear of dying left me I embraced it far too quickly and whole heartedly and now its taken on some romanticized joy and transcendence for me. We're having an affair, Death and I, courting each other on and off for years. And he'll win in the end, I'll be his willing bride. But our courtship now is to try to lure me into his bridal bed early. He's trying to woo me into slipping the veil over my eyes and taking my vows with him now and sometimes I'm so tempted. At least there I'll be a bride, instead of the monstrosity I am here.  But if I accept that we'll be together at the end, when the Fates clip my string, then why shouldn't I wait? Why should I give myself over now? Because I'm tired, and I know only pain, and in his arms I can find escape, and be refreshed, and know peace.  None of it means anything to me when I feel like this, not even the PAST. Maybe that's the most tragic part, that my soul is being so smothered by this fat body and chemical imbalance that I just don't care about my past lives. They're gone. They can't hurt me anymore. Its this life, here, now, that hurts just to breath sometimes. Is it really that selfish to want a little peace, a little reprieve from the pain? Can it really be so bad then, to let Death court me, if it lets me close my eyes and imagine peace?  Its the hardest for me in the mornings, I think. When I'm still so close to my dreams and I'm here alone, waiting for work to begin, with just my thoughts and pen and paper. Its here where I have to put my game face on, my smile. Or if I can't smile I at least must wipe the cobwebs from the corners, sweep the dust under the rug, and make of my eyes a blank window that can't be seen into. maybe that's the worst, to have to hide it, this pain, day in and day out, because its my pain and darkness and no one else's and therefore there's no need for anyone to know. They couldn't do anything if they did and I wouldn't want them to, anyway. I deserve no one's pity, not even my own.   One of these days I'll no longer have the energy to put my face on, and nothing will ever be the same after that. Ever.      

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     There are secrets that we keep Down in the tropics jungle of our hidden hearts Secrets even we don't know exist. The air moist with palpable knowledge.  Secrets.. Some stones are better left unturned.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Written. 6. February. 1998   ( I should note:  This was written after the first and only relationship I've ever been in fell apart.  I was so fucked up from the experience as a whole that its taken me 4 years to be able to look back and and begin to piece together what lessons I was supposed to learn from it.  So. There you have it, or part of it, at least. )  When Dave in Atlanta gave me this book, after explaining its purpose- He told me to fill it.  "Put your deepest thoughts and feelings into it.  Make it your sounding board for your pain.  And when its full, send it to me.  As your teacher, consider it your first and only homework assignment."  As a person, I wonder about that statement and the motives behind it.  I never need a teacher, or a mentor for my Wiccan studies.  At the time he made this statement to me we were no longer lovers, and to me, no longer even friends.  I was raw, my wounds fresh, my pain bloody, pooling.  And in some ways I had resolved to make this my outlet.  To dip my finger in my bloody holes and write it all out in this book.  And then he 'assigned' it.  Why?  David, while good at heart, is an inherently selfish person.  From his thoguhts, it manifests itself in his words, his actions, his love making.  I don't know if other people don't see it, or if they simply don't acknowledge it.  David is a man who has known past glories, but no longer has the capacity to live out new ones.  But he twists that, manipulating it not into a noble telling of a legacy, but into a cheap, bastardized version of a sob story.  He plays upon his old great deeds, whimpering like a lame horse, wanting the pity, the sympathy to carry him through.  David feeds off of others' pain, drinking it in, as a means to make himself appear more pathetic, more woeful, thereby insuring that someone, somewhere will pick up the slack he refuses to in his life.    Send him the book, he says, when its full- so he can look at it from the vantage of someone older, wiser, with more knowledge.  Send it to him, so he can see the progress, and show me where to go next.  Why?  He doesn't want the progress, he wants the pain.  He wants to drink in the heartbreak lasviciously, like a pervert at a pornoshop, eagerly fondling himself as he thrills to cheapened sexual acts.  He only wants it so he can debase it, flinging it about heedlessly, a means to say, 'See how guilty I am over this.  Pity me the burden I bear, the price of past glories.'  He wants to rip down the curtain of me and plunge his hands into my soul, greedily, selfishly.  He wants to rape me of my most private emotions, my deepest joy and sorrows.  Sucking my wounds until they become infected, watching avidly as gangrene sets in.   And then he'll take that.  Then he'll blow his load in a shower of extracted pity.   A philandering of plucked strings, all contrived to get other people to bleed for him, provide for him, love him, while he sits back in humble gratitude, inwardly applauding his skill that once again he didn't have to lift a finger for himself.    This is the David from Atlanta.  This is the man who effectively lured me in and raped me.  Not with his hands, but with his mind.   With his words.  This is the man who sucked my clit even as he sucked my heart dry.  And forever after this, no matter what anyone says-      I did not run away from Atlanta.  I walked away from him, from his groping mouth, his raping words.  I walked away from a battle I neither needed nor wanted.  One I firmly believe is not worth my time, my effort, my pain.       So live your life, David.  Leech from other people who're willing to turn blind eyes to your malignant personality.  Continue raping hearts and souls.  But not mine.  My pain, and my life, are mine.  No one else in this world is responsible for it but me.  And on one, most especially you, is entitled to view, or use that.  Live your life, Charles David Wilson, but keep it far, far from me.  You'll not get this book, and you'll not see my contentment in my new life.    But David-  I freely give you my justified anger.  I offer you my bitterness and my cynicism.  I blithely present to you my shoulder, icy as it is.   See if you can rape that.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Written. 2. July. 2001   They Never Had  Lastly came the children, stained with the sins of their parents. Lost, hardened, pleasure sacrificed to survival; childhood giving way to a reality they never deserved. Desperation in the air,  Defective love, corroded, decayed, Futile hope, tattered, frayed. They tread on, year after year, as the memories fade- and the desert becomes all they ever knew. Broken and stained they wander- searching for a hero they can't remember... And a childhood They never had.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink Jessica's journal    Into Darkness.   She moved in the night like sinewy sentience Curling and twining 'round the thoughts Dark and mysterious- a lunar lit nymph In my head On my mind Cool and caressing Sensual hedonism  And the thoughts give rise to desire as she dances in her gypsy sway evoking images of times long past and hidden pleasures. Slow and seductive She writhes, fusing herself to my consciousness insinuating her smoky form into the margins of my life, Until I need her, want to be her,  too restless to be satisfied with silence. I turn, in my thoughts.. And follow her into Darkness 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      More.        You can not quit me so quickly. Can not walk away. You can not turn your back on me Can not refuse to fight for me. To give me up so easily.  Sheer lunacy For you to give up on me and all my wicked ways. To refuse my love. Absolute Insanity For you to lower my defenses then shun my breathless avowals to die for you.  You must not surrender without first battling my fear, conquering my bitterness, winning the war of me.  You can not quit me so quickly. Lest you break me, forsake me- and leave me begging you... for more.   All Rights Reserved.        

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    And If I Jump  Written.31.January.2002   Precariously perched upon the precipice of some sparkling epiphany And do I want to learn it?  Darkness ahead, Shadows behind and the only way open is down But am I strong enough to jump?  No future, agony of past they always say climb to the light Only I don't know if there is a bottom to climb from.  six feet or six million miles this open grave stinks of my own living decay Although I dug the hole myself.  Sickly sweet scent of sanguine salvation silence at the edge of a shimmering razor have I the will to finish it?  Blind gropings in darkened corners desperately seeking a hand to guide me How do I know if its the right one?  Do I jump, can I fly? Why is there no safety net below me? Is there a light below, or cruel cosmic joke?  And if I jump... will I plunge into the healing of this epiphany  Or be dashed against the slick stones of my own shattered hopes? 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Let Me Die  Written.26.January.2002  Black mood, bad day Let me die and fade away. I want the peace I need the silence to cease the endless cacophony of voices Close the open wounds Stem the flow of pain Please let me die.   The yearning ache for love never had Bitter envy for those with less, but more. Let me die I'm not here I'm not real I know only agony. I want to open my arms to the Shadows and let them O'er grow my spirit I want to die!  There's nothing left for me to say and only pain to feel Let it all fade away leave me in some peace I never did a thing with my life Would that I could go to sleep Never wake up.  Let Me Die.  Please.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Sin Free  Written. 24.January. 2002  You have honoured my request for silence my need for secrecy. You have harbored the knowledge within you and smiled in the light of day.  Silently, we have crept Stealing the night to come together to say a final goodbye- time and time again.  And ever on the morning after Smiling in the light of day- not by word or look or deed Have you let our secret slip away.  But comes the day when all must change We must part, ever more refrain from seeking pleasure in dead of night and Lying in the light of day.  So keep our secret sweet phantom lover Honour my request for silence Think not on that we parted must be Look to the day we meet again.  Honour my request for silemce to keep us both sin free.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 1. January. 2002   Of Mine   Lend me your mouth that I might fill it with words.  Offer me your mind that I might fill it with thoughts.  Open for me your fingers that I might place within them a sword.  Bend to me your will that I might make of you an instrument.  Shed for me your tears that I might purge my pain.  Scream for me your Sorrow that I might add it to my own.  Sing for me your joy that I might know happiness.  Give to me your soul that I might glimpse a spark-  Of mine.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Let Me Go   The tears are ever right behind my eyes and the pain is always just a heartbeat away.  The Darkness forever issues its sickly sweet call and the Shadows ever so gently wrap me in shrouds.  The wind whistles mournfully through the broken headstones of my heart and the lonely willow of my Passion sags under its heavy burden of Sorrow.  The scarred landscape of my love begs silently for life and my barren womb slowly withers in dejection.  The flesh caged mind longs for release from bitterness and the moonless night of my Spirit quails under cynical onslaught.  The soul bleeds fresh within its thicket of thorns and the wounds of life ... never really heal.  So I stumble, and I fall, shattered- Scrabbling blindly in the Darkness ahead of me and only the utter silence of death offers reprieve. Fate, cruel whore- For now I have the courage to let it end ... with the will too weak to conclude my quest.  But I'm dying already.  Let me go.                                                     By Jessica Gasparini, Copyright 2002. All Rights Reserved.           

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Written 24. April. 2002   And into the shadowed Nocturne they swept,  weeping for their lost innocence,  reveling in their corroded morality...  until the Darkness surged forth to meet them,  spreading its spidery wings and enveloping them..  In eternity. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 10. April. 2002   Speak   Speak the tenses, the tensions. Passed present, nervous future. But don't go calling it what it wasn't. Swore I felt you go stiff now See you smirking at who I was The missed opportunities hold sway, knowing tomorrow will have been just the same.  Tell me the story about last time When we sat silent, breathing into our argument to come. the subtle slights, distance looming between us then, makes us hesitant, to bridge the gap once more. But the hurt caused each night keeps us apart for another tomorrow.  Talk to me about yesterday in an hour so I have time to prepare to hear to listen to maligns when we were strained controls today's emotions in the confrontations ahead.  Feeling the tension, reliving all the jagged memories about the future. Please don't let me comment on what will have been.  Speak the silence, confusion Began with one moment of sneering at dreams Speak of the tenses, the tensions Speak of the pain Of passed presents, uneasy futures.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written.20.May.2002  Sorrow.  Such overwhelming sorrow. Sifting through my mind, Stifling my will to live. Searing in its intensity.  Neither pain,  Nor darkness. Entirely different, Sorrow. Anguish shrouded in resignation.  Shuddering in its icy silence. Sluicing over my breaking heart. Dousing the flames of my spirit. You can not know.  Shh, darling, don't speak. She'll not wait for you to decide. To Die. Act now, or forever hold your breath  Waiting for the Sorrow to pass. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written.20.May.2002  All You See  Sometimes I cry for you and the sorrow you feel.  Sometimes I lie for you to hide the pain you see.  Sometimes I bleed for you so that you're not alone.  How I need you, need to feel you.  Would that you could see me as I am, a guttering candle in the hurricane of your presence  How I need you,  need to be with you.  I can not do this any longer I am dying for you And you do not see.  I can not be her any more She is gone from you And I can not replace her.  You can not do this to me ever again For I am fragile and easily broken.  You can not rule over me once more For I am equal and remain untamed.  And how I need you. How I yearn for you.  How I love you.  And all you see... is her. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Written.20.May.2002   Sing the Voices.  Sing the voices Soft to list Carried away on Cool breezes.  Chant the praises Thrumming fast to hear Keeping time with pulse In heart's secret place.  Dance the Circle Feet against dirt Drumming deep within Pull soul to Surface.  Raise the energy Shape the funnel Intent fueled frenzy Power in the Night.  Expel the need Showering climax cried A unison of wanting Breath exhaled as one.  Sing the Voices In dead of night Under Lunar's full Enchanted light.  Sing the Voices, Sing the Phrases Praises Cry out Sensation Release in Joy  Sing the Voices,  Call to Her Glory.  Good Mother Earth, We rejoice in thee.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 1. may. 2002    TABOO   Lurking under your sight, just below the surface of your mind - the fetid thoughts you try to hide from yourself. Twisted longings, depraved arousals, forbidden desires... TABOO.  Please Daddy, show me how you love me. C'mere little girl, and touch me in the secret place. Rough padded paws on my back, hot canine breath on my neck...  Never give in to abnormal temptation. But such lusts, such heat suffuses my sense, makes me breathless with want.  Wanton. Hedonism with a razor's edge.  Don't think about it. (Oh Daddy, yes, you love me so hard, so deep) Don't acknowledge it. (No crying little girl, it only hurts the first time I push it in.) By the Gods don't act on it. (That's it doggie, just keep licking right there... )  Crawling and clawing on the periphery  of acceptable society. Driven to madness unless you seek  your warped pleasures...  Taboo.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        urlLink Jessica's Journal     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 27. April. 2002   Hideous Kinky   Hideous Kinky And I begged for it, Didn't I? Down on my knees in the wet pre-Dawn grass Me and your cock and your words so crass and my twisted longing for this to last  Hideous Kinky That I condemn While you fuck me and I beg you for this to end. The pain's not so bad But this wound will never mend.  Hideous Kinky How it all came to be. In the dark, in the corn and me on my knees. Just a kiss, just a stroke You raped me so good, Did you know? 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 15. March. 2002   Appreciate   Let it all fall by the way Fade and blow the dust Across the Universe Let it be forgotten Or if remembered, fondly so.  At least you took the chance At least you didn't lose in the end. Later they'll say you did what you could. Later, when you're dead - They'll find you're life, O Brilliance! Too late to appreciate.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 14. March. 2002   How   How hard do you try  runnin' through the shadows?  How long can you wait before giving in to the fear?  How high do you climb in order to reach the summit?  How far do you go to get what you want? 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 28. February. 2002   From Crysania   I get defensive here sometimes Nothing to prove - no need to validate Justify With Sleet icing down overhead and I', deliciously lost in my thoughts. Let the Dawn fold and the Day break Leave only Night Supple Darkness Sensual Sensation Behind my eye Under the right Conditions is utter contentment, Pure pleasure. Try it sometime. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 5. March. 2002   They Do For Me   Do the edges of the world soften for you? As the Day fades and Night seeps in? It does for me.  Blurs and drifts into the Shadows - becomes cool and sensual Romantic Caged within the Daylight's cynicism.  Shining armour, golden towers, The faeries and the sprites. Fey frolicking through full foliage - lit by the moon's soft glow.  Do the edges of the world soften for you When you close your eyes and dream? They do for me. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 20. June. 2002    Fiend   Get out of my head you vile usurper. Out of my thoughts, rancid serpent. Off my mind, devious manipulator. Away from my consciousness you... Fiend.  Unrelenting you are Insidious and viscious Unrepentant, you laugh Watching me backs towards insanity. Madness to be so affected by you - And you're not even in the room.  Be gone from my waking world, thieving deceiver, Leave go of my haunted dreams, arrogant knave. Unravel yourself from my soul, duplicitous instigator  Fiend.  Stay away from me. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 23. June. 2002   Everything   You're everything I never wanted to be. Harsh and brutal Cold and cruel, Calculating.  You're the sum of all I loathe Egotistical and vain. Haughty and disdainful, Selfish.  The epitome of all I hate Calm under pressure, Detached, decisive. Mysterious and cryptic, Conspiratorial. Shameless, arrogant, Manipulator, bold, brazen A natural leader. Charismatic.  Oh, you are everything I never wanted to be.  And all that I can't live without.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 20. June. 2002   Fill The World   The things we never think of Could fill the world with thoughts. People the planet with efficiancy And never be bought or sought after, like a waking dream Slipping through bloodless fingers Regret and remorse hold court here in the flash bright chambers of your memory.  Perfect hindsight, blind to the future, trudging perilously ahead Caught up in contraptions to make life easier. Overhwelmed by loss of time and effort.  All the counless things we never think of Cluttering up what could've been.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written 16. April. 2002   Troubles me, to think of where we're going. How we've gotten where we are. Irreverence, Sadism -  What a horrible creature is man, arrogant and cruel. Seduced by technology and asphalt. Spill your own blood there and see how it feels.  Pull yourself from the mirror for a second, And see through the eyes of the dead. The poor, defenseless -  the Mother's Children.  Just because you're a lamb  led willingly to slaughter - doesn't give you the right. To take the lives of the only creatures worthy on Earth.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written between March and May. 2002   Momentary Pause   Counting time in infinite seconds Bleeding into endless hours Flowing towards eternal days.  Forever in a grain of sand.  A split second in a mountain of time Inexorable movement toward the moment, the infinite minute - when it's over, forever. Crawling and scratching at the boundless boundaries of time Over and over, ad infinitum.  Impossible task, unsolvable riddle, Unanswerable question.  To find the moment, In an infinity - identical, meaningless moments.       

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written 13. March. 2002   Could It   And into the mind came the thoughts, the questions, confusion - Need, want, desire, pain. Veiled in happiness.  How do I? Why should I ? Don't rock the boat - But what if it's worth it? What if it isn't?  Turn away, Don't look back - Let it all fade Because it could never happen... Could It?  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written 12. June. 2002   So It Goes   Sickly sweet, consumed by rage, made bitter with pain. Careful construction of a thousand illusions shattered with a husky whisper. Come tumbling down to land at my feet - staring in resigned acknowledgement. Such are the standards I hold myself to.  But now the wound is closed with a  cynical scab, and it only itches a little, around the edges. Small scar in the making. What's one more among the countless rest?  Not festering, nor screaming in anguish just... letting it happen, flow over and through me - 'cause I'd rather be done with it then bring it to light.  No martyrdom here, no cry of foul. Too many details to be justified in that. Too many greys to plead black and white. I'll give it up, I'll let it go, let the scar find its place.  Pick your battles, choose carefully when to fight - Here's my sword - I am neutral to this plight.  And so it goes, and we move on and I can smile again... Someday. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written.9.June.2002  Mobius   Time's like this I can see life spinning out before and behind. The whole of my existence a heartbeat in the silence of eternity.  Here today, gone tomorrow. Filled with meaning to none but ourselves. An infinity of precious moments, only in our minds.  Inexorably the arbitrary days pass, rooted as we are within fleshy cages - creating seconds to tick away, humanizing time as we blunder towards death. Minutes to hours, hours to days, a life in a second of true time, inconceivable to us.  So at time's like this I step back, to see the twisting cord of infinity before, after, now and again, ad infinitum. I know my place in the Universe.  In time, only time remains. Tis the only constant, fixed and known among all the secrets we've yet to behold.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written.9.June.2002  After All   Peeking through, just a glimpse of what I gave up for you. Blissful ignorance, a lost soul wandering, happily unknowing.  All I left behind to follow you Friends and family, compassionate moments, sobbing merrily at weepy movies. Close knit life of material hours, sewn tight with a happy, if provincial ending.  And everything I gained by taking your path. Pseudo enlightenment in a Twin peaks fantasy, wealth of understanding, Human Nature explained. Dizzying journeys into madness, back again - and willingly diving down for more.  Cynical, clinical observation, ever searching for hidden meanings and illumination to half veiled truths. Conspiracies abounded with you. But so did contentment - jumping sky high at truly scary movies.  Down the rabbit hole you took me, past the cellar door. Nothing was ever the same again.  But after all, it was my choice.  So I know not regret, although in vulnerable moments I look behind Catching a glimpse of the world I surrendered, peeking through.  All I shunned to be with you.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written.6.June.2002  Personality Disorder   Love and Darkness and my will to live, All tangled in a heaving web of self deceit. I am so duplicitous with myself. Laughing sardonically at my own cries for merciless mercy. The dreams in which I'm dying are devoutly to be wished.  To find relief from Sorrow To find surcease of pain One perfect silent moment of truth within my soul.   And yet my pleas unheeded go By my insidious ears, falling deaf, falling mute. Snatched away on the gales of self loathing. Shut out the light, and I stumble into blindness clumsy, colliding with my will to live. Beating it down unintentionally, Please remove my binds, take my hands from my ears - let me see what I can.  Never, never, never...  trust your love again.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 2. June. 2002   Foolish Games   What foolish games we play  Tearing ourselves apart Breaking our own hearts, with the aching in our souls  Such weakness we support letting ourselves break giving in to our dark thoughts opening our own wounds  How vainly we cry out screaming our created pain begging for release from self appointed misery.  What Sorrow to know that it is all in our heads That the power to heal is ours...  And we don't take it.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 24. July. 2002   The Bar Scene   Wasting Away Waiting to Die Killin' time, and I'm not even high. I'm just the driver, cabbie, chauffeur the masochist who agrees to go along And I can't even join in the fun... 'Cause this circle of friends only holds four.  Such a searing lesson, Glaring reminder Of all I'm not allowed. There's evil afoot, pure self loathing - How apropos to be surrounded by mirrors. As if the staring, eyes weren't enough.  So this is what I'm reduced to - If I want to have fun. Sit at the end of the line, and wait until I'm needed to drive. Is it any wonder than, That I prefer solitude over this Hell that so many enjoy.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 15. July. 2002   Self   Under the chest nut tree - I sold you and you killed me  There in the fetid core, the truth that bound us free And all we could do was watch, to see it end. Sometime in the night, the music died. Silence hovered, pregnant  with meaning, accusation. I held you,  and you raped me of all that I held dear.  Leapt eagerly into the open mouth of my own grave for you. Now I'm scrabbling for a hold among the bracken... But its made of thorns and my hands are bloody        with regret.   Vultures circling, You're towering over me, that same sardonic smile. Triumph in your schizotypal eyes. Will you wait until I'm dead to suck the marrow from my bones? Or devour me alive while my screams play melody to your feast? If I turn to look I know I'll see..  The mirror and the chest nut tree where I sold you, and I killed me.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Texture of Sound   Texture of Sound brushing over my skin like Egyptian linen.  Fabric of Crescendo ripping up and down my spine.  Explosion of Melody coursing through my veins.  Weave of Arrangement fitting to my body like flesh.  Tapestry of Music encasing me in pure emotion.  Threading of Lyrics twining my soul to the Universe.  Texture of Sound fills the void of loneliness gives meaning to my life.    

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Die Happy   I'm not interested in completing Herclean tasks for your love. No desire to sell my soul for your tenders of affection. I don't want to climb the highest mountain to prove I'm worthy of your acknowledgement.  I just want to love you from afar, feel your eyes onme now and again - I simply want you to notice me. You don't have to love me. No need to vow undying devotion. Only see me, at the end.  I'll make do with that. I'll learn to deal with that. I can carry on, if I know that  You see me. Acknowledge me. Know that I exist. And have patience with me.  I'm dying loving you. But I don't expect it requited. Won't jump through hoops to gain it. Can't rally to prove it.  Just be with me, at the end. Let your face be the last thing I see... And I can die happy. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 26. November. 2002   Mourn Ahead   As the day seeps into night you begin to wonder about your life And how it is, you want to be remembered.  Or you ruminate on the future imagining having lost your most beloved Trying to mourn in advance, knowing you'd never survive the loss  Ponder the pain, then of being torn, snatched, wrenched away from the only person whose soul fitted to yours like flesh over sinew  Its a selfish thing really to want to continue though you're half complete want to become the one who carries on, being ever looked upon in sorrowful commiseration.  Find you want to be the tragic survivor desire the pain of living without And so begin to draw from the future grief mortgage to get you acclimated to that state of being  You Mourn ahead, take out an advance letting longing for it grow with each year until day seeps into night And you find yourself mourning for your loss before it happens remembered as one who mourned.  Jessica Gasparini.     

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written.26.December.2002   So Well   You know me so well not at all all my quirks and desires nothing of my needs and wants See my tastes and proclivities no idea my fantasies and fetishes  You know me so well What I savor and cherish Blind to that which thrills me and kills me Understand my words and reasons completely lost to my thoughts and emotions  You know me so well the secrets I tell Promises I spill The ways in which I move in life The people I surround myself with So well-  But you only know me as much as I let you see Give you permission to me You only Know  One facet of me. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 27.December.2002   The Let It Be   I moved like David tonight Didn't notice it till just after And I wondered why I wasn't angrier. A Painting went for a million and one But the portrait he seared into my soul was priceless.  All those trials and tribulations Lessons that altered the very way my brain worked Skewed my reality until all I saw was youo- And what you wanted me to. I still can't extricate myself.  How did I lose myself in you? Why have I never found what I lost? What power do you still hold over me?  And if I never learn to live without you?  Then let it be. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 30. January. 2003  Again   Time and time and the wheels of fate the grinding erosion toward inevitable death. Ghosts of the past and future spectres All from one e-mail. Indistinct and impersonal on the surface clawing open festering wounds long scabbed over. Trying to make me gangrenous with envy, with longing, with remembrance. Striving to lure me back to your void  Another turning of the wheel, time inexorably bringing us together aain, this macabre dance, morbid web we weave- 'round each other. Who is the master here? time and time and time again. Eternal and infernal, my emotions for you. Offered and coerced, my reaction to your words. And through it all... sorrow.  You could've been great. You wasted yourself on meaninglessness. And I can't waste any more time on you 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Wheel Turns   The wheel turns He has risen from the grave of my memory From the ashes of my burned out heart back from the rubble of my shattered psyche.  In the flesh and the blood. His words searing across my consciousness Rip right through me.  But I renounce. I defy you. I do not follow. I will not fall into. You. Again.  Pompeii is my past now. Frozen in time. And You along with it. I refuse to disturb the ruins.  I make of Your words an echo, impotent wailing  against the cages of my mind. You have no power over me. Nevermore. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 7. January. 2003  I'll Be   I'll Be.  Didn't really think you could Best me, did you? Or wheedle your way into my life without losing a piece of yours in the process.  Two way street this Mutual manipulation. Across the distance past the time I've sold you to the highest bidder and rid myself of your stink.  Try to do the same to me- You'll find a void Where I used to be. How will you fill it.  Sticks and stones, fate's favourite son you can no longer afford to run. Karma is coming and you're not prepared You should've known, I'm always there.  Look in the mirror David, For that's where I'll be. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 10. December. 2002   I  Ran   And I ran Feet stomping, side stitching, heart pounding- Into the brink. Launched myself off the cliff- With a smile. No fear.  Running through the Shadows; Storming through the smoky veil of complacency. Laughing. No Shame.  I ran. Over the river through the woods tearing toward the underbrush the precipice in sight Made the decision. Took the leap of faith in myself.  I ran Hell bent for leather right for the beginning of my life.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written 10. March. 2003  Untitled  The Minutiae of memory distant details too fleeting galaxies lost in a single day with the inhale of new ones.  And how do we find the balance between the past and the present with room for the future? Do we live in our memories or forget the past entirely?  So we meander betwixt the two drifting to the past and back again In time we learn the lessons intended. Wanderers in our own lives, the minutiae of our memory weaving the tapestries of us together.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written 7. March. 2003 Untitled  Are we losing the moon? Have the secrets of the primordrial ooze been discovered? Suppose there is no impact? Only Speculation remains our window Our stepping stoned to other planets - means to the cosmos, the Sentient Universe.  Are we losing the moon? Rue the day.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written 22. April. 2003   Soon   Soon and soon and soon And this waiting makes me ache That I should be so close and yet so far But all I can do is wait.  Breathe through each moment move past each day bring myself  closer and closer and closer  To change to hope to life or something like it.  A chance granted with stipulations abundant- Don't fuck it up now. Just wait.  Wade through the ache walk past the restless imaginings Focus on right now.  Get the details right And everything falls into place Soon and soon and soon Wait.  Sweetest things they say Did they ever have to wait for this? Or mourn for past and future?  All inside my head.  Soon and soon and soon So I wait. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 25. September. 1995    The Fall   I Stand here, yearning, wanting, waiting. The pain I know is never ending. The love I feel is little consolation. Fate has dictated that we will hurt. Free Will is our empire of dirt. The Universe is infinite. Coffee and conversation are necessities. Cigarettes are a staple addiction. I stand here yearning to take him in my arms. I stand back, knowing its not my place. I sit here wanting to take away his pain. I move aside in an effort for him to remain sane. I stand here waiting for the storm. I stand here knowing it will come. I stand here understanding the nature of his pain. I stand here, by my free will I stand here, waiting to face the fall.   

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 17. Novemebr. 2003  Climax   And I felt you hesitate inside of me Wondered at the vagaries of perception that widened the chasm between- Like a breath drawn in and held just a moment too long. I sensed the pause, the change in myself.  Did it have as much meaning as I so yearned to give it? The order of things was never in question. Looking up, I marveled the silence of it- when silence reigned every change. But felt obligated to mark the moment with sound.  And then I felt you move again the rythym regained- We pressed on, strove to come back together, breach the gulf of who we were and who we are, Until everything exploded in sensation. For a moment we were one, at the climax. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    WE  Written.10.May.2004  Crude and rude and completely without tact Brash and rash and utterly lacking in decorum No finesse and unrefined, absolutely uncouth Raw and crass and severely in need of diplomacy  Dark and dreary and gleefully macabre irreverent and irrelevant and enveloped in shadows Morbid and morose, devoid of Light or Joy Sorrowful and forlorn, lost in the valley of the dead.  Anti-Social and sociopathic, seeing through schizotypal eyes Depressed and repressed, with an oppressive lack of self worth. Manic and frantic, socially dysfunctional in every sense. Psychotic and chaotic, a fractured psyche  We are all of these and more  We are generally not amused.  We are myself in pieces. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Holiday Countdown   Written.10.May.2004  Six Hours left to live to die to spread my wings and fly?  Three Hundred sixty minutes to flail to rail against the injustice of it all?  Time and time and time slips by bleeding me leaving me without the will to go on  And shall I feel afraid? Shall I run or hide from the inexorable  ticking of the clock? Should I turn away in fear? Stand bravely at the edge of the abyss, and see myself reflected in its Vestigion Darkness?  Five hours, forty eight minutes now, to reconcile or find justice or simply just to be -  before the end.  

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Written. 24. May. 2004   Welcome to my Head   To enter an access code, press pound, To start the Inner Monologue, press play. Then strap yourself in, and keep your doggie bag handy - You'll need it. When visiting my head, taking the scenic route through my psyche The debris and ruin, downed power lines sparking in the wet Turgid Darkness enveloping all.  Duck the rotting corpses of my past swinging lazily from rusted aluminum trees. Keep your appendages in the vehicle, please - lest you lose them to the snapping jaws of my inner demons, ever ravenous for fresh guilt. Don't get out to explore the rolling fields of dead grass since you might get pulled under by the horrors - clambering gleefully within it, reaching down to dig sharpened talons into my wounds and keep them bleeding.  Hide your eyes from the atrocities on the left, my inner child slowly skinned alive by my sadistic cynicism, Just don't listen to the cacophony of screams.  And before the nightmare tour ends, if you're still in possession of your sanity - breath shallow through the blood falls Add your shadows to my Valley of Death.  Welcome To My Head. 

						
</post>

<date>16,Maio,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Written. 24. May. 2004   Gay   I am gay - and yet I've never dated. I am queer -  In every definition known. I am lesbian -  because men appeal not to me. I am womyn - and crave a woman's touch. I am female - thus I rejoice in the female form. I am fag hag - for I relate better to gay males. I am big nelly bottom - due to lack of experience. I am beefy, brutal top in my mind and heart.  I am broken. I am whole. I am strange. I am normal. I am...  Queer as Folk.    

						
</post>


</Blog>