<Blog>

<date>28,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Another three days since my last entry. Maybe that will be my normal frequency...not sure, though. I guess it all depends on how busy I am. This weekend was a blast. It all started Friday night with Cliff's birthday. Let's just say the "fun" started around midnight and lasted until 3:30 or so. Didn't have any reprecussions the day after (the same cannot be said for Cliff...or Chad for that matter), which makes me kind of happy. Went to bed around 6 AM and woke up on Sat. at 11:30. Attemped (unsuccessfully) to buy U2 tickets to the May 16 concert at the United Center. After that went to the mall with Tons, Chad, and Daniel. That was nice...didn't buy anything there. After that went to the Taco Bell on Lindsey near 24th. Then went to the Albertson's on 24th and Robsinson, only to find that there is a Taco Bell right there! Tons felt stupid, which isn't unusual. Somewhere in there we went to Hastings, where I finally spent some money on something other than food: a CD. I happened to come across the Passengers: Original Soundtracks 1 CD in the Used section. It was only $5.99, and even though it isn't the greatest, I feel that as a U2 fan I should own it.   Stupid Daniel Alert!!!   So Tons rented  Airplane 2: The Sequel  for us to watch Saturday night while we were at Hastings. Daniel thought it would be a good idea for him to rent a movie. So he picks out the one he wants and gets in line behind Tons. I'm behind Daniel (naturally). So he puts the movie on the counter and the dude (a GSA, I believe) asks Daniel for "his card." Daniel proceeds to tell him that he doesn't have "his" card with him. He then asks Tons if he could "owe him for it." The GSA asks for Daniel's driver's license and Daniel begins to mumble, after which the GSA goes, "Do you have an account here?" Of course Daniel doesn't, everyone in line is looking at him making a fool out of himself, and I am getting pissed (naturally). Tons doesn't understand Daniel's question...why would Tons rent a movie for Daniel? He should know by now to  carry money with him at all times, because no one is ever going to lend him money ever again . At least I'm not. So anyway, it all ended when Tons offered the GSA his card to scan, Daniel paid, and we  finally  left. Back at Walker (I spent the entire day - 12:30 to 2 AM in Walker) we watched  Airplane 2 . Tons was going to do homework so I thought I was going to have to leave but he never did, so we just watched TV. Later on, around 2 or 2:30, we went to Mama Lou's, which had been decided several hours before but didn't actually happen until then in traditional 4E fashion. Mama Lou's was fun and we stayed there for a few hours eating and talking (not about U2, amazingly). Made it home by 6 AM, put on  2001  and fell asleep. Today I woke up at 3 PM, got clean and presentable, and went over to Walker to watch the Super Bowl. I brought all my supplies - Coke, Dr. Pepper, salsa, tostitos - and most of it got used up (except for the DP). Super Bowl was fun, "my" team won, and we had some interesting discussions. Couldn't watch  Survivor II  because I'm on rounds, but my VCR taped it while I was gone. :-)
     
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I know, I know, I haven't done an entry in a while. And this will be a short one - I have to go to bed!  Today was useless...no class, nothing to do except get U2 tickets which was a complete  failure . I'm not very happy with myself right now. And, the way things are going right now, I'm having serious doubts that I'll be making my 9 AM class. Hopefully Mimi will remember to knock at my window just in case I fail to wake myself with alarm sounding off and stereo blaring...ah, the things I can sleep through. Anyway, gotta get to bed...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well here's my journal entry for today. Haven't done my homework yet, but since it's almost midnight I wanted to get it in before today becomes tomorrow. Got absolutely nothing done today as usual. Slept until 1 PM or so, then realized I had to work CA hours out in Cross at 3:30 and forced myself out of bed. Attempted to get some stuff done today but didn't actually leave my room until 2:45 which left little time.  CA hours were - of course - non-productive but I did get a little work done on my personal website of which this journal is a part. I think it's almost done...just have to figure out what to do with the fourth link (currently "empty"). Got back at 5 or so and went to do with Tono and the rest until 6. Then wasted some more time on the site and watched "Boston Public." It was a good episode tonight; next week is a re-run but there are four new episodes coming up in February so that's something to look forward to. After that I did more work on the site (I guess you could say I'm a bit obsessed) and then went to staff at 10:15. Got back from there around 11:20, had a chili pie from Couch Express (which I ate in the office) and came up here.  Some musings: I wonder where Linda is. I know I responded to her last email but haven't heard anything from her since. Also wondering where Cliff is as I haven't seen him either physically or on AIM all day. Really need to talk to him about the fourth Chicago date for U2 - need to know by Wednesday morning!  Homework is calling me...I wish it didn't but I have quite a bit of reading and writing to do before 9 AM. I'll probably leave Rhetoric Studies to do during my hour-and-a-half break between that class and American Lit. That'll save me some time tonight. More to come, as always.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Woohoo!!! Fourth Chicago show added! That's right, Wednesday, May 16, 2001 at the United Center!!! I realy want to be on the floor...I really want to be on the floor. Internet presale is on Wednesday (this week) so I'm going try as hard as I possibly can. Woohoo!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well, here I am doing my 1.5 hours of CAs out in Cross. Not complaining...it's nice and quiet and a great place for me to waste time and  not do my homework . Hah. Anyway, still trying to get that template working just right so it'll mesh with my new personal website. Yes, yes, a personal website. I've been toying with the idea for what...about six years now? Finally I think I'm ready, and thanks to the almighty Blogger, it might actually happen. And even if it doesn't, I'll still have this wonderful blog to remember my life by. Wonderful.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I know, I know, it's kind of early for me to be awake considering when I went to bed. Popped awake for some odd reason and now I'm resonding to a Zone questionnaire. Probably going to try to go back to sleep for an your after I'm done...more to come!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Going to bed...I think. Well, at least no more computer for tonight. I promise. See you in...oh, about 10 hours? That's about 4 PM! Hahaha...maybe a little earlier than that. I have homework to do. G'night.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Still working on the damn template...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Just trying a blog in progress...fun stuff.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      So, this is my first post to my e-journal. Aren't I a member of the computer age. You know, I've wanted a way to keep a journal on my computer and/or the internet that was easy to use and easy to pull up old entries and I've finally found it. You have absolutely no idea how exciting this is for me. Wait a minute. I have no idea who "you" are. I guess you're just a sort of second-person device I'm using in order to prove to myself that I'm not crazy. Hmm. Well, I won't worry about it. Promise me you won't either.  Hopefully I won't get board with this whole posting thing and actually keep a regular journal like I was supposed to last semester. I mean, I kept one, but it wasn't as frequent as I wanted it to be. And since I'm always sitting at my computer, and that's where I make entries from, I don't see a problem with it...  So anyway today was pretty short overall. Slept in, did pretty much nothing. No class in the morning or afternoon...nothing until Tuesday.  Went to the Sooner Championship Celebration today at Memorial Stadium. That was fun but a bit cold and too long...they could've sped things up a bit. We're fans, but we'd rather not be cold. After that I watched the Golden Globes with Tons, Tim, Teve, and all the rest...ate pizza...had nice time. Smoked at various intervals through all of that as usual. Worked on the "Vibrant Vacations" website t - wait! "Beautiful Day" just came on VH-1 - so anyway, finishing that previous thought, I worked on the website today. Finally think I have it where I need it to be, shouldn't be too much left to do on it other than create all the other pages. That  is  if the  bitch  likes it. Never know. I think I'll be going to bed pretty soon...it's late or early or whatever it is. Probably going to tweak this Blogger stuff for a bit though...see you soon, my little blog. See you soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
        Short post alert!   A whole week has gone by and no word from me! Well, let's just say the week was boring and the weekend was  not . Slept a lot...like, all day Saturday and all day Sunday. But, that's what weekends are for, right? Got my assignment for my teacher observation: Capital Hill HS in OKC. Sounds like fun...have to call the teacher and find out when, where, etc. Can't wait. In other news I'm finally going to start working on the  farSite design  website currently located at  urlLink http://129.15.136.97/ . This comes after finding out that my work on  urlLink Vibrant Vacations  has come to a halt for reasons beyond my control. Eventually I'm going to register www.farsitedesign.com, but eventually I'm going to do a lot of things. Damn those Regents! I want my money! Well, duty calls...laundry and website design. Fun stuff!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Ah, February is upon us. Happy February, world! Sorry I haven't posted in a few days...I guess my whole theory about 3-day waits after posts has been shown to be wrong. At least I haven't stopped posting all together. I'm afaid I don't have anything extremely interesting to write about, but a few cool things have taken place since my last post. I finally got a new bed!!! That's right, no more giant hole, no more climbing out every morning, no more sore back, and no more rolling into the middle even if I wanted to lay on the side. It's wonderful! Got my car back, too. It looks just like new. That's very exciting, because I was worried about how it would look...but actually the repaired areas look  better  than the old, scratched up areas. I can't wait to drive somewhere - maybe tomorrow. I have become hooked to Super Mario World 2: Yoshi's Island.  It's absolutely addictive. Anyway, there's lots of people around so I'll cut this one short. More to come...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2001</date>
<post>

     
       I'm still alive. 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      The site went through a major redesign today. Hope you like it.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Went to Six Flags Over Texas with most of the Couch/Cross staff yesterday. Woke up at 5:45 AM...left at 7:15. Stopped at McDonald's on Lindsey for breakfast &amp; coffee, then went the rest of the way to Arlington. Had a lot of fun, although it was hot, sunny, and extremely crowded. Got to ride all of the rides I wanted to ride, including the Titan, the Texas Giant, and Batman. Left around 6:15 PM and at at Friday's in the ballpark. That was fun as well. After dinner, it was back to the road - we made one stop in Denton, TX to gas up and buy more coffee...then it was straight back to Norman. Went to bed around 12:45 or so. Today was Sunday, so I woke up for church and breakfast. Overall, a good weekend...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Another week has passed. It was a fairly productive week - probably the biggest weight off my shoulders was the successful delivery of my social ethics presentation on the statistics of violence in schools (for EDFN 3003). Another "event of the week" was my philosophy test - I got a 97% on it. That should help out the grade quite a bit. Going bowling with my resi-friends now.....more later!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today is Easter Sunday. Went to church at 11 AM with Tono and Cliff. It was the pefect St. Thomas More mass: crazy reading girl, cute reading kid, wacky choir guy, lots of chanting, and Cliff almost passing out. Who could ask for anything more? Went back to Walker after lunch and picked up Tim and Daniel and went to Chili's for lunch. Yes, I know it's not spectacular, but it was good. Now I'm back in my room, pissed that none of my favorite radio stations are streaming on the internet.... Going over to Walker now to watch Indy 3 with the guys. Have homework/research to do...and laundry...but it's Easter. It can wait...right?
     
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I'm  still  alive.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I finally decided that I should post my first journal entry of the semester. So here it is. And, before I get started,  I really promise to try to post on a regular basis . It might not happen, but I'm going to try.  So anyway, I've just been through a week and a half of Resident Advisor Orientation 2001 - fun stuff, let me tell you! I've been busy non-stop since August 6. Today (Aug. 15) is my first day off since then. I have absolutely nothing to do. Ok, so that's not completely true. I'm sure I could  find  things to do, like go to the bookstore and get my books or make some signs for my floor. I probably will but I don't want to think that far ahead. After all, I haven't even slept yet.  So anyway, I'm on Couch 10W again. It's the only upperclass floor left in the towers, so it's in very high demand. Right now I have some residents with single rooms, but it doesn't look like it's going to stay that way. Whatever happens, I'll deal with it, but right now I'm very happy with my 27 residents - that's less than any other floor in Couch.  On a more personal level, I'm having mucho fun with all the RAs in Couch/Cross, especially some of the rookies. They're really great and I know we'll have a great staff this year. I can feel it.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      This is just a test post to make sure everything's working. More to come later.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I found it!!! It was in the PC Office the whole time. I'm very giddy. Hehe. Hoho. Whatever.  Have lots of work to do tonight. Going to re-tape Enterprise...I'm hoping tonight's encore presentation will not have the feed problems that UPN was having on Wednesday. Also going to call home and "check-in." And of course I have homework to do as well. I  would've  done it earlier, but...I couldn't. Hah! So there. My traditional weekend procrastination actually had a valid reason. Isn't that special.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Some people have been clamoring for an update, so here it is.  I would normally write about the week’s occurrences, but I have only one thing on my mind right now – the location of my backpack. You know, the thing you put your books in and walk around with when going to class and such. It’s missing. I realized this about 20 minutes ago and began to have a panic attack. I’m actually still having it, because the bag is still missing.  My first thought was to re-trace my steps. Unfortunately, I can’t seem to get my days straight. I remembered working in the Cross office from 6:45 to 8 PM and I know I had it with me. I thought I worked on Friday, and Friday is the last time I remember having it with me. So, I walked out to Cross and checked the office – not there. On the walk back, I realized I worked in the Cross office on  Thursday , not  Friday . Silly me. So then I thought more about Friday. What did I do on Friday? Did I indeed have my bag with me on Friday, or was it Thursday I was thinking about all along? Hmm...I’m not sure.  I know I worked in the Couch Office on Friday for Natasha from 2 to 3:30 PM. Did I have it with me then? I’m not sure, because I had exactly 15 minutes to get ready for my shift (shower and all), so I doubt I remembered to bring it with me.  I had duty rounds Friday night, and I remember going downstairs to open the office up and realizing that I hadn’t brought my books (I was planning on getting some homework done) but couldn’t leave to go get them. Well, I guess it turns out that I  couldn’t  have gotten them, because they were already missing.  I’ve been thinking as I’ve been writing this, and now I’m pretty sure that the last time I had my bag was on Thursday when I worked out in Cross from 6:45 – 8 PM. What did I do after I worked in Cross?  I went to the PC Office for the Murder-Mystery Dinner Meeting!!!  I probably left it in the office. I don’t distinctly remember walking back from Cross with it, but if I didn’t, it would still be in the Cross Office. Right? I didn’t go back up to my room before the meeting in the PC Office – I went straight there. All right, so now I’m pretty sure that it’s in the PC Office. Whew, what a relief. Of course, I was pretty sure that it was in the Cross Office earlier, and it wasn’t. So maybe I shouldn’t get my hopes up too high. But the mere  possibility  of it being in the PC Office puts my mind at ease. At least I’ll be able to sleep, since I’ve got church in 8 hours.  I’ll have to leave Jeremy a message (maybe I’ll do that right now) and call him tomorrow and see if he can let me in there to check. Of course, the office was open on Friday, so if I left it there on Thursday it could very well be gone by now. I sure hope not.  I really hope I find it. I have homework to do! Bedtime now...more on the Case of the Missing Backpack later. Let’s pray for a happy ending. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Thought I should post my AIM info for this week before I change it.    Attack on America.  We will never forget 9-11-2001. May God bless the family and friends of those lost in the attacks in New York and Washington, D.C. and the plane crash in Pennsylvania. Now is the time to come together as one nation.  Now for some reading!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today was a day of remembrance, a day of prayer, a day of reflection. Yesterday, President Boren requested that OU oberve a moment of silence at noon today. I took part in this moment of silence as bells rang across campus while President Bush spoke at the National Cathedral. It was a sublime moment - but a peaceful moment.  Today was a long day. This morning I had a one-on-one meeting with Brooks (my supervisor) at 11:15. I woke up a bit late (10:40) and made it down to the office around 11:17 - but he was running late so I was okay. The meeting went well. After that I stayed in the office, sticking around until after the moment of silence. I then went to get a haircut (which took almost two hours!!!). After that I went with Sheila to buy canned goods for the United Way. We had almost $400 to spend, and we spent all of it. We filled an entire Chevy Caprice station wagon with food - it felt really good.  Dinner was fun as well. David Steward invited me to join him and enjoy his culinary expertice. I was a bit wary at first, but it turned out to be delicious. We also got to hang out in the FIR apartment for about two hours which was nice. USing practice was next at 9...then a trip to Borders to buy the latest book in the  Star Wars: The New Jedi Order  series, entitled  Rebirth .  Now I'm here, writing this. I think I'll start reading my new book.    Heaven on Earth We need it now I'm sick of all of this Hanging around Sick of sorrow Sick of pain Sick of hearing again and again That's there's gonna be Peace on Earth. 
</post>

<date>11,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today is a day I'll never forget. To say that it will live in infamy is an understatement. My generation, on a national scale, now has a day that they'll never forget. I know I'll never forget when I found out about the tragedy.  This morning I woke up late, around 9:40 AM. I quickly showerd and dressed, and didn't touch my computer at all. I managed to get out of my room around 10:10, the plan being to stop at Couch Express for some coffee. As I left my room and entered the elevator lobby, I ran into a resident from 10e. He asked me if I'd heard about the World Trade Center collapsing. I looked at him incredulously. It was a story I couldn't even make up in my wildest dreams, and as we rode down the elevator, I kept wondering how much crack he was smoking. When the doors opened on the first floor, I immediately noticed how loud the TV in the lounge seemed but initially paid little attention to it. I made my way to Couch Express and got my cup of coffee. As I headed back to the north doors of Couch on my way to my 10:30 class, I noticed that not only was the TV loud but there was a crowd of people gathered in the lounge. My curiosity got the best of me and I got closer to the TV so I could watch too. Much to my amazement, I saw on the television what I thought I'd never see - a 110-story building collapsing. My mind filled with thoughts, my stomach became uneasy, and I found it difficult to tear myself away from the news coverage. After five minutes of standing there with my mouth hanging open, I decided that I should get to class.  The walk to Gittinger was eerily quiet - no one was talking or even making eye contact. It seemed as if everyone was grieving for our fellow countrymen in New York and Washington. There were so few people walking to class that I briefly thought that classes had been cancelled but I then realized that I was already five minutes late and attributed the lack of people to that. I entered Gittinger 338 and saw a room full of somber faces. My professor was there, so I assumed that class was still on, but then figured out that he had no intentions to continue with class. We were dismissed and I made my way to the Union because I'd heard that they had the news on in Meacham Auditorium. I ended up sitting in Meacham from 10:45 until 11:40. At that time I made my way to my noon class at Sarkey's. That class was not cancelled, but my 1:30 English class (back in Gittinger) was. At that point I made my way back to Couch to watch more news and catch up on what I'd missed. My 4:30 class was cancelled as well.  At 4:45 I called home...everyone was ok. We talked for a while. Dinner with Steve (and the Chad) happened around 5:15. Chad and Steve followed me to my room after dinner and we watched more news. After they left I moved to my bed, got comfortable, and watched NBC news. Somehow I managed to fall asleep around 7; Anna Wong woke me up around 9:30.  My emergency floor meeting at 10:30 went well with most of my residence in attendance. Now I'm continuing to watch the news, but I do have some homework to do. Maybe I'll get to work.     Attack on America:  A Day We'll Never Forget 
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      My promise did not come true.  The weekend is only half over and I've already had all the fun I can handle. Yesterday was Orange Peel at OSU. Went up to Stillwater with Tono, Steve, and Cliff. Our trip was plagued early on by dire predictions concerning the weather. Apparently a line of stroms was forming to the west of us, from here all the way to Kansas (probably farther north too, but I'm no meteorologist so don't take it out on me if I've got the facts wrong). So anyway Tim and Chad were going stormchasing and Tono (and Cliff) were intersted in going with him. Had this happened, Steve and I would've had to drive up to Stillwater on our own, with Tono and Cliff meeting us at Lewis Stadium for the concert. Another issue that complicated the situation included the real possibility of a weather-related cancellation of the concert. The problem with that was that we wouldn't know if it was cancelled until we got there.  Well, as it turned out, Tono and Cliff didn't go stormchasing and instead opted to wait with me until Steve got off work around 4 PM. At that point we made last-minute preparations (ATM visits, getting maps for possible stormchasing if the show was cancelled) and then went to the Conoco Travel Center at the corner of Lindsey and Classen to gas up and purchase foodstuffs for the drive to Stillwater.  The drive itself wasn't bad with no traffic and not too much construction once we got out of the OKC I-35 corridor (which is  always  under construction, apparently).We made good time and luckily encounterd no inclement weather on the way there. We arrived at OSU around 6:00 and drove around for a while trying to figure out where to park. Instead of parking in one of the open lots designated "Staff Only" (where, incidently, everyone else seemed to be parking), we parked in some church lot and paid $5 for the honor of doing so. What can I say, other than that we're suckers.  At that point we got in line...it was maybe 6:15 or so. The line was rather long and the clouds looked menacing - rain and other cool atmospheric phenomenon were not far off. Even I could tell that much. At 6:30 (the designated time to "open the gates"), the line started moving and we eventually made it into the stadium structure itself. Because of the weather situation, no one was allowed to go out into the stands so everyone milled around inside the stadium. We staked out a spot near one of the entrances to the stands which was also conveniently near an elevated walkway leading to the upper level of the stands. The elevated part was open underneath, created a nice sheltered area perfect for sitting/standing. This will become important later.  We stood there for a while and then - the rains came. Now the importance of the ramp becomes apparent - it protected us from the rain and, a little later, some very small hail. Soon after an announcement was made that the show would be delayed a half hour.  In the end, the show's start was delayed a full hour and the line-up was switched around - David Spade was first, followed by Sister Hazel and then Blues Traveller. Highlights of the performances include David Spade not sucking as bad as everyone had feared (he still wasn't  that  great, but at the very least mildly amusing), Sister Hazel doing the two songs that I wanted to hear and an unexpected cover of The Police's "Everything She Does Is Magic," and Blues Traveller being cool (with the exception of their extremly drawn-out songs - enough already!!!).  Made it out of there pretty late and drove straight back to Norman. Stopped at IHOP and had some food/coffee. It was yummy. Stayed up late last night watching "Witness" with Harrison Ford, a movie I'd never seen before. I fell asleep before getting all the way through it, but I do remember waking up several hours later and hearing (and seeing) "What Lies Beneath." It must've been Harrison Ford night!  Homework calls. More later. Good night!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Listening to Pearl Jam.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I've got a new operating system. Isn't that nifty?
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2001</date>
<post>

     
      &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Ok, so...I'm going to stop trying to be witty. Wait a minute...am I claiming that I was witty at one time? I guess I am. Well, I'm still holding firm. You'll hear no more pithy comments from me. I'm not going to try to be intelligent. I'm in Oklahoma, after all, and I'm sure you'll agree that the environment isn't quite condusive to the acquisition of knowledge. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;"But you're at the University of Oklahoma," you say. "Isn't that where you're supposed to 'acquire knowledge?'" &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;In theory, yes. After spending an entire semester in ENGL 2713 like I just did, you'd probably feel inclined to agree with me. You see, ENGL 2713 is "Black American Literature," and, as such, falls under the umbrella designation of  a "Black Studies" course. Now, don't get me wrong, I've got nothing agaist Black Studies. You can study Black all you want. After all, our American education system forces persons of African descent to study White for most, if not all, of their lives. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Now, back to the class itself. When I enrolled, I was led to believe that the class would be about literature. Here's the course description:  Examines masterworks in Afro-American literature. Particular attention given to individual quality and style, as well as to the larger question of tradition of Afro-American letters. Actually, we didn't examine any "masterworks," unless you consider  Assata  by Assata Shakur to be the work of a master. It's a good but, but give me a break - it's no  Huckleberry Finn . &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;"But Ben," you say, " The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn  was written by a white man. How can you compare that book to an autobiography of a black woman who was at war with a nation, who chose fleeing to Cuba over staying here and being treated as less than human?" &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Good point, but...that's not my point. My point is that we didn't read any "masterworks," nor did we discuss the quality or style of anything we read in class. What we  did  read was about the horrors of slavery and the injustice of lynching and the struggles of the civil rights movement and the general state of Blacks in America today. While I had no problem reading any of this, we didn't read it for it's  literary value . We read it for it's poltical value. Every single class discussion was a polical one, and like most political discussion, there was always two sides: the Blacks and crazy let's-save-the-world liberals on one side and me and a few like-minded sorority girls on the other. I didn't mind this either. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;What I  did  mind was that this class claimed to be about literature - African-American literature - but we spent the whole class trying to prove that African-Americans don't exist. Now does that make any fucking sense? I went into this class thinking I'd get to read some good books, or at least a few short stories. What I got instead was a class that tried to turn me into something I'm not. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;It's true that I'll never understand what it's like to be a young African person living in America. My classmates made sure I knew that much. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;But it's also true that all I really wanted to do was sit down and read a good book, like  The Bluest Eye  by Toni Morrison. Maybe I'll read it anyway.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Recently, a rather heated debate occurred at a table in Crossroads in the early hours of the morning. Who was there (beside myself) and how it came about is not important. What is important is the issue that was raised during the debate: the existence of God.  One of the participants posted an entry to his website detailing his reaction and immediate thoughts about the debate and asked anyone else who was involved to formulate their own responses, which he would then post.  Unfortunately, this person reconsidered and removed his post after I had already responded to it. Because I so firmly believe what I wrote, I feel that it needs to be posted here. Please remember that this is a response to another piece that I no longer have access to, nor would I post it here if I did have access to it. All direct references to the author of the original piece have been removed in the interest of anonymity, however references to and quotes from the piece itself have been left intact.   “We believe in one God, the Father, the Almighty, maker of heaven and earth, of all that is seen and unseen.”  This is the first full sentence of what Catholics refer to as the Nicene Creed (modern wording), which we hold as the profession of our faith. Belief in one God is an essential tenet of Catholicism, as it is with the other religions that evolved out of Judaism. While we hold other truths to be essential to our faith, such as the Immaculate Conception of the Virgin Mary and the Resurrection of Jesus Christ, the existence of God is primary.  That said, I feel it is safe to attack the argument laid out by --------------------. The following is a quote:  “It could be said that the spiritual is different. But why should that be? Asserting that it is isn't enough; what's the difference? Sure, I can't prove the existence or non-existence of God. That doesn't change the issue. I can't prove the existence or non-existence of space aliens at this point, but they're out there or they're not.”  While it only seems fair to assert that the spiritual is no different from any other realm of human thought, this is certainly not the case. When we deal with the physical world, we deal with (mostly) concrete concepts such as length, width, depth, time, and a host of other dimensions that I am not qualified to write about. In addition to the physical world, we have the workings of the human mind. Intensely personal and mysterious, there is still much to be explored about our brains, such as how we think, our conscience, and how I am able to sit here and contemplate my own contemplations ( metacognition , for all you educational psychology lovers out there). But our knowledge and understanding of our mental selves is indeed rooted in the physical world, as synapses fire and sensory organs provide data for analysis. Beyond the physical and the mental is the emotional, which often defies all logical reason (see  women ). However baffling, the emotional self is rooted in the physical world, as glands secrete and hormones do their thing.  Finally we come the  point  of my response—the uniqueness and personal nature of the spiritual self. I cannot prove the existence of God, nor can I prove the existence of space aliens. Unfortunately, space aliens are not God and should not be compared to Him. If space aliens do indeed exist, they exist in our physical world. By listening with a radio telescope, we might someday have proof of nonhuman intelligent life (alternatively, they can just fly over here and make a personal introduction). Conversely, the most powerful radio telescope will never find proof of God’s existence, nor will His existence be proven by any other physical means.  If a definitive answer of whether or not God exists is necessary, then religion is certainly not for you. The existence of God does not equate to the existence of space aliens or the spherical shape of the earth; rather, it equates to faith. For some, money may function as a god, or power, or sex, or anything one believes in. My god is the one God, the Father, the Almighty, creator of heaven and earth, of all that is seen and unseen. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      On Sunday night, the best drama on network television (excluding HBO) was honored when Kiefer Sutherland was awarded the Golden Globe for Actor In a Leading Role - Drama Series for his work on  24 . Congratulations, Kiefer, on your win and the recognition it brings to  24 .
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I've come to a realization, one that's been "brewing" for a while. I love  24 . My week is not complete without  24 . It is quite possibly the best drama on television right now. I hope it wins the two Golden Globes it's been nominated for. I know I'll be watching. Good luck,  24 , and thanks for making my week complete.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Well, here I am, back in Norman. One week of relaxation (i.e. RA Orientation) and then on to 16 more hours of class.  My break was absolutely wonderful. Got to spend a lot of time with the family, the pets, and a very good friend. Activities included movie-going ( Lord of the Rings  and  A Beautiful Mind , to name two), drinking coffee at various 24-hour establishments (Huck's and Round the Clock), bowling (although not that much), driving around (quite a bit of that), and getting crazy-drunk on New Year's Eve.  More to come...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah, so, I just posted that picture, and I've noticed that my journal page is getting rather long. Do you think I'm ready for an "archive"? I really don't post enough to warrant it...maybe a monthly archive...hmm...something to think about.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so, I saw this picture of Dick Cheney and I thought..."Wow, could you look any more Cheney than that?" And then I told myself, "That is Cheney," but I thought the picture was funny anyway. So here it is.    
</post>

<date>04,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      "Ben, you're bleeding from the head." - Sean O'Bleness
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Well, people have been wondering what this meant...so, I decided to take it off my profile and post it here. I can feel the cold steel I can make a wound that won't heal 38 millimeters like the police I'm at the door with John and Yoko Livin' love and peace and love and peace and love and peace Feel like an old shoe, a re-release Soon to be deceased Pull the trigger, the rock and roll nigger, Is bigger than Jesus on a bumper sticker Pull the trigger, I'm a rock and roll nigger, Bigger than Jesus on a bumper sticker My pulse is racing, my eyes are chasing For an autograph, I've been waiting Beatle baiting, there's no escaping History is taping Hey John, war is over we don't need your help America is making war on itself War is over we don't need your help America is making war on itself 600 and 76,000 Will go down In the streets of America With a bullet in the next 20 years 20 years, these bitter tears In the business of bitter tears John: More bodybags than Vietnam What's my name? Mark Chapman And we run into the arms of America. More to come...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Well, it looks like Iowa is still possible and&mdash;at this point&mdash;likely. My dad is currently looking for the cheapest possible living arrangements for five months in the form of a furnished apartment or extended-stay hotel. All of the benfits are still included. How can he pass it up?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so, you might notice the test post above. I was just randomly wondering if this thing still worked, since I haven't used it in, oh, about 7 months or so. But it does! Now, if I could only convince myself to use the damn thing. Grrrr...  Anyway, I'm up working (or should be working) on a paper for my Shakespeare class, as well as two small papers for my Partnerships in Education class. Anyway, I'll try to post more later.  Christmas break is coming. Woohoo!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Test
     
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
         My day:     11:30am  - Woke up "early" today. Normal wake-up time for a Sunday is much later, but alas I had a mission today: I was going to shoot stuff. Yes. My post from early this morning was very real. I was getting ready to shoot at stuff. The hour between waking up and leaving for the apartment consisted of sitting at the computer for 30 minutes, showering, dressing, and drinking coffee off and on. I put on my best fleece for my excursion - I was ready for wind.   12:30pm  - Arrived at the apartment. Mike and Ann were getting ready, and it was determined that we should go to Wal-mart to pick up some ammo and some clay pigeons.   Sometime between 12:30 and 1:30pm  - Stopped at Wal-mart to get the stuff. It was my first time actually looking for something in the "hunting" section of the store rather than just passing through it. We got what we needed and headed to Ann's parents' house, which is in the middle of nowhere.   1:30pm  - Got to the house. Ate food - it was good. Some chicken concoction, zuchinni and squash with cheese, and green bean casserole. For desert I had some Fannie Mae candies, and a little later some lemon pie (made with Cool Whip...yummy!). During dinner I got to drink Squirt, which is a favorite drink of mine back home, but it's unfortunately not available in Oklahoma. It's a citrus drink, kind of like Citra, but way better.   3:00pm (approx.)  - Went out with the guns looking for crows. The gap of time between dinner and our crow excursion is due to the fact that Mike had to clean or lube or do something to his guns. Anyway, we got out to the field and saw some crows. Ann was driving, so we approached slowly. They were up and to the right in some trees, and we were on a dirt road that cuts down the middle of the field. Ann pulled up so were were nearly parallel with the treeline. The theory was that if the birds didn't see us get out of the car, they wouldn't get spooked and fly off. It worked, but once mike got his rifle out and was ready to shoot, he had to go out in the open. As he crouched down to steady his aim, the birds took notice and flew off. Disappointing, for sure.   Some time later  - Mike encouraged me to shoot the guns. To be honest, at this point I was still toying with the idea of just watching. But curiousity overtook me, and I went for it. My first gun to shoot was the handgun - a Ruger .22 Competition something or other. It's a nice little gun with a sight. It's loud, but not too loud. One shot didn't bother my ears much, but three or four in quick succession did cause some mild - and temporary - ringing. Next up was the rifle, which was of the same caliber as the handgun but of course a lot longer and with a more intricate sight setup. That gun was a bit quieter than the other, but in a way a little less fun. Finally, I got to use the shotgun - a 12-gauge. I only fired that one once, and it had quite a kickback. All of the bullets at this point were being shot into the ground...I wasn't actually aiming at anything. Actually, one time I got pretty close to a piece of farm equipment while attempting to aim at a mound of dirt. That's the last time I aimed for anything but the ground.   A little more time later  - Once we realized that the crows weren't coming back, we went back to the house to grab some pop cans: Squirt and Diet Rite. We also grabbed some adhesive targets. We went out to what is essentially a gravel drive with tiers of railroad ties to one side. The first tier is about 5 feet tall, then there's some grass at the five foot level, and then antoher wall of railroad ties about 5 feet high. All in all, it's a great place for target practice. We lined up the cans on top of the first wall of railroad ties. This way, any low shots would hit the first wall; any high or off-center shots would hit the second wall further back. Of course, the object is to hit the cans. And hit the cans I did. Well, at least a few times anway. I didn't use the shotgun any more, but I did use up a lot of clips in both the handgun and the rifle. It was fun   7:00pm  - Well, have to stop the story here (temporarily) because I have to get some food. More to come! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so, I'm going shooting tomorrow. Yes, shooting. With guns. Or maybe a gun. I don't think they'll let me touch the big ones. Mind you, I've only touched one other gun in my life, and that was a big ass shotgun when I was in New Mexico. I nearly shit myself. Now, I've held and touched all of the guns I might encounter during my outing, so at least I know what to expect. But to actually fire one...that will be interesting. I'm actually excited. This could be a milestone in my life. I'll make sure to give a full report.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This is a great video that I want to share with everyone. I'm sure many of you have seen or at least heard of the infamous Windows 98 crash during a demonstration with Bill Gates there. Here's a link to the video - I hope you have a good laugh.    urlLink Windows 98 Crash 
</post>

<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Pearl Jam &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Riot Act  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Sony/Epic, 2002  Musical Quality:   Fun Factor:    Review:   Review coming soon!!!  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Avril Lavigne &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Let Go  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Arista, 2003  Musical Quality:   Fun Factor:    Review:  Well, this is my first album review, and I must say it's a pretty good one. You'll notice that there are two star ratings: one for "musical quality," which takes into account how the album sounds, whether or not it's innovative or different, and of course lyrical relavance and prowess. The second star rating is what I call "fun factor," athough it could also be called "pop factor." Basically, I'm rating the "poppiness" of the album. How catchy it is, how radio-friendly it is, and how much it will entertain the masses. Some music lovers hat "poppiness," but I don't necessarily think it's a bad thing. So anyway, if you hat "pop" music and you see a high "fun factor" rating, stay away! Also, the reason why I call it "fun factor" rather than "pop factor" is that there are two kinds of music I like: good music and fun music. Good music might get a high rating on "musical quality" but little or nothing for "fun factor"; fun music may be musically awful, but it's either damn catchy or just plain fun, hence "fun factor."  Anyway, on to Avril. I'm actually really impressed with the 18-year-old from Canada. Other than the fact that her first two singles, "Complicated" and "Sk8ter Boi" were and still are horrendously overplayed (and her third single "I'm With You" is well on its way to joining them), the songs really are good pop songs, and the rest of the album lives up to the reputations of the first three singles.  The album is definitely a fun listen; the only song that sometimes makes me want to puke is the pseudo-rapping Avril attempts on "Nobody's Fool." It seems a little out of place on such a hard-rocking pop album. Speaking of hard-rocking pop, I think Avril is doing a great thing for music. Even though it's just as bubblegum as Brittney in a way, at least she's helping to reintroduce guitars back into mainstream pop music. And that's definitely a good thing.  I'll stop here, but if I feel like adding more later, I can. Ciao! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'd like to start doing music reviews, since everyone else I know thinks that reviewing movies is the coolest thing in the world. My reviews will probably be a lot less useful, but considering some of the shit y'all watch, I don't think my taste is weird at all. Anyway, my first review is for Avril Lavigne's  Let Go , released last year (but I just started listening to it). Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Woohoo! All of the pages have been "adapted" to a color-changing scheme. How do I do it? Advanced technical know-how, that's how. Actually, it's just a mix of ASP and stylesheets. You see, every element of each page--both colors and graphics--is controlled by the stylesheet. By having five different stylesheets and five sets of images (thank goodness there are only two per page), the ASP code merely rotates in a different stylesheet each time the page is accessed.  It's interesting because all of the images were originally created in grayscale and then "colorized" in Paint Shop Pro to create the various color schemes. Supposedly, stylesheets allow you to overlay a slightly transparent color over another, thereby chanigng the color below. In theory, this would work for my grayscale images since the stylesheet considers them to be background images, anyway. So, just call in the background image, then overlay any color I want over it, making it 50% transparent or so. Cool! I should try that.  Anyway, I hope everyone thinks the color-changing is nifty. On the old version of the site, only the background image changed, and there were only two of them, and if your monitor didn't have high enough contrast, you could even tell that there was a background image there. I think this color-scheme changing is a lot more effective.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      All of the pages have now been  transformed . Colors are coming soon, I promise.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Last set of "entries" in my AIM profile. It's changed now...  It's early fall, there's a cloud on the New York skyline Innocence, dragged across a yellow line These are the hands that built America These are the hands that built America  The best show on television is back on. I'm talking about 24. Watch it. Tuesdays at 8 PM on FOX.   back in Norman... back at OU... back as an RA... but on a different floor. Well, at least something changed. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Redesigned the main page. Redesign of other pages to match will follow. Colors are coming. So is  urlLink Iowa . More on that later.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Murder Mystery Banquet #3 is tonight. There will much merriment afterwards as the cast converges on O'Connells. That should be fun. I hope all goes well - I have a feeling we won't run into any major problems with the performance. As for angry would-be guests clamoring to get in...well, that's another story. And, of course, the result of overselling and having a standby list. But, you do what you have to do. And standby was what we had to do. More on Murder Mystery later.  Also, the journal is now available at  urlLink http://beno.is-a-geek.com/blog/ . Enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'm working in the office tonight. Duty rounds. Listening to Zwan. Fun stuff. More updates later...and for you old 4easters, join the message board!!! Just sign up at  urlLink www.mywang.org , and e-mail me for instructions.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Zwan &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Mary Star of the Sea  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Martha's Music/Reprise, 2003  Musical Quality:   Fun Factor:    Review:  Zwan's debut album is, in short, a work of pop art. From the moment "Lyric" starts rolling out of my speakers until Billy Corgan's pleas to "Come With Me" close the disc, I am entranced. "Mary Star of the Sea" is certainly a canvas that has few equals in modern pop/rock. The album is dominated by 3- to 4-minute rockers; my favorites include "Lyric," "Endless Summer," "Baby Let's Rock," and the epic "Jesus, I." These songs are complimented by lighter, more acoustic pop tunes like "Heartsong" (one of my favorites), "Yeah!," and "Of a Broken Heart," and the aforementioned "Come With Me."  If the 4 1/2 Musical Quality stars are any indication, I am truly impressed with both the lyrical depth and musical integrity of this first release from Zwan. The Fun Factor, too, is higher than usual for an album of this quality, with a 4-star rating. This is due to the fact that most of the songs on the album sound like they would be "radio-friendly," unlike Pearl Jam's "Riot Act."  Those of you that are aware of my Smashing Pumpkins background know that the only album I actually own is "Adore," which is admittedly their most unconventinal album. I do have a vast collection of Pumpkins MP3s supplied by Cliff, but I don't usually make a habit of listening to them, mostly because I have yet to understand their oraganization. I am admitting to all of this to prove that my Pumpkins background is rather limited, so I was not part of the crowd of Pumpkins fans that ran out to buy this album hoping to relive the old days. I'm not sure if they got what they were expecting - I wasn't expecting anything but good music. And Billy Corgan & Crew have delivered.  I am a bit disappointed in the lack of airplay for "Honestly." It seemed to hit pretty big here in OKC but then got overplayed and consequently disliked, and now I don't seem to hear it at all. Hopefully Zwan as another single in the wings to take the place of "Honestly," a good tune in its own right.  My prediction is that Zwan will enjoy great success in the future as long as they decide to stick together. I am anxiously awaiting a tour announcement for the US - I will certainly be in line waiting for tickets. 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so, I'm supposed to be writing a paper but I'm procrastinating (what else?) and have decided to post my review of the Zwan album. It should be interesting...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      My apologies for over a month without posting. The first Murder Mystery Banquet was last night, and we have three shows left - tonight, March 8, and March 9. See our article in the Oklahoma Daily, which will be featured in print form on Monday, March 3 (or in the internet  urlLink here ).  Finally bought the Zwan album...look for a  review soon. And I promise to finish the PJ review.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      From  urlLink http://welovetheiraqiinformationminister.com/ : Still no confirmed sighting of Muhammed Saeed al-Sahaf (M.S.S.). An anxious world holds collective breath... France refuses to support breath holding but would still like to be involved "once everyone exhales." 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Ed Vedder after "Save You," April 3, 2003, Oklahoma City (Ford Center)   "I'm glad you could all be with us tonight. There's a lot of fucks in that last song, and it's fuckin' great to be here. And fuck is a great fuckin' word. And it seems like ten years ago, freedom of speech...it all had to do with if you could say fuck or not. Because it is, it's a word worth fighting for. You know, you say like, fuck him, fuck her, fuck me. Fuck. And then great ways to say it, you know: That's fuckin' beautiful. Fuck! And I personally can't say that I ever said it this way, but I'm sure you could say: Let's fuck.  "But now, freedom of speech, it has a lot to do with some much bigger issues. And somehow we played a show the other night and it's all of a sudden been misconstrued. They said 24 people left because they were upset at an anti-Bush administration remark.  "You're booing the story right? You're not booing me. Let's clarify that.  "You know, you could've written that story differently and you could've said 11,972 cheered and applauded at what the singer said. And we did support, pledged our suport and love to the troops. You know, how could we not be for the military? Look at this fuckin' haircut.  "So, no matter what it is, no matter how you feel, I think it's important for people to be able to protest, say what they feel, and put public pressure...put pressure on politicians and government just so that they will do a better job. There' snothing anti-patriotic about that. Because their job affects our families, our safety, our security, our relatives who are in the military, our friends, it affects everyone so we have a right to be a voice and be part of that, I would think, as part of a democracy. That's all we wanted to say.  "This is Given to Fly." 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Pearl Jam &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Riot Act 2003  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Oklahoma City  Musical Quality:   Fun Factor:    Review:  On Thursday night (April 3), Pearl Jam rocked the Ford Center in downtown OKC. It was a truly amazing show, and I felt I should share my experience with you all (y'all). You see, I preordered the "official" bootleg of the show, which will be shipped to me in five days or so. But preordering also allows me to download the unmastered MP3s of the show the day after. They're available for download, and I encourage you to give them a listen. Below is the setlist, and comments for some of the songs that really stand out. Of course, when I received the mastered 2-CD set, I'll be sure to rip that and give you access to the higher-quality recording. Enjoy!   Long Road - A lesser-known song from the Vitalogy era. It was featured on the "Merkin Ball" single with another song, "I Got Id."   Grievance - This song was obviously tinged with an anti-war, pro-protest sentiment: "I pledge my grievance to the flag." Only song from Binaural, Pearl Jam's 2000 album.   Jools and Jim (Pete Townshend) - Only the end of this song (about 30 seconds) as sung, which is just "Oklahoma" repeated, followed by a final "OK." The crowd went nuts.   Corduroy - The first song from Vitalogy, and a welcome one. Features a solo by guitarist Mike McCready (at least I think it was, I was kind of far away). Overall, the band did a good job of highlighting both of its awesome guitarists.   Save You - The first song from their latest release, Riot Act. Full of energy, full of "fuck"s, as Eddie mentions a bit later. Just plain cool.   Given To Fly - This is a long track, mostly because of Eddie's speech at the beginning about...well, what else - free speech. Apparently, two dozen people walked out of Wednesday's concert because of anti-Bush sentiments. Normally, Eddie comes out with a rubber Bush mask, dances around the stage in a gold sequined suit, then places the mask on top of the mic stand and proceeds to sing Bushleaguer. Well, none of that happened in OKC (thankfully, because half of the crowd might've left). But still, he thought it right to let his beliefs be known. Booing persisted, but come on. This is a Pearl Jam concert. You know they're going to be liberal, anti-war, anti-Bush. Why go if you're going to boo them? Makes no sense.... Anyway, the song itself was really good, and it was the first track from Yield.   Dissident - Ahh, track five from Vs. What a great song, and even better life. The crowd treated the beginning as a sort of "lighter" song. Perhaps they didn't know about the chorus.... Always remember, escape is never the safest path.   Even Flow - Once again, "Even Flow" cements Mike McCready as one of the coolest lead guitarists of his generation. The first song from Ten - and I'm not complaining. Extremely energetic, Even Flow rocked, plain and simple. The six-minute-plus time is mostly due to Mike's improvisation near the middle of the song (a two-minute solo). Absolutely brilliant. Ed says of Mike, "he just played all the notes."   I Am Mine - The first single from Riot Act, and a nice change of pace from "Even Flow." Eddie's vocals are great, and the band is right there with him. The build-up is perfect and Mike's short solo at the end is just right.   Love Boat Captain - Third song of the evening from Riot Act. I knew they brought the keyboardist on the tour for some reason...   1/2 Full - Another amazing solo from Mike McCready. The fourth song of the evening from Riot Act. Anyone who claims that Pearl Jam has "lost it" or can't rock any more...well, you should've been there.   Not For You - This song started with just drums, then the baseline. I don't think anyone recognized it until the rhythm guitar kicked in. I know I didn't. And speaking of still rocking...phew, what a rush. A little bit of improv near the end, very interesting. Second song of the night from Vitalogy, and there will be more....   Off He Goes - Ahh, the forgotten album. The only song of the night off No Code, Pearl Jam's 1996 album. Definitely a slower song, and worthy of lighter usage.   Elderly Woman - The best sing-a-long song ever! Ok, well, one of them. And sing along we did. Everyone did. It was fucking awesome. Wish I'd had the whole 4 East crew there with me. Started off real nice with Eddie counting and the band coming in right on time with his vocals. Can't get much better than that. Interesting: Ed dedicates the song to Chickasaw. Not sure if he meant Chickasha or what, but it was damn funny. From Vs, if you didn't know.   Untitled - A track debuted on Live on Two Legs, Pearl Jam's live album released in 1998. First song co-written with Matt Cameron, the band's new drummer (formerly of Soundgarden) who joined the band on their Yield tour to replace the departed Jack Irons.   MFC - Stands for "mini fast car," and a fast song at that. This was a fun one. From Yield.   Happy Birthday - Well, shit. Mike blew out one of his guitar amps. Ed says "sometimes happens twice a night." So, Ed drags out his ukulele. At a normal show, we'd here "Soon Forget," with Ed on the ukulele, from Binaural. But not tonight. Turns out it was Ed's brother's birthday, so we all sang happy birthday to him. And then we sang happy birthday to one of their light techs. Just wasting time, but it was cool.   Drifting - While Mike is getting his amp fixed, the boys pull out an rare one. This time it's "Drifting," their 1999 Christmas single. Ed claims it was "written while flying over Oklahoma," and it certainly has a "Western" edge to it. Features Ed on harmonica.   Get Right - Another song from Riot Act. The long break due to technical difficulties didn't bring the band down any..."Get Right" is just as energetic as the rest of the show has been so far.   DEEP - An oldie! The second song of the night from Ten, and it's rare one. In fact, before Thursday, they hadn't played it in seven years. Aren't those rare surprises cool? Eddie must've brushed on the lyrics, because he's dead-on. I checked.   Blood - Another surprising track, this one from Vs. One of those Ed-screaming-for-three-minutes songs. But still damn cool.   Encore Break 1 - Oh no! They just left! No good byes. What does this mean? It's the encore break, dumbass.   Better Man - What a song to come back on. The lighters are back out, of course, but just for the beginning. And it's another sing-a-long. Who doesn't know Better Man? From Vitalogy.   Daughter/(War) - I'd been hoping for "Daughter" (from Vs) and finally I got to hear it. Was expecting the song to morph into W.M.A. as it usually does, but Ed asks the crowd if they "want to try a little freedom of speech." "We're not trying to push it, but it might be a good time to try a little freedom of speech. If you don't want to sing along, don't sing along. You have the freedom of silence as well. And if you disagree, I respect that. We respect that. More power to you. We respect that. The guy who wrote these next words, his name was Edwin Starr, and he passed away yesterday, and...just have to sing these words these words. We have to, you don't." I'm sure you know what comes next. There was an amazing number of people that actually sang along. Of course, there were still boos. Stupid Okies. Shut the hell up and let the man sing. Afterward, Ed says "thanks for letting us do that." What a nice guy.   Do The Evolution - A staple of Pearl Jam's live act and full of energy as always. Couldn't help but think about the Star Wars Episode I trailer. You know what I mean. From Yield.   Rearviewmirror - The big finale, or so we thought. Look for the nine or so minutes of "jamming" in the middle. Damn cool, and it would've been ok to end it with RVM. Of course, Yellow Ledbetter is a nice way to end too... From Vs   Encore Break #2 - Another break. I knew they'd come back. They always do two encores.   Alive - There had to be another big song from Ten. I'd been hoping for "Black," but "Alive" worked just fine. Only one question remained: what would they end with? There's only two choices, really: "Rockin' In the Free World" or "Yellow Ledbetter." Those of us who were lucky enough to be in Albuquerque on October 20, 2000 got both...but that's pretty rare.   Yellow Ledbetter - A great ending to a great show. Mike's guitar is flawless. In fact, he ends the show, with the rest of the band pretty much making their way off the stage. From the "Jeremy" single, perhaps the best that Pearl Jam has ever put out. Also includes "Footsteps," another great song. Album Breakdown:   3 songs from Ten  5 songs from Vs  3 songs from Vitalogy  1 song from No Code  3 songs from Yield  1 song from Binaural  5 songs from Riot Act  4 b-sides  1 cover (2 if you count "War")  1 happy birthday   Oh, and here's an easily link if you want to download:  urlLink ftp://bono:edge@129.15.136.176/MP3s/Pearl%20Jam/Pearl%20Jam%20-%20Oklahoma%20City/   
     
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I'm finally going to bed. Had duty earlier...I just love the 10pm-2:30am shift on the weekends. It's my all-time fave!!! Been up making publicity for a "big" program Ann and I are planning - "SEX Around the World." It should be fun. I'm excited.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This weekend has been a long and arduous one. Whenever a group of friends seems -- emphasis on  seems  -- at odds with each other, good things usually do not ensue. However, things seem to have been worked out and maybe, just maybe, I can go back to the old way of doing things. Yes, I know I'm sounding like a traditionalist but hey, if it's broke don't fix it. Sure, it may be rough around the edges, but the more times we get cut by it, the more chances we have to smooth it out.  What the hell am I talking about? Anyway...now stepping into the non-metaphorical world...it's time for me to head out. Got things to do tonight.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Don't forget to check out the beers I've rated. Go  urlLink here .
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
      iTunes for Windows is the shit.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Once again I assert that Ms. Amy Steele is one of the nicest, most concerned, most approachable people I have ever met. I'd pay  her  to be my lawyer ten years from now. No lie.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I moved. Been moving, actually. Still not done. My day off yesterday was pretty much moving. We're about 70% done - still a lot to do but it's all little stuff. Big stuff furniture, TV, stereo, etc. is already in the new place.  More to come.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I missed a day! Before you know it I'll be missing multiple days and then I won't update at all.  It looks like we're moving downstairs to the two-bedroom. It's just not possible to come up with the $1600 we'd need to move to the other apartment we'd been thinking about in Lansing. But at least the place downstairs is a lot bigger. Unfortunately with all that extra space, we'll have to find stuff to fill it up. So now the hunt is on for furniture...how fun. Moving will start tomorrow as soon as we can get in touch with our landlord and get the go-ahead. The hardest stuff to move will be the big furniture (dressers, beds, etc.) but we've already got someone lined up to help us so it won't be too bad. We'll have all week to move the stuff so it won't be a one-day thing which will make the whole process a lot let stressful. And of course it's just down the stairs and around the corner, not five miles away. No U-Haul rental necessary.  What's really interesting about this whole apartment fiasco is that in the course of communicating with our landlord, he informed my sister that he was looking for someone to work in his office. Supposedly he's a chiropractor in Orland Park (about&nbsp;12 miles west of here) and he's looking for someone with an "MBA" to work for him. Well, my sisters not totally stupid and she knows I don't have one of those and told him so. I guess he knows I work for a bank and must have  some  business experience so he still wants to talk to me. Now, I've never spoken to the man for more than a minute. I ran into him once in the parking lot after I had first moved in. He took the opportunity to confirm the fact that I'm her brother and not some random guy living with her in a one-bedroom apartment. When my sister calls him tomorrow to tell him that we're taking the two-bedroom, she's going to tell him that I'm interested in this "job" he has in mind for me. Hey, if it's more money I'll do it - I'm easy.  A family friend was confirmed today so we spent most of the day at their house. It's amazing how much a cheap card and a $10 check can buy you - in this case, a delicious dinner.  It's pretty late, which indicates that I don't work tomorrow. Normally, I'd be in bed right now or at least thinking about it if I had to work at 11am the next day. Hopefully I'll be able to utilize my day off for moving and not sleep all day. I got to sleep in today, anyway, and I like to have at least one of those a week.  In other news, my trashy sister got a tattoo. I should've known something was up when she said, "Hey Ben, if I show you something, do you promise not to tell Mom and Dad?" I said no at the time but I found out about it eventually. Apparently it's small, located on her lower abdominal area (I still haven't seen it). However much I might disapprove of this body mutilation, I have to say that the tatoo she got sounds pretty cool. It's the heart-in-a-suitcase logo from U2's  All That You Can't Leave Behind  album and accompanying Elevation tour. Apparently the tattoo artist (artist...artist!?!?) took the design off of&nbsp;an Elevation tour T-shirt she brought in. What will she do next? More piercings? Another tattoo? Who knows...I just wish she'd get through this "rebellious" phase. In my opinion, she's a bit too old for it. But maybe I'm just all grown up and she's not. Maybe I'm the one that's old. If so, that's fine. I'm comfortable with it. Now  she's  the one that needs to grow up. Sooner rather than later, for my sake. I'm the one that has to live with her. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Worked again today. Seems like a regular thing, doesn't it? Currently, I'm listening to Pearl Jam and smoking my pipe. Does it get any better?  More on the apartment saga.... Today my sister talked to our current landlord about upgrading to a two-bedroom in our complex instead of moving out completely. This would allow us to remain within the terms of our lease. Bad news: a two-bedroom here is $80 more than the one I was looking into in Lansing. Good news: we wouldn't have to break our lease or come up with first month's rent/security deposit on a new place. Which one ends up being cheaper in the long run? Looks like I'll be crunching some numbers.  I'm pleased to note that I have two subscribers. Thank you, Chad and Antonio. You've help me become slightly more famous. Until next time....
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
         If you use Winamp 2.x or 5.x and just love to sing along to your music, WinLyrics is a must-have plugin. Most lyrics are available for download and many of these contain timestamps that allow WinLyrics to highlight each line as it is sung. Awesome!
</post>

<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Saw this on a friend's xanga site so I thought I'd do my own.      create your own personalized map of the USA  or  write about it on the open travel guide 
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Smoked my pipe again today. It's a good pipe. It makes me happy. Worked today too. No problems with Cathy today - she was actually nice. Unfortunately, I didn't get a lunch today. Instead I had to drive to Oak Lawn (103rd and Cicero...about 15 miles each way) to "exchange some documents" with a Suburban Bank & Trust branch. Well, at least I got to spend some time away from the bank.  I'm thinking I should write a book. Ok, I know what you're thinking. But hear me out. I have a map. It's not too detailed but it's got all of the essentials: coastline, kingdoms, cities, mountains, rivers, and more. I've developed a "mythology" for the map, including descriptions of the kingdoms, brief histories, and random facts. I think what I have so far would transfer nicely into some sort of fantasy novel. Only one problem: I have nothing else. No plot, no characters, no general idea. Just a fairly detailed setting. I guess it's a problem I'll have to work out...but in the meantime, here's the map I've developed for your viewing pleasure.    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My first real post. Finally. Worked today at 7:30. I was five minutes late. Cathy gave me hell for it. Or at least I think it was because I was five minutes late. It could just be because she's a total bitch. Or because she doesn't like me. Or becuase she resents the fact that I know more than she does. It's probably a combination of all three and a battle I don't think I can win, so is it really worth fighting? Sure, I can get there five minutes earlier but that won't solve everything else.  Got my new pipe today. It's a cheap meerschaum I ordered off the internet mostly because I don't know of any excellent toboccanists here. Also got some tasty tobacco with my order but of course I paid for that too. A couple of pictures below.       
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Leaving for Pella, Iowa in about 16 hours. Should be a nice drive and a fun weekend. Look for more pictures...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Happy Easter  to anyone who actually reads this thing. Went to Easter Vigil last night at 7:30pm (two hours long) and Easter Sunday mass today at 10:30am. I feel so holy.   In other news....  My parents, apparently crazy in their old age, have bought a camper and installed a hitch on their Liberty. Pictures below.     An exterior view of the camper.    Josie seems to like it. Jeep is in the background.
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Once again, 24 was excellent. Still my favorite show on television and no one can tell me any different.  Managed to wash all of the dishes today. There's nothing in the sink. That makes me happy.  Work tomorrow at 11am, no complaints. Well, except for the fact that I have to stay until 7pm. But, with DST in effect, it'll be nice and light when I leave and therefore much less depressing.  I'm into less depressing.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Diet RC is really good. Yes, I've converted to diet soda. I realized in my quest to cut carbs (no, I'm not one of those crazy Atkins people) that regular soda has a lot of sugar. But unfortunately I absolutely hated the taste of Nutrasweet, which all of the major diets use (Coke, Pepsi, etc.). But not good old Royal Crown. They use that new-fangled Splenda, the brand name for sucralose. Splenda is really good and doesn't leave that yucky aftertaste in my mouth. But it does make me pee a lot, a side effect I've learned to deal with. Now I've gotten to the point where regular soda tastes too damn sugary too me and I detest the way my mouth and specifically my teeth feel after drinking it. So, even when a Diet RC isn't readily available, I'll settle for a Diet Coke or Pepsi. Yeah, I still hate Nutrasweet, but it's better than all that sugar.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hmm...it would've been nice if I'd realized that my "Palm Sunday" post was actually on Monday...which means now I have two Monday posts. Not the end of the world.  Have the day off tomorrow. Supposedly my sister and I are going to (shameless plug) Earl's Lock Shop in Lansing to make a copy of our mail key and to make a copy of her car key (I lost the spare).  I have a bedroom now. Well, I've had one for about a week now but the idea is still new and wondrous to me. Here is a picture of my room:    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's Palm Sunday. Yes, I went to church. Early mass, actually. 8am. Yes, I'm a little bit crazy. But I'm more Catholic than I've ever been, so I guess that's a good thing.  New apartment is coming along nicely. Pretty much have everything where we want it. Now we just have to find more furniture. My sister has a friend whose family was moving so they got rid of a bedroom set which is now in my room. So now I have two dressers and a nightstand, yippee. No really, I'm excited. No more sneaking into my sister's room to get stuff out of her extra dresser. That was always a little strange anyway...  What we really need now is a couch for the living room. Looks kind of bare with just a recliner and some tables. And new beds. Now that I don't really have a need for a futon, I'd really rather not sleep on one, especially since it's never going to be put into its upright position again. Why would I?  Smoked my pipe today and picked up some yummy beer on Friday night. Three Floyds Alpha King pale ale. It's very good and made right here in Munster, IN (ok, ok, about 10 miles away but still...). Happened across it at a Jewel Osco in, appropriately enough, Munster, IN. I'm going to check out Torrence Liquors in Calumet City soon. They supposedly have the best selection of "good beers" in the immediate area. Should be fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Finally got the phone line back. I was beginning to go crazy. Now if I could only get Comcast to finish their "rebuild" so I could get cable interent...  I'd write more but I have to be at work in 30 minutes
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I know I've sung the praises of Opera many many times but I can't seem to get enough of this little program that does (almost) everything I need it to. Insanely fast web browsing, an innovative mail client, built-in newsgroup reader and newsfeed (RSS) reader, and you got everything you need to be an internet guru. Add to that some features that I haven't tried, including Opera's new built-in IRC chat client, and  you'd think you'd have a serious case of "bloatware" on your hands. I remember back in the day (and maybe still although I haven't used the program in its most recent iterations) when Netscape was a do-it-all program that handled browsing, e-mail, and even web page creation. However, Netscape always seemed bloated to me and the features besides web browsing were not as intuitive as they could have been and each component didn't share enough commonality as far as functionality and UI are concerned.  Enter Opera, which seamlessly integrates browsing, e-mail, and all that other stuff I've already mentioned into one exceedingly attractive program. There's something to be said for the only remaining web browser to innovate continuously (unlike Microsoft which as lately seemed to confine major enhancements to its web browser with each subsequent release of its operating system) and include these innovations in a program without having to utilize add-ons (last time I used Mozilla, mouse gestures were a downloadable add-on that never seemed to work right). With Opera, everything is built-in, ready-to-use, and functional the first time you start up. Everything from inline text find, inline link find, mouse gestures, and an abundance of keyboard commands make Opera a joy to use. In fact, I rarely use my mouse when working with Opera. For all but the largest webpages, there's no need. Everything I need to do - every  command I need to execute - is available using a simple keystroke. While I admit that I have not committed the entirety of the extensive list to memory, the most commonly used shortcuts are have become second-nature to me. These include "F2" to enter an address, "CTRL+N" for a new tab, "CTRL+E" to write a new e-mail message, and "G" to make the current e-mail as "read" and move to the next unread. I also helps that Opera makes use of many of the "standard" shortcuts made ubiquitous by Internet Explorer and Netscape such as "F5" (IE) or "CTRL+R" (NS) to reload the current page, "F11" to invoke full-screen mode, "ALT+HOME" to go to your designated homepage, "ALT+LEFT" or "ALT+RIGHT" to move back or forward, and "CTRL+W" to close the current page (window in the Single Document Interface world of IE). Again, Opera's well-executed Multiple Document Interface (MDI) allows for some shortcuts that aren't found in other browsers and some features that I find useful and unique. These include "CTRL+Click" to open a link in a background tab, "SHIFT+F11" to switch to Small-Screen Rendering mode (SSR), an awesome feature designed to make rendering pages on handheld devices a lot easier, and "F4" which turns on what Opera used to call the "Hotlist" but is now called a "Panel." The "F4" key displays the last-used panel, which can be one of ten including Search, Bookmarks, Mail, Contacts, Transfers, History, and Info. "Shift+F4" shows the Panel Selector which normal rests on the left side of the screen but can be placed elsewhere (right, top, or bottom). The Panel Selector allows for easy access to all of the panels which can also be activated by pressing "CTRL+0-9." There are so many modifications that can be made to the extremely flexible UI that I can't possibly explain them all here but with so much customizability, any experienced or novice internet user can find a layout that suits them.   Some noteworthy browser features include the Rewind and Fast-Forward buttons which compliment the standard Back and Forward. Rewind attempts to bring you back to the page you "started" at after clicking on a variety of links. This comes in handy when, after doing a Google search, you find your self ten clicks into some website. You could hit back ten times or hit the Rewind button, which takes you instantly back to the search page. Fast-Forward operates a little differently and takes you to what Opera thinks should be the next page in a sequence. It works amazingly well; when searching with Google, for example, the Fast-Forward button will take you to the next page of search results. Another nice feature is the Wand, a tool similar but better than IE's AutoComplete that stores usernames and passwords for any page that requires a logon. Opera remembers logons by page or by server. Visit a page that has a stored Wand password and a simple click on the Wand button or "CTRL+Enter" will fill in the required information and submit the form. The address bar also includes a built-in Google search box (now you can see why I offer up so many Google examples). With Opera, there's no need for Google's IE-only toolbar: Opera already blocks unwanted or all popups and allows searching from the address bar. Other great features include the ability to zoom pages (from 20% to 1000%), turn images on or off, and select the stylesheet for the page you viewing. This is an especially useful feature because you can turn the author-defined style sheet on or off or choose your own to apply to the page. This is useful in determining whether or not your page is standards-compliant. All new Blogger templates are, so turning off the style sheet has no detrimental effect. What's left is plain text that is still perfectly readable but without structure. Now that's what the world wide web is all about.   I especially like the e-mail client built in to Opera, dubbed M2. It is a standards-based client that lacks some of the advanced features of the overly bloated Outlook 2003 but makes e-mail communication easy and intuitive. Rather than utilizing a folder-based structure that almost every other e-mail client features, M2 uses a database-inspired organizational structure that makes use of filters or what Opera refers to as "access points." Rather than messages being downloaded to an inbox as in a traditional e-mail client, all M2 messages are saved in the "Received" view. Specific views can filter messages based on any number of attributes, such as read status (unread vs. read), contact (who sent the e-mail), attachment (based on type of attachment such as document, image, music, etc.), user-defined label (including important, todo, mail back, and valuable), and spam status (if the e-mail has been marked as spam by Opera's built-in filter or by the user indicating manually that the message is spam). Messages are also instantly searchable. Know that you've received an e-mail with the word "facetious" in it? Just do a search and it'll pop up. Opera indexes all searches and saves them for future reference until they are deleted by the user. All of these features make M2 very different from other clients and take some getting used to. Once the adjustment period is over, I think many users will find Opera's method of handling mail to be vastly superior to folder-based clients. Perhaps the one feature that M2 lacks that would be nice to have is the ability to compose messages in HTML format. Currently, M2 only supports composing in plain text. This is a drawback but think about it - how many e-mails do you write that require advanced formatting? For a quick note, plain text is just fine. On the other side of things, M2 recognizes and displays HTML e-mails just fine using Opera's rendering engine. A search on the Opera message boards for composing e-mails in HTML resulted in this post from an Opera customer service representative: "It is more a matter of resources. We have more important things to spend our development resources on." In response to the issue of being able to receive HTML e-mail but send it, the same representative responded: "There is a saying: 'Be conservative in what you send, be liberal in what you receive.'" Finally, in response to the assertion that if Opera is so anti-HTML, why would it allow users to read it but not send it? Response: "Opera can read bad HTML code, but that doesn't mean that we want to encourage people to write bad code." For those that are interested, the complete thread is available  urlLink here .   After all that I've written, I think it seems pretty obvious that I hold Opera in high regard. It is surprising, then, that I still make regular use of Internet Explorer. For what, you ask? Well, I still have a Hotmail account that I use regularly and I like to visit MSNBC once in a while, and Microsoft likes to make sure that every bit of content it produces is best viewed in IE. There was even a bit of controversy recently regarding Microsoft's MSN.com which was deliberately sending a sub-par stylesheet to Opera users in an attempt to encourage them to use IE. Additionally, Opera seems to have some sort of problem viewing my bank's  urlLink online banking , so I am forced to use IE. This is an odd problem considering that the site worked just fine with the Opera 6.x series of browsers but stopped working with the 7.x series. I should post a complaint.   Overall, though, Opera serves my needs just fine and for everyday browsing, searching, news reading, etc., it is my browser of choice. I've included a screenshot below which is the way my copy of Opera looks most of the time. On the left is the Panel Selector, the Mail panel, and a tab featuring this very blog. Above the page is the address bar which features standard navigational buttons (rewind, back, forward, fast-forward, reload, and wand), the address box, the built-in Google searchbox, the zoom level selector, the security button, and the images/stylesheet button. At the bop is the "New Page" button as well as the tab bar, followed by the menu. As I've already mentioned, all of these elements are completely customizable and may be moved or turned off at will.    urlLink      What more could you ask for in a browser? Opera 7.5 excels, and with continued development, it can only get better. An ad-supported version of Opera is available for a free download from  urlLink Opera Software ASA . Opera may be purchased for USD 39. Donations are available for web designers and other web professionals (I happened to qualify) by visiting Opera's  urlLink Global Donations  area.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sometimes you realize something that makes your life a whole lot easier. When I say “life,” I’m really referring to this thing I’m typing to write now. Yes, I’m talking about my journal. I found out, rather interestingly, that not only is my journal located at  urlLink http://home.comcast.net/~bhinc , but it is also available at  urlLink http://bhinc.home.comcast.net/ , which is infinitely better. Why is it better, you ask? Well, for one thing, you don’t have to make the goofy little ~ symbol when typing in the address. In addition, it allows me to work in a “root” directory, meaning that I don’t have to link all my files as “/~bhinc/images/…” but rather “/images/….” See what I mean? Infinitely better.  Enough ranting. Time to watch  Timeline  and go to bed.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, I know the title of this post may sound trivial and even bit presumptuous. The assertion that any one thing can bring about unprecedented levels of happiness is certainly an audacious one, especially when one most often hears such statements in concert with developments such as winning a million dollars or finding your true love. Even so, I have determined that having broadband after spending so many months playing the waiting game with a modem has brought about a certain level of happiness in my life. Near-instantaneous pictures, streaming audio and video, and downloads in a flash. That's some good stuff, especially after being spoiled by the T1 connection I enjoyed for 5.5 years as a student at the  urlLink University of Oklahoma . One pastime that I have "re-discovered" after acquiring broadband internet access from  urlLink Comcast  is the ability to stream internet-only radio stations. One of my favorites is the commercial free, only-80's  urlLink Club 977 . They play some great music and when using the broadband feed, it sounds really good. I use their SHOUTcast feed with Winamp 5.03, but they also stream in Real and Windows Media formats. Check them out of you're a fan of 80's music - you won't be disappointed.  It has been a few days since my last post and, appropriately, not much has happened since then or I would have posted in the interim. My dad was here for a visit from Monday until today. My sister worked Monday from 2:30 - 10:30 so he and I went out to dinner which was nice. We also did a little shopping where I acquired a few new shirts for work and a new pair of shoes (thanks, Dad). Last night he was off to U.S. Cellular Field to watch the White Sox get slammed by the Texas Rangers. Oh well. At least he took some pictures with my camera. He was fortunate enough to be able to watch the game from the Sherwin-Williams corporate skybox. Here's a great picture of the scoreboard from the skybox:     I'm off tomorrow so I anticipate a lazy day as I normally do laundry on Sunday. What will I do? Who knows...but whatever it is, I hope it's fun. Right now I'm going to watch the season finale of  Enterprise  which my sister so graciously taped for me. Thanks, Lauren. I appreciate it.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As the title of this post might indicate, this is my first time posting by e-mail. Yet another of the many once-premium features that Google has incorporated into the updated and upgraded Blogger. And, even though I'll be able to spell-check my posts when I use Opera (see  urlLink http://www.opera.com/support/tutorials/opera/spellcheck/  for more information), it's even easier to utilize Outlook's spell-check capabilities. Plus I'm able to post remotely without havening to go through the sign-in process at Blogger.  Had to work this morning at 7:45 am and woke up late, but what else is new. Neglected to take a lunch today so I was able to leave an hour early - that option is especially nice on Saturdays when I  really  don't want to be at work. Speaking of work, I've put a new-and-updated resume together because I'm interested in applying for a job. It's a customer-service-related position at Park Press located in South Holland. They are a local printer that prints a weekly free paper as well as other projects. I'd at least like to find out how much they're willing to pay.  Supposed to hang out with Chuck tonight but he didn't call when he was supposed to and no one seems to know where he is. His loss, I guess, even though I've been waiting for Chuck to re-appear on a more regular basis ever since I moved back to Illinois. Hopefully he'll get over whatever blockage he has and be "normal" again.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I finally have cable in my room. Just took a trip to Best Buy and a little handiwork with a drill. Also have my computer linked via 18 feet of cable to my VCR, thus allowing me to download all sorts of video files and pipe them to the TV/stereo. Very nice. And now that I finally have  broadband , I can actually  download  stuff. Also very nice.  Have to work at 7:30 so bedtime is rapidly approaching. My dad is coming in for a business trip/visit on Monday and he's staying for three nights. At least he'll buy us lots of stuff. Hey, I'm allowed to have hopes and dreams.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, what a wonderful technologically advanced world we live in. And I thought Xanga's subscribe feature was useful. Now I realize how limited it actually was.  You are now able to subscribe to my journal using two formats:  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; RSS 2.0:  urlLink http://feeds.feedburner.com/bhinc  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Atom:  urlLink http://bhinc.home.comcast.net/atom.xml    You can use any of the available newsreaders that are out there to subscribe or you could use the most awesome  urlLink Opera 7.5 . I highly recommend this. Currently, Opera only supports RSS feeds but I'm hoping a later release will add support for Atom (as it stands, Blogger only allows you to publish feeds using Atom and a 3rd-party service must be utilized to publish an RSS feed).  Questions? Let me know. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      And now I begin the process of moving everything I've done over at Xanga to my new Blogger - no ads and it's on my own server space so  I control it . I'm going to try to pre-date the posts from Xanga so the follow chronologically, something I couldn't do when moving from Blogger to Xanga. Another perk.  Man, this Comcast broadband is fast.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Finally! We have an appointment for Wednesday (05.19.04) to get  Comcast cable internet  installed. I have been waiting for this day for a long while.   In other news...   Google's bid to take over the world seems not too far off, and they are updating their services to reflect their newfound wealth (ok, not yet but certainly after the IPO). One service that I'm excited about is GMail, Google's free e-mail client. I'm so tired of AOL and of course once we get Comcast up and running I'll be using one of their accounts. But GMail sounds intriguing and I'll definitely try it once it becomes available to the public.  Another of the services they've freshened is Blogger, which you may recall was my blog-of-choice before moving to Xanga. The real reason for moving to Xanga was its ease of posting and the ability for other Xanga users (some of whom I count as friends) to post comments. While I don't seem to have received any comments to date, I still like the idea of people having the ability to post. The final reason for switching to Xanga was the loss of my T1 connection to the internet and my handy static IP address, which allowed me to run my computer as a server on OU's network. Well, Google seems to have fixed all of Blogger's shortcomings when it comes to Xanga and I'll soon have webspace with Comcast if I decide not to run my computer as a server again (which invites all sorts of hacker-type attacks). In addition, Blogger seems to be more standards-compliant than Xanga and therefore Opera 7.5 (the best browser out there) likes it a lot better than Xanga. It's a good thing for me I haven't done too many posts to this thing so it won't be too hard to migrate.  Look for my new-and-improved blog to debut somewhere on the internet next week. I'll of course make one last post here to let everyone know where it's gone. And for those of you who are wondering, no, you do not have to be a Blogger user to leave comments with Blogger. Anyone in the world can. And that's a lot of people.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah, it's been a while. Been busy working and sorting through boxes of stuff my parents brought from Iowa that was "taking up space in their storage unit."  The  good  news is that  Comcast  has finally finished their upgrade in our area. Thus, they will be adding a slew of new channels as well as  cable internet , which should be available sometime this week. Note that as soon as I am signed up for and making use of said  cable internet , I will once again maintain a 24/7 online presence. While this is not as useful as it once was (my AIM usagee has decreased considerably over the last four months as people seem less inclined to want to chat with me), it should encouarge me to make more frequent posts to this journal as well as keep with with other methods of communicaion.  That's all for now...laundry day today, then "Laugh Out Loud Sunday" on FOX, although I'm sad that the season finale of   Arrested Development &nbsp; has already aired while  Simpsons  and  Malcolm  continue to have new episodes. And of course I'm looking forward to the last episodes of   24   on Tuesdays. Still my favorite show by far.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's Thursday, my day off, and I'm sitting around doing nothing. I'm poking around the internet, going to my favorite nerd-oriented websites (BetaNews, News.com, etc.), reading and sending e-mails, etc., when I realized that it has been somewhat of a long interval since my last journal post. You could blame this on my over-active social life, but we know that's not the case. I'm always here, at home I mean, and you'd think I wouldn't have a problem posting on a regular basis. But I always have so I guess that's just the way it is.  My car, Jack Bletta, is still banged up. I have an appointment to take it to the body shop (Cars Collision in South Holland) on June 28. Yeah, that's a few days from now, isn't it? Seemed so far off just last week. Also have an appointment for a rental from Enterprise but I never called them back. Guess I'd better do that. Still not sure what the status of the repairs is - I mean, I'm not sure if they're going to fix it or not. The other guy's insurance company is going to send an independent appraiser to the body shop to check it over before they start tearing things apart. Good heavens. I hope he OKs everything so I get my car back.   urlLink   Now on to job-related news. I've currently put my name into the hat for two positions. The first is at Great Lakes Bank (my current employer) as a Senior Teller at the Hazel Crest branch. For those who are unfamiliar with Great Lakes, the Hazel Crest facility is located on 183rd St. just west of Kedzie Ave. It's definitely farther than my current branch (South Holland Walt's) but I'll probably like the job better. Only problem is, I'm not sure if the pay will be comparable or not. I'm looking for a lateral move - just to another "division" of the bank. I'm hoping that this is the one. The  other  job I'm applying for is not anywhere close to home but in Pella, Iowa. Leighton State Bank has a Loan Assistant position at their Pella branch.  urlLink    I've faxed them my resume and left a message but haven't heard back yet. I'll call again today. The job itself sounds pretty boring (I'm assuming there's little to no customer contact, which is what makes working at a bank interesting) so we'll see what happens with that. Honestly, I'd much rather be a banker or a teller but in a town as small as Pella, these jobs may not open up that often.  Let's see, what else is going on. Not much. Not now. More to come as always.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jack Bletta the Black Jetta has been through a lot but he's never been rear-ended, at least not until June 10, 2004. While on our way to what was to be a fun-filled day at Chicago's Museum Campus (and free I might add), my sister and I decided to take the "long way" as the conventional route - I-94 West from 159th Street to I-55 North and then on to Lake Shore Drive - was extremely congested. Our jaunt down 103rd Street was without incident and we made it south on Torrence and east on 106th just fine. It was north on Ewing that was going to be troublesome. Everything was fine until I took a wrong  urlLink   turn under the Skyway (I should've went straight but I turned left instead) that immediately preceded our whiplash-inducing encounter with another vehicle. I quickly turned around and made my way back to Ewing and once again headed north. As we approached 96th Street (where Ewing experiences a Norman-esque angular curve), the van in front of us abruptly stopped. I looked up to see the driver motioning to "go around" but as traffic was approaching in the other lane, it seemed unwise at the time. Then...bam. Yes, we were slammed from behind by a '96 Ford Ranger XLT. Well, maybe not slammed, but certainly more than tapped. Below are some images of my car taken today with, of course, captions. Oh, and you can click them to make them bigger.   urlLink    The most "injured" part of the car, or a least the area that looks the worst. This is the left rear bumper area.   urlLink    Same type of thing, only on the right side, and not as serious.   urlLink    The trunk isn't exactly flush with everything else anymore. It doesn't open, either.   urlLink    Left corner of the rear bumper. Looks like that's going to be replaced, at least I hope so.   urlLink    The only non-bumper body damage I can find (besides the trunk not lining up) is this little portion that seems "pushed" in. Hopefully they can "pull" it out and not replace the whole quarter panel...again.   urlLink    The area under the license plate also suffered some damage...guess that's body damage, too. Doh!   urlLink    One more picture, totally unrelated. That's what it looks like when our air conditioner has been on for a while.  There is, of course, more to come on this whole accident thing. I filed a claim today with the other guy's insurance company so we'll see how long all of this takes. At least I'll get a new bumper out of the deal. I needed one.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       No, not really, but Rs and Ws sound so good together. At left is some artwork I Photoshopped (don't you love how that's a usable verb even though I didn't really use Photoshop). Some say that Reagan should replace Hamilton on the $10. Well, I've got my own thoughts on Reagan and I don't have time to put them all here. I'll be watching the events this week when I can. A more detailed discussion of my Regean-related feelings will follow...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Now that I'm on this "picture kick," here's a shot of my cat Abbie's new favorite spot. Isn't she cute???    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       It's June already. The months are just flying by. The picture to the left is my buddy Jake who graduated from 8th grade yesterday. Congratulations to Jake. He also has the honor of being a member of the last graduating class of  urlLink Holy Ghost School  which is closing its doors after the 2003-2004 school year. It is interesting to note that Holy Ghost is also my grade school alma mater. I graduated from Holy Ghost ten years ago - 1994. Man, I'm old.  Rented some movies. Going to watch  Paycheck  and  Peter Pan  today. I've already seen bits and pieces of  Paycheck  but I managed to fall asleep both times I tried to watch it, so I'm looking forward to seeing the whole thing from the beginning without interruption.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I started my new job yesterday and I already have my first day off! No, really, Wednesday is going to be my normal day off from now on so really it's not that weird. As for the job itself, I haven't yet figured out what a banker  does . I mean, sure, when I have a customer, I do whatever they need me to do, right? Like open an account, print out a statement, etc. But when I don't have any customers...well, I'm still not sure. Supposedly I'll eventually be given stuff to do but until then I've just been sitting there and "looking" busy. I guess that's all I can do for now.  In other news, my phone service has now been fully switched to  urlLink Vonage . For those unaware, Vonage is a VoIP provider (or Voice over Internet Protocol). After a rocky first few weeks where I'd randomly lose dial tone due to some problems with my phone adapter (the little black box between the cable modem and my computer), I think all of the bugs have been worked out. I'm really impressed by the service and it's cost-effectiveness. My sister and I don't use our home phone much - both of us have cell phones so that makes up the bulk of our calling. Unfortunately, my cell phone doesn't work anywhere inside my apartment so having a home phone is essential. Currently, we're on the $14.99 plan that Vonage offers which includes 500 outgoing minutes, which includes local and long distance calling. For $10 more we can get unlimited local and 500 long distance, or for $5 more than that we could get complete unlimited calling. However, since the bulk of our calls from home are to Iowa, it seems that the 500 minutes is plenty. And it's a lot better than paying $40 or more a month to AT&T for local and long distance service. If anyone is interested in trying out Vonage, let me know and I'll "refer" you to them. I get a credit for this, of course, but you're my friend, right? You don't mind.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On Thursday I was fortunate enough to make it downtown to visit Chicago's newest attraction: Millennium Park. The park cost millions to build but to me it seems well worth it. It's not a park in the recreational sense (although one of my pictures may dispute this fact). Instead, it's more of a cultural experience. Located on Michigan Avenue just north of the Art Institute of Chicago, Millennium Park is truly a sight to behold.   urlLink   The first of my pictures is one of two of the newly built Pritzker Pavilion. It was originally designed to replace the venerable Petrillo Music Shell in Grant Park but this venue is decidedly upscale and is currently home to the Grant Park Orchestra. The pavilion was designed by world-famous architect Frank Gehry and is absolutely stunning. The pavilion itself stands 120 feet high, with "ribbons" clad in stainless steel that extend from out of the top of the stage area which connect to an overhead array of crisscrossing steel pipes that define the lawn seating area.  urlLink   These pipes also serve as anchors for the speakers that are suspended throughout the pavilion to provide the sound quality necessary for such an outdoor venue. This can be seen in my second picture of the Pritzker Pavilion. It's certainly a breathtaking sight and I hope to take in a performance there at some point if only to say that I did.  My next picture is of "Cloud Gate," a sculpture by world-famous British artist Anish Kapoor. While the sculpture has become affectionately known to Chicagoans as "The Bean," the stainless steel behemoth (weighing in at 110 tons) is actually inspired  urlLink   by an ingot of liquid mercury. It's highly polished and beautifully reflects both the park and the cityscape of Michigan Avenue behind it. Even better, visitors are encouraged to walk under (and eventually through) the sculpture, which is polished inside and out, and become part of its magic.   urlLink   Next is a shot of the Lurie Garden which is a sort of nature preserve smack in the middle of the city. Since everything has just been planted it's going to take a while to reach its full potential but its beauty is already evident.  Finally, and probably my favorite part of Millennium Park, is the giant Crown Fountain designed by Spanish sculptor Jaume Plensa. It's framed by two 50 foot high glass block towers. Water continuously cascades down all four sides of each tower. On the sides of the towers facing each other, a video screen depicts faces of regular Chicagoans.  urlLink   In fact, 1000 random Chicagoans were chosen to be filmed for this artistic wonder. The faces move, smile, etc., and change randomly. However, before each face disappears, its lips pucker and water shoots out of its mouth (caught in my picture). It is obvious that this is the most "fun" part of Millennium Park, especially on a hot day as this one was. For those interested or familiar with famous Chicago skyscrapers, that's One Prudential Plaza in the background with Two Prudential Plaza looming just to its right.  I had a great time visiting Millennium Park and encourage any visitors to Chicago to check it out. It's a great new world-class attraction to add to our list (including the Art Institute, Field Museum, Shedd Aquarium, Museum of Science and Industry, the "Magnificent Mile," the Sears Tower, and many others).  In other news.... My car will not be with me this week. They got the wrong part again so it's probably going to be another week. Doh!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You'd think I would've learned my lesson when it comes to long intervals between posts...but I guess I'm doomed to repeat my past mistakes.  First item of business: I was rear-ended again. I was driving my rental car (a crappy 2004 Chevy Cavalier...ewww!) minding my own business trying to get home on my lunch break. I'm heading eastbound on 173rd Street, approaching the intersection with S Park Ave. urlLink    I stop at the stop sign and signal my intention to turn right. There's a break in traffic so I could've turned but I wait - I'm not taking any chances in a rental that I didn't take out the "optional" insurance on. Then...wham. I feel a jolt. I know that jolt - someone just rear-ended me. Again. I look in my rear view. It's a police car. What the hell? A police car just hit me? Am I dreaming? No, I'm not. I was actually rear-ended by a Thornton cop who was just driving around. I get out, he gets out. "I thought you were going to turn." My first thought: how many times as  he  heard that one? That's no excuse and he knows it. Of course, we're in South Holland so he radios Thornton dispatch to send a SHPD officer to the scene. He arrives, chuckles, and proceeds to fill out the report. By now half of the Thornton police department has shown up (which believe me isn't that many people) to see what happened. They laugh, they joke, they can't believe it. Neither can I. While this is all happening I call work and tell them I might be a little late getting back from my lunch break. They ask why, I tell them. There's silence. They know why my car is in the shop. They say OK and I'm back to watching the cops come and go. After it's all done I get the standard police report. I go home and try to calm down - this is a lot to handle. Finally I get up the courage to  drive  again and head back to work. I have my police report, everyone wants to see it. I make copies because I know no one will believe me. I call Enterprise - their office closed at noon. Damn. So I get connected to their 800 number. I listen to the options. There's no "got hit by a cop" option so I pick roadside assistance. Not exactly what I'm looking for but maybe they know what to do. They did. They took my accident report and didn't seem to think it was a big deal. Ok, so now that's done. Later that week (the accident happened on July 10) I actually go to Enterprise. They take a more detailed report. "We haven't heard that one in a while," they joke. I'm not laughing. Apparently it's not a big deal to them either. I guess there's no doubt that the Village of Thornton will pay. So at least that's good news. So now I've got a dented rental and still no Jetta. I guess the body shop ordered a part and they sent the wrong one. If it's there by next Monday that's  three weeks . But, it's ok. As long as I don't have to pay anything they can keep it as long as the need to to get it right.  Next item on the agenda: I've taken yet another plunge into the information age. Today I signed up for Vonage telephone service, a VoIP provider (for those who are not as internet-savvy as some of us, that means Voice over Internet Protocol). For a $30 setup fee and $10 shipping, they're going to send me a little box that plugs in to my broadband connection, which in this case is a cable modem furnished by Comcast. I plug my phone into the contraption and presto - my phone calls are now relayed over the internet rather than SBC's aging landlines. And they're even going to transfer our phone number. When it's all said and done, we'll get 500 "anytime" minutes a month, both local and long distance. There's a whole list of features that are free, including voice male, caller ID, call forwarding, call transferring, 3-way calling, etc. SBC and AT&T can't even come close to that kind of value. Plus, I figure the money I save on having phone service over my broadband connection will lessen the impact of paying more  to have a broadband connection . Does that make sense? I think so.   urlLink   Final item: I got a promotion!!! Yes, after only four months on the job, I have been promoted to the position of relationship banker at Great Lakes' Matteson branch. This is a nice step up for me as I'll finally have my own desk, phone, computer, and business cards!!! All you friends out there, be prepared to get a little mailer from me. Everyone is going to see these things! And, for those who might be confused, no the bank is  not  in the mall. It's a rather large free-standing branch across the street which also serves as the corporate headquarters. Be happy for me. I am.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>