<Blog>


<date>30,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm blogging from my cousin's house in JB right now. Big ass screen.. cool. Anyways, the trip has so far been filled with visiting and spending time with relatives. I'm missing KL, though. But, at the same time I'm chilling out and appreciating the quality time with everyone. Besides, I had  a few sms msgs and a couple of phone calls  that put a smile on my face *Hehe* * wink wink*  I've been using up the credit on my brother's cell sending msgs to people *Hehe* I promised him I'll pay for them, that refrained him from killing me. Fahmy called around 11pm and told me he's meeting up with Shakhira at BarFlam for drinks. I texted Shakhira when I got back from my uncle's place and she said she's  "borrowing"  Fahmy. Crazy girl. *sniff sniff*  I wanna be there!!!    Counting the hours until Monday... When I'll be back in KL and celebrating New Year's with everyone. Crap! I still haven't gotten an outfit for that night. Well, gonna sign off now.   G'nite. 
    
</post>

<date>28,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa.. last night was freaky. Not weird-freaky.. but major-fun-freaky. Went to dinner with Diana, Ninie and Shakhira at Modesto's. Ninie's having her birthday thang at  urlLink BarFlam  tonight, so we went over so she could finalise her reservations and stuff.   Original plan:  A drink or two while Ninie talk to the guy there.  Finally:  Stayed until midnight, left the place and somehow ended up back there. Diana went home, but we stayed until after 3am. *shakes head* Shakhira had mas0r fun, me and Ninie danced to practically all the songs. We were dressed majorly casual, while the most of the crowd (the girls, anyway) were decked in clubbing attire.  urlLink BarFlam  was surprisingly crowded and kicking, for a Thursday night. A couple of guys from the place came over after work and we hung out 'til morning. I had to leave around 10.45am to pick my sister up and head home.   That brings me to the not so good piece of news. I'm leaving for JB later. That means, I had to leave Shakhira's place when I didn't want to and also I'll be missing Ninie's birthday do.  BOOOO!  I'm really dissapointed. Oh well, atleast I had some last minute fun last night and this morning. The bright side is, I'll be back Monday (the 31st) in time to celebrate the new year with the girls. No definite plans for the night, but all I know is I wanna have one hell of a time.  Well, gotta get some stuff done before the trip. I'm gonna go now, maybe I'll be able to blog from JB.. I don't know. See you next year! 
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
            Take the  urlLink "What kind of Squirrel am I Test!" 
</post>

<date>25,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      This is freakin spooky. Annoying too. Somehow my password to my  urlLink blog  was changed. I don't remember changing it, let alone to only a single letter. Weird. Was I tripping like mad when I was writting the last entry and changed the darn thing?  I highly doubt it.  Oh well... Whatever.  It was just confirmed that I'll be going to Johor on Friday.  This  Friday.  3 days before New Year's eve.  As you can already imagine, I'm highly dissapointed. Yeah, a little pissed too. Mom said we'll drive down after I get back from class Friday afternoon. Suck ass. I didn't ask her how long we'll be staying there, but I hinted on some NYE thingy during breakfast this morning. Hopefully, we'll be back by Monday. Pray for me!  Oh, I finally sent the roll of film to be developed. The roll with the pictures of the people we met at the Beach Club a few weeks ago, and also of Hari Raya and some snaps from last night's open-house. I'm feeling pretty strange.. Funny, even *Hehe* My mind has officially ran out of things to write, so I'm gonna say byebye right now.  Bye bye.
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Been 5 days. What's been happening? Quite a few actually. As usual, it's  quick re-cap time!  This time, I'm not going day to day. Instead I'm just gonna mention days where interesting things happened. As much as I can remember. Here goes..  On Saturday, 22nd December, a bunch of us went to the soft launch party of this new bar in Bangsar. It's called  urlLink barFlam  (the site says it's pronounced as flame). Before that, Shakhira had this BBQ thingy. So it's chicken wings and lamb before we got dressed up. The original plan was to drop by the opening for a bit, since we know the guy who works there, plus it'll be cool to check the place out. After that, we were planning on going to KL and hit Gatecrasher at Movement... That, or just some other place. Just some place where we can dance like mad and have fun.  As it turned out,  urlLink Flams  was pretty kicking. The music was a mixture of everything, yet it kept the happy-mood up. Like I kept repeating last night,  "it's a feel good place"  *Heheh* Me, Shakhira, Rakhma and Nini got there first. Then we decided to stay and called up the rest to come join us there. Mach and Farah turned up next, then Marcus and Gerald. Fahmy called, so I told him to make his way over. A friend of Shakhira, Hisham, also came to hang out. We danced the whole night to practically all the songs. It's kinda different from the rest of the places in Bangsar. Too bad it's kinda small.. Everyone was dancing everywhere and anywhere. Towards the end of the night, there were also  people up on the bartop shakin' boo-tay . After  urlLink Flams , everyone hung out at Shakhira's place. Some went home, some slept over. It was a good night.  That brings us to..  last night,  Christmas eve. Muff invited a bunch of people to his place for a Hari Raya open-house. Got to meet up with some of the  urlLink people from school that I haven't seen in years . The guys, anyway. We got there around 3pm and left a couple of hours after that. I think. We headed to Coffee Bean in Bangsar to meet up with Gerald, then went down to Telawi because Shakhira was hungry again. We ate at Modesto's, and somehow I ended up buying a new skirt. Some time during the meal it was decided we'd hit Flams later, after we go home and change. I left a top at Shakhira's place, so that got paired with the skirt.   Last night was mad!  I think it was even more fun than Saturday night. We got there around 10pm, got the same corner table (by the entrance) as the other night. At first, it was only the 4 of us.. Me, Nini, Shakhira and Diana. Then Marcus and Gerald turned up. Fahmy called up, and I told him to grab a few friends and come over. He turned up with 4 friends, and then later in the night Carlos showed up with his girlfriend. It was one massive party.. Okay, maybe I'm exaggerating. But I did have mas0r fun. There was the countdown to Christmas, and santa hats and glowsticks abound. The place was packed like mad, and the whole stretch of Telawi was filled with people. We partied the whole night, and I even ran into Dolly there. There I was, dancing like I'm on drugs with a santa hat on my head, when she walked in with Fahmy. Pretty funny stuff. Fahmy ran into her when he was outside making a phone call.  I don't know what time we finally left the place. Everyone (minus Carlos, his girlfriend and Marcus) went back to the apartment with us. Everyone hung out at Shakhira's place doing whatever. Even a couple of guys from  urlLink Flams  came over. All the guys, and Nini, ended up sleeping like logs. Sheeshh. Even an earthquake wouldn't have woken them. Me, Shakhira and Diana stayed up talking and laughing. I still haven't gotten any sleep, yet. I had to rush back home because the family wants to go to an aunt's place for lunch. Fahmy and his friends left the same time I did. Well, Shakhira had to send me home and Diana to her car in Bangsar. We left the other 2 guys, since they certainly didn't look ready to wake up.   Anyways, I got back home, freshened up and changed clothes at lightning speed and left for my aunt's place. Thank God, I didn't have to drive. Got back home and now just waiting to get ready for another Aidilfitri open-house tonight at Rakhma's. We're gonna go there around  8pm. I have to hitch a ride with Shakhira. Gotta wait for her to call me, since she  lost her cellphone last night . Poor girl. I know it was in the car when we were heading home. I answered a call and then passed it to her because there was an sms message. Now we can't find it anywhere. I suspect it fell out of the car when we dropped by her petrol station to get water and stuff. Suck.  Oh well, my eyes are getting tired from staring at the screen. I'm gonna stop here and go wash my hair. It stinks of stale smoke.  Euuuwww!  Adios. 
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't slept in 2 days. Do I feel sleepy right this moment?  Nope!  I don't know when or   if   I'll fall asleep tonight. I've been out the whole day today, driving around. Weird thing is, I felt my co-ordination go to bust when I was on my way back home. It's not like I was swerving the car all over the place like a suicidal maniac.. But I did feel weird and kinda felt scared for me *Haha* Nahh.. It's nothing serious, I'm on paranoia over-drive these days.   Well, this is gonna be super brief. I have guests staying in my room (where my darling 'puter is) for a couple of days. They're out visiting some relatives, so I came in for a quick post and email check.  urlLink Hotmail  is really getting up my ass. It's junk mail haven in there! *Grrr* Anyways, Imma go now.  Ta. 
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       *Survey*   I'll probably end up changing some of the answers to the 1st part soon.   I see: major changes I need: to lose weight I find: nothing I want: control I have: sufficient I wish: to understand I love: nothing I hate: self-inflicted emotional pain I miss: my dad I fear: fear itself I feel: scared I hear: music I smell: nothing I crave: confidence I search: sincerity & truth I wonder: if everything has a meaning I regret: lots  When was the last time I...  Smiled?: 10 minutes ago Laughed?: Couple hours ago Cried?: last week Bought something?: Friday Danced?: Half hour ago Were sarcastic?: Last night Talked to an ex?: no ex Watched your favorite movie?: I'm not even sure what my favorite movie is... Had a nightmare?: Don't remember  What was the...  Last book you read?: Controlling your fat tooth Last movie you saw?: Swordfish.. again Last song you heard?: Britney Spears - Slave 4 U Last thing you had to drink?: diet coke Last time you showered? This morning Last thing you ate?: a chicken nugget  Do you...  Smoke?: nope Do drugs?: I cannot safely put anything in writing for this Q. Have sex?: no Sleep with stuffed animals?: not on purpose Live in the moment?: I try Have a boyfriend/girlfriend?: nope Have a dream that keeps coming back?: Yeah, but it was a while ago Play an instrument?: nada Read the newspaper?: yeah Have any gay or lesbian friends?: not that I know of Believe in miracles?: Yeah, I guess  
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry for slacking on writting entries. I've been busy/lazy/exhausted for the past few days and yesterday was Hari Raya.. So, obviously I was mass0r busy with all the food and socialising *Hehe* I think I gained 2 pounds (atleast) since yesterday. Suck ass!  ANyways, the continuation will be written. Only not now. I'm feeling  mentally tired , not from all the excitement.. well, maybe a little from that.. but also from dealing with other emotional issues. Not mine, though. I'm happy, I refuse to let myself feel sh*tty and I don't see the point in feeling icky. Like my sister said,   "Most of the time it's all in the head."   Smart girl. It's like, if you keep wallowing in it, keep thinking about it and  KEEP  finding reasons to bring yourself down, obviously you'll be forever stuck in the whole 24/7 pool of tears. Which I, personally, think is bullshit. My philosophy:  No matter how bad you think your situation is, there are others far worst.  Trust me. *Blegh* Enough about that.  What's up with all these pop-up ads?? I'm  trying to write this extremely short post and it's taking me forever! *Grrr* I'll be typing away, and all these windows will pop up and I have to keep closing them. I got tired of that, so I decided to ignore them. Did that help? Noooo.. More pops up. Fullscreen even. *tears hair out*   Okay, I'm actually escaping all that food downstairs. I had a slice of bread with some curry and chicken just now. I feel like having my mom's laksa, but that's gonna have to wait til later. I grabbed an apple and ran up here. It's only the 2nd day of Hari Raya, food is still in abundance. Help!  
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow. Just had the best night ever! I finally got home around 9.30pm (today).. maybe 9.45pm.. or later.. *shrug* I dunno *Hehe*  Anyways, last night was mass0r fun. Actually, the  "night"  started around 4pm.  urlLink Shakhira  invited a bunch of us over for dinner at her apartment. I got there early, 'cuz I was from Uni and didn't feel like making 2 trips and probably get stuck in traffic (her place is on my route back home). She left her key for me because she had a few errands to run and had to pick  urlLink Rakhma and Nini  up. They got to the apartment around 4pm and we hung out for a bit. Shakhira had to get back to work, so the 3 of us watched movies and MTV and looking through the photo albums Rakhma brought, filled with pictures of her in Melbourne.. her house, her friends from Uni, stuff like that.   Finally decided not to eat at home because some of them couldn't make it.  urlLink Yasmin  couldn't make, and also a couple others. It was a  girls-only  kinda thang. We went to this seafood place nearby and  urlLink Diana  joined us there. She got stuck in a bitch of a traffic jam. The food was  deeeliiishhh!  We ate until we could barely swallow our own saliva *Haha* I think I still see the bulge on my tummy from last night ;)  After dinner, Diana suggested hanging out someplace and just have fun. We haven't really hung out for quite some time, so it was a pretty cool idea. We went back to get changed, and I had to send the car back home. Shakhira picked me up after she dropped Rakhma off. Rakhma was feeling tired, so she passed.   We ended up at The Beach Club. It's this hang out place with (yeah, that's right) a beach theme. The staff in hawaiian shirts, outdoor sitting area, various kinds of music, beach-bar-like decor and all that. The place was packed! We couldn't find a table in the main area and the one upstairs was closed. We finally got this table, but no stools, so we had stand. The crowd was mostly foreigners.. tourists. We had our own corner with ample space to shake that ass =P It was so much fun, just 4 girls having a good time. I even had a cramp in my right leg when I was dancing *Haha* Too stupid! My legs are hurting right now. Ofcourse, there was the customary sleaze factor. And, not forgetting,  some cute ones to gawk at  ...or drool, whatever suits your fancy =)  Nini saw this cute guy while she was on her way to the restrooms and later made me go with her to find him. Spotted. Sitting at the bar, looking real fine *Hehe* I told her to go say hello but she chickened out. After much  "you go. no,you go"  Shakhira went with me to where he was. I actually went up to him and told him the old "my friend thinks you're cute. If you'd come over and say hello, it'd be really cool". He asked me where we were sitting and if he could go meet her. So he followed me back to our little party and I pointed Nini to him. *LoL*  You should have seen the look on Nini's face!  Priceless. He ended up partying the whole night with us, even when we moved to another spot. Strange thing, we ended up inviting him and his friend back to continue the fun.   Things were mad last night, on the way back, at the apartment... Back at the apartment, he was given glass after glass 'til he finally had enough and went into the spare bedroom around 4am. His friend hung out at the living room with the rest, I have no idea what time she went in to sleep because I crashed in Shakhira's room for a bit. When I went outside to join Nini, the room was empty.   Okay, this has gotten majorly long. I'm gonna have to continue in another post. Still loads to tell, plus the stuff I left out. Next up : Details, the morning after, etc..    To be continued..   
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       *due to extreme boredom and an abundance of free time*   1. Full Name: Sharifah Aishah 2. Nicknames: sarip, aishah.. yeah 1st one sounds like a guy 3. Eyes: dark brown 4. Height: 5'0" 5. Hair: Black roots (hehe growing out my red streaks) 6. Siblings: 1 bro, 1 sis. I'm d eldest 7. Shoe size: 6 usually 8. Age: 22 9. Birthday: February 20th, 1979 10. Sign: Pisces 11. Where you live: PJ, Malaysia 12. Sex: girl 13. Righty or lefty: righty  ON GUYS FOR GIRLS TO FILL OUT (for girls only)  14. Boxers or briefs: boxers 15. Long or short hair: Hmm.. spiky's cool n longish is cool. I'm indecisive. 16. Tall or short: Taller than me definitely 17. Six pack or muscular arms: pack 18. Good or bad guy: There are good ones? =P 19. Hat or no hat? depends 20. Body piercings or none: Piercings 21. Tan or fair: whatever 23. Stubble or neatly shaved: shaved 24. Rugged or sporty: *shrugs* 25. Studly or cutie: cutie 26. Accent or not: I   ON GIRLS FOR GUYS TO FILL OUT (for guys only)  27.Regular underwear or thong:  29.Bra or sports bra:  30.Cute n'mysterious or wild n'sexy:  31.Dressy or casual:  32.Dark or blonde:  33.Long or short hair:  35.Long or short nails:  36.Hat or no hat:  37.Good or bad girl:  38.Fat or thin:  39.Hair up or down:  40.Jewelery or none:  41.Tall or short:  42.Curly or straight hair:  44.Tan or fair:  45.Freckles or none:  46.Pretty indoor chick or party chick:  48.Accent or canadian:  49.Shy or outgoing:   Misc. Questions  50.Chocolate or white milk: Chocolate, but white wif my cereal 51.Root beer or dr. pepper: root bear 52.Mud or jello wrestling: mud 53.Sunshine or rain: rain 54.Vanilla or chocolate: Vanilla 55.Skiing or boarding: I suck at sports 56.Day or night: night 57.Summer or winter: Summer 58.Cake or pie: pie 59.Love or lust: love 60.Gold or Silver: Silver 61.Diamond or pearls: diamonds 62.sunset or sunrise: sunrise 64.Do you sleep with stuffed animals: no  65.Have you ever broke/sprained/fractured a bone: sprained my ankles loads of times. nothing broken yet.  69.Favorite color: black, blue, light purple 70.Whos your favorite singer: No particular fave, I listen to loads 72.Who are your friends: I have a few superclose ones and a number of "casual" ones 73.Who's the loudest: Hell.. they're all loud. 74.Who's the quietest: Lemme think.. 75.Who do you tell your dreams to: nobody 76.Do you want your friends to do this survey: If they want 
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
        I am 50% British, just like  Hugh Grant  Thought you drive a British sports car you are most likely to have a blowout in LA.  Take the Brit Quiz at  urlLink www.darrenlondon.tripod.com/britquiz1.htm   Quiz written by Daz  
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       AAAARGH!!  Just found out the paper is due in 2 days, and not 3 as I thought. Wait.. it's Tuesday already. So the damned thing is due... TOMORROW. Shit shit shit. I'm still researching, can u believe that? I'm almost done, though. Thank goodness! After this I'm going to arrange the facts and type it straight away. I don't expect much sleep tonight. I was  sooo  hoping on going to the lake and do a bit of running in the morning =(    Today:  Sent my sister to uni, researched paper, slept for a bit and had dinner at the Hyatt. Now stuck with shitload of werk.   Well, gotta run. Adios. 
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       Paper due in:  3 days.  Length:  15 pages.  Written:  0 pages.  Me:  screwed.  In other news.. I'm going shopping again. Yay! *haha* A little rainfall and I have enough to go on a binge again. Kinda. Maybe I'll get another pair of jeans... Definitely more tops, maybe another pair of shoes and, ofcourse, a belt. Can't wait. The sooner I get this stoopid paper done, the sooner I can go.   Okay, back to work. I hate research  *Grrr*  
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink        You were PJ Harvey in a past life! You're can be somewhat reserved, but when there's an issue you feel strongly about you're not afraid to share your opinion. You're the walking definition of sophistication and people admire you for your strength and composure. You are highly artistic and enjoy creating masterpieces any way you can!  Click on the piccie if you wanna take the same quiz. Go ahead... It iz fun. =) 
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I went shopping with some friends yesterday. Got myself some new clothes, lippies and shoes. Not as much as I'd hope.. But I guess it's better than nothing. A majority of the stores were on mass0r sale, we obviously went crazy.  I finally got a new pair of jeans, my old ones are falling off my ass and lookin' really pathetic. I got a pair of those  cool superlows  from  urlLink Levi's . No, my tummy ain't exactly a carbon copy of J-Lo's, I'm still not sure why I got it *Haha* But it looks good and I found out I'm down  3  sizes!  Yay!   I still need a new belt, a few more tops and a couple of other stuff. Thing is, I've already hit my spending limit. Ulp. I'm gonna have to think of something. I have a couple of paychecks coming, but not much at all. Besides, I have to pay my cellphone bill. Aargh!  Whatever.. I have a super cool pair of jeans!  
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Have u ever felt so angry you could just burn everything down? That's exactly how I'm feeling right now. Plus a few more destruction. This is the longest I've felt this angry. I even fell asleep for an hour and woke still steaming. I can't even eat.. All I've had so far is an apple. Oh and a sip of water. Right now I'm OD-ing on diet coke.   I don't even know why I'm blogging. Nobody needs, or wants, to know about my anger. I'm the girl who's always cheery right? Blehhh.. Screw you!!! 
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm loving this. What  "this"  is, I'm not sure *Heheh* I'm feelin fine and I don't know why... It can't get anymore retarded than this. I just rejected 2 calls because the number didn't look familiar. Did that make me feel bad?  Noooooo!  Why? Cuz I'm in a weird happy mood. Maybe it's all that food I had for dinner.. Maybe it's time to call the asylum.. I don't know and I don't care. Crap. I may start dancing around the room or something =)  Nothing major today. Got up around 2pm, rambled on the phone at 3pm, showered, drove around doing some stuff and then dinner with a couple of my cousins. I feel stuffed. I can't believe I ate an apple after dinner and some of my mom's tiny cookies. Field day today *hehe* Tomorrow I'm getting back into the low-cal swing. Going shopping with my friends on Friday and probably end up having dinner with them. I hope that wouldn't turn into another off day for my diet.  Whatever.. this is getting boring. I need something new. That way I'll have something to write about without falling asleep myself. Oh yeah, one last note.  Fahmy, keep your chin up.  Quit thinking about it too much and concentrate on what's coming.   Later. 
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I was clicking through the net this morning and came across something very cool. I was checking my referrer log from  urlLink the other blog , and saw this IP from France. Cool eh? But that's not it. Whoever it was found my journal through an images search of  "aishah" . I checked that out and found this :    urlLink      Pretty cool I must say. That cartoon chick's name is Aishah..  das me!  *Heheh* Anyways, there's a whole site about her. Read it  urlLink here . I have yet to read the whole thing, but gonna after I finish this. By the way, to see the full-sized image, just click on it. I scaled it down cuz it was too big.  I just got back from Coffee Bean with a few friends. Rakhma just got back from Melbourne and we hung out for a bit. It's been a while and it was sooo good to see her again.   This site is nowhere near 100% ready. Things are starting to get kinda busy around the house and I still have to get my shopping done. I'll fix this up when I can. Right now, I wanna get some sleep. 
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      And a brand new site and blog is born!!  Yay!   Same free host, I know.. it's even in under the same account *Haha* Yeah, I'm too lazy to find a new one. Actually I did register under  urlLink Envy.nu , but they don't support blogger. Bah. I realized that after I finished putting everything together, including making the images. So I spent a little bit more time making new ones. *Grrr*  I don't know if I'll be posting on both blogs, I still like the old one. Which, by the way, you can read  urlLink here.  I got bored today, and decided to switch into geek-mode and design something. This looks very  beginner-like , I think. Still need to add links and a whole bunch of other stuff.   Okie then, just trying this out. Later. 
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       First post... testing? 
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        HOT DAMN!!   I just had the craziest 6 days!   It started  Friday  night, with the usual partying at  urlLink BarFlam  (ran into Dolly there), and the usual after party hang-out at Shakhira's. It was funny, practically everyone didn't sleep the whole night. Some slept for a few hours after sunrise. Me, Shakhira, Rakhma, Farah and Gerald stayed up talking about stupid things and laughing. Including the stupid stuff we did as kids, we discovered each one of us was already psychotic as kiddies *Haha* Rakhma went to catch a few ZZs after Shakir and Boboi crashed on Shakhira's bed. *LoL* Shakhira and Rakhma even painted the guys' nails. Gerald, as usual, was cracking stupid jokes and getting into fights with Rakhma. Oh, and a friend of Rakhma's, Ajim, joined us. I drove his car 'cuz he was too sloshed. Oh Oh.. one more thing.. Rakhma and Gerald  danced on the bar!  It was crazy.   Saturday  was another party night, which was unplanned, I think. I can't quite remember how we ended up partying in  urlLink BarFlam  again. But this time Fahmy managed to join us, he brought Shakir and Boboi with him. Gerald and Rakhma couldn't make it, something about being tired and Gerald has to work the next day. Ofcourse they came over for the customary after party chill-out session *Hehe* Funny shit happened, ofcourse. Oh, and this is night number 2 of no sleep for me.  Sunday night was more chilled... I can't quite remember what we did exactly, though *Haha* I'm such a spaz! Crap.. I'm losing track of which nights I stayed up. I think I was awake for 3 nights in a row and finally crashed at 4am on the 4th night. Whatever.  Anyways, I went home around 3pm Monday, went out to dinner at 8pm and then out again at 11pm. Shakhira picked me up, we were both bored shitless, so we drove around looking for things to do. We ended up in Shah Alam, picked up Fahmy and went to get food. Shakhira ate, we had drinks. Then me and her headed back. Oh yeah.. after dinner, we (Me, Rakhma and Shak. Gerald went home) went to hangout at Hartamas.. Guess who we ran into?  Kevin.  Shakhira's ex.. she saw him and wanted to split, but he was faster and caught up with us. Me and Rakhma chatted with him for a few minutes, while Shakhira said hello to another friend of hers. Guess it was awkward for Kevin and Shakhira... Shak just nodded hello and stood at a distance. I guess that's one of the reasons I went out again, to make sure she's alright. She told me she did feel like crying but decided to imagine this other guy's face instead. *Hehe* Crazy girl. Then again, that guy   IS   cute =P  I was still at Shakhira's place Tuesday night.. Can't quite remember why I decided to ditch the idea of going home. I had a pretty good night sleep, I think. Oh yeah, dinner at Modestos, saw Anas leaving work, called him over to join us, waited for Ajim, picked Gerald up and off to Shah Alam. After sending everyone home and Ajim to his car, it was already 2am so I stayed over again.   Wednesday, I went home around noon to get clothes for the night's orchestra and also money. I was home long enough to grab something to eat, shower and toss fresh clothes into my bag. I went over to Dolly's to borrow a top, off to the bank for some moolah and back to Shakhira's. The show was pretty good.. actually the orchestra was really good. Shakhira's sister plays the violin and it was her last performance with the orchestra. Me, Shakhira and Gerald went to watch, unfortunately we got too hungry to wait until the end. We left during intermission and had dinner at Planet Hollywood. After that it was Bangsar to hang out.  Ofcourse, we ended up at  urlLink BarFlam . Surprisingly, it was already packed at 11pm, we couldn't even get a table. We were about to leave for another place, when they told us to chill at the table outside while they reserve the next available one. So, we stayed.. and got our favourite table a few minutes later. It was superbly nice of them, eh? Fahmy and Shakhir came to join us. We stayed until 1am, 'cuz we thought of hitting Orange. Called Anas, got him out of bed and he joined us *Hehe* Gerald went home because he's got werk in the morning. Shakhira invited this guy we just got to know, Marc. Orange was empty, so we ditched that idea and hit Spiral instead.  The usual after party hangout, Fahmy and Shakir left at 6am, Anas and Marc stayed.  OMIGOD!  Last night was ridiculously funny! Shakir was talking non-stop to Marc and it was pure crap. Funny shit!! *LoL* All of us stayed up the whole night just hanging out and stuff. I went with Anas to get his work clothes from his house, and surprisingly we had loads to chat about *hehe* Finally left Shakhira's at 12.50pm, sent Marc to his car, Anas to  urlLink BarFlam  (he works there), dropped Shakhira's cellphone to be repaired and I headed home.   Freaky long entry. Cool. Not too detailed, but I think I covered almost everything. I may have mixed up certain events and the days.. Some things happened on different days? I'm confused *Haha* But, I don't think I wanna write anymore right now. I'm still laughing over last night and this morning, not to mention the past days *shakes head* 
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday night's plans went to bust. My mom won't let me out, so I was stuck at home bored shitless and feeling steamed. I couldn't sleep because I  sooo  wanted to be with my friends. I was exchanging sms messages with Shakhira, finding out what's happening over there. They decided not to hit Carbon and partied at BarFlam instead. I told her to let me know once they got home, I wanna meet them there super early.  Shakhira messaged me around 4.30am saying they're almost home, just making a pit stop for some stuff. She told me who were going back to her place, and all that. I got up and called her, she was with the guys and asked when I'm gonna get there. Obviously, leaving the house at 4am will be mighty suspicious, so I told her I'll get up again around 6am and be right over. She called at 6.30am (thank God), asking me to come over pronto. They guys wanted to leave, and she's making them stay until I get there *Hehe* Yeah, eye candy was there too.   Fine. I showered, changed, a quick brekkie and  was out the door by 7am . Hung out at her place until 5.30pm, dropped Anas off at the station (I had to get fuel, anyway) so he could catch a cab home, and I was back by 6pm.   It's only 10pm and already I'm bored shitless. Shakhira and Rakhma are having dinner at the Hard Rock Cafe. Some relatives were over for dinner, so I couldn't leave. I've been out the whole day, mom would blow up if I were to go out again. Looks like I'm stuck here. There's no way I'm gonna sleep any time soon and I just finished reading a whole bunch of stuff, so I don't feel like reading anymore. Movies.. the room's being used, so it's the 'puter if I wanna watch anything. Bleh.  Oh well.. I'll just find something to keep myself occupied until morning comes. Don't know what I'm gonna do tomorrow, though. Right now, I'm gonna quit whining and do something.   G'nite. 
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      It's past 7am, Friday morning. I have yet to sleep.  COOL!  *Hehe* I spent the day at Shakhira's place, got home around midnight and have been killing time since. She picked me up around 1.30pm, went back to her place and woke 2 guys up so we could go to lunch. Huge ass lunch.. Good thing I don't eat rice or I'd  really  be in trouble. Called Diana and she came over.   One of the guys, Shakir (Fahmy's friend), left right after lunch and the other guy, Anas, couldn't wait to get back to sleep. Told him to crash in the spare bedroom, 'cuz I thought of watching TV in the living room. Me and Diana went to see a friend to pick up some stuff, the moment she got there. Shakhira had some things to do at her station, so she came upstairs once in a while. Around 5.45pm we sent Anas to Bangsar, he's supposed to start work at 6pm. He works at our current favourite,  urlLink BarFlam . Funny bit, he called Shakhira's phone asking to speak to me. He told me he tried calling my number and go a   not-in-service   message. Weird. Freaked me out a bit, thought my line got cut off. He then said he called my brother's number (I sent him msgs from there once), thinking it was my other number. Guess who picked up? My mom *Hehe* Okay, so maybe it's not  THAT  funny. But it was kinda strange he still has my brother's number and suddenly calling. He said I probably gave him wrong digits. Heck, it was 3am and I was asleep.. Can u blame me?  Another half hour or so before I have to shower. Ahhhhh.. a nice hot shower. Can't wait. Class is at 10am, and I'm functioning on zero sleep. Just hope my coordination is good enough to enable me to drive. My stomach's growling, I think it wants food *Haha* Unfortunately, at the moment, even the thought of food is makes me wanna puke. Maybe later I'll get something to eat. Something fat-free (like fruits) or low-fat, I hope! *crosses fingers*  Wow. Just noticed it's getting bright outside. Throughout the night, I: 1. Surfed the net + cleared emails 2. Downloaded Move it slow by Kevon Edmonds 3. Did laundry 4. Watched a movie 5. Redid my bed covers 6. Some other minor stuff I don't remember  Since I ran out of things to do, I'm back online and blogging all that stuff. Planning on hitting Carbon on Saturday night, should be a slightly bigger crowd than usual. Should be fun. Just hope I don't get sick again =P I think this should be enough for now. Tata, kiddies. 
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Macho has gone back to Santa Monica, Yazmin left for Perth early Tuesday morning... So now it's Rakhma that's still here. She'll be heading back to Melbourne early next month but she was planning on going back earlier, like end of this month or something. Bummer. Oh, but Farah's gonna still be here until end of February, so that's cool.   Sunday night, a bunch of us went out for dinner at TGIF. It's kind of a byebye thang for Mach, me and Shakhira even gave her a present. Shakhira bought her a couple of thongs (really shiny, kinky ones *Hehe*) and I added a couple of candles and did the wrapping. We took a few photographs at her place and then it was time to say goodbye :-(  After leaving Mach's place, the rest of us went to  urlLink BarFlam  to hang out. Muff and Yazmin came to join us later, we left kinda early and I was home slightly past midnight. I think. I can't remember *Hehe* Me and Shakhira went back to BarFlam last night. I can't remember what we did before that, but we had about an hour to kill, so we decided to have a drink or two. Left the place by 1am, and headed home. I crashed the minute I climbed into bed.  That brings us to tonight.. or last night, whatever. Tuesday night, Ladies' Night at Flams. SHakhira picked me up around 6pm and we went driving around 'cuz it was too early for dinner. We ended up at Midvalley Megamall, I bought a new toe ring and Shakhira attacked the MNG clearance sale. By 8pm, we were about to die from hunger. Well, Shakhira anyway.. I was just craving Chilis. So, it was American Chili's for dinner. I can't believe I had fries. Just yesterday I was pissed because my weight is yoyo-ing between 47.5 and 49kg. Yeah, I weigh a tonne. Shut up.  At this rate I'll never hit 45kg. I don't know what's the matter with me, I can't resist peanuts and all these salty fried stuff. Not to mention all that extra calories from the visits to BarFlam. Bad.   REALLY BAD!   I'm actually thinking of giving up and just maintaining the weight I am at now. Feel free to motivate me.  Anyways, after dinner we went to pick up Rakhma and drove around some more. Obviously, a short visit to Flams was inevitable. Gerald came by to join us. A few drinks and then it was time to go. By the way, the eye-candy waiter guy was there... So, that was cool. That's all he is, anyway, just something to look at. Sad, huh? After Flams, we went to Shah Alam and paid Fahmy a visit. I drove everyone around Shah Alam, having no idea where we were going. Later, we parked at the McDonald's 'cuz we need to pee *Hehe* My phone rang, mom wants me home. Suck ass. So here I am, bored shitless.   We planned on going clubbing this Saturday night. Probably check out Carbon, since they play house music and I wanna dance. Eye-candy guy's gonna be there, I think. Maybe I'll give Wafi a buzz and see if he wants to join us, since Fahmy's gonna come too. The more the merrier, right?  RIght now, I'm gonna go. I'm feeling a little dissapointed and kinda bummed, and it's not cuz I'm home while everyone else is out. Hmmm.. maybe this should motivate me to shed all these extra kilos. As if it's gonna change anything, anyway.  
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       -= Friday Night =-   As much as I didn't plan to.. I found myself in  urlLink BarFlam  with my friends. Earlier in the day, I thought of just dropping by for a few and get my ass home by midnight. That's what I told Rakhma and Shakhira, they wanted me to party with them but I've been going out all the time, and I didn't want my mom to start complaining. Shakhira picked me up around 3pm yesterday, so we could go get a belated b'day pressie for a friend and Shakhira wanted to eat. At first, they changed the venue to Scandals, an R&B club that re-opened at a new location. Later that evening, plans were changed and it's back to the old watering hole *Hehe*  I was hanging out at Shakhira's place, talking about the night's plans and somehow I felt like partying. I didn't think my mom would be cool about it, so I was just asking her what time is everyone meeting up and saying I'd drop by to say hello. The more I think and talk about it, the more I feel like joining them for the whole night. I decided to just take my chances and check with my mom. She wasn't extremely happy about it, but it was still an okay. I went back home to get my things and back to her house. We got ready, picked up Rakhma and was on our way.  We got to Bangsar around 11pm, and the area was kinda quiet for a Friday night. Thought it was kinda odd, but probably because it was still pretty early. When we got to BarFlam, it was another story.  There was actually kind of a queue outside!  I saw them not allowing people in, so that was worrying. But Shakhira called this guy we know and told him to reserve a table for us. He called earlier saying he couldn't get our usual table and it's gonna be the one next to it or something. When we got inside, the place was so packed there was barely enough space to move around. I found the guy, and asked him where our table was. He said he tried to hold on to it for as long as he could. The hostess from the door told Shakhira that this group of people  "stole"  her table. She pointed to the table and said when they wanted to sit there, they were told it was reserved for Shakhira. One of the guys said it's okay, because they're her friends. How fucked up is that?  The manager came and talked to this people at the table next to it, and told us we could just join them for the moment cuz they're leaving soon. Yeah right. Shakhira didn't want to, besides Diana told us that they're gonna bring in a table from outside and put it at our usual corner. As they were preparing to bring the table in, the guy (the one who reserved the table) came over and said there's a table free in the back and asked if we wanted it. Hell yeah!  We ended up sitting there and thanked him. It was just 3 girls at first, then Fahmy and Shakir came. Gerald turned up much much later.  The table was small and we only had 3 stools, but it was alright. We moved to another table after the people there left, it was on a raised platform so that was cool. There was a  "tribute to Movement"  (the club burned down earlier this week) thang and one of the DJs went on for a bit. Nothing spectacular, but some tracks were cool. Ofcourse there was the  late night special , this time the female bartenders got on the bar and poured tequilla into wide opened mouths. They were dressed cowgirl-style; belly baring top, hotpants/miniskirt and red cowboy hat. They danced on the bartop for a while, like always.   I danced a bit, felt bloated from all that coke and started chewing on ice cubes. One part of the night I started feeling farked. I don't know why this keep happening, but last night I know I felt mas0r disappointed over something (no details, yet). Then I started feeling a little bit annoyed, so I just stood there observing the crowd and following cute ones with my eyes *hehe* I started dancing again to get rid of the shitty feeling and joined in on the laughter. I had fun.. Kinda different, but it was alright. We stayed until closing, finally got everyone in the car and headed home. I wasn't feeling very socialable, so I didn't participate in the convo that much. I dozed off for a bit and got up when Fahmy wanted to leave. I just felt like being by myself, so I told them I was gonna lie down on the couch for a bit. I ended up falling asleep and only joining them in the room in the morning.   Bla bla bla.. Shakhira had to go the station for a bit, Rakhma and Gerald left, Shak got back, we went for lunch, back to her place, hung around watching a movie and went home around 5.50pm. I took her car (she was too lazy to drive) and went over to return it at 8pm. So... here I am, putting everything into words. Long entry once again. Now I'm sick of typing.   I'm out. 
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Doh! I forgot to publish the last entry. Stoopid me.   2 nights in a row of getting totally shitfaced. I'm almost embarrassed to even look in the mirror. Thinking of certain events is making me cringe a little.  Then again, it was mas0r fun!  Minus the pounding in my head and the nausea, ofcourse ;-) Tuesday night was the required visit to BarFlam, it was their  Ladies' Night  and the girlies get free drinks. Not the usual free flow like other clubs, it's only 1 drink. Their theme (or whatever):  "Well dressed, well treated ladies get free drinks" . At the door, the girls were given this coupon to fill out and to be exchanged for champange at the bar. It comes in those cute baby champange bottles. In keeping with the whole  Ladies' Night  thang, the bartenders were shirtless for the night. They wore white shirt cuffs and tux-like collars with bowties. I don't know if I explained that right...  At midnight, they had this   Midnight Special  , where they got the girls to stand around the bar. The bartenders then climb on the bar with a tequilla bottle each, and move around pouring shots down your throat. Cool, eh? At one point, one of the guys was dancing on the bar and pulled up this girl. Talk about some hot moves *LoL* Me and Shakhira got there early, right after dinner infact, around 9.30pm. Nini and a couple of her friends joined us about an hour later. Ran into Dolly (she joined us) and Carlos dropped by for a few minutes. We left kinda early, I think it was just after 1am.   We stopped for food, and then headed to Shakhira's place. I slept in the car because I was feeling woozy. Shakhira woke me up when we got there and I crashed on the couch as soon as I walked in. That was around 2am. My head was spinning and I was feeling royally fucked. I got up around 4am, went to the loo, washed my face, changed and couldn't fall asleep again. The more I tried to sleep, the worse my head felt. I gave that up and watched TV instead. I had no idea what time Shakhira was gonna get up, so I kept myself busy with magazines and playing games on her phone. Good thing a couple of friends called, so I didn't go insane with boredom *Hehe*  And that brings to yesterday,  Wednesday . Diana came by in the afternoon, so did Ninie. Ninie left for Brisbane last night, so she dropped by to say byebye. Later, we had dinner with Rakhma, Yazmin, Muff and Gerald. After dinner, Gerald went home while the rest of us headed to Bangsar. We hung out at Coffee Bean for a bit, and somehow it was decided we'd do another night of partying. This time in Orange, an R&B club. Rakhma, me and Shakhira, anyway. Muff's got work the next day and Yazmin couldn't make it. Rakhma had to send her car home, me and Shakhira picked her up, headed to her apartment, changed in record time and made it to the club just before 1am. We were supposed to meet up with this guy who works in BarFlam. We've somehow became sorta friends, and he got off work early last night, so he joined us. Doesn't hurt that he's kind of an eye candy *Haha* Also met up with Raflis and his friends there. Shakhira was especially happy to be hanging out with one  particular friend  *wink wink*  After the place closed, they were thinking of heading to another club, Carbon. I was feeling good (right then, anyway), so I didn't mind. We headed to Carbon and found it closed. Dang. Then again, at that time I was already feeling sick. I must've looked one hell of a mess, cuz they were laughing and asking if I was alright. We went home after that, I slept the whole way. I don't what happened, but we were practically home when it hit. I reached for the plastic bag Shakhira handed me earlier and barfed. Boy, was it ever disgusting. And it friggin' hurt too. I changed out of my jeans and top once we got upstairs, and passed out on the bed. Not for long, anyway. I got up an hour later because my head was thumping like mad and I had to pee.   I went to the living room and found Shakhira watching TV. I joined her and we chatted for a bit. As much as my icky feeling allowed, anyway. We hung out until Rakhma woke up, then Shakhira showered and left for her station. She said she'll be back in a bit to send us home. I got home around noon, or just before... I'm not sure. Still feeling a little  euww , standing up n moving too fast still gives me a headrush. I've also developed this rash-type on my arm. It doesn't itch, though. Weird.  *Gasps for breath* Whew! I skipped a few details and descriptions, because I don't want it to get any longer. If, for some reason, I feel like getting detailed, I'll blog again. Right now, I'm gonna end this.   Out. 
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       +Sorry, publishing is temporarily unavailable+   Sunday.. Fahmy's open house. I think I got there close to 4pm, found a table and attacked the buffet. Well, not really attacked.. but I did indulge in some *ugh* oily stuff. The chicken was yummy, I loved that one. After a plate of bits of this and that, I stuck to fruits and water. Shakhira called and said she was coming over, so I thought I'd eat again with her. She turned up, but I decided to pass on a second helping. After some recalculating, I realized I had like 6 sticks of  sate . Bloody hell.. and I'm supposed to be on a diet. Oh well, atleast I got rid of the center fat part. I'm not even gonna try to explain that. Oh, and Wafi turned up later that evening. I think it was after 6pm, he was from another house. After all of Fahmy's friends left, it was just me, Shakhira, Fahmy and Wafi at the table. Yada yada yada.. We left around 7.40pm or something. I was supposed to go to this other house for dinner with the family.  I skipped the dinner and stayed home instead.  For a while, anyway  *Hehe* I watched TV for a bit, while eating that yummy chicken (I'm such a glutton). Good thing I still have a little bit of sense and it was a tiny piece. *Wheww!* After a half hour of TV, I called Shakhira to see what she's up to. She was gonna to meet up with some of the girls for dinner, I didn't go 'cuz of that dinner I was supposed to go to. They're still there, but Shakhira said she's leaving and that she's coming over to pick me up. I had to rush and get changed.  We had to drop by her apartment for her to get changed and get some stuff. We asked Wafi to join us in Bangsar, if he's free. As usual, we went to  urlLink BarFlam  for drinks. Shakhira was still hungry, so she ordered the sauteed prawns. I held back, but I did snack on the peanuts Anas (a waiter there. Cute one *heh*) brought over. It was just the 2 of us, hanging around talking about this and that. Didn't think Wafi was gonna turn up because everytime  he says "I'll see how it goes", it means no *hehe*  He called around 11.30pm, we have just told the waiter to keep the bottle and getting ready to leave. Shakhira went to the loo, and Anas was asking why we're leaving so early. I was talking to him when my phone rang. Wafi was asking where in Bangsar were we, I told him and asked if he's coming. He said he'll call me back, so okay.. I went back to our table and told Shakhira. We were finishing our drinks when Wafi turned up. Heh. He was already in Bangsar when he called. The bottle was brought back out, we hung out for a little bit more. Around midnight Wafi said he had to go, so we sent the bottle away and left. I got home around  12.30am and crashed right away.  Yesterday was nothing but food and sleep. I got up around 10.30am, had breakfast. A sinfull, fatty breakfast. Watched a movie and then fell asleep around lunch time. Finally dragged my ass outta bed around 5.45pm, showered and went to hunt for food. Found my mom in the kitchen about to eat, so I joined her. More oily stuff into my mouth. I don't recall what I did after that, but I went out with my friends around 8.45pm. Had dinner with Shakhira and then met up with the rest around 9.30pm. Got teased mercilessly, couple of drinks, reached home around 11.30pm, hung out, babbled on the phone and crashed.  Boy, oh boy.. What exciting life I lead *GAG!*  
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Another night of no sleep.  As of 10.45pm, Saturday, I have been up for 38hours.  I had a lecture in Uni Friday morning, picked up my sister and headed home. I don't quite remember what I did the whole day, but I know I had bread with chilli con carne for lunch. One slice of wholemeal bread.. I was craving meat, any kind of meat.. beef or lamb or chicken. I thought of going to the movies with my brother and sister (plus our cousins), but I was feeling kinda tired and didn't feel like dealing with a whole lot of people.   I stayed home watching movies on VCDs instead. I finished  A Knight's Tale , got a little teary during the ending *Hehe* I think I was eating pears yesterday... I can't quite remember. I made plans with Shakhira and Diana for an early dinner, around 7pm. Me and Diana got to  urlLink American Chilli's  on time, but Shakhira ran a little bit late because she fell asleep. We called her cell a few times before she finally picked up. She was apologizing like mad and said she's on her way out the door *Hehe* I had the grilled chicken ceaser in mind originally, but ended up having the  Guiltless Grilled Chicken Pita . It's served with beans, but I was craving salt so I asked for fries instead. No point going  guiltless  on the pita and then stuffing my face with fries, eh? I didn't care, I haven't had fries in the longest time. I didn't finish the pita bread (ate half), but I did finish the chicken and vegetable filling.   After dinner, Shakhira had to go pick Rakhma up 'cuz they were going clubbing. Before that, Shakhira wanted to go have a few drinks at *where else?* BarFlam (yeah the fucking cute one was there and he came to say hello). I tagged along but Shakhira was to send me back to my car later. I wasn't planning on going clubbing with them. *Sigh* I have no idea what happened, one phone call later.. and I'm sending my car back home, packing some party clothes and jumping into Shakhira's car. We ended up in this R&B club called Orange.    *Groan*  I don't know what came over me, but I was acting like such an arse. I felt fuckup all of a sudden and didn't get up from my seat most of the night. My eyes were hurting due to all the smoke, so that didn't help. I barely spoke and I know look ultimately moody. Somehow, I ended up yelling at Fahmy (I am  soooo  very sorry), and surprising my friends. They wanted to hit this club called Carbon, but I wanted to just head back. Then again, I didn't want to cut anyone's night short so I told them whatever's fine. Bla bla bla.. me and Fahmy's friend split from the rest to go back to Shakhira's place. He didn't feel like partying anymore either so we went back. The rest somehow decided to ditch Carbon and go eat instead. We waited for them at the apartment and watched TV and talked and all that.   We stayed up til dawn hanging out, they guys then fell asleep... So it was me, Rakhma and Shakhira. Later Rakhma went to bed, so the two of us just hung out talking shit. I couldn't stop apologizing to Fahmy for yelling at him, and to Shakhira 'cuz I feel really bad for cutting the night short. I finally got home around 4pm, hung out at home bored shitless and having no idea how I'm feeling right now.   All I know I'm majorly bored, have yet to eat a proper meal (a few fries in the afternoon and a bite from mom's plate just now), annoyed at something but don't know what... Crap. I don't know. My eyes are feeling funny, a little dry even. I need to wash my hair but too lazy to hop in the shower right now. Tomorrow.  Tomorrow. Fahmy's house at 3pm for his Aidilfitri open house. Food. Lotsa food = Trouble. Some of my friends are gonna be there, too, so that should be interesting. I'm getting incoherent. I tried to get the fucking scanner to work but it's being gay. I'll try again later. Too bored to even write, this has gotten majorly long anyway.   G'nite. 
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       +How la Darryl? + FUCKING cute! +   *Hehe* Me and a couple of friends can't stop saying that. One would ask the question, and the other will answer with "Fuuucking cute!" Just a little entertainment between us.. kind of an inside joke, I suppose.   Well, it was another sleepless night for me last night. I got up around 1.30pm yesterday feeling majorly shitty. My head hurt, I was hungry and my energy level was zilch. It's been 2 days and I've yet to recover 100%... This is nuts, considering the  laid back NYE  we had. I couldn't even finish the soup and bread I decided to have for lunch. Felt like barfing. All my body wanted was fatty stuff..  FRIED  fatty stuff! I ended up eating a banana fritter (2 bites, then I threw it away), a cookie (a nibble here n there, then it got binned) and maybe 2 glasses of pepsi. The sugar helped perk me up a little, thank God. It's a good thing I wasn't rejecting fruits, because that's what kept me going.  I finally gathered enough energy to shower and run a few errands around 4.30pm. After that I crashed infront of the TV and watched  A Knight's Tale . Funny stuff, but I'm halfway through the second disc. Shakhira called and we went to Bangsar for dinner. I wasn't planning on eating anything 'cuz I was still feeling a little icky. I had another pear while waiting for her to pick me up. Once in Bangsar (decided on this place called FeiFei), I found myself having the  Cantonese Style Fried Noodles . The noodle stayed, only the prawns, chicken slices, veggies and gravy got digested. Nini joined us as we were finishing dinner, and then we headed to Coffee Bean to meet up with Rakhma.   Now here's where the trouble started. Well, not a major problem, really.. My tummy started to hurt   BIG   time. I could barely sit up straight, let alone stand up. The food wasn't agreeing, and I ended up in the bathroom. I'll ommit the gross details, but I'll tell you this: it wasn't pretty. I felt a little bit better, but still dodgy. Bla bla bla.. Me, Shakhira and Nini ended up in  urlLink BarFlams . The place wasn't packed, but most tables were occupied. Wednesday night, and it's only the 2nd.. People are probably still recovering from NYE. Here is where it gets interesting *rub hands together*  We were sitting there at our favourite table and checking out the DJ. He wasn't spinning yet, so he was talking to people and walking all over. The 3 of us were just looking and commenting *ahem* on his yummy-ness *Hehe* Yada yada yada... this guy we know said something to him (we saw him pointing in our direction), and the DJ guy came over to say hello. He hung out with us for a bit, then he had to start spinning.  He is just TOO cute!  He's pretty friendly.. and kinda funny. Oh yeah, his name's Darryl =P  Whoa.. I'm actually getting kinda tired. My eyes anyway. Still loads to tell.. but I'm not making any promises of a continuation like the last time. I'll just end up too lazy to write anymore on the subject or whatever. Oh, did I mention I broke my phone's antenna? Yeah, it was on new year's. Don't exactly know how it happened... But I did accidently hit the damn thing with my hand at one point. It's still intact but  really shaky and feels like it could just snap off anytime . Bummer.  I do tend to go on and on, don't I? I guess I'm gonna stop rambling now... Contemplating on what to do next. Should I sleep? Should I just keep myself busy? I lost a photo album containing recent shots, I could go look for it.. But just not in the mood. Oh well, whatever.. I'll just see where my messed up mind takes me.  Ciao. 
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         Happy New Year!!    Last night's new year celebration was kinda different. Yeah, I had fun (as usual)... This time around it felt really laid back, though. But it did cost me more moolah *Hehe* Me and a few friends got this 2 bedroom suite at a superly low price. My friend's uncle is somebody there or something, so she got a special rate. Countdown was at Bintang Walk, after the fireworks we went to have a drink while deciding where to go... We decided to just walk towards Beach Club, but the place was packed like mad. In the end we ended up in  urlLink Flux . We didn't stay there long, though... Probably a couple of hours at the most, but I did get to dance. So, I was happy.   After that we headed back to the hotel and all of us just hung out and talked. A few other people came by later, so it was pretty alright. I had fun, even though didn't get to do much. As the matter of fact,  I haven't had any sleep yet  =) I nodded off around 8am for maybe 15minutes and then around 1.30pm for another 10minutes probably. Thing is, I'm not feeling sleepy at all right now. Not even tired. Cool, eh?  Anyways, just wanted to wish everyone a  HAPPY NEW YEAR . I'm still calculating last night's expensense, and it's giving me one hell of a scare. Adios. 
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      That little fight had been resolved yesterday. We met up for a late lunch, said sorry and spent the day hangin out. It's such a relief to get that behind me, I said I was sorry for not being funny *Heh* We had lunch, looked at clothes, had dinner and then drinks at BarFlam. Eye-candy was there, so it's super good *Hehe* I'm such a teenager. Who cares, he's cute and I like him. Deal with it! =)   I've decided to back to my original diet of salads and fruits. I've gained a whole lotta ever since my birthday and I'm not exactly thrilled. For dinner I had a whole meal roll and carrot sticks. Lunch was kinda late, I had this salad, Raita, at Dave's..  sucked major ass!  Breakfast was a slice of wholemeal toast (nothing on it) and then an orange for my mid-morning snack. I think I had an apple before lunch, 'cuz Fahmy only picked me up at 5pm for lunch. I guess it could've been my early dinner, but the Raita was fuctup and it left me unsatisfied. Hmmph.  Oh well... I'm gonna go now. My tummy's growling a little, but I'm gonna wait until breakfast. My favourite meal of the day. Before that, here's a test I did a few minutes ago.  G'nite.   urlLink     What Psych-Ward do you belong to?    
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm  urlLink Jean Grey  Goodness Gracious, you're everyone's favourite do-gooder Jean Grey, also known as Phoenix. You look after your teammates, get along with everyone, have a wonderful man who loves you and have pretty much achieved perfection. But look out when you're PMSing and you become Dark Phoenix: a raging homicidal bitch with a knack for causing trouble.  urlLink What X-Men Character are You?  
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Had a fight/misunderstanding last night. It blows major ass. I dont get why the anger is so massive or why it's being prolonged. I'm not one who likes to stay angry and usually don't. I made the first move, but have yet to get a respond from the other side... I don't know if I should pick up the phone and call. Okay, fine, maybe it's my fault.. but I explained it was meant as a joke and all that. I deserve some form of forgiveness right? The impact is kinda huge.. I was in tears last night and don't even feel like talking today. This thing is too tiny to lose a friend over. This is too stupid. I really, honestly, don't know what to do. Help? 
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
             I am  A Floater  .  Floaters, the free birds of the shit family. Floaters drift through life without a care in the world, taking everything with a grain of salt, and smiling the whole way though. But friend of floaters are far and few in between. Because of there lofty views and social behavior, floaters tend to seem like they just don't give a damn about anything, the reason being, because they usually don't.  What Kinda Shit Are You?   
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Screw that last post!  I'm not one to give up or wallow in self-pity, right? Besides, I think it kinda made me sound  waayy  emotional or something *Hehe* I'm having fun.. nothing wrong with that, true? I'm just gonna with the flow and enjoy the ride while it lasts. I don't know where the stop is, or what it's gonna be like.. I'm not about to worry too much about it. I'm here for the fun times and the excitement of curiousity. Woohooo!  Had dinner at Hartamas with Fahmy, Boboy, Shak and Ajim. Anas got off work at 9pm last night, but joined us later when we hit Planet Hollywood after dinner. We hung out there for a bit, a few drinks and then made a move. I think we left at midnight or a little after that. Nothing much, just hanging out talking and observing the crowd.   As for my exam.. it was at 10.20am, so I was there super early. Oh, and dumb me didn't notice that they   DID   paste the exam schedule  outside  the door. Oops. Since I had a couple of hours to kill, I headed to Shak's place to study. The paper turned out alright, I guess. With that out of the way, I am free of study worries until May. Except for one thing, I gotta get an application in for my degree course. I don't think the forms are out yet, though. I'm feeling pain in the financial department, so I'm gonna start serving the evil empire of Business Trends again.   Right now, I gotta go shower and hit the bank *Ouchy ouch* and pay off my debts. A couple bucks here and there and *Walla!* the total is about a hundred bucks. Funny shit.   *Logs off* 
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I think it's time to totally forget about it. It blows. But, hey, that's life.. right?  Life sucks.  I know this moment would come, regardless me wanting it to or not. True, I was curious what'll happen when it does. I suppose, deep down I was hoping it would be a little bit more encouraging, y'know? Oh well, you can't force or make someone do or feel something they don't wanna.   This is bullshit. I don't know why I'm letting this bother me in the first place. I mean, I went through my whole life with the  "R"  word.. so why should this be any different? Why am I turning into an emotional bitch? It's not like there was anything in the first place, right? I gotta get a grip. I mean, why be such a  "girl"  over this and risk losing one heck of a good friend? I don't want to lose a funny friend just because I can't stop thinking like a teenager. *sigh* Still hurts, though =(   Anyways, I have my final exam in the AM. I'm still not done reading the book but getting there. I had an early dinner, am now letting my stuffed tummy settle down so I could continue studying. The funny part of tomorrow is, I have no frickin' clue what time my paper is. Scary shit, right? I know it's in the morning, so I'm gonna play it safe and get my ass on campus before 8am. I went to check the schedule this morning but the damn faculty was all locked up. Yeah, I know, it's Sunday. But the least they could've done was paste a copy   outside   the main door.   Gotta go study now. Later. 
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The photos (from my birthday) are superb! I can't stop looking at them. Everyone looks so happy.. and sloshed *Hehe* The angles of the pictures are great, thanks to Ajim and Wira.  Thanks, guys!  Damn, I was hugging everyone and just as I suspected, there were a number of me and eye-candy *Hehe* The group photo we had one of the waitresses snap turned out extremely well. What can I say.. they're all just  perfect!!  Very excited here.  Had dinner at Modesto's (Telawi) with Shak, Ajim and Denen. Gerald hung out for a few, then he had to split. After dinner, me and Denen hit  urlLink BarFlam  for a bit. Shak and Ajim went to pick Myrna (Shak's cousin), 'cuz she needed to talk to Shakhira about something. So, it was me and Denen for about an hour or so. Oh, yeah.. he's just  TOO  cute!!! *sigh* I'm losin' it, aren't I? I've got it baaaddd! *Haha* After BarFlam, we went to uptown to meet up with Fahmy and the guys. Stayed there for a short while and then headed home.  Dolly bought me lunch today. Ofcourse I picked Chili's.. what else, right? Tomorrow's Aidiladha, warning sirens are already sounding loud and clear in my head.. abundance of food and I fear that I might lose a lil bit of self control. Help! Help! Know what? I'm kinda bored and getting lazy to write more. I'm gonna stop here and maybe blog more later tonight. I want a nap before dinner. O-oh.. I don't know what I'm gonna have tonight. Not really hungry, though.. maybe I'll skip.. I dunno.  I'm out. 
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         IT'S MY BIRTHDAY!      Last night was...  wow.  I had fun, loads of fun. It was a mellow kinda fun, I think. But then again, I was dancing the whole night with everyone to practically every song and didn't sit down until the lights came on. Time flew by  SO  fast! I guess that happens when you're having a blast *Hehe* Oh, and ofcourse the venue of the celebration was BarFlam.  When I got there, even the hostess and the security guys (at the door) wished me a happy birthday. We had 2 tables reserved under Shakhira's name. Yeah, the usual tables.. what else? *haha* Anyways, it was mass0r fun. I even got a couple of presents from the guys who works there. One from this security guy and another from a couple of waiters. Yeah, eye-candy's one of 'em *Hehe* At midnight, Shakhira even got the DJ to announce my birthday and he played a song for me. Sweet, huh?    The crowd:  Me, Shakhira, Farah, Ajim, Gerald, Fahmy, Im (he finished his shift but came back to join the party), Boboy, Wira, Shakir, Hani, A.J. and Carlos (he came for a drink n had to split). Anas was always dragged to our tables cuz he's part of the group, he drank n even danced with us.  Loads of birthday wishes, hugs, kisses and dancing after that. I even danced with eye-candy, but not for long cuz he has to work. Oh, we even had photos taken,  2 rolls worth.  We stayed until closing and then went to eat while waiting for Anas to finish up at BarFlam. After that it was back to the headquarters (Shakhira's place) for the usual after clubbing hang out. Anas and Im came with us. We hung out, the guys had to leave early morning because of work and classes. Some went to sleep, me and Anas decided to look for a movie to watch. Halfway through we got bored and hung out with Shakhira and Ajim in the room.   Bla bla bla... I dont feel like writing every single thing. But, take my word for it...  It was a great night.    THANKS YOU GUYS!    After sending Anas and Im to work (they start early today), we sent Farah home and then Shakhira and Ajim dropped me off. I thought I was late for something at home, but apparently I was mistaken. Nobody wished me at home, yet. =( Good God! I gotta go drop of the rolls to be developed before the shop closes. I want the prints ASAP. Can't wait to see how the photos turned up. Hopefully the ones I'm looking forward to come out okay.   Gotta run. I'll blog later about my presents count *Hehe* 
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I am confined to the house until... I don't know.  5 days until I add another candle to the cake. Another year to my years. Another step closer to the future I fear.  Gulp.    Friday night. Friends are out. I am home. Stupid me and my promises. Promised mom no more night outings until after my finals. Things I do just so I could be there to celebrate his birthday. I didn't realise I like him  that  much! Sheeesh. Must be the eyebrow piercing he got *Hehe* I don't even know if I'll be able to go out on   MY   birthday. Probably just for a bit, not stay out the whole night and freak out. Bummer. Oh well.. I'll do that after my exams. I suppose it'll be sort of a delayed celebration or something. At this point, I don't even feel like celebrating. Okay, that's a lie. I'm always up for a good party, but with mom getting on my case every 5minutes... 20th February is looking pretty dim. I don't even feel like planning anything. Not to mention I overspent during the past week. I don't even know what I did with my money. This is nuts.   Now I'm bringing myself down. I suppose when there's a possibility of not being able to party as hard as you want, dealing with parental and inner issues and with the pressure of finals... I just can't sit down and plan anything. My mind's way too occupied. I can't even plan tomorrow, let alone something a week away.   My birthday's gonna suck mass0r ass. 
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      um yah. been outta d house since Friday the 8th. Partied that night. Celebrated eye-candy's birthday on the 9th (countdown, it's actually on the 10th), got smashed more than he did, had mass0r fun. Partied again on the 12th, got even more smashed, still feeling super dumb about getting overly sick, i think i had a good time and my crush is gettin out of control  *Help!* . More fun continues.. finally went home on the 13th. Went to the airport to send Shakhira's sister off (starting Uni in Melbourne, Australia).   Today (14th): Got up at 1pm, had one hell of a fucked up lunch (can't even remember what), munched on tiny cookies, went to 1Utama with Fahmy, watched him eat wishing I could too, Shakhira joined us, followed her around shopping and last minute v-day gift hunting, Fahmy dropped me off, munched on tiny cookies, had dinner alone, munched on tiny cookies, got emotional, danced to a few cool tracks alone, all the while feeling super fucked and now feelin majorly fat and depressed.    Happy Valenfuckingtine everyone.  
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow.. I'm not writing as much as I used to. Been very lazy and all that. You understand.  Oh yeah, got the photos from the shop.  Superb stuff!  Went out with Fahmy, Rakhma and AJ on Sunday. Fahmy was craving this meatball pasta at Dave's, so we went there. Yazmin came by to say hello, she had to drop her cousin off there and joined us for a bit. Rakhma left with her later because it's her mom's birthday and they're having dinner together. Me, Fahmy and AJ had dinner with SHakhira and Ajim. Fahmy left, I hopped into Shak's car and we drove around looking for things to do.   Monday, we had lunch at this chicken rice place in Kampung Baru. The crowd: Me, Fahmy, AJ, Farah, Ajim, Gerald, Shakhira, Rakhma and Shakir. Ajim and Gerald were from the office, they stayed for a bit and then had to get back to work. They're too crazy, long lunch and then left work early. Someone came up with the idea of hitting PLanet Hollywood. We did that, I messed up (hehe) so the girls had to leave early. Went over to Shakhira's place to grab a bite to eat and settle down.. Was home by 11.30pm.  Rakhma left for Melbourne yesterday *Sniff sniff* we went to the airport to see her off. Gave her a couple of pictures in frames, one of the crowd on Friday night and the other of me and her. I miss her already!!!! Anyways, I'm feeling sucky because of  LOADS  of stuff. I'm so irritable right now... I'm even seeking comfort in food. Bad. I'm filling up on diet coke, atleast that's practically 0 cals. Bleh.  Imma go now. 
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Party session at  BarFlam  last night. Rakhma's last friday night out in KL, she's heading back to school (in Melbourne) on Tuesday =( Still haven't slept since I got up for class at 8.30am yesterday. Crazy crowd, crazy acts and mad laughing back at the apartment. It was very cool and we even took photos. I had fun. I don't feel like getting detailed right now. I'm kinda bummed 'cuz I can't be out partying again tonight. Parental issues =\ Sucks, eh?  Anyways, I'm not gonna think about it too much.. It'll only make me feel worse. I'm just waiting for bedtime, if I can sleep that is *Hehe* Just looking forward to 1pm when the prints will be ready. Can't wait. 
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I've gotten super duper lazy, haven't I? Just didn't feel like blogging, I guess. This machine I'm using is kinda slow, so it's annoying. Quick update.. Shakhira and Ajim are gonna have a birthday thang next Friday. Dinner, and then BarFlam. Was at BarFlam last night. Eye candy's too cute. I fell outside, infront of the coffee place next door. Fucking embarrassing. Huge bruise on my right knee.  Ouch!   Have yet to get any sleep since yesterday.Woohoo. I don't really feel like writting much, mainly due to thoughts all scrambled up in my head. Can't get proper sentences out, let alone tell stories. We'll save them for some other time, hmm? 
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Surveys... Surveys...   1. LIVING ARRANGEMENT?  Mom, sis, bro and a few cousins  2. WHAT BOOK ARE YOU READING NOW?  None at the mo, just magazines  3. WHAT'S ON YOUR MOUSE PAD?  I got it free from Dell, so it's some art by them with support numbers  4. FAVORITE BOARD GAME?  cluedo  5. FAVORITE MAGAZINE?  Cleo  6. FAVORITE SMELLS?  vanilla's nice, davidoff coolwater for women, Clinique Happy for men  6. LEAST FAVORITE SMELLS?  crap, piles of rubbish, BO  7. FAVORITE SOUND?  my phone ringing =P  8. WORST FEELING?  unrequited love, regret  9. FIRST THING YOU THINK OF WHEN YOU WAKE UP IN THE MORNING?  breakfast!!  10. FAVORITE COLOR?  purple, blue, lavender, black  11. HOW MANY RINGS BEFORE YOU ANSWER THE PHONE?  a couple, after I see who it is.  12. FUTURE CHILD'S NAME?  never thought about it  13. MOST IMPORTANT IN LIFE?  consideration, faith and positivity  14. FAVORITE FOODS?  fries, vegetables, chicken  15. CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA?  Vanilla  16. DO YOU LIKE TO DRIVE FAST?  Not anymore  17. DO YOU SLEEP WITH A STUFFED ANIMAL?  nope. it'll just end up on the floor anyway  18. STORMS - COOL OR SCARY?  not scary, not extremely cool either  19. WHAT TYPE WAS YOUR FIRST CAR?  Not exactly mine, but the first I drove after I got my liscense; a red suzuki swift  20. IF YOU COULD MEET ONE PERSON DEAD OR ALIVE?  toughie. I guess my dad. Or Keanu Reeves *Heheh*  21. FAVORITE ALCOHOLIC DRINK?  bacardi limon, baby! Nahh.. diet coke for me, thanks =)  22. WHAT IS YOUR ZODIAC SIGN?  pisces  23. DO YOU EAT THE STEMS OF BROCCOLI?  yep  24. IF YOU COULD HAVE ANY JOB YOU WANTED WHAT WOULD IT BE?  owner of a sucessful advertising empire  25. IF YOU COULD DYE YOUR HAIR ANY COLOR WHAT WOULD IT BE?  maroon or burgundy  26. IS THE GLASS HALF EMPTY OR HALF FULL?  well, atleast there's something in it  27. FAVORITE MOVIES?  bug's life, reality bites, ever after, fast and furious  28. DO YOU HAVE YOUR FINGERS ON THE RIGHT KEYS?  most of the time  29. WHAT'S UNDER YOUR BED?  magazines, a pair of old sneakers, dust  30. WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE NUMBER?  6  31. FAVORITE SPORT TO WATCH?  i don't watch sports 
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm sick =(    My stomach hurts like a bitch. I went to the doctor's last night, and he said it's noisy inside *Hehe* It's gas and acid and all that in my stomach and small intestines. He gave me a few diff pills for the pain and gas and acid. I even got a shot on my butt. I looked like hell, and he said he'd give me the shot if I can't take the pain. Obviously, I agreed. There's no way I'm gonna be up half the night crying again.   It actually started Tuesday night. I thought it's because I didn't eat anything, and it wasn't this intense. It was alright the day after, except when I was a little bit late with dinner. Had to run a few errands, and the pain started. Even after dinner it didn't go away completely. I got up around 1.30am with cramps from hell, I thought I just needed to eat something. I had some cereal with milk, even drank soya bean milk. Nada. I went back to bed and cried and whined myself to sleep. When I got up for breakfast it was alright, but started again at lunch time. I had lunch at around 2pm, I guess it was a little late. The pain didn't stop and got worse every hour. By dinner, I couldn't take it anymore, and had my uncle drive me to the doctor's. It's ridiculous, I can't even sit for long let alone walk around. I spent the day lying down in a fetal position, cuz it doesn't hurt that much when I'm like that.  I had an appointment this morning at 9.30am. Had to cancel, I can't even get out of bed. Right now, it's alright. I mean, it still hurts but not as bad as a half hour ago. I think, as long as I have something in my tummy, it doesn't hurt as much. Crap. I'm gonna get fat again, aren't I? I was so pissed off I had a piece of chocolate a couple hours ago! Then I had fish crackers and a little bit of cornflakes with milk. I'm such a glut, don't you think? It's not even dinner time yet! I soooo wanna skip dinner, but I don't want the pain and I gotta get well enough to make my appointment tomorrow morning.   Eye candy update: There's a positive development, me thinks. He called a few days ago and asked if I was gonna spent the night at my friend's place. I said no, because I had stuff to do in the morning for my brother. He said he was thinking of hanging at my friend's place after work. I told him to just go, but he said some other night  because I wouldn't be there  *Hehe* Am I excited, or am I excited? Actually there are still a few updates but my stomach's hurting again. So, I gotta go. Feels like a knife cutting everytime I exhale!  Wish me luck. 
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't stop munching. I've been eating fruits like it's going out of style and surprising myself with this kind of a sweet tooth. I seem to want dried fruits and candy and stuff. Good thing I've just  refreshed  my apples supply. I've been eating piece after piece of guava, which I suspect may have just added up to one whole fruit. ANd then I started reaching for this dried apple thingy my sister bought (sugar! Evil sugar!!), after a piece I decided I'd better go for something less damaging. Yeah, the apple. I've also decided to use water as a way to curb this eating frenzy of mine. So that started frequent visits to the loo. Oh well, atleast it's calorie-free and keeps me full, right? Then again,  my stomach looks like I'm carrying a friggin' baby!!  Oh, did I mention the fish crackers I've been snacking on? I'll break small pieces off those fried sins, so it won't seem   that   bad.. I'm living in denial. Crap. Now I feel like going downstairs for more.   Okay, I'm done complaining. Not really. But I'm getting sick of ranting over my food intake and my weight (which, by the way, is yoyo-ing between a few pounds. How I wish to see those double digits again *sigh*). I'm gonna stop and drink water until it starts leaking through my ears.  Adios. 
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Didn't go to Petaling Street yesterday. Shakhira was feeling tired and she spent most of the day sleeping. I hung around at home, bored shitless and finally decided to go for a drive. I thought of hitting One Utama and just walk around, but ditched the idea. I drove there, though, and then went over to bangsar for the heck of it. They had a big stage set up on Telawi 3, so that road was closed. I found later, they had an F1 party there last night.   Anas messaged me, saying BarFlam was having a 70s party and said to drop by for a laugh. He told me some time back they were gonna have that and all the waiters had to wear afro wigs. I should've dropped by and see how he looks like with an afro *hehe* I had a sorta dinner with Shakhira and Ajim at TGIF. The place was pretty packed, we had to wait for a table and even then it was in the non-smoking area. After dinner, we headed back to Shak's place for a couple of hours and then I headed home.  I have yet to sleep since yesterday. I spent the night re-organizing stuff in my room while boogie-ing to music and exchanging SMS messages with Shakhira. I also did a spot of writing after that, when I finally stopped I had rambled for 4 pages. There were still a lot I wanted to write about, but the pen was dying, my hand felt jammed up and I wanted to shower. I left for Shakhira's around 8.30am and hung out there until noon. I had a movie date with my bro and sis at 2pm and we had to get our reserved tickets by 1.30pm. We saw   The Mothman Prophecies  . It was not too bad but kinda slow, though.  I've been bored eversince I got home from the movies. Shakhira has no plans, Dolly's entertaining her nephews and niece, Fahmy just got back from Fraser's Hills... It's 7pm right now, and I'm itching to go someplace. I know I have to wait until 8pm before I can go out again, but nobody has any plans. I feel like hanging out, but don't know where and all that. * Sigh * Hopefully somebody comes up with something later.   I'm outtie. 
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      High time for an update, don'tcha think? *Heheh*   Let's see... Since my last update a few things had happened, ofcourse. On my way back from Johor on Sunday evening, I got a phone call from Muff. He told me  Yazmin's dad had passed away a couple hours earlier.  Needless to say, I was shocked. He's been sick for more than a month now, been in the ICU and all. But, the last time I met up with her, she said there was progress... Poor girl. I was in shock and felt super sad for her. Kinda reminded me of my dad, though.  Shakhira was also out of town, and both of us didn't get back to KL until after 10pm. Since it was kinda late, we went for the funeral the next day. It was scheduled at 10am, but they arrived at the cemetary a little past 11am. A whole lot of people turned up, even the Prime Minister's wife and people from the Prime Minister's Office. After the burial, we went to see Yazmin to offer our condolences and such. I couldn't help being teary eyed when I hugged her, the girl even wished me a belated birthday! She kept saying she didn't forget. That was too much, I felt like crying. She's just too sweet and seeing the tears... well, it's beyond words, ya know?  That was the major news of the week. Other than that, it was the usual out-to-eat-and-hang-for-a-bit thang. Oh, and I got myself a  new mobile number  yesterday. I'm sick of paying RM63 for access and running up RM200 phone bills. So, I've joined the masses in the world of pre-paid mobiles. My number's kinda cool, too. Oh, and I met up with eye-candy on Tuesday night. He was hanving dinner with a couple of people he works with (I know them, too) and I went over to say hello. I was in the area and called him to see if he wanted to join us for a bite. He was already with his colleagues at the time.  Let's see, what else. Nothing that comes to mind at the moment. There's a plan of hitting Petaling Street later, around 5pm. Sounds good.. Maybe I'll blog when I get back. If the connection's not being a bitch and I'm not lazy. Later. 
    
</post>

<date>02,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         From Geocities:  Beginning April 2, 2002, we will no longer provide FTP access as part of our free home page service.     Ahh.. Crap! Just when I moved my blog here, they decided to make me pay for FTP. Looks like it's back to blogspot.. bummer. I have to re-code the page and move everything. This blows. Maybe I'll just design a new layout or something. Aarghh! Oh well, atleast I have about a month to get it all done.  I'm blogging from Johor right now. I have yet to sleep, cuz I'm trippin something bad *Hehe* I don't know what made me decide to join my cousin on this trip. This has got to be the furtherst my trippin has gotten me. Too funny.    urlLink      click for fullsize     I've just uploaded the  first half  of my birthday photos. I spent the night scanning and editing the photos. Had to do it while everyone's asleep.. You understand *wink wink* Anyways, to view them just click on the  gallery  icon on the left *points* The album should be the first one up there. It's labeled "I turned 23!" or something like that. Damn, I feel old!! I'll get the rest scanned real soon, I promise. Right now,  urlLink happy viewing .  Haha My aunt just got up and caught me not infront of the 'puter. She was shocked I didn't sleep and asked why. Told her something about not being sleepy. I don't know if I'll be able to eat breakfast. And I just remembered I'm gonna go bowl with my cousin at 10am. Should be an interesting game *Hehe*  I guess I'd better jet.. Enjoy the photos and feel free to leave comments. Ciao! 
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
          I am heartbroken.    It's definitely time to give up. No longer shall you hear excited reports on eye candy. Too disappointed.      *SIGH*     p.s: the bday thang went superbly well. that's when my brokenhearted situation started, by the way.  
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
          Don't kid yourself. If you eat a Twinkie, your thighs know. If you sneak a Pepsi, your belly knows. If you eat a Ring Ding, your butt knows. If you go to the gym, your muscles know. If you eat a healthy diet, your organs know. If you drink water, your blood knows. If you smile, the world knows!      A little piece of motivation there, applying to both body and mind.   Played around with a few photos, getting creative and stuff. I think the end product's not too bad, if I may say so myself. It's been uploaded onto the  urlLink photo album , under the  Misc  gallery. It's nothing spetacular, pretty tiny infact, but I like it.. So there =P  In other news, things are slowly heading towards the positive.  Very, very  slowly. Certain areas are beginning to show improvement, nothing definite maybe.. I can't help being cautious and even a little suspiscious. Some majorly important parts that still need fixing. Just hope it can be fixed. Would suck even if only 5% remains broken. Wish me luck!  Had drinks at that sorta new place nearby (Tmn Megah, for those in the know). Totally forgotten about its existence! I had dinner there once a few months back. Got there slightly after 11pm with Shakhira. There were guys selling VCDs! Yay! Been a while since I got some new movies, so I bought a couple.  I'm not staying online long tonight. I'm just posting this and gonna log off. Probably do a spot of writing, which I put off last night. Might end up playing with more images or something. I dunno..  Eyes are hinting at shutting, but I doubt the mind will let me rest just yet. Too many things playing in my head, with no pause button to halt it. Body's tired, though. I might just curl up with a pillow and let sleep take over.  Hmmmm... Nice... 
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         *Lost? I don't know... perhaps?*     Things are just so twisted these days. I'm beginning to fear life. I'm spinning out of control, doing things I normally would not, can't make myself care about things dear to me, I've even kinda stopped caring what people think of me... Major changes that are currently taking shape is getting too much to handle. I feel like i'm being thrown against a brick wall, causing pain and anger. I'm lashing out in the  worst  way. Patience running thin, tempers flaring and tolerance level dipping dangerously. It's like the typhoon of mood swings.   I can't seem to get along with anyone at all. Things tend to rub either me or others the wrong way, I can't even get words out of my mouth without some of it ticking someone off.. Which cause stress and, at times, exchanges of extreme harshness. My life right now is one BIG mess. Huge. I'm stressing out over what the hell I'm gonna do with myself (work/school) all the while dealing with pressure from some, situations involving friends, tension between me and the family and financial matters that can't seem to be resolved. All that stuff, and more, is causing major breakouts of the acne kind. *Humph!*  I seem to get pissed off everyday now. Not majorly pissed, but irritation that threatens to blow out of control. Ofcourse, in between feeling irritated, there are the full blown anger explosions. I don't get it. There are times when I'm just sitting there minding my own business, feeling fine. Bordering on chirpy, even. Someone would bring something up that will at first be  "WTF??" , move on to be a mild annoyance, which in turn, will evolve into something so stupid that it pisses me off. Sometimes, I don't even know where the hell all that (stuff they're saying) came from.   People would also get all mad at me out of a sudden. Okay, so maybe I'm doing something wrong or whatever. Even so, there's absolutely no need to put me down and get all condenscending. I'm not a kid and I'm not stupid. *shakes head* I don't know... Everything's piling up and I'm afraid it might just topple over and suffocate me. Actually, I'm even scaring myself. I can't seem to make myself care or bother about most things anymore. I do realise this, but, like I said, I'm spinning out of control and  I don't know how to stop.  Everything's scary and freaking the crap out of me. I'm falling deeper into a state of denial, while everything collapse around me. Bit by bit, it's getting ruined and I'm not sure I'll be able to pick up the pieces before it's too late.   I'm losing grasp on what used to be my life, feeling the once solid foundation shake, seeing everything I care about moving further away... I seem to be losing my friends, family and direction. To put it into simpler terms:   I'm fuctup.   My priorities are screwed and totally misguided. Yeah, I do realise all this.. But I can't seem to re-align myself.  I am not okay  and it's frightening to feel control slipping away. I don't know how or where to call out for assistance, to ask for the one branch from a solid tree to help me stop spinning. But when it stops, will the world make sense? Will the track I was on still be there and ready to welcome me back on it? Will the ground stop being all wobbly? I so want to see the picture again, to know where the pieces on the floor go, to be certain it will fit...  I'm scared. 
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Who's gonna get fat?? ME!!   This is horrible! Simply horrible.. I had dinner  twice  tonight. I don't know what the hell's the matter with me. I ate chicken curry with half a slice of bread, some vegetables and some of this calamari dish my mom made. After that I was like  "Ooh..I'm stuffed" . Then a friend called. I told her I'd go with her and hang out while she ate, since i've already had dinner. Bad idea.  Ended up at Muhibbah with her parents, they've already ordered like   7   dishes. I told them I already had dinner. I seriously wasn't plan on eating. But somehow ended up having bits of everything. Especially the vegetables and tofu. Then there were the fried calamari, deep fried fish... Good thing i stayed away from the prawns and clams. But still.. I wasn't supposed to have anything!! I feel like barfing. Good thing I'm not bulimic. Tomorrow I'm going jogging, and am not planning to eat much this weekend. It's back to my salads n bread n nothing else!!!  Bleugh. Anyways, I did this quiz for the heck of it.    urlLink        You Are A Romantic Kisser!  You'll only kiss if the mood is right and if you think you are falling in love.  Some may say you're old fashioned, but when you kiss, you see stars!  One kiss from you, and anyone will be hooked forever.     urlLink   How Do *You* Kiss?       urlLink More Great Quizzes from Quiz Diva  
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         Am I back again?      Suddenly, I've decided to resurrect this blog after months of death-like slumber. Talk about cobwebs! Been half a year, hasn't it? Obviously, loads have happened. To put everything down right now, would require superhero strength and magical powers. Dedication would be another factor and the patience to type it all up. As long as I know what's going on, that's fine. It's not like anyone reads this thing, anyway =P    Highlights in point form:-   * I've graduated from the university  * Supposed to continue studying but majorly lazy. Gonna try working instead.  * Some drama had taken place recently. Probably still going on.  * Break-ups, misunderstandings, changes in relationships, new experiences, first times, etc  * The above *points* are both good and bad. Some.. totally unwanted and I wish it would go away.  * Was in Melbourne, Australia from 13/8/2002 until 7/9/2002. Longer than was planned. Photos  urlLink over here   * Finally went to a friend's club when I was there. Had a good time. Thanks, Simon =)  * Had my hair cut and highlighted red/violet in Melbourne.  * Got stressed over certain issues involving friends. To the point of tears, zits popping out and falling sick.  * Calming myself down, but sometimes just can't help getting worked up. Like right now.   * Heading to Genting Highlands for work on Sunday morning.  * Clubbing has been taken to a new direction. More guy scanning involved.  * Fun has included words like :  Beach Club, Portugal, Sangria, fun dance partner  and  dance floor action  *hehe*  * Changes in certain areas of friendship is bumming me out  * In the midst of smoothing things out. Wishing positive changes are for real and will last.  * In major denial over eye candy (yep, still on that). But this time working on getting over it, for real.  * Rakhma's boyfriend, Tariq, and his friend, Julian, moved to KL.    Okay, that's all for right now. I'm feeling too crappy to go on. I'm in major paranoia and shit like that. I feel unwated and kinda like being regarded as a drag to certain individuals. Disliked, ignored, left out... they all are kinda the same, eh? Maybe it's just me.. But I somehow think not. It's pretty obvious when it feels like you're having a one-sided conversation. Trying to converse with someone who's probably rolling their eyes and getting annoyed. You have no idea how sad I'm feeling right now. How lonely and hurt.    Check it out, I'm such a drama queen. But, I feel all that.. Can't help it. Please let it get better. 
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Over a week ago...   He introduced me to his friend as  "My girl" .   He then proceeded to hit on my friend last Thursday night.  What the...?? 
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Resurrected from slumber of years. For the time being.   Got myself a job at  Leo Burnett KL . Been there for a little over a year. having the time of my life. Learned so much, still learning a whole lot.. very excited.  Met a lot of people who i never thought i would.. DJs, F1 drivers, etc...  Still single as ever.   Done a few things, accomplished a bunch, changed this and that..  First times for a number of things has occured.  Almost a different person now. Almost, not quite. Still the same ol' girl deep down, but with different priorities.  Enjoying the ride of life, though bumpy and choppy at times.   Current mode :  I wanna do this, so be it. Will think about consequences later.  Current music :  Gatecrasher (1st compilation) - Late set (Disc 2)   Next up :   Work-wise :  Sunday event @Planet Hollywood                                Non-work :  Lang Tengah with the Events team   Current thought :  Work @9am. Shitload to do. Preparation for Sunday.  Current petty shit :  Unanswered sms message  .out. 
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        s p o R a d i c    That's  exactly  what this blog is.   Item 1 Forgot about this. Got busy and/or distracted with other things. Plus, lost internet connection for a while. With too much to update when it was restored, brings us to....  Item B Got lazy and/or bored with pouring the contents of my head and heart online. Referring to the above mega-update requirement leads us to...  3rd Item Too many things rushing out, don't even know where to start. Plus censoring contents were starting to piss me off. Shortage of patience, y'see ;)  Anyways.. What's been happening since April?   The Lang Tengah trip was   EXcellent  . Small island off Terengganu with only 3 resorts, located in between Redang Island & the Perhentian Islands with no/minimal mobile reception (only certain spots for certain providers). The room was huge, with 2 single beds. I stayed alone cuz one of my colleagues had to cancel. Her daughter was hospitalized. There are no TVs & refrigerators in the rooms. There's a common room with 1 TV. No cable. There's also 1 room with a pool table, and we saw speakers n a disco ball hanging in there. Maybe it turns into a "discotheque" or something at times.  Let's do the chronicle thing. A short, summarised version.    Day 1   Reached Kuala Terengganu Airport, transfer to private jetty on a bus (the guide was just too funny. although he didn't know that), speed boat to Blue Coral Resort. Mysterious welcome drink, welcome note n briefing by the resort dude & found out only 1 room is ready. So we dumped our stuff there and waited for lunch.   All meals were provided, buffet-style (ala carte items were also available, but u gotta pay your own), every group had their own assigned tables (u sit there for every meal). After lunch n checking into our respective rooms, changed into suits and beach wear, explored a neighbouring resort. There, me, As & Mervin jumped into the water for a bit. Ahhhh... Too nice! Headed back and chilled in the pool. Evening: Cyril & As' verandah, chatting & munching.  After dinner, we hung out, had drinks and played pictionary. I won every game, with diff partners *woohoo!* then crashed.    Day 2   First to wake up. Went around waking everyone up for bfast. Tanner was the first to join me. Siew Mun & Mervin didn't get up to eat. After bfast, had shower n joined Tanner on the beach for drinks. Had to scrape plans of joining the resort's snorkeling trip with Lam. Dozed off on the sand to teasings and the rest attempted a volleyball game.   Lunch. Got snorkeling gear from the resort n hit the sea. My first time ever! There are some really funky fishies out there. Especially the one with the huge-ass face! Saw my first parrot fish, colourful fella. Had one fish stare me right in the face when i first went in. Freaked me out for a bit there. Shit load of sea cucumber and corals(duh), ofcourse. Had a laugh at each other, especially at Tanner & Cyril.  Hit the pool, showered, then joined the Tanner, Merv & Cyril at the dining area. There were sitting outside, having munchies & beers. Chilled out, gambled (blackjack) and short nap before dinner. After dinner, watched TV for a bit, hung out at the beach with Merv, Siew Mun & Lam. Merv helped finish the chilean wine Anas gave. Chitchat, took out more drinks & munchies, settled for more blackjack. Over-all, I won RM7. Before the drinks got me, and i dozed off. Yep, yet again. Yes, to teasings n laughter.   After gambling (Merv won pretty big, i was told), Cyril called it a night. The rest moved to Siew Mun's room, which i promptly crashed on the bed supposedly for a short nap. Next thing i know, he was waking me up asking for my room key. I went back and zonked. They apparently moved to Tanner & Merv's room to smoke n almost died laughing. Tanner got emo & almost killed himself, thanks to Merv *hahaha*    Final Day   Went to breakfast by myself. The rest already said they're not gonna get cuz it sucked. Had a quick one then back to shower and slept a bit more. Hung out at the verandah reading, then to the beach. I had to vacate my room earlier cuz are ppl checking in later. Dumped stuff in Siew Mun & Lam's room. Hung out at their verandah, then As' verandah.   Discovered lunch was not included. Went to the next resort to check out their food, came back n ordered off the menu. Merv went on to Perhentian, by hitching a ride with the next resort's snorkeling trip boat. The owner's really cool to let him do that, Siew Mun sorta know him anyways.  Checked out, said byebye to everyone and hopped on the boat. Got to the airport with hours to kill before we can check in. Had food, drinks and rounds of cards. Played Chotaiti, refreshed my memory since it's been awhile. Cyril & As went into the waiting room first, we joined them when we found out it was much cooler. Damn Terengganu's hot!! Played more cards n watched TV while waiting to board.   Reached KL and straight to LB to get the cars. Hung out there for a bit before heading back. Tanner dropped me & Siew Mun home, after food at Murni in SS2.   All in all.. it was a good trip. Very relaxing. The island's a great place if you're looking to zone out & not expecting loads of activities like watersports & shit like that. More foreigners than locals, so it's really quiet & laid back.   Check out www.pinganchorage.com.my for packages to the islands. That's the operator we used, call them to get the latest prices (which can be cheaper).  *whew!* Until next time... Out. 
    
</post>


</Blog>