<Blog>


<date>27,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      couldn't death be as nearer as i wish it could be? no one knows how wanting i am for that fate upon me while young. and it's moments like these - where anger is not just anger - and the frustration kills me inside like a stake in my chest refusing to let go... where i can't handle the pressure. just when you think life can not be any worse, it seems like anyone around you begins to cook up some vandetta over your very being just to spite you and make sure you're an insignificant dust mite in this deadly planet. friend, family, neighbour... it doesn't matter who.. just as long as to them, you're someone they can take a ride on... assume you're a parasite's victim - and count the days you're no longer needed.  no, i'm not hallucinating. although i wish i were. to see that loathsome blood, scaling down my arms and skull... yes, to numb the emotional pain, my medication was some head contact with the wall a couple of times. it's not the first time... but it helps me a great deal to manage all the thoughts that rain in my medula oblongata. it helps me sleep, without thinking or recalling the events that torture me like a nightmare... in fact, i can't remember what happened last night, but it felt like a nervous breakdown. why can't the brain have a power button? depression, death... whatever... isn't it just one of those days where you hate everyone?
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      alrite... i'm back in the game. i've been practically "out of comission" the past *almost* one week! down with an awful cough and cold ain't fun. it may have kept me away from the Net, but not from my darling laptop! i've finally got a new look for my webabode running. although the links and parts of it ain't done, at least fickle ol' me FINALLY decided on a look i like, i guess... *grin* anyway, miss Sharon like an imsomniac squirrel without nuts on a winter's day... and today is Valentine's day! *mischievious grin* got a lil' dinner do with Gary tonite. nothing private, tho'... heheh... it's actually a fancy dinner cum launch of a close friend's company website... so, sue me if i made friendship mix with lurve on Vday! besides, Gary is such the romantic even if it ain't Vday... gotta get going with my web-home stuff... =)
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      and now, my net exposé begins... i turn 22 today, and i'm absolutely clueless. to add to the *depression* of becoming a year older, my best friend, Sharon, leaves for Perth today. so, i guess i'll be left to fend myself of all the emotional storms and find other eccentrical inspirations while she's away... oh, well... it'll only be for a year. and we know how time can flutter it's wings away.  and yes! must mention an awwww-some thanks to 'crankcase (was it ever "Cranky case", lionel?) for convincing me to expose my life in cyberspace...  it's 6am now, and i'm an insomniac. so, what the course of the day will provide on my 22nd year on this life-buzzin planet, you will know crumbs of it sometime later... so, whatever you'll be off doing... stay! *smile*
     
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      it's official. my life can only go down hill form here on. for whatever reason... i just can't be quite the optimist right now. i'm probably deemed the most irritable, obnoxious, b****** person on everyone's list. walk on the street or on the crowded narrow rows in the pasar malam and you would probably murder me for shoving you aside like the world is my oyster... well, it is to me... "The world is MY oyster, and I want to shuck it!" what's wrong with that? sue me for being vague, but i like to keep the details off the record. neat eh? go figure...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm dying... of my cough and cold. sitting here in the office in the middle of the afternoon. seems like the past 3 months i've been consistently falling sick around the same time of the month... hrmmm... go figure. anyway, the past one month - thankfully, i haven't been bumming around uselessly. i've been working as a programme executive at Malaysia's *first* Internet Radio station, www.asian-family.com. no, this ain't a promo. just letting you know how much i'm enjoying my job doing production work.  and that i'm finally getting my butt back to studying and finishing a diploma... in 4 months. heheheh... going off to Perth - Down Under!! anyway, i leave you here for another interval... getting annoyed at my sniffling self, air-conditioned office and popping ears... *aaachooooo!*
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      in the office now, at 8.15pm. fascinatingly a workaholic of course... i have about 6 more working days before i leave this Internet radio station place... seems like my colleagues are planning some sort of a farewell party. awww... so sweet of them. i'm really flattered. though i've only been here a short 2 months and 2 weeks, it's been a whole lot wonderful meeting different sorts of ppl... esp the local celebs... *gag* choking on my pride... heheheh... y'know, i've had like a couple of nicknames over the past weeks - schizo skunk (why skunk? not cos me stinky, the company name is SkunkWorks, go figure), ext 15, toilet wookie and the most recent Night Train. see! Crankcase, it's all your fault! hahahahha.... i'm not gonna elaborate on why the other nicks, you're just going to have to figure that out yourselves. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      ladies and gents, introducting lady Fumble-lina! *argh* i've become a dumb blonde with amnesia all of a sudden. i can't remember the terms, theories and all that junk i've been learning the past 3 years! i can't believe how bad i am now in front of the class. fumbling, stuttering... even the words can't get out of my mouth. memory recollection is just failing me! *wail*  i can't even think on my feet... *sniffle* what has become of me? i need to get this brain jumpstarted. and quick!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      motivation - why do you need it? how do you acquire it? i'm definitely in dire need for one now. *grin* i don't know how you'd define a lazy person, but is this excuse of missing work and feeling adequate at doing it at the office an excuse not to want to do papers and assignments in Uni? geez... no wonder everyone said it would be hard. or is that the looking glass theory for me?  bah! i've got soo much to do this week and yet, i'm sitting on my tush - procastinating! argh! argh! arrrgh!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm just sad. you'd think there'd be another word to use, but sad is just sad. there couldn't be another sadder day than today. i don't know what's going on. just a blur of confusion, loneliness and longing, i guess. you'd think ideals, dreams and wishes are a reality in your mind until you've faced life's complications... or is it really complicated? existentialism...  i've been in Perth for 4 weeks now, each of which just flew by with mixed emotions. what's life like living away from home? the feelings of freedom everyone else so professes isn't there. i just feel more lonely and less free... independence is there, but so was it when i was home. home. home... the familiarity. the security. yeah, i'm homesick! i'm a blardy homesick woman! not spoilt. i'm not complaining about doing my own laundry (although, i am afraid of spoiling the wool/nylon/delicate fabric sweaters...), my own cooking, paying my own bills, cleaning up after myself... bla bla... eventualities i knew i'd face no matter where i am sooner or later! it's just the fact of being far away from the familiar surroundings. having to start over - meeting people, learning how to get around, getting used to what's happening around (socially, politically)... and just basically learning how to "do as the Romans do in Rome." it's just emotionally draining. i just wonder how ppl who move around so much, handle it...  i'm trying to learn to re-introduce myself to a new group of friends. it's not easy. when you're trying to measure up and make sure you don't get into the wrong crowd. then there's the phase two of getting the ppl you want to befriends with to accept you... having to use previous experience in this case does NOT seem to help at all. every case scenario is different. totally... *sigh* so far, it's general consensus that the class thinks i'm about 18... 19... years of age. for a girl, you'd think i'd be flattered. but honestly? no, i'm not. i'm not the type of female species who want to conceal their age. i prefer to be the age i am. really! (yes, try asking me 10 or 20 years from now...) it's just ironic how when i was back in secondary school, ppl thought i was in college or working. now its just the other way around. *sigh* really. anyway, i think my classmates think i'm a geek, or a nerd or something. i'm not. i've learnt all that in class already! i can't help it. (don't ask me why i'm doing it again. long story. and i did not fail anything!!!) why i think this? well, seems like i'm friends with them cos i can help them with class work. and lectures are another thing, they're damn boring! how do you learn something all over again, but presented to you in a different - more long winded & boring - way? *sigh* what can i do? the stupid Uni won't put me in to their Degree program. now i've got to spend a miserable 14 weeks doing a Diploma. *sigh* i am sad...  and that's just the tip of the iceberg for my life for now...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      melancholy. who would have thought, i'd be here... in these dreams, or the surreal situations one only watched on tv and not letting it happen to you because you were brought up in such a way. or was i? questions. whatever i've been doing for the past few days, only i can't feel my conscience. was there ever a funeral? or was it just never in existence? what is a conscience? 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      depressed. upset. frustrated. too analytical and in an existentialist mood. all traits of the protagonist from a film noir movie. yes. i've had too much critical analysis for my history of cinema module. *sigh*  i've come to a cross road again. where i feel like a wind lily. where my life is questioned. where my actions are evaluated. where the people aroung me are being more analysed - and possibly becoming victims of my over-sensitive reactions. who am i? what am i? what makes me? what drives me? who drives me? what are the consequences to my actions? what will come around to bite me in the a**? when? one day. one jolly good day.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      hey... two parcels arrived for me today. it's the two books that poetry.com published my poetry in. pretty neat. maybe one day i'll get a whole book for myself. hmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm just so tired. tired of all the fussing and annoying arrogrance of some people... why lah? just because i'm a passive aggressive, it's even harder to vent out frustrations. i always end up with a little tear down my cheek... =/  *sigh* what drives me is that i know what i'm doing... and though it may be right or wrong, i can be humble enough to accept it.  "the future is not for us to see" - how very true. and yet sometimes, i wish that i can control it. i'm such a control freak that i want to have in my hands all that i can know about myself in the future. but over the last 3 years, i've learnt to live 6 months at a time. maybe even less now. it's exciting once you get the hang of it. but terribly frustrating when your inner clock screams for stability. that rarely happens now. all i want to know is whether i'm doing the right things in the present to secure my future...  thoughts aside, i've been trying my hand at non-linear editing the last two days. i've been quite fearful of this part of post production ever since one of my assignments in college turned sour. =/ but that seemed a long time ago now. i can't say i don't like post-production, cos its the learning process bit of my 'grasshopper' training. heh... Ken calls me his 'grasshopper' ever since i started calling him 'si fu'... *grin* anyway, it's alright. i won't say i'm good at NLE... and i do enjoy production... but who's to fuss n choose when knowing both actually gives me a boost - in the resume... heheh... =)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      aw man... Catherine is so sweet! i just got a card from her today. also attached with a letter from Jackie and a pooh drawing from WaiYi - made while in the middle of class lectures... lol! man, i miss those guys. Perth seems like a passing dream. and yet, a dream so very real from the friends i've made from my short time there. here's a hug going out to them! {{{{{{{{hugg}}}}}}}}  and also, WaiYi also reminded me of the crazy stuff i can vividly remember from Perth's days... heh... waiyi> "sometimes i sit in oliver and drive around . wishing . and hoping . .  hehe dat  *someone* will sit in the *backseat*   LOL ..." Oliver is Kolt's Suzuki Sierra... a lovely rugged green (the only color in WA) 4WD. we affectionately call him Olly. and there was this incident when Kolts, Edo and I went to watch a movie at Carousel. and when Kolts had to send me home, i had to like lie in the back of the 'car' cos it didn't have a back seat! btw, that's illegal in Perth... heheh... it was rather cosy, cos Kolts had lined it with his bag of fluff bought from WA Salvage (methinks). also, the guys drove to Edo's to get me a doona (comforter) to hide under... LoL! anyways, while Kolts is back in Fiji till February, WaiYi is taking care of good ol' Olly... who's been thru a LOT! we love that car... Kolts eccentricities passed on when we even sat by the sidewalk outside VicPark's PotBlack one late night staring at Catherine's new Accord - just to christen her car with a name. we had Lucy, Annie, Mel... all kinds before we finally settled with Jasmine. =)  *sigh* miss moments like those, don't you?
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm... now i can see why my dad's disillusioned with people, and so is my 'si fu' who's right now a very disillusioned producer. i don't know if i should blame it on marketing or the broadcast channel, but we didn't find out until late Wednesday afternoon that the broadcast date for the project i'm working on, is in March next year. and all this while they were rushing us for today's delivery... that caused quite a hoo-haa... what's worse is that while some ppl in production had to work over the holidays for a deadline 3-4 months later is caused by some people's inconsiderate nature of work - the people to blame are on leave or holiday - go figure! *sigh*  anyway, with the "life's like that" aside... i went to watch LOTR with Jinho, Dawn & Gary last night. i couldn't totally understand the film - although as usual, i was sort of *gawking* at the concepts and ideas of the whole story... amazing imagination that Tolkien. i should be reading the book if i want to follow the trilogy anyway... heh... man, the elves are gorgeous...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Christmas has come and gone... quietly... and tiredly... could barely keep my eyes open waking up at 8am just to start all the cooking fuss... began feeling that foreboding feeling about the whole idea of entertaining *loads* of people.  hmm... fortunately or unfortunately, there wasn't a *LOT* of people who came...  anyway, it's back to work. have to run through the scripts again for tomorrow's V/O dubbing... *sigh* i feel so fatigued just thinking about work...  man, i feel so hot n flushed... i wonder if it's the weather or the wine... heh... i could do with a really cold smoothie right now!
     
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      ah yes... the holiday season arrives. but Christmas doesn't feel the same anymore since i left school in 1996. those days we had our Christmas Nite concert that puts me the the mood and feeling of what that day means... it's just not the same anymore huh? *sigh*  and also what irks me most is how some ppl don't understand the meaning of sending off Christmas greetings as "Merry X'mas"... oh, for heaven's sake! Christmas is the day we celebrate Christ's birthday... why replace His Name, "Christ" with X? What IS Christmas without CHRIST huh? *mumblemumble* if you ask me, it's pure laziness and ignorance that the person uses "Xmas" instead of "Christmas"... yea-yea... i'm grumpy... but it's the truth, don't you think? pity those who wish me "Xmas" in my bad mood... hahahha.... really!  Merry Christmas all, btw..  *wink*
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      there's nothing else more embarassing in life than being sensitive to everything else around you... i wish sometimes i wasn't so sensitive to everything. maybe even a little more thick skinned... hmm...   i keep thinking about what Vicky asked me the other week, "Are you always so soft-spoken?" i was rather shocked. soft-spoken?? told Gary and Fairul, they didn't seem to think so! maybe compared to Vicky i am. heh... one thing she pointed out true though, is that i am a passive aggressive person. not good, i know. =P  work has become incredibly insane lately! i'm already all fatigued out from just two months of work. work that i thought i used to love so much. doesn't it mean something when work has become a burden instead of the very thing you used to enjoy? i wonder...  i'm just trying to hold out. maybe it'll settle down more once we deliver the first batch of three episodes. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      whyyyy...???
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      and what's more frustrating? its been months since i've had this blog, and i still cant figure out how to function the archives... =/
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm flustered, mentally exhausted and terribly drained. i've been back home in Malaysia from Perth since mid-October... and it's been hectic after starting work the week after arriving. Since then its been writing, shoots, editing... over and over... in the midst, juggling social life, personal emotions and career. i have to admit, i am one who loves to keep a foot in the door whenever i can. ooportunties that slip past me make me regret and hear in my head the echo of a non-liked ex-lecturer that "Opportunities come only once." is there truth in that? or not? all i know, is that i can bear the thought of saying "no"... and maybe, that just may be what will bring me down... *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      life's getting tougher and tougher even with greener pastures in hand... *sigh* isn't it life's equation that when something good happen, something bad or sad must happen to neutralize the feelings? painful, i know... but it probably can't be helped.  my career is taking a flying start while my relationship is grinding the bottom... *sigh* everytime i try to share my happiness with my friends, and if gary's around... you'll sudenly feel that mooning over of gloom hovering by the side. it's ... it's... frustrating! it's emotionally draining! i'm supposed to be celebrating at the news... instead, i'm trying to recover from stress with more stress! =' ( it makes me want to cry... i mean, yea, aren't i supposed to be celebrating? my first international project! my FIRST international project!!! and i've no one to share it with me... while i was in Perth, i opened and shared a bottle of wine or two and dinner with my group of friends when i found out poetry.com was publishing one of my poems! here, i'm trying to salvage my relationship, while worrying about what's going to happen to it while i'm travelling in and out of the country. why??? *sigghhh*  =' ' ( also, my birthday's coming up... and... yes, the impending gloom. not of being a year older. Hey! i love growing up... it's so much adventure, experience and tons of stories to tell of the past. the only gloom i'm talking about is the feeling of loneliness on that day... everyone's busy with Chinese New Year, or their own thing... or if they do remember, it's all about "ooh, how old are you?" "time to get married" and all that nonsense. =(  i don't want to get married, i'm just getting started with my life! i'm just beginning to enjoy it!!   i always see birthdays as a time to be by myself, or just a celebration with family and or friends, to recollect the past and see the milestones life has brought and what it can bring. unfortunately, it always ends up just another day or a miserable day for me. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      right. if anyone tells me, "you're working on Sunday??" and or "you poor thing", following that statement ... i'll personally burn their brains out for being such narrow-minded, conformists, inconsiderate zombies! of course there are people who work on Sundays! people who probably earn more money and servicing those who're sitting on their asses in front of the idiot box every day... (heh, except for me... who's part of the industry that encourages ppl to sit in front of that idiot box... and i don't make much money) how else would you be watching TV, listening to the radio, going to shopping malls??? some people just don't think. really! they probably only use less than 2% of their brains...  sheesh...  besides, it's a thrill to be working when the masses are not. to be going against the flow of where 'everyone' is going... heheh... what is the thrill of going to work 9-5, 5 or 5 and a half days a week and sitting in the office all day long? i meet more people the more i work, the more i get out, the more i see... regardless of what day it is. =D hey, i'm going to Japan! (yes-yes, it's not going to be the end of it - i am going there in and out for 12 months... heheh...) holidays? i do holidays for work. =P i get holidays in between projects, longer than what most people can get from annual leave, if i want... heheh... and i'm passionate about my work. absolutely! =D la.. la.. lala... laa... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      emotional rollercoasters, sleepless nights, endless worries... and all I can think of now is Japan.  it's been a crazy three months for sure. and crazy is just a mild word to even begin to describe those months! and it all has to end, with Japan.  i can't be in deisbelief anymore as i can only think of how thankful i am to one person. my heartbrokenness, sleepless worries, all swept away by awe... and the feeling of flight and grace. Lord, for the long years i've put you aside in my life, thank you. i don't know where i would be without you, even though i had put you in the back seat of my life. i knew you were there. taking for granted, you. but you've provided so well. so much. so graciously. how can i even begin to speak?  over the impending thoughts of the ending of my three month contract with the present DM2 project, i'd been having sleepless nights, wondering where i would be a month from then. what would my future be like? will i be shifting careers? will i be jobless for a period of time? how will i help my family, my brother study? a self-less sacrifice to give to my bro what i can, what i have. only to wonder and worry. i told Him, once and for all, take these worries away please... it torments me so much not knowing where i will lay my head tomorrow. take care of my tomorrow, Lord, please. and indeed He did.  early in the week, Ken msgs me to tell me to submit my resume for the long awaited channel v job. i finally feel a little more secure. then, Jeremiah calls... he needs a scriptwriter. the project with Discovery is given the green light. the travel show to Japan.  i'm going to Japan. in and out for 12 months. I'M GOING TO JAPAN!!! *grin* okay, scriptwriter... finally, a job in English! heheh... and that's not all. i just found out i am also the director for the second camera unit now! and He gives in abundance!  this is unbelievable! a few weeks ago i was kicking myself for being a lousy director... and now.... now...  and ringing in my ears, is Jeremiah's words "you're only as good as your next job... not your past jobs." words to think about. words to thank God for.  i feel like it's all a dream, and that the reality would probably sink in the moment i'm on Japan soil... i mean, realistically, i've seen things in planning that never takes off. but do i need to be so cynical? after the trust and giving i've given to Him?  first things first, finish DM2, take a breather... then swallow the reality of "Japan's freaky festivals"... and i mean, freaky! 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      still bored. but happy now. i started a blog for the Jing gang... http://jing_gang.blogspot.com and didn't expect those guys to join it so soon! but imagine the smile on my face when i saw postings from Adelyne, Yuh Meei and Elaine! =)
     
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      heheheh... i'm soooo bored! i got to work after draggin myself out of bed on a miserable monday morning... only to find out the NLEditing starts at 6pm tonite!!! =/ miserable... miserable! and i'll be working the night shift from today till the end of the month.  gawd! i can't wait when my contract's done. i'm so restless and miserable here its crazy. even tempted to take a career change! lol... see how lah.  even want to go on a short holiday break around the 1st or 2nd of February with Tania. mebbe off to the East Coast or something. mmm... 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      oi... taik ayam, you're not getting younger either! =P btw, if you're crankcase... you don't update your blog as much anymore... *nyeh*
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yea... Gary got me another book - this one a biography of David E. Kelly... damn interesting book! inspiring as well. now-now, i'm no groupie or some mad fanatic... but the fact that he's a model for someone like me who would be moving her career up the production ladder in terms of creating and writing shows... isn't that a good thing to do? =D  let me get back to reading about the "Man behind Ally McBeal"... where was i... oh, yea... he was earning $19k per episode in L.A. Law... damn... . .
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      aaaarghh... *blur*rubs eyes* i don't know why, but this sleeping at 4 or 5am and waking at 10am is murdering me... i'm surprised i don't even have eyebags or look like a close relation to the panda. =/ thank gawd anyways. hmm...  been catching up with some of my ol friends over the last few weeks, if not making new ones. had that little high school graduating class of 96 gathering just after Christmas. it was rather intimidating at first cos of the news that the last gathering had some of em exchanging name cards, asking how much you earned, what car you drove... mmm... that didn't quite happen to the same scale as this one. rather, cliques were harder to overcome. but it was cool seeing Julia, Elaine, Kai Ling and Adelyne. =) miss having Yuh Meei around as well... i wonder if we could start a weblog for the ol' jing gang... hmm.. another idea!  also, Sharon's back for hols and helping me out with the scriptwriting for the show... just that can't spend much quality time with her while she sits at a nice cool Starbucks outlet to beat the Malaysian humidity... =/  then there's Tania - good ol friend and godsister of mine whom used to inspire me with her eccentricities. *sigh*sentimental feeling all over* that woman got a lovely darling cocker spaniel for her belated 21st bday! aaaaaaaaa... Monty is such an absolute darling!!! i can't wait to get a proper house so i can buy myself a cocker spaniel...  hahah... i digressed from talking about Tania to talking about her pet cocker, Monty! lol.. you can see how much i love her! (sorry-lah Tania... i didn't mean it thAAT wayyy...) just hanging out with some of my ol friends makes me feel like i'm 16 again. not that i've ever felt a day over 16 since then.. hahah.. well... erm... actually... i began to feel age approaching when it hit me - it's exactly a month till my 23rd birthday! omg!  =/   bleh... why hide my age?! i'm not like those women. don't intend to be - in a lot of ways - as long as i can help it... hellllppp!!! hahah... HAHAHAHAHAHAHHA*gag*choke*... bleh...  here's a snippet of inspiration n reason: "I refuse as I age, to deny my years. When asked at 30, I'll be 30. When the question comes up at 45, I'll take 45. For what year should I subract? The one in which my son or daughter was born? Or the year I first fell in love? How about the one less favourable? Like the year I came down with pneumonia. Or one of those grief-filled years spent saying goodbye to someone close? Maybe I could choose the seemingly insignificant. That year I saw a falling star? Or the one spent not enthralled with life, just content with it? No, I'll keep them all, the good years, the bad and the not so memorable. To deny one would be to deny myself. Because added up, they are my life." ~Sheila Cabrera 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      that was a surprise... thanks, Inflicted, for letting me know someone's reading this. =) now that makes me feel a little more conscious of myself. heheh...  today's been quiet. couldn't sleep last night until 6am - so i spent the time doing some work. this afternoon, i wanted to go over and check out some of the houses in development. I asked Gary to accompany me, but as usual he was late. so i took my dad's car and drove down to Puchong. it's frustrating to know that your own boyfriend can't be reliable when it comes to time. he just has this relaxed attitude to everything and it drives me out of my wits. of course, that probably falls back to how provided for he is by his family background... he just doesn't know... *sigh*  i feel so liberated whenever i'm behind the wheel. like there's this feeling of flying - that i can do everything and anything i want. but of course, right here that can change once you get some stupid driver cutting your 3 ft distance from the car in front of you!  i'm just feeling a little bit better today. just needed some space for myself. and from work - i've been so unmotivated to even get up and go to work these days, it's just sad... i need to re-fuel on motivation again... how? and with what?
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      my life is just so miserable right now... being a director understudy is tough when i keep kicking myself... i can't seem to do anything right! (or sufficient in this case) i can't direct, i can't edit - my coordination seems off the mark. hmm... maybe unpolished? heh... i'm so damn bloody useless!!! oh, ya... and my BM is scum! why do i have to be so insufficient with that miserable Malay language. a language we've been *force fed* in school for so many damn years, and it's still scum... *sigh* i couldn't feel so damn low right now... because there's so much more to add to the pessimism... *sigh*  the past two months have been hell for me. why do i feel like things can't get any better? i'm so demotivated, disillusioned, pesimistic, angry, irritable... i haven't slept more than 4 hours the past 3 weeks. i can't do my work properly... *argh*sigh*moan* and the next person who tells me i'm not the only person in the world with problems, i'll smack him in the kisser! or i could use Ally's response and say, "because they're MY problems!" (-that's why she makes them such a big deal, to those uninitiated to McBealisms...)  ='(  i want to take a whole month off once my contract ends. but then again, that would mean 28 days of being a bum - spending $, wasting 'precious' time and being nagged by my *tiresome* mother who can't stop bringing up her stupid dreams of moving to America or any other stupid white-men infested country! as if i didn't have enough problems of my own, i'd have to deal with such xenocentrism! if she mentions America one more time, i'll... i'll... scream!!! i don't care if she hits me back... i'm so sick and tired of this!   maybe i'm being too pragmatic, but isn't being in control of what you have at reach now the stepping stones to reach for the skies? or is that just one of my illusions? i get more depressed when i see and hear stories of younger people doing so much more wonderful things and talented things with their lives... why can't i be like that? or am i missing a piece of the picture?  on the other hand, i can't forget what JinHo's idea/words about moving up the career ladder too fast... we're still young. it's too early to move up and out (of the country, to seemingly greener pastures). there's still so much more to learn.  i like that thought. but it's only a pacifier to me now. maybe i've grown too materialistic, or just let down my guard with all the principles and naive ideals i had. irregardless, i'm definitely a different person than i was 8 years ago... strangely, some people don't change y'know...  can't i just hide out in some small god-forsaken town peacefully, away from the murmurs and bustle of the zippy city life? can't... as wishful thinking as that is, i've no $. Ha ha ha... *wicked laugh*  mmm... does anyone really read this??
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *giggle* what a laugh... i figured that most men are little boys, but i never thought i'd see two of them so squemish! lol! my mum got back from Manila last night and brought home a dozen of the infamous "balut" - which is a Filipino delicacy of a chicken or duck egg boiled after its been 80% formed inside the egg. heheheh... sounds disgusting huh? anyway, i got Gary to eat one last nite. and man, was he speechless and squirmy!!! LoL! he said it tastes like essence of chicken, which he doesn't like! then, today i brought one to work to give Ken. he was practically holding it away from himself the moment i told him what it was! and yes, he was pretty squirmish as well... hahah... i was so bemused at his reaction! i wonder if he's going to take it home and eat it... heh... i know after eating one without looking (the more you look the more you're disgusted), Gary got my dad to show him the parts of the formed duck...  hahahaha... some fun! and insane! i thought the Chinese would eat anything?! insects, frogs, dogs... and they wouldn't even eat a duck in an egg!!! hahahahahah....
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the New Year's arrived... and it feels just like another day. frustrating day... or so it seems. can i blame my pessimism on the leaky pipes belonging to my neighbours? it flooded my house since Saturday and FINALLY stopped today! only after I sent to their doorstep a lil flyer "requesting" the neighbours to do something about it. the management is just so useless... went there ad all the excuse they could give was they're collecting the entry sticker money!!! wat the **!?!? they should be called money collection office and not management office... *bah*  *sigh* i can't remember a moment in time where i felt happy ever since i got back from Perth. =(  i don't know why everything about people here agitates me so much. i've only been gone for 4 short months. so why am i suddenly so annoyed at every inconsiderations that people's attitudes are like here... =(  the driving, the cutting of lines, the hassles, the stares.... *arggggghhh*  sadly, this simple agitation has even affected my relationship with Gary. the poor bloke. if i were him, i'd be history by now. *sigh* but he gave me my late Christmas pressie today... or a "New Year" pressie he says, and it's this book about Ally McBeal the series. even has an interview section with David E. Kelly... really inspiring! i've read through half the book already... it's really inspired me to keep developing that series i've had in my mind since Aug last year... staring at the book made me realise again, how much Gary loves me... *sigh* all fuzzy now.... it's not the book. it's the thought and feelings that came with the book. he knew what i liked, loved and needed...  amidst frustrations, boiling tempers, screaming and crying bouts... after the rain, you'll know who's really there for you... 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      him/her: hahahah... it definitely gave me more space from Gary! i think i bloody well owe him an apology for yesterday's harsh SMS!!! thinking that it was him writing that guestbook entry made me call him an annoying, childish, hypocrite and not to call me anymore! ooops... *sigh* the mistakes made by being clouded in anger...  anyhoo... with that in mind, i need to really sort out my feelings. i really still care and love Gary because i'm the sort of person who never forgets each relationship for making me who i am. i treasure them all despite its bitterness and otherwise. i do feel guilty for the things that has happened in the past. the things that may have cause the relationship to take a slide down the gutter and destroy Gary's self-esteem. *sigh* but Fairul is right, i can only try to rebuild that trust, but it's Gary who has to do the rest. i was just too drained. but i am still guilty for it.  i'm also afraid of being on a rebound. maybe my dating others makes Gary think it's all alright on my part. but that's just how i'm distracting myself. i am moving on. and he needs to do that too. i only fear whom i may trample upon those hearts nearby... i wear my heart on my sleeve. and being set into society as a singleton may not be a good thing for me and the other person... i mean, that's how i used to see it and the reason why i was in such committed relationships. i really fear rejection, i fear my heart being used. i fear fake emotions and feelings. i fear being led. hence, i hid in the comfort of the one i fell in love with.  there is already a named "rebound boy" (that was by Tania's christening =P ). and i'm questioning myself for all the things i had fought for... the non-committal relationship cries, the need for freedom and independance for myself. it's strange how as soon as i leave and close a door, i turn around and bump into someone...  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "Would you be happier if you were someone together  Would the sun shine brighter if you played a bigger part  Would you be wonderful if it wasn't for the weather  You're gonna be just fine."  ~Would you be happier, The Corrs  am feeling rather 'glowy' today.  the rain pattering outside couldn't help more with this light feeling. my spontaneous side wants to run outside and just dance in the rain with songs in my head.  ahh.. an Ally moment... lol. like i say, TV shows are just an amplified (and exaggerated) versions of our fantasies. especially the way David E. Kelley amplifies it... hehe...  =)  *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "him" i apologise about the guestbook thing. i thought Gary had posted it and it made me really mad. *sigh* anger clouded my judgement yesterday.  things are moving a lil by lil everyday. and sometimes it drives me crazy when Gary calls and he says something that either makes me annoyed, angry or frustrated. right now i'm just not sane and reasoning may just be beyond me. it may have been three weeks since the break up, but i've been put into this whirlwind of emotions non-stop. i've at least only made my last post a mere mention with no action. i can't let loneliness eat me. and i won't.   if it's not just about dealing with the after-math of the break-up... i'm beginning to become paranoid about the Japan project. you know when people say "no news, is good news"? well... no news causes me paranoia.  anyway, on to better things. i met up with Wing Meng over the weekend. i love catching up with my ol friends. even part of the conversation we had about the family feud between Melesa's family and mine came up because i had asked Wing Meng before if Ham had mention any reason why she had stopped talking to me. made me realise the qualities of a real friend.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i want to be gone to be swallowed into earth's core,  so i will love and hurt no more.  why can't i be left alone  with this miserable heart  that leads me astray?  leave me alone! let me be...  or else i will hurt  and be hurt until eternity.  for my heart's become  a curse so sure,  of its loneliness  it makes my face azure.  let me cry myself to sleep and in this tears i do weep i shall be hidden in recluse and to the world, i shall be of no use.  i am tired of life's love suffering. time waits, time heals... time makes you suffer it's tumultuous meals. i feel like hiding under my sheets, and let the world pass me by and be forgotten. i wish Gary would give me some time. he's driving me to insanity with so many pressures and questions worse than before! *sigh* i shall only endure the punishment because i asked for it. my actions have done him wrong, hence i shall face the consequences. as for my heart, i wish to be done with it. for even as it cries ill, it causes my mind and body pain in doing what it thinks is right.  i don't want to make any more decisions right now. i thought i've had enough for the past two weeks. i've had second thoughts and become stressed to the core. i shall just hide from the world as though i'm no more...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i started the day stressed. i end the day stressed. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      when life throws you peanuts, throw them back...
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      mmm... thinking of starting my diary again...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      it's been one helluva strange day today. emotions rushing from one end of the spectrum to the other. the day started in detachment as i woke up after 4 hours of sleep to go to for morning Mass to catch Gary's Rite of Elect. yea, despite the break up, i still feel obligated to support him through his journey to his baptism. only God knows my reasons. maybe one that makes me wonder if the break-up was the right thing. i mean, i did pray that Gary would be baptised in the event of marriage looming in the distance. apparently, that didn't quite work out, did it? mmm... dad always said my prayers were always answered. it was a blessing i've had since birth...  came home after Mass, waiting for Tania's call. wanted to have lunch and some girl talk with her. wasn't quite up to going to st. john's with Gary and Colin cos i was quite sleepy and just needed a nice talking with. (i fell asleep waiting for her call.) that happened way later in the afternoon, after a little shopping and browsing and an interesting conversation with her mom... lol... after her mom left, we had a jug of vodka seabreeze at TSB... (no, i'm still not an alcky!) man, was i high... i think i didn't have enough in my tummy to stomach the alcohol... *giggle* anyway, the conversation did me good. talked about the break up, asked Tania how Gary told her abt it (yes, he seemed to be doing the announcements and behaving like nothing happened with me... *sigh* maybe he's trying to get attention or sympathy from others. but frm my friends? =( ), considered going for another island holiday to Redang this time (lol! talk abt being ladies of leisure!) and some whole other stuff...  especially the bits about the kind of guys i tend to attract as compared to hers... hahah... if it was as true as what Rachel and Dawn said (the nite before while at Jessima mamak), that my smile takes the bait, i told Tania i'd consider plastic surgery! lol... can't tell if it's a curse or a blessing that i tend to attract guys who want a long term committment with me... she forbade me to do that so she could at least live a decent (dating) life through me... LoL! like crazy teenagers, Tania whipped out her handphone to call up Jurgen (the German guy we met at Tioman) and pass the phone to me, only to have her call rejected... i then tried on mine, and he picked up! hahaha... conversation didn't last long. it was funny tho. Tania immediately deleted his number from her phonebook! as if we were almost like drunk teenage girls making crank calls... heheh... i must admit, i do feel like i'm living like a teenager (with her own earnings) at this age than when i was actually a teenager.  anyway, i had to rush home and return the car... i was in a high... dizzy... felt like the world was moving under my feet... drove at 110km/h home... plonked onto bed after making a short call to Aqmal... i wonder if i said anything weird... last thing i remembered was recalling Bridget Jones's drunk diary entries...  woke up to phone ringing. dad asking me what i wanted for dinner. lol... i'm pretty sure i said nasi lemak and chicken. you'd think someone drunk at 5pm and waking up with a hangover two hours later would still have her sanity... *giggle* had a 'cold' shower, then dinner which made the acid content of my tummy a lil worse... then when to the doxob mamak thing...  hehe... itinery for the day. it doesn't quite describe the emotional topsy turvy i feel from this morning to right now... but i guess it'll do. because i am rather wordless at the moment. today's been a real breezer of a day to actually stop and think my emotions over. especially after last nite... sometimes, you just have to be careful with what you wish for. especially whenever i tell myself that life's getting a little too boring... mmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      been keeping myself occupied as much as i can lately. yesterday, had lunch with Lorraine, Tsui Ping and Chiu Hsia... then later in the evening played Scrabble at Insomnia with Sharon. Aqmal and his friend, Val dropped over. it's been pretty nice having people around. especially people who wouldn't quite fuss over me just becos of a break up.  mmm... Aqmal's sweet. he made me this CD with happy songs and it really worked. =) i especially love the song "Smile" by Nat King Cole. some of the other songs from the swing era also were effective... my cheeks really hurt after that... lol!  man, what can one do without friend's around?? *sigh*  yesterday, Fairul rang me up just before he boarded his plane back to New Zealand. he told me that while packing that morning, he found the ring that Gary and I had bought him from Kota Bharu last year. he started crying. sentimental bloke. i love him for all he's done for us, and me. he's one dear, dear friend i'll always hold close to my heart. this made me realist that the relationship wasn't just about Gary and me, it was also about the people all around us. this relationship this time seems to have a huge impact on everyone. Gary told me last nite that when he told him mum about the break up, she shed a tear... already missing me. i felt awkward. yet... sad. it's not easy... i don't know if it was fair that he told me that. but it's not going to be easy if he keeps calling me everyday either. *sigh* i just wish he would give me my space... this is the reason why i asked for the split after all.... *sigh*  anyhoo... i really can't wait to start production work. i'm really looking forward to it a whole lot. it would get me back into the swing of things. meantime, i had been drilling myself to start my research... hahah... yes-yes, no more procrastinating!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      today, Valentine's Day... i dedicate to John Keats (1795-1821), poet of the Romantic period who couldn't have been more inspiring on such a day for lovers. not just the exclusive kind, but one for lovers of life, lovers of nature, lovers of the earth. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ever feel like when you've got something you've been pining for a long time now... like you suddenly think that maybe you didn't deserve it or you're unsure it's what you've really wanted/needed? i'm in that state right now. a singleton. and unsure of it. mmm...  maybe i'm just feeling different. a little more free - or too free, that time creeps up on you when you've suddenly had too much time. i won't brood over this. i can't afford to let my guard down or my self-esteem. i shall look forward to each new waking day (afternoon) and smile, thinking that what i do is for myself and my family.  and better still, concentrate on enjoying and building my career. what else could be so wonderful? i am after all, picking myself up and mixing around with a whole lot of friends again. that sense of camaderie never left me. i love to be surounded by people. people who are different and always keeps me on my toes. yes, i get bored easily. and there's nothing i like best than surprises and the unpredictable.  years ago, that wouldn't have been me. i would've always dreamed of knowing, of being able to control my present and future. now, i've learnt to live by the day. it is pretty exciting. =) exhillarating and adrenalin pumping.  "A thing of beauty is a joy for ever:  Its loveliness increases; it will never Pass into nothingness; but still will keep A bower quiet for us, and a sleep Full of sweet dreams, and health, and quiet breathing." ~Endymion, John Keats
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      an after thought. is it bad luck not to have a bday cake on one's bday? lol... not that i'm superstitious... mmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i want a non-committal relationship. *sigh* i'm so emotionally drained from all this relationship-thingymajig that it spoils everything - mood, life, self-esteem, and good things that come. how can one live normally when one pulls you down? i really cannot take this. i long for singlehood. singletons, hurrah...  *sigh*frus*sigh*  after dinner with my family and Gary, i spent the later half day/nite of my birthday with Julia and Elaine at Nouvo for what was supposed to be a girl's night out. i had fun. clean fun. but deep inside feeling bad for bailing on Fairul and Gary. can't i choose how i want to spend my brithday? i want to run my life my way. i already have my parents to nag and harass me, i don't need another person doing that to me. life is for living, not sitting down and moping.  i'm glad to smile and think of the day that didn't end in an argument or a quiet cry in my bedroom.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      no, L... one does not *need* alcohol to have fun! =P i had my share of a drambuie, margarita and a malibu at Tioman - but i don't believe in relying on alcohol for fun! i believe the best recipe is good friends and an open mind. =) besides, Night Train was *last year's* highlight.. heheh...  feeling rather melancholic right now... i'm 23 today and don't feel a day over 20! the age factor is just the lovely number of years i've grown up with experiences and stories to tell. had a luncheon this afternoon with Ken (si fu), Wai Jhee, Carol n' Phoena (the work ppl) as a little 'b'day bash' cum end-of-work do this afternoon. twas rather cordial... just wondering about tomorrow, which will probably be just another day. hehehe... i can only imagine a nice lil surprise party one birthday in my life... one with a roomful of helium-filled balloons with streamers tied to them, and a group of friends whom i could just have good clean fun with! but it'll naught happen, esp since i described it here! =P lame rite? ehehehe...  i just got back from a lil dinner and pool game with Elaine and Julia (Adelyne was with us for dinner). it's cool being able to catch up with old friends you've only last shared stuff when you were 15... =)  ah... and Monty! Gary's been dog-sitting Monty for about more than 24 hrs now. and man, is that little adorable thing more than a handful! hehehe... it's pee-pee or poo-poo here and there... hehehe... but he never fails to soften you with his puppy dog face. he's really a handsome dog! Gary n I brought him along to dinner to meet Julia and Elaine... he behaved so well! just lay there quietly on Gary's or Julia's lap. of course, after that he didn't want to walk anymore... spoilt. heheh... i finally taught him how to climb and descend stairs. he's a little bit of a chicken, but he's getting it. he hasn't learnt to jump yet, so Gary's dog Cutie is safe when she jumps on the couch or bed away from Monty. i think by the end of the dog-sitting period, he'd be climbing all over the place at Tania's! hehehe...  y'know, the last day of the Tioman trip i woke up having very unusual dreams. one had Gary in it which i could vaguely recall what happened. another had my first bf in it. later when i got home to nap, i then had another dream. this time of a long standing crush i had when i was 12. =/ i was so puzzled why i was having dreams of guys in my life... mmm...  anyway, the week's turned out good. relaxed. and in a certain melancholic kind of way. and i'm hoping it's not because i'm reading "Bridget Jones - The Edge of Reason" hurrah, Singletons! =P
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ah yes... post holiday blues. =) just got back from a lovely island holiday at Tioman this afternoon... and now i am a nice reddish brown. *grin* went snorkelling, trudging down the beach, lazing by the resort's pool, dipping, sunning and just enjoying the spoils of a holiday - away from civilization.  yes, am feeling slow and easy from the refreshing rest and relaxation over the last three days.  Tania was lovely company and it was good to have a "just girls holiday." something which just might be the first of many for me. =) hopefully we can make one every year - even after either of us are "smug married" - whenever that would be...  the snorkelling was terribly interesting. =) first time for me. the 30 minute boat ride to Coral Island was worth the bumps and splashing of salt water... clear, CLEAR azure waters and a really WHITE sandy beach!!! *sigh* and the corals - or what i got to see, were amazing. at first, couldn't get the hang of the flippers - corals and sand got in between my feet and flippers, then hated the bobing feeling of the life vest. so took 'em out, and was insistent that i learnt it myself to enjoy this opportunity. the breathing thru the mouth piece wasn't easy either, but i couldn't do without that can i? =P i still can't relax float well, but it was good enough, before i started feeling claustraphobic. hahah...  the next snorkelling location was the interesting colourful marine park. =) all the fishes near the jetty area by the local authorities. Tania got mistaken as food by one of them. and i kept snorting and drinking saltwater! didn't figure that my tube was facing the water... *doh* anyway, pretty fishies - colourful ones... like a rainbow. but not as pretty as the next location.  Renggis Island. A teeny island off the coast of the resort. Lovely corals. saw see urchins, blue fishes (you can see that i'm not so familiar with the names of these creatures) and a lot more pretty corals. Tania saw a puffer fish... heheh... nothing happened. thank God. =)  the holiday was wonderful. perfect, i would say. no hiccups. the chalet was... unexpectedly good! it was like a hotel room! man, no wonder Berjaya is so expensive during peak season. but we're pretty fortunate to go there during off peak on a cheap (but extremely reasonable!) package. and the off peak season was the best time for me. needed that away from crowd atmostphere.  *sigh* post holiday blues. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa... adrenalin's still pumping! just got back from ... erm, hard to say where. all i know is that i left the house at 2pm and came back half an hour ago, after driving around almost aimlessly just trying to avoid the jams. =/ left and headed to the bank in SeaPark... took me 1 hour and 30 mins to get to another bank in D'sara Utama...cos i kept turning around and going round and round to avoid the traffic. then, finally got to the second bank 3 minutes before closing!  geez, if i'm not sitting in the office running around... i'm sitting in the car driving around! go figure... and after all that, i can't wait to get my own car... =P  yesterday was terribly insane! got to office at 10am - voice over dubbing till 2pm, script preparations, transcribing and translating, video capturting right till 8pm without a break! i didn't even have time to have lunch. =( then after that, Gary brough over McD's... gobbled it up - while finishing the last 10 minutes of video capturing-  then went downstairs to the editing room to sort out things with Desmond... finally left the office at 10.30pm... got home at 10.50, washed up and just slept...  didn't wake til 12.30pm today. and then... i forgot about lunch with Sagau. *doinks* no harm done. had to go to the bank anyway, so when dad got home, i took the car out...  i thought i'd be sitting at home, relaxing from all the stress the past 3 months working on DM2. but noo... i'm still running around. =/ mebbe i can take the long awaited breather when i leave for Tioman on Sunday, eh? lol... we'll see! i suddenly think, for all the adrenalin and stress... 3 days and 2 nights are not enough for me to unwind. i can't even turn my brain off for a second cos i'm already thinking of what needs to be done for the Japan project!  =!  hmm... i wonder what to do tonite... my adrenalin won't stop...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      just when i thought everything is all right... and i've recovered and dealt with a past hurt and withholding of feelings... something else has to creep up and remind me that things are not over yet.  last night, i finally opened that lil' black box that Gary gave to me. i don't know why... but i thought i could deal with it after having reconcilled my hurt. maybe i haven't quite. and now, the ring has become a symbolic fixture of my past. a past that could have been my future. i've never been so enthralled by such glitter. i didn't realise until just now what it really represented... all the happy past, the pure and true feelings we had shared... how could all this material thing be so symbolic? *sigh*  i can only stare at it. as beautifully crafted as it is, painstakingly by a jeweller... to make it glitter... because it had once been just a translucent stone...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      making decisions have not been quite easy for me... things in my life seem to be on a standstill for now - careerwise, i mean. sometimes not knowing where you're going to be makes it harder to decide what comes next. or it could just be a catch-22 situation -- make a decision to decide where i'll be.  mmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      went to watch 'Bandits' with Stephen today. can't help myself when i saw his car number plate... 7929!!! *grin*
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the enemy of love is the memory of mind, to remember and to forget of which has been left behind...  doth when i choose, none, if i could... between mind and heart, will i be able to love in part and whole again...  your eyes eats me whole, like it doth devours my soul; no other hath before, been into the core of my heart...   i live again. in words sowing.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* i feel like i'm waking up from a dream. with a lump i my throat, wishing i could cry... but i'm all dried up. inside. i don't want to wake. from this state. what's real -- from the surreal...  "Words are flowing out like endless rain into a paper cup, They slither while they pass, they slip away across the universe Pools of sorrow, waves of joy are drifting through my open mind, Possessing and caressing me."  ~Across the Universe, Beatles 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      a new month. the third month of the year. time seems to be jammed on the accelerator pedal...  life gets more promising, when you're optimistic enough to take heed to it. =) i finally got hold of Jeremiah with little updates on the Japan project. at least i'm not so paranoid now... heheh... but i just can't wait to get started with production. i don't quite want to continue rotting at home for the next month... i'm starting to get a lil squeaky. =P  had quite a bit of fun last nite at the doxob gathering. nothing outrageous, but the usual mingle-social sort of occassion. after that went down to Nouvo... a lil bit more fun... *grin*  i tellya... i must get back to work! all this partying and rotting at home is not going to do me any good! this workaholic is getting restless! heheheheh....
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      feeling docile and submissive isn't exactly a trait i like to be in. being intimidated by someone because of his or her achievements is one thing i can deal with... but in a relationship, it's just... not me. i'm a control freak. but right now, i don't feel like myself. it's nice to feel up there on cloud 9 and having someone there, but having the lack of control over things is bewildering me...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i feel rather detached. strangely. from all feelings. but am conscious of what's happening. bad things have been happening around me... grandmom's going for an operation - mum and bro flew over to Manila today, Gary got into an accident last nite - thank God it wasn't serious and no one got hurt! then there's aqmal's dad's car window which was broken into on Saturday - and my wallet 'violated'. at least i got all my important stuff back... all that among other things...  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      it's beginning to sink in...  mal's leaving for NZ is sinking in and its leaving me with lumps in my throat... would it be easier if i just ignored it and let the days pass? dealing with this impending long distance relationship thing all over again shouldn't be something new for me, but i just think it's unfair... and that's just the irrational me. the rational me says, "well, you got yourself into this in the first place!" brrr... yea... yell over and over how much i want to be a singleton, and a little over a month after 'liberation' i find myself in another relationship. well, i  did  think it was just going to be a rebound thing... but like Sharon would be telling me "Zon, listen to yourself!" heh... yea, i don't think i am the sort of person who could survive with a one off thing... bleh... this absolutely sucks... *sigh* just something i wanted to speak my mind about outside BB.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      gaah... am too busy blogging at bigbrother. its getting too juicy for my own good! hahah... anyways, if you want to know what's happening to me, get your mouse clicking there...  urlLink  http://spymag.gwoink.com/blog.html 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      grrr... blasted headache! been staring at the computer screen too long... 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      man.. what would i give for some chips right now... *sigh* nibbles... i had some sour cream n onion pringles b4 lunch today. but what i really miss most is that huge bag of chips, Thins, i used to have in Perth... *yumm* *crunch*crunch*  the big brother thing seems to be going alrite. i had a bad start with Edo spilling too much unwanted explicit details in just his few articulated words... but who cares?! hahah... anyway, i'm just wondering what it's going to be like by the end of the week when the nominations start. damn... will i walk the walk of shame and get ousted out first? hahahah... am tempted to put back that thread at doxob forum to get some support. but i shall decide otherwise. heh.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      am tired and frustrated. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      okay... maybe it's not so good... today's been quite terrible. waking up in the afternoon, when i was suppose to go down to the bank in the morning with dad abt that bank loan... then go down all the way to work and continue doing some offline editing with Wai Jhee... i'm just out of focus and in a terribly hormonally 'foul' mood today... i don't know what's gotten up my skin, buyt even work seems to get on my nerves. the whole idea of travelling or commuting across town to get to the office irks me... i've got a good paying job, in a line i enjoy, and a wonderful boss/si fu... and yet... i can only feel dissatisfied and grumpy... *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Edo's got me hooked... you won't get enough of me on this big brother blog.  urlLink http://www.bigbrothertwo.cjb.net  also accessible via...  urlLink http://www.spy-magazine.net/  i can't believe that i'm continuing to succumb myself to more Net exposure... heh.  life's been terribly busy - not that i'm complaining... it's gooooood! heh...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i am feeling depressed... agitated... annoyed... upset.... frustrated... sad... and irritable all at once... i always hate this swirl of sudden uncontrollable emotions. i can't seem to ever point out the reason why the attack of emotions is just driving me to seclusion. maybe it's hormonal - i did just have my period cycle end. *sigh* the bane of being a woman...   i actually grew up hating being a girl - for so many reasons that seemed unfair to me. my mom used to drill it in my head that i must do chores "because you're a girl" ... "you can't go out late at night... because you're a girl" ... how's that for shallow? somehow i've the idea ingrained in my head that it's worse off being a girl than a guy. you just have to be ever so extra cautious with what you do, what you wear, who you're with... it infuritates me that we are the "weaker sex" because of that. it's completely tiresome to be fighting off a whole lot of stereotypes just because you don't want to live them. and when you don't - it gets more upsetting. am i in my own world here? or am i creating such illusions in my head? 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      life revolves around normal people... and i'm not normal! =P my credit card application got rejected for the third time... all because i'm not contributing to EPF... *sigh* why-lah?! money also these people don't want! things are pretty inconvenient taking out cash frm the ATM every so often. and making big amount cash purchases are worse. =/ oh well, i guess i just have to look at the better side of things - less bills to pay!   speaking of money, i've also become the "ATM on two feet" at home to my dad and bro... mmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i've had it up to my head in work... and what a better time to have relationship problems than now. how exciting! gah! the stress and the unfocused attention i've been struggling with to juggle the four projects i'm handling, and annoying clients to boot - has just been driving me insane the last two weeks. things have mellowed down a bit now, but i'm swamped with worries and an increasingly hormonal attitude. i can't stop thinking about what's next after my contract ends here, what i need to do to get another job, when i can get down to Manila to visit my grandmom, the financial issues of getting a car, the idea of starting to pay up the house loan... damn... is this what it's like being a grown up? i can't stop putting pressure on myself. i just know i can do better - then of course, there's the unending cycle of insatiable appetites for more...  i'm so driven by my work now, that i think relationships are becoming secondary to me. its like it can't mix anymore. can't strive for a balance.  i had a strange argument with 'mal over the phone last nite. i could barely hold my own. i was tired and drained - like i've been the whole week. and the matter at hand was how i didn't respect his time... he's also been 'hinting' at how we haven't been spending much time together the last week or so... i just don't know what is driving me nuts more, the fact that he knows how stressed i am and is complaining like some annoying deprived old hubby not getting enough of it... or that i feel guilty. one thing is for sure, i cannot stand being in such a submissive position whenever we argue. i knew this relationship was going to be different - different from the times i've dated SNAGs who just gives in to whatever my argument was. so maybe i just can't deal with it. can't deal with someone who's now giving me a taste of my own medicine - the double standards i so freely used to my advantage.  *sigh* i'm a control freak - and i'm losing control of it.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      depression seems to be common for me these days. *sigh* Aqmal's left for New Zealand on Tuesday... and my days suddenly seem empty. things haven't been exactly rosy the last few weeks. my grandmom passed away June 26 and the family had to fly down to Philippines for the funeral. it was the first time all four of us went down together. it really felt like a family reunion with all the relatives to meet and catch up with. but i was just glad that it wasn't a really sad occasion as funerals are expected to be. although, i did feel quite sad for not being able to see her before she left. the last time i saw her was in 1995. been meaning to pay her a visit earlier this year, but never got the chance because of work. *sigh* i think i'm becoming one of those people you love to hate in movies - those characters whose work eats them up they don't even have time for loved ones...  anyway, the funeral was really nice - for use of a better word. i just couldn't get over the fact that there were two coffins lying in church during the funeral Mass. dad joked it was a two for the price of one package... *uhrm* the whole procession from my great grandmom's house to the church was not without incidence. because the village was a fish farm surrounding the river, the river rose to ankle level and people who had to walk had to contend with the black murky river water crossing low level parts of the street. i felt rather bad cos while they had to walk, my family and my uncle's sat in his van to church. we walked anyway to the graveyard after the Mass. and my mom led a Rosary prayer. it was quite a solemn Sunday afternoon. sun up, sky brightly lit, birds in the background and church bells ringing. God couldn't have given my grandmom a better day... i really loved the idea that my grandmom's wish was that all family members wear white instead of black. it was nice to see everyone so nicely dressed up.  i know He's holding her right now in heaven. dad said she's gone to a better place now, and always reminds us that as Christians, death was something that should be celebrated, not mourned. the day we arrived in Manila and was driven to Bulacan by my uncle, we went straight into the house to pay our respects to Nanay. during the supplication prayer session, i wanted Him to show me something. i hadn't been in touch with Him spiritually the last few years, but i just knew He would let me see an assurance of my grandmom's presence. so i just closed my eyes and asked Him to take care of her... then i saw a white light in the background... with my grandmom kneeling in front of Christ. His hands were over her head as in some anointing gesture. i told my dad two days later about the vision... and he said it was the day of the anointing anyway... the third day my grandmom passed on. it was like an affirmation. and i'm glad. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* sometimes i wonder if i'm really being stupid. this whole LDR thing drives me nuts - in the most emotional rollercoaster way. up and down... up and down... up and down... i'm beginning to get nauseatingly sick! and why do it stick to it? someone give me a hammer, pls?  seems quite pathetic being at home right now. ironically, having my own car but having no where to go. well... not yet at least. but that's not the issue here.  you know, i just remembered something. being Merdeka today, hahah... i recall my first break-up was on Merdeka 1997. it wasn't a very good break-up either. i remember we were arguing horribly that day in church. i was with Adrian and some of the other youth committee members were cleaning up the youth room. Adrian and i had already been in this begruding argument the preceeding week, but that day was the last straw. quite a nightmare really. *sigh* so while all the other Malaysians are out there having fun or taking the holiday in stride, here i am all of a sudden in a manic depressive mood about my past relationship. *choke*  *sigh* i hate being alone...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      my life's in a rut right now. don't know what i want to do, don't know what i want. just feeling very agitated and restless with everything. maybe it's my impatience of wanting it all... and eventually, feeling like i've nothing at all. *sigh*  'Mal and I are sort of with an argument or irritated with each other at the moment. i figured i think we're misunderstanding each other as annoyed about something. yesterday, when we saw each other online, i was just too tired to say anything. he on the other hand was just too cranky to say anything as well. we barely said anything nice or sweet. and just went offline. *sigh*  i hate that we're not talking to each other much the last 48 hrs. even the SMS' have dwindled. i really hate long distance relationships with a vengeance. i don't know why i'm going through this... =~(  work's a rut now as well. i started at this new place end July. this production house does quite a bit of work for a local TV station. big name productions - mostly syndicated programmes. good for my resume and experience - but i can't quite stand the office environment. =( working with 7 other girls in a production office is almost hell. not just the PMS-ing, as Dino (one of the two only males in the office) would put it, its also the attitudes and girly talks i cannot stand! all the gossiping and oogling over the male species. argh... these are the juvenile behaviour i so dread to be around with. and these people hardly do or even know their work. i'm begining too see cronism at work here. hey! i'm a workaholic. and i love my work! being around women who constantly come in to the office dreadfully late and just sit on their asses all day to gossip is not exactly the kind of workmates i love to work with! *argh*  i really can't decide what to do right now. i've officially committed myself to a responsible adult when i adopted my first set of wheels early this month! yes, everyone - meet Wendy - the moment i get a pic of her =P she's a wonderfully economical dark grey 1.3 Proton Iswara... that already got me travelling at 1400+ kms in the last three weeks! gawd! i love her... but i'm also beginning to feel the pinch of paying for petrol, and soon enough the installments to owning her =) heh. the idea of having my own car was quite surreal to me the first week. i was like... "what time should i wake up to catch a cab to work tomorrow?- waitaminute.. i've a car!" sometimes while driving, and thinking of where to go and how to get there... i still have to let it sink in that i'm driving my own car!! really... she's swell.  my brother drove Wendy for the first time last nite. gawd... and it wasn't without worries! i was so fretting if he'll drive her well... and imagine the $$ i'd have to fork out if anything goes wrong! daarngit! i'm a responsible adult now... eeesh...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm feeling very quirky-odd today. hearing Mal say "jolly good feel" made me lough out loud hysterically. maybe its from having too much sleep. i couldn't be any more sleepy after being a pig in bed the last two weeks. geezz... so much for re-scheduling my waking hours.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      think i'm just going to be anti-social today. stay at home on a friday nite. hmmm... maybe even finish up with my room - that's beginning to see signs of procrastination.  i went to watch Signs with Hj Syam yesterday. i think the film was alrite. nothing to shout about. just thought the facts about the religion bit were all messed up. *shrug* very unusual for a Hollywood film to be blatantly unresearched. ah well.  i didn't sleep a wink yesterday. after dropping Syam home at Bkt Jalil, i went home straight in autopilot and slept. only to wake at 3am and made a huge tomato, mushroom and cheese omelette. yumm... juicy! stayed up to watch Nickelodeon Jr (for pre-schoolers)... heh. couldn't help thinking of ideas for coming up with some TV shows.  how exciting! @ 
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      alrite, he's got me in tears! i just read Patrick's  urlLink blog  and it's absolutely wonderful news to know baby Angelus is here! CONGRATS you guys! =) mummy and son are doing great. link up to Pat's blog if you just want to know how the young family is doing. =) 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       >  I can't sleep. Just too many things rolling in my head. So I decided to come online. When I switched on ICQ, I had the nicest message from Patrick...  Jethrel(02:20 AM) : angelus and i read your blog. he was on my lap ... angelus and i and edna just wanted to *wave* HIYE AUNTY ZONA! Tee hee ...  I think I feel a tear rolling down.  I've been trying hard to get re-aligned with the rest of the world - in terms of waking hours that is. I've suddenly found so much energy and am in Day Three into Project Room Clean-Up. never thought it would take me this long. i think i'm only 70% done. @  Just thought I'd mention, I'm still jobless - but hanging in there. Couldn't do any better without great friends.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      my days feel empty. and the irony is that i've chose it. i've chosen to be unhappy. but i guess i have to do this for myself. i don't know the reasons, but i've to put my faith in a future i can't see.  i didn't want to get out of bed today. i felt content staring at the ceiling. but i knew i had to go to church. i went with my parents to Mass, first time in almost two months sitting in my dad's car. heh. but the day had seem quiet. in my mind and surroundings. sitting at the back pew, i noticed someone familiar on my far right. it was Adrian Chong and his gf Michelle. later, on the left corner of my eye, i saw Gary. *sigh* i was just hoping Jon wasn't sitting behind me. i think the last thing i wanted right now being surrounded by my past. after Mass, i was hoping to say hi to Adrian, but Michelle seemed to be shuffling him out quickly, so i didn't bother.  everyone seemed to be around this evening, i walked out and saw Adrian Lim. started wondering why i'm suddenly surrounded by old friends. yesterday, talking with James again. then tonite, had dinner with Adrian. drove around a while. and i kept thinking about that hill that Mal and i used to go to watch the stars. the simpler things made me happy with him. i wished things were just like that.  but i know i have to move on. even if my heart was going to be left behind.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      life never gets simpler as you grow older. i'm in another phase of life, standing at a crossroad with a list. where are my priorities? what are my wants? what are my needs?  suddenly the comfort zone that i'm in with my career and relationships are shaken. not because of a dilemma, more so because i'm facing another type of identity crisis - being an adult. *sigh* why do i even need to deal with this? can't i just live every day waking up as it is?  oh, and i overslept this morning. only went to bed at 730am after a long night talking with Mal. i guess it's not resolved. i feel unsettled. but it left me to cancel my bak kut teh lunch date with Sharon and Arboon in Klang.  i just came back from meeting James at Coffee Bean. it's been a long time since we talked. was hesitant even telling him what was going on in my life, but since Sharon left us be - going off to the Oktoberfest (in September?) do in Bangsar with her sis - i couldn't just be talking abt other people with James all nite. it felt almost awkward.  but telling him about Mal and what was bothering me about work left me even more unsettled. so much to think about. *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>21,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i'll never be able to understand how Mal and i can argue for hours - battle it out with words that insult and hurt, philosophize the world's ideals and norms about what our relationship would be, and churn it inside out... and still come out of it stronger.  *sigh*  life is unfair to me right now. why does someone who seem so right, be so wrong all at once? =~(  happy birthday Mal.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      my biological clock is officially upside down again! slept only at 8am yesterday. and now all i see is the length of night. hmmm...  went over to Linus' place earlier. he showed me some of his work - including Demolition Frog. i really envy people like this. those with the drive and motivation to produce work from their own initiatives. its a driving force for me to get off my ass and do things of my own as well. not just working at named places and working on other people's projects. there's just so many things i could do with what i have and the friends around with so much talent. and yet...  having all this free time, i should try to be disciplined and start doing things i like doing like painting, drawing and photography. especially photography - i want to pick that up again and try some black and white photography.  and i was thinking of one of my old ideas of reproducing my poetry in an art film style. talked to Linus about it and he said he would love to help me out. i've just got to run through my stuff and see ones i'd like to bring alive. this is my chance again... instead of claiming just one short docu to my name.  i'm even thinking of clearing out my room (and all that accumulated mess!) and table to make way for a desktop computer. one i can use to do some editing and graphic work... yes, i'm itching with creativity. let's just see how this works out!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      wow. alrite. someone pinch me. i'm absolutely in a daze right now! i just met up with Patrick on ICQ and he just told me the news. his wife is expecting any day now!  Patrick is an old friend from high school. and i remember those early mornings going to school and meeting him at the EPF bus stop. we'd either catch a connecting bus down to school, or at crazy times, walk down the 2km to school. we hadn't spoken in a long time, and last news i heard he was engaged.  thinking of someone my age being married and having a family right now is just overwhelming to me. but at the same time i feel so excited and happy for Patrick and Edna! they're expecting a baby boy, Angelus, any time now. wow! i wish them all the love and graces from God. it's really wonderful news to me. and i'm almost at a lost for words. =D  it feels like after what's happened in the last week, i've learnt and felt the beauty of life and death. can you imagine experiencing so much in just one week?  i really can't wait to meet Angelus, and his mummy Edna, when they come back from Sabah in November. this can't be better news to me! =)
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      went with Sharon to watch xXx at MidValley today. was hesitant to see it cos i was put off by my ex-colleagues drooling over Vin Diesel. @__@ watched it anyway, the way i watch all other films - analyzing it inside out - heh. i liked the CG effects in some of the scenes. and its a film dedicated to the talent and bravado of film stuntmen. watched it wondering if i could ever work on a film...  later, we met up with Sagau (Nick, as we used to call him back in college) at Syed, Bangsar. one of those usual evenings of ex-classmates having a catch-up. talked about Tony's wake, among other things. Sharon wasn't there, cos she was still in KB. so Sagau and i shared with her some silly stories and goss on who's doing what and working where. sitting at Syed in the lower Bangsar area didn't make me feel the slightest bit among pretentiousness. though it was a different atmosphere sitting at a table (like those at Coffee Bean's) by the sidewalk. a wee bit like French sidewalk cafés ala Malaysiana. ^__^  the strangest bit of the evening wasn't sitting there. it was when a robed Caucasian man came up to Sagau and asked for a donation. he said some kind words in Tibetan (or something), then muttered "You have a lovely wife..." i shot a look at Sharon, hoping i misheard him! apparently Sagau didn't realise this cos he was too busy trying to decline. and Sharon was just laughing out loud. i was sitting next to Nick! and it just made me feel all strange... his wife?! but we laughed it out later when we told Nick this amusing mistake.  as if last week wasn't enough -- while at the wake, and we met up with some of my primary sch. classmates, Chow Keat and Andrew refuse to believe me that Sagau wasn't my boyfriend. @__@  and now i'm his wife?! all laughter aside, we went on to other topics. joking about things here and there. when i suddenly realised Sagau was actually flirting with me! i honestly couldn't believe my ears... i took it as a joke, dramatically grabbed Sharon's forearm and asked "am i hearing right?! is he flirting with me??" Sharon played along and asked him if he's had a long time crush on me or something. he laughed and asked how she could ask him that?! and that she should call him later to ask! @__@ man... these guys are my long time friends, and if they're starting to play a mean joke one me... *shrug*  the night's events sort of left me wondering about relationships in your 20s. people who get married - some to their long time sweethearts, or those after a long relationship marrying the next person they meet. is it all about timing? or just that sudden gap feeling that's there when you've just got everything else in life under control? i come home from work sometimes and wonder what other things there are to look forward to. it's really strange, cos i've been so used to being with my boyfriend or surrounded by friends and all kinds of activities. now, though being in an LDR with Mal, it actually feels like i'm single. *sigh* i don't remember feeling like this in my LDR with Gary. i guess maybe i'm all grown up now. and with Mal, i have a mature, rational relationship. and like Sharon said, Mal is my equal.  nevertheless, there's still something about marriage and commitment that gives me the shivers. there's so much i'd love to do and see on my own. Mal says i like being around people, but when it comes to certain things i'm personally passionate about, i tend to do them on my own, or alone. Quite the opposite of what he's like. one of the things i mentioned to him to make him say this was my intention of visiting Europe one day on my own. maybe on a work-holiday programme... who knows, in the next year or two. hmmm... 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        i turn around and stare at the impression on the bed. "where am i?" i ask myself almost absent-mindedly. Train's Drops of Jupiter is playing in the background. the pillows are scattered on the bed, and the sheets are still warm. i see my clothes lying on the floor, but my fleece jacket is hung nicely on the cupboard across the bed.   suddenly i noticed the sound of the tap in the adjoining bathroom is turned off. i hear shuffling, and he walks out. "lazy bones, get out of bed! i can't believe it's 3pm already..."  it's almost surreal just lying here - almost like a scene from a movie.>>
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm feeling utterly cynical today. seems nothing can go right. i've lost my sanity by a thread, and i feel like i could just buy myself a ticket and fly to Auckland to see Mal. that's all i want to do right now.  *sigh* reality pulls me down.  like an iron strapped to my ankle.  i felt relieved when i quit last week. and it was fine for the first few days. but now that i've hit one week and no one has sent me any news of my job applications, i'm about to hit the panic button... i'm beginning to think it was a mistake. *sigh* i prayed about it, and He told me to trust Him. but how long can my nerves take it? its just my human nature taking the worry-path. i asked Mal if i made the right decision leaving. he said, "yea, otherwise you'd find yourself buying a handbang!" there's putting light to the situation. heh. =P  its just the whole $$$ issue that's beginning to eat me up. and you know what?! i'd been rejected 3 times to get a credit card, and finally when my mom agreed to give me a supplementary card and it arrives, so do 2 more cards from the bank that approved my car loan! eessh... now what am i going to do with 3 cards? @_@ and its not helping - the temptation to buy a plane ticket and fly to NZ...  i met up with Damien Tuesday. and he was asking me about the guy i keep talking about in my blog. he wasn't sure if it was the same Green Satria Boy he met. i was so amused when he thought it was someone else. he always seem to have this idea in his head about me being a mistress! =/ geez... 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "chaotic memories, all alone in misery stuck in between, moments of cheers and emotions endeared."  you don't realise how short life is until you've lost someone. especially someone your age. four days ago, i got a phone call from Sagau abt one of our classmates, Tony, who had commited suicide. i was at the supermarket that morning - already unsual for me to be awake at that hour since i quit my job - and was just extremely stunned when he told me what happened. i couldn't believe what i heard. i kept asking Sagau if it was true. if i wasn't some cruel joke. though half of me did wish it was. *sigh* Sagau told me to call Sharon and tell her the news. i couldn't. i went home, and just sat in front of my laptop. i had sms'd Mal what happened, and he met me online. but i just felt totally empty and distracted. it was too surreal to believe...  Tony was my classmate in primary school and later again in college. i wasn't close with him, but some of us from primary school usually had get togethers off and on and i remembered how Tony would tell us where's good to eat. he was a bit of an eccentric in his own way - a health freak and a fashion enthusiast. yea, he was very much in tuned to his feminine side. but he was definitely a cheery soul. and no one could believe he'd taken his own life. =(  i finally called Sharon about an hour after Sagau told me the news. i felt lost trying to tell her the bad news. she didn't believe me either when i told her. kept saying "i don't believe it... i dont believe it..." i teared when she said that. started seeing images Tony back in primary school and college. it was so surreal. i wished it were just a dream.  i went with Sagau to the wake at the PJ Crematorium later that night. met some of my old classmates i hadn't seen in a long while. its always strange how something like this has to happen to catch up with old friends. =( i had found out from Janice how it happened. Tony had been casually telling his parents that something was going to happen September 11th. but no one listened. Monday night, he drove his car to a deserted neighbourhood and plugged up the exhaust, took some sleeping pills. police found him ard midnite. no one could explain why he did it. Janice said Tony was feeling rather depressed the last 3 weeks, but he never said what about. he did ask a friend to help him get a psychiatrist's number. but other than that, he seemed perfectly fine.  *sigh* the things we take for granted. what we see and what we couldn't. do we wait for something bad to happen before we say that we could've done this or that to help. or had i known..? i started contemplating on my own moments of depression and the one time i suddenly had visions of hurting myself about three years ago. i acknowledged God's presence in my life to help me pull through all these moments. and i had wished Tony had that too. made me feel guilty for not being able to help. but what i can do now is pray that God embrace's Tony's soul with Love.  i cannot understand how close death is to me, around me, this year. first it was Jon's dad, just a month before my grandmother's passing. then Tony. i can only ask God to help me understand life's value and appreciate those around me while i live.  Sze Yen, one of my classmates had put up a tribute to Tony. Just if you want to pay it a visit.   urlLink http://members.fortunecity.com/zyenweb/tribute/wongyiewhong.html 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i don't know why i feel so lost. i tend to feel like this when i'm home, online and Mal's not. this sort of space makes me think of the things that we used to do - like watching foreign independent films, blowing bubbles in the apartment lane, sitting at A&W brainstorming ideas or just sitting around in his car and talking about everything. it feels like a gap or a void in waking every day without him. it's just going to work, having lunch, coming home... or seeing friends off and on. doesn't seem like there's anything more to it than that.  Mal sent me a darling teddy bear late last week. he's a scruffy, desolate looking thing. but he's the sort of bear you learn to love. he's grey, has stitches and nice feeling velvety patches all over him. he's adorable. and i agree with Mal that he has quite a bit in common with Benjie. just thinking of Benjie and all he represents makes me smile, cos i know he's not just a bear - and all that i'm thinking about him reminds me of how Mal and i talk about things. *sniffles*
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *blink* sent in my resignation this morning. finally. couldn't make head or tail of my change in demeanour, and coming home almost everyday bitchin about my colleagues doesn't make for good karma. man, why am i even talking like this? so, i got Mal to help me write my resignation letter. i really couldn't do it myself because of all that anger.  anyway, i feel kind of at ease now knowing i can be a free spirit again. and i won't need to mind the over-dose of estrogen everyday. even Dino said the other day that their conversations were getting worse - almost like they were in heat or something. =/ mind the crudeness.  i guess its time to catch up on sleep (heh), update my website and numerous leisure activities that will help me regain the positive psyche. was kinda happy that Mike asked me the other day if i was interested in attending the Life & Love Seminar. i think i need some spiritual uplifting again. it's been a looong while. but there's never a better time to start again.  on the other hand, i'm missing Mal like crazy. *sigh* am beginning to feel that depressive yearning state. almost at a higher state of helplessness. =( we meet each other online, almost every night. but that's just never enough. we even have our lil' virtual dates once in a while, and i think its really sweet! cos we learn a lot about each other that way. i miss him. =(
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      high high high! heheh... on what? being happy! no, my drink didn't get spiked - i only had ONE vodka lime. unbelievable too, cause i thought it was going to take me at least 3 drinks to be dancing on the podium! heh. danced all night through for almost three hours... whoa... the opening act DJ was pretty good, and Tall Paul wasn't so bad either. hmm...  now i'm aching all over... like a workout overdone! my lower back, shoulders, feet, calves.. *moan* and even my butt!!! tsk tsk tsk... it was really a fun night! it was just the four of us - Kai Ling, Elaine, Sharon and I. Julia's back from Switzerland but she's totally jet-lagged! seems like Sharon's a new addition to our group. hahaha.. Kai Ling told her "I'll see you next Friday, okay?!" i rarely mix my friends... collegemates, high school mates. but i guess it's alright when they can all get along well! =)  my ears are abuzzing... i wish i could get a nice relaxing massage right now... *contented sigh* hmmm....
     
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      oof! i'm dehydrated from the hot n humid weather - and from last night's cosmopolitans! tsk tsk... had dinner plans at Lianna's, she invited Lydia n I over. after fetching Lydia and we got to Lianna's - she wasn't there! she forgot about us! yea, it wasn't a very nice thing for her to do to us. but that didn't put a damper on our evening out. Lydia and I went n had dinner on our own then scampered down to Sangria/Nouvo for some drinks and eye candy. heh. but the DJ upstairs for R&B nite was the only eye candy the whole night...  Lydia and I agreed to look up some dance classes to kill time... I told her I saw a few ads in the papers about Latin Dance classes and she said she'd be interested to join me. whoopee!  Mal n I had another argument the previous night... @_@ seems like a once a week quota or something. *shrug* i don't know what got to me, you'd think knowing he's coming back in Dec would make me a happy content lil' girl... i'm too hooked on him. every little word from him seem to determine where my emotions lie. that's not good. i'm not sure if detachment would do me good either. maybe i should just do one of those emotion management thingamajigs... muahahah... on a better note, we did sort it out last night.  gee! i'm going to Atmosphere tonite for Tall Paul. no Bangsar this week! tsk tsk tsk... but suddenly I'm at the Sultan Ismail area two nights in a row... @_@ Going with Sharon, Kai Ling, Elaine, Kee Yau... 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the air is as chilly as her heart, empty and alone; the moon clouded by sight and nothing could feel right.  standing in a sea of rhythms where strings sings melancholy, she wipes the cold tear from her cheeks never again will she feel sorry - for being left alone in clouds of emotions.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      eeck... been playing with a few blog templates. don't like em all. *sigh* i want my laptop! @_@
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Love Song For No One - John Mayer   Staying home alone on a Friday  Flat on the floor looking back  On old love, Or lack thereof  After all the crushes are faded  And all my wishful thinking was wrong  I'm jaded, I hate it  I'm tired of being alone  So hurry up and get here  So tired of being alone  So hurry up and get here   Searching all my days just to find you  I'm not sure who I'm looking for  I'll know it, When I see you  Until then, I'll hide in my bedroom  Staying up all night just to write  A love song for no one   I'm tired of being alone  So hurry up and get here  So tired of being alone  So hurry up and get here  I could have met you in a sandbox  I could have passed you on the sidewalk  Could I have missed my chance  And watched you walk away?   I'm tired of being alone  So hurry up and get here  So tired of being alone  So hurry up and get here  You'll be so good  You'll be so good for me
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      [took me almost 4 hours to finish this post...] i just got back from a nice evening with Sharon, and Nick. yea, one of those weeknights at the mamak with friends. =) i like these evenings really. it's usually unplanned - when i'm with Sharon - after sort of a girl's day out, we'd then call Nick to come out after work for his dinner. hehehe..  anyway, finally took my laptop down to Pyramid late this afternoon. took Sharon down with me cos we had plans to have waffles n' ice cream at Gelare. i hadn't expected to end up shopping most the evening! @_@ i have no idea what she did to me. i was just planning to get a book and look for the John Mayer CD... but i ended up spending more than i dreamed! gaaah! she's brought out the monster in me, i swear! telling me that Mal would like this particular top i'm trying out... which i bought. *sigh*  *pops John Mayer CD into CDROM*  after dinner, drove down to Gelare. Nick met us there. and after a nice yummy waffle, we accompanied him to Lotus for dinner. pretty interesting conversation the whole night. Nick asked us some advice about this girl who's "thrown the ball on to his court." lol... never liked giving advice to ppl contemplating a relationship. external 'help' is never good. i myself don't like ppl meddling. it happened to me once before. it didn't turn out so good. i've seen other friends do it, and it always turned sour. Nick was persistent though. and when a friend's in need... i will only be diplomatic. i put myself in the girl's shoes. and i relate to his 'problem' from his p.o.v. as well. his issue was almost similar to mine. only according to Sharon, i don't have much leverage in the issue, cos i'm in too far. this girl he's intending to go out with is Malay, and i had to repeat to him the same thing he told me when i was contemplating on going out with Mal - "If it's going to cause problems between you and your family, it would not be a good thing."  Sharon noticed i kept stirring each time advice was given to Nick. i can't help it. i'm in a very similar position. but i can't tell Nick not to go out with this girl just cos of all the problems i'm going through, cos then i'd be a hyppocrite. i can only share with him what i'm going through, then he has to make his own decisions.  i'm in too deep. it's true. *sigh* i don't know how i see myself getting out of this. it was an issue with my parents. a BIG one. and now they think i've broken up with Mal. his leaving for NZ has only made it easier to hide for now. but now, he's coming back for summer...  call me naive, but i've grown to see people beyond their race or religion. and i understand being in a relationship where the two parties oppose each other strongly in society is just unrealistic. i'm playing with fire. it's a Romeo and Juliet tale come to life. am i stupid? letting myself fall into something i know i strongly will not compromise with? isn't that an irony? that i've compromised myself being in a relationship with Mal, and yet, if things go further i won't compromise everything else? my religion, my family, my beliefs? i've even read through forums online about a Catholic-Muslim marriage, and everything points to the negative. i know Mal isn't talking about marriage, and neither am i. (esp. coming out from a relationship so recent where i nearly married) but with my parents seeing things in the eventualities, i have to keep my feet on the ground and be informed of what consequences i'll face.  i'll lose everything. i'm the loser where this relationship leads to. i live in Malaysia. and that's part of the reality.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      brrr... played literati with Mal just now. the game's becoming all too freaky for the both of us. it's become some kind of oui ja board. almost. i don't know if you can psychoanalyse the words that we put down as part of our sub-conscious, but we're not the ones picking out the letters from the rack. the last game was pretty explicit. hahah... Mal got scared when he saw the letters "Q N Z MEET". he's off to bed now.  and i'm off to watch tee vee... comedy night on Star TV. *wink*
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm beginning to enjoy this time off. heh. not so stressed about things anymore. had a nice talk with dad last night. i guess most of my money worries were caused by all the expectations from them. and i kinda got that cleared. although, i've never been one to ask them for money. i've always been earning my keeps since i was 14. they give me an allowance but i'd never ask for extra. that, i work it out on my own. so it's kind of odd now, if i'd have to resort to asking them for help. but that's what they're there for. besides, they know where the bulk of my savings have been going to anyway. whatever the case, they're still my FINAL resort.  i called Mal last night/this morning. spoke to him for about an hour and a half. it's actually been more than two months since we last spoke. we talk online almost everyday... but that's different. it kinda put a smile on my face, in quite a long while. =)  i actually feel nice n light. not bogged down. except for my puffy eyes that is. heh. felt like i could've danced in th rain a bit last night. heheheh... i was supposed to wake earlier to go for lunch with Arboon today, but he cancelled cos he was helping a friend make a police report of an accident. his friend's parked car got hit by a lorry. geez.. even parked cars are not safe these days! last month my dad's car was hit on the driver's door while parked in Sg. Wang. the driver didn't even leave a note! grr... i think Malaysian drivers are an inconsiderate lot. it feels like every man to his own! dog eat dog... you know. even a lot of people's attitudes are changing. i just think that we've become a proud lot. not very friendly any more. *sigh* except to white ghosts (kwai lohs). hahah... it's just sad. sometimes i feel like a stranger in my own home, y'know?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      doesn't it make him wonder, why he doesn't hear my voice anymore? doesn't he want to? everything he seems to do these days, just makes me feel more and more distant. i feel like he doesn't care any more. he talks about things like he's so far away. he is, physically. but its further away from thought now. he talks to me like he tip toes around quicksand. i stare at my phone and wish i could pick it up to call him. but my pride tells me otherwise. because i feel like its become one sided. i don't know when i would see him next. i don't know what he's thinking. i have to pry it out - but even then he barely says anything. i think i've lost him. to my own emotions.  he thinks just saying that he loves me, would hurt me more.  he thinks that telling me he wants to see me, would scar me inside.  he thinks that telling me the truth, would draw me away from him.   he thinks. but he doesn't realise.  i'm already being drawn further away, the more he hides.  he doesn't want us to deal with the hurt together. it's not about us anymore.  it's about you and me.  *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Jostein Gaarder is bloody brilliant! i just finished Solitaire Mystery, with a two day interval in between reading the book. call me a hyppocrite, but i have to say that i'd really make a movie out of the book. i was never an advocate of book adaptations really. but with Gaarder's rich visual descriptions, i'm itching to see it produced. itching to visit Greece and Europe at that, and buying more books of his. hmmm... if only i can find my Sophie's World.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm having a very strange conversation with Stephen on MSN right now. about body toxins, poison, cells and keeping em alive. @/@ it all started when i said Sharon's on a carbo diet... hmm...  he showed me a pic of his husky he had while in Michigan. OMG! it's such a darling! check out his darling blue eyes... *sigh* i can't wait till i have my own doggie.      procastination. i still haven't sent my laptop to TechDos. tsk tsk tsk. so i'm surfing on the desktop. *sniffle* i want my data back!!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      crawled back in to bed at 10am. i got too tired from all the fuss with my laptop, and having to retype that article David gave me to re-edit. looks like i've to bring it to the shop tomorrow... all the way to Pyramid.  my handphone woke me up at around 11-ish. it was Ken. usually i'd sleep through it ringing, but this was Ken - my mentor, my si fu! heheheh... he said he got my programmed idea proposals two days ago, and wanted to meet up with me today. yay! i went back to sleep after that.  woke up finally at 3pm, watched a bit of TV before picking up my new specs (yay! back to rims for me... some groovy magenta rims with magnetic clip-on sunnies). then headed down to Double Vision, before i found out it was too late... ahhh... he's gone down to Low Yatt! drove all the way to town and met up with him at the CB there. sat there talking for about 2 hours. there didn't seem to be any hint of work available at the mo'... but talking to him made me feel more motivated about getting down to coming up with more concepts and ideas. =) life as a TV writer.  looks like i'm gonna have to start churning out more stuff to pitch. hmm... where do i find inspiration?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      worse day of my life!!! my laptop crashed on me... the first time in two years. i've no mood for anything else. i've become too attached to that piece of technology. it was an extension of my life.   back to being a paperholic.  *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmm.... what is this? celebrity blogs?  Damien(17:02 PM) :  hey there  chocolate wookie(17:02 PM) :  heyo  Damien(17:03 PM) :  how come i never read bout me in your blogs? me no have the right effect on you hehehehehe - don't add it in now ah  chocolate wookie(17:03 PM) : hahahah.. i can always cut n paste this conversation now.  -------------------------------------  i've no clue why we're not speaking to each other. i just can't stand it, why does my life have to revolve around him?! i've enough things in my life to depress me right now. i won't deal with his protectiveness, his pride, his ego, his brokeness. maybe that's why his ex cheated on him in the first place! i'm not her. i never was. dammit. if he can't tell the difference, he can just as well live with it!  i'm not emo right now. nor am i PMS-ing. i'm well level headed as i'll ever be. dammit!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      One & Alone  Stuttered words, in a universe avast Memories pale in the future, Lovers dream of what is the past Against what is of nature.  Always to be alone Made fated by time's labour, Even those who wish of love Will suffer in life's harbour.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i've decided to bury myself in some books - since Nick says i've too much time to think. bought some yesterday while at Kinokuniya with Sharon. two books on production writing, and Jostein Gaarder's Solitaire Mystery. which reminds me, where the hell is my Sophie's World?! bleh. i think i must've either borrowed it to someone or misplaced it. @/@  spent the evening at KLCC yesterday. i just got bored of MidValley, so decided to drag Sharon along... sat at CB, browsed at Kinokuniya and roamed some interesting stores on the 3rd floor. most of them heritage stores. very stimulating. heheh.. Sharon noted the lower floors seem to be low brow. i agreed, impulse buys are all downstairs - like how they put POS products by the cashier, you don't need to think to spend. the higher u go, the more expensive, you think twice before swiping. heh.  passed the Petronas Art Gallery. it was closed, but passing by brought some reminiscent memories. *sigh* wished Mal was around...  later we had an interesting dinner session at the foodcourt. Nick joined us after work. laughed a bit. he's really quite different to talk to now, then while he was in college. heh... sometimes you'd wish he was still the quiet one. hahah...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      don't feel so good... want to crawl under the sheets. need someone...  
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      just watched Mad About Mambo on HBO. three things, i love the Irish accent in the movie, i love Keri Russell's hair and i always wanted to learn to latin dance. hmmm...  first time i saw Keri on Felicity (while in Perth), i just had to do something like that. i'm a sucker for curls. had curls when i was a baby, but it grew messy after that - thick, wavy hair with a mind of its own.  oh, and the time Javier taught me the merengue... *dream*  and Alex's Irish accent imitation... "Tell me a stoh-ry!"  mmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i think Moby has the most interesting music videos. "In this world" has those cute little 3D animated creatures in it. i noticed most of the productions in my resume revolve around 3D animation. hmmm...  wide awake from 6am. sitting in front of the tv. it's official. couch potato! no, it's not one of those all nighters where i didn't sleep the whole night through. i actually slept too much! yes, Mal, i'm a sleep monster. bleh.  got to to go the bank today and pay my 2nd installment on the car. hmm... then wait for Voon's call before i pop over at View Hunter. just had this strange feeling this morning when i woke up - like something's going to happen today. i wonder.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      dammit... i want a dog. i want a darling male golden cocker spaniel who can love me, cuddle up with me, one i can feed, pet, hug... just for company. *sigh*  dammit... i've been cussing too much.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the tip of my tongue's been having this strange quiver for the last week. like the equivalent to a nervous twitch. i don't know what's wrong with me. @/@ well, at least the pain i've been getting in my left knee is almost gone. if not immune to it...  commentated for Mass this evening. man, why is it the older i am, the more nervous i get in front of crowds? i feel like i've digressed. i used to do this when i was 12! but it felt good, doing something for Him again. its been a long while.  headed down to Charlie's Place for my bro's gig. only i had already missed them playing. met my cuz' Joshua there. bro bailed on me - he told Joshua to stick with me cos my friends were more 'happening'... *rolls eyes* so i practically had to "babysit" him the rest of the evening! blah. cos my bro n his friends decided to up and go to Bangsar. it seemed everyone was going to Bangsar, cos i called Andy up and then we met up at TSB. (geez, i've been going to Bangsar too much the last two weeks!) while layan-ing Joshua, he was just picking on my driving and stuff. a 17 year old picking on me?! i don't get it, why do i get bullied so easily? i'm practically the un-coolest cousin around. i try to be hospitable and this is what i get...?! gah. anyways, sat there with Andy, his bro and friends - just chilled. then Nick came over cos he was in Syed. (yea, EVERYONE seemed to be there) bro bumped into me. i gave him my car keys and said, "Nah, take the car and take Joshua back!" hahah... then went to Dharoos for supper with Nick - cos the fries at TSB sucked! =P  now i'm back home, chatting with Mal online. =)  man, i think i need a snog...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      gawddangit! i hate LDRs - with a passion! *sigh* sat at Echo with kai ling, sharon, elaine and bf kee yau, ben n some others, sipping away on my vodka ribena... just pining. sharon did drag me up to dance. but i didn't last long up there. the dj was good. but i just wasn't up to it. i'm just all yearning and reminiscing... Mal's the one who got me started on all these raves n clubbing. it's weird how while going out with him, the total clubbing i did in two months was the total of my last two years! @/@ i just miss his company, among other things. *sigh*  dammit... i hate having no work, no money. i wish i could just fly there right now and be content being with him. *sniffles* maybe i should just sell the car... almost desperate into loaning some money off ppl. bleh. stupid things. the weeks seem to pass too damn fast for me, weekend after weekend. but i don't even have a day to look forward to. not even his coming back. =(  *sigh*  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      slow day. i think i've slept too much. called voon up this evening. i'm hoping i can get something up by the end of the month. looking at my bank account balance is scaring me.  it's friday again. julia's leaving for switzerland tomorrow. elaine and kai ling called me out for tonite. sharon's coming along. well, it beats staying home. *shrug* especially when your bf's thousands of miles away... *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      =D i'm in a better mood today! just played literati on yahoo games with Mal, and juggled another table. strangest thing, i had the letters MAL on the other table and FREEDOM at the table i played with Mal... hahahah... i wonder if that was a sign!  *dance*dance* la la laa laa la!
     
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *laugh* men are such idiots, but i have to admit there's one idiot who's got me all mushed up about him. =) he's a darling when it comes to bringing my feet down to earth, when it comes to putting light into my dark corners and loving me for who i am. i just wish he wasn't so far away. spending hours online with Mal counts for something, especially when we can be so reasonable despite my bouts of emotions. being like this and almost biting off a lot of my friends' heads off lately, just makes me feel like he's my point of sanity.  he just went off for brekkie. i guess the 5 hour difference between here n NZ contributes to my re-arranged waking hours. @/@ it's worth it. cos there can't be anyone else i would rather spend my time with. so, i think i'll go to bed now with a smile on my face, thinking of the last thing Mal said to me. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      men! they're all the same. they're either snags, buayas or just protein driven idiots!  for one, doxob's become some stupid forum of testosterone overdosed, under-sexed dudes... and it's putting me off! used to like hanging around there for one reason... heh.  i also seem to be surrounded by idiots who won't leave me alone. and it's getting annoying. i used to have like so many cool guy friends to hang around with and talk about so much cool things. now, intellectual stimulation has bypassed me and all they want to do (in Lydia's words) is "make out with me!" =( i've got at least a handful of guys sms-ing or calling me up that i've resorted to avoiding them. *sigh* i hate being mean. i also hate that being a girl in a male-dominated industry, i risk work or better opportunities when these interested males don't get what they want. i work for good intentions. i'm good at my job! i won't succumb to these stupid acts for work! i will survive... la la lala... *dances*  men.. and their puny brains! hah. one of the phone calls i answered just now made a stupid joke about my car having gear problems, he said i don't know how to treat a stick! bah! idiot, if you want to get a girl, don't insult her intelligence.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* i need to learn patience. one thing i lack tremendously. my edginess, short temper and restlessness does not bode well at this moment being in between jobs. i've been too emotional and i need so badly to snap out of it. i just feel like there's no way, that things have become almost impossible. so many should haves and could haves.  got an email about a scriptwriting job i tried to pitch for. didn't get it. oh well, guess that's part and parcel of life as a writer...   everyone i talk to has been telling me to try out something else. maybe a career change... i just don't know. it's not that i'm thoroughly unhappy working in this line. i love it! i just went through a bad patch very recently working at a place with certain kinds of people, that's all. is that a reason to change careers? *shrug* i don't even know what else i can do. and getting pressured by dad into getting a full time job isn't helping either. =( so much pressure, so much expectations i've never had before.  learning. struggling to survive.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i am absolutely, positively unhinged! i felt like i could've been a mad woman, road-bully and murderer let loose on the streets today. very irritable.  i went to collect my cheque at fe2 this afternoon. got Dino to bring it down. didn't want to go up there. @/@ then went with him to Secret Recipe for lunch. it was a rather 'quiet' lunch... barely said much to Dino. strange moments when you're unhinged. got to 'bump' into Vijay ard the Hartamas area. yea... bumping into old friends again.  then met up with Lydia at Coffee Bean Ampang. she just got back from visiting her dad Bintulu. hadn't seen her since she quit fe2 - so exchanged a bit of goss there. it was so strange how my hormone levels seemed balanced at this time. hahah... maybe it was the pure choc (at least, i'd like to think that). the rains didn't help much. other than being a nice weather to sleep. bleh. i got stuck in the jams... what would you expect going home to PJ from Ampang! bleh.  you'd think a person who's so unhinged, easily irritable would be safer at home, under the sheets or something. i guess i was just looking for  something to cheer me up and look for a balance. *sigh* hadn't found it. took a detour before coming home, went to look for some CDs. especially John Mayer - but they were all out of it!!! *wail* so got myself The Corr's In Blue special ed, and happy Ronan Keating... hoping it'll change my mood a lil. hmm...   oh. and i've also started watching pre-sch programmes on Playhouse Disney. @/@ i think my biological clock's coming undone...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      feeling unhinged. very deranged. all that's going thru my head right now is this damn pumpkin eater nursery rhyme... @/@
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i think some people are just born to this life to annoy the hell out of other people. and i don't know why i end up being the annoyed one. i'm grumpy, moody and was in a terribly unusual cussin' mood a while ago. the worse thing is that the height of all annoyance comes from a 15 year old juve. bleh.  yes, PMS-ing and hating it.  been reading Mal's blog, err... live journal, the last few days. after much 'persuasion' into getting the url from him. @-@ i was kinda upset and somewhat disinterested when he eventually gave in from his apprehension. i only read it two days after i had the url. that was friday. reading it rekindled my feelings for him again. i guess you could say, things did get better. strangely, i went into depression again when we got back together. not because it was bad, it's just being in an LDR without knowing when we'll see each other next -- of course, next July's definite =( -- is very painful. i can't go to NZ for $ reasons. being committed to my car, n having no work makes things rather diffucult. then there's my mum going back to Manila in December. *sigh* i'm 23 with burdens as big as the world. well, that's how it feels like anyways. *shrug*  just being stupid right now and wishing there was a definite answer to everything. like, getting married to someone who'd take care of everything for me. hahahahah... *delirious* it's the hormones talking. who am i kidding? i won't get married.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      hahahah... i'm still awake! i've been fuelled and fired into doing some work. if you can call it work - cos i'm enjoying it! ;) i've just completed documenting three TV program concept proposals.  i went for my brother's gig last nite at the Actor's Studio. and sitting there head-banging to the live music just warped me into inspiration capital. i'm always stirred and motivated by music. it's just a matter on what my mood is and what music amplifies or complements it. i went over with Lionel. and he had fun. introduced him to some of my friends as well... since his joining Stone Angelina, he does need to meet more of his peers. =)  also met up with my cousin Joshua (at the gig), whom i only found out this evening that he just came down from Hong Kong.  after sending Joshua and Lionel home, called Peter out for a drink. the rest of the evening just went on with more inspirations. i felt so anti-social and grumpy at the start of the day (or evening, heh) but it's ending quite nicely for me. =) discussed so much about the media/TV industry and stuff with Pete. it gave me a boost to go home and get typing.  of course, when i came home i met up with Mal online. more inspiration. i don't know what i would do without him. he's really my muse. i've never felt more driven in my life.  i guess its a reminder that no matter how many (pessimistic) people there are out there who can drag you down, there are still those you can help you get up. and you choose whom you allow to do that to you.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* bored. got a headache. very anti-social. even after coming back from an evening of socializing. hate ppl right now. bleh. all are sheeps.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      gawddammit... h1yfqy8ryy3woafhf!!! O __ O i just got an email from Peter today.   ...(a whole lot of work talk here)... anyway, our paths will cross again, when you're not too drunk. grin guy, pete   *sigh* was i THAT trashed that night at Elyna's?! =( there goes my track record. dammit.  got dragged out of bed by Mal's persistent sms'. i'm just feeling too damn lousy. don't want to leave the house. damn fridays. *sigh* my room's ceiling is leaking, and the radio's all wet. i think i'm wearing out Sharon's Norah Jones' CD. and i think i'm coming down with something. and at the same time, my tummy's all rumbly.  bleh.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      slept at 9-ish this morning. after i managed to pull thru an all-nighter being drunk and writing a draft script! i think that's the last time i drink so much b4 rushing a deadline.  but Mal kept me company the whole time. even providing a lil' comic relief. *sigh* a darling...  morpheuse: i cant stay up without sleep for dat long anymore... midnite_lily79: u going to nap? morpheuse: did that already in my salad days midnite_lily79: salad? morpheuse: yea..salad... midnite_lily79: u count ur days according to what u eat? midnite_lily79: there's your chocolate days midnite_lily79: your salad days midnite_lily79: your shortlive steak days midnite_lily79:  morpheuse: time of youthful inexperience, innocence, or indiscretion midnite_lily79: heeheh midnite_lily79: cute midnite_lily79: i like that... morpheuse: Salad days frm Antony and Cleopatra: "My salad days,/ When I was green in judgment, cold in blood." midnite_lily79: ooh morpheuse: ooh? midnite_lily79: heh midnite_lily79: *hugs* morpheuse: u mean, u never come across this pharse before? morpheuse: *hugs* morpheuse: u joker morpheuse: *hugs* midnite_lily79: i hadnt read anthony n cleopatra midnite_lily79: joker? why? midnite_lily79: i've got tempest, hamley, comedy of errors, midsummer nights dream, macbeth morpheuse: cos i count my days according to what i eat... midnite_lily79: hamlet midnite_lily79: its cute. midnite_lily79: i like the analogy midnite_lily79: might use it for one of my shows. morpheuse: oh, thought hamley is a new story by him... =P midnite_lily79: heheheheh midnite_lily79: pharse midnite_lily79: hahahahhahahahahahhaha midnite_lily79: the things u can laugh abt with typos morpheuse: yeah...parsimonius midnite_lily79: morpheuse: u mean, u never come across this pharse before? midnite_lily79: no. i think this whole salad thing is a pharse! midnite_lily79: hehehe morpheuse: i think im a farce midnite_lily79: =P morpheuse: oops...pharse midnite_lily79: yea. i agree. midnite_lily79: heheehhehehe midnite_lily79: to pharse or not to pharse morpheuse: quite a pharse morpheuse: ok midnite_lily79: that is the question midnite_lily79: quite a smelly one... midnite_lily79: =P morpheuse: set pharsers to stun, men "aye, aye cap'n" midnite_lily79: ahhaha midnite_lily79: there's no art to find the mind's construction in the pharse morpheuse: use the pharse, luke... midnite_lily79: ROTFLMAO!!!! midnite_lily79: tha's a goood un!! midnite_lily79: ROTFLMAO!!!! morpheuse: glad u liked it... morpheuse: =P   man, it's been cold the last few nights... i feel like ice-cream. @/@
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      got back from the party about almost two hours ago. and i think i'm still a lil high from all that JD coke. the last one i had was pretty potent. didn't seem to see straight. and Trina thought i was flushed. either she couldn't tell i was wearing make-up or something, cos Stephen said i looked fine. heh.  Stephen was my 'date' for the night. i had asked Sagau last week, but he said no. it would be pushing it too much anyway if i did go with Sagau, especially after that wife incident. i asked Stephen pretty last minute - online too! hahah.. saw Lianna on MSN and she asked me if i was going tonite. i did want to go... for some reason. but not alone. so when Stephen msg'd me on Yahoo - hahahah... u'd think i was picking someone out of a hat! lol... i did go through my phonebook tho. =P  but the party wasn't half as bad. heh. maybe cos i know i don't have to go back to the office the next day and listen to all that estrogen chatter. i tell you, these people seem to look like i've given them something to feed on bringing Stephen along. gawd! how much more superficial can they get? Stephen did ask me how come i couldn't go alone. i just couldn't. i could. i know i can. maybe i just need a sanity point. heh. and sitting ard the whole night with Dino, wasn't how i wanted to see myself tonite. not after feeling like i've drank one whisky too many. @/@  talked a bit to Ben - my 'date' in the Anuar Zain music video - after i saw Trina looking at me and mouthing, "come over and say hi." gee... Ben's sweet anyhow. heheheheh... then later had Peter, the guy who edited the last version of the music video chat Stephen and I up. pretty interesting evening overall.  enough for all this social hoo-haa. it's time for me to get to work... gotta rush a draft script for tomorrow. otherwise, its no dough.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Mal nearly messed up my blog yesterday. or maybe it was more my fault. i had tried to use Blogger's FTP... that meant my site "midnite_lily" being taken by someone else. but things are alrite now. i guess i have to thank my stars that it wasn't anyone else.  am going off to Elyna's place for a party now. ex-colleagues and more production people. hmmm... will be back with some more chatter.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i just got back from MidValley - again. seem to be going there at least once a week lately. hmm... the sign of bumming. or "freeelancing" as Andy would say with a laugh.  the most apparent thing with these mall visits is my spending habit. gaah... some retail bug has bitten me, and i think the virus came along with the credit cards! @/@ i actually went to Evita Peroni today and bought myself two clips. both costing more than RM20. these little trinkets are absolute indulgences to me. sinful! i've four of their items now, and the first pelican clip i bought for RM50 like three years ago. i shook my head in disbelief as i muttered to Sharon, "the logic of me! i say i wouldn't spend more than RM100 on a top, but i would spend this much on tiny hair clips!" taking me into an Evita Peroni is my sin haven... heh.  went to watch S1m0ne with Sharon as well. and it's a great movie - entertainment wise and definitely something to think about. i was gasping in disbelief even more when during the credits i read "Simone - as herself"! alrite, so the technology is already there, and this is just an entry into another film revolution on the loose! i had actually thought those shots were by some ambigious actress. apparently Simone is made for the film! and more films to come, i presume. as it is, i'm viewing  urlLink www.realsimone.com  i'm gonna do some more digging about this "vactor" ;) how can i help myself when i've already worked with one myself?  if there's one thing that i'm beginning to hate, it's being nice to people. whoa! don't get me wrong, i'm not done yet. it's the second part that annoys me - people whom i'm nice to who take advantage of it. a terrible lot! *sigh* i don't really like to say no to people, especially if some favours or requests are not beyond my reach, but it gets too damn annoying when some people think they can keep asking and bugging the life out of you! =( i've three such people right now hot on my phone-line. what am i to do? =((
     
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      day three in a cafe - and i already decided to get myself a wireless LAN card! >_  i'm such a geek... last night at Elaine's, i found myself channel surfing the Astro remote alternately with KY. stopped at channel 13 (TechTV) and  urlLink Chris Pirillo  was on - everyone else was like muttering how they think he's weird. all i could do was smile and say how cute he is, how pretty his wife is and mumbled that i read his blog. of course, i don't think anyone understood me. >_ Office  (instead of Three) i was laughing at some of the scenes while thinking of the production aspect (y'know - camera angles, jump cut editing etc). then when Elaine popped in Jennifer Aniston's  urlLink  Good Girl   vcd, everyone was bored to death. i could only see parallels to  urlLink  Catcher in the Rye   and examine the slow film for its story aesthetics. gaah... i'm always out of place! >_  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      HAPPY HAPPY JOY JOY!!! *jumps up and down excitedly* he's coming back two weeks earlier! yay!!!  n_n oops... *peeks around* don't want to attract attention here @ starbucks now. hahahaha.... yea, i'm wi-fi hopping! tsk tsk...  tonite i'm going to Elaine's place. her parents are in Penang for the weekend, so she got Ju & bf, Kee Yau, Kai Ling and i to go over and watch "Three"... brr.. what's with all these chinese horror flicks these days anyway?! looks like KL's my date for the nite - hahaha... don't you just hate it when you're stuck with two couples while watching a horror film? bleh... at least Elaine & Kee Yau's not so bad... i dunno abt Ju's new bf - gonna meet him for the first time tonite. hmmm....
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i wonder how much inspiration a writer can get from sitting at a cafe like this. >_   chocolate wookie(22:49 PM) :   i wonder how much inspiration you can derive from just sitting in such a noisy cafe.   Morpheuse(22:50 PM) :   heaps...i used to have a game i like to play...take a person of the street, study his/her behaviour, and give them a backstory..   chocolate wookie(22:53 PM) :   ahh... like creating a character for the person. hehehhe...   chocolate wookie(22:53 PM) :   i dont think i can do that today.. hung over frm the coffee now... @_@   Morpheuse(22:53 PM) :   yeah..and it works even better with a newspaper...   chocolate wookie(22:53 PM) :   huh?   Morpheuse(22:54 PM) :   HAHAHAHAHA! h/o frm coffee? i'll petition for coffee to be sold under addictive and dangerous substance products act...   Morpheuse(22:55 PM) :   newspaper...u try linking a few stories together...then link that story with a person u just see..=D   chocolate wookie(22:55 PM) :   yea... with coffee, i react just like a drunk person.   Morpheuse(22:55 PM) :   like..a murder here...then a missing briefcase report...and u see a smart dressed men walking with a limp...   chocolate wookie(22:55 PM) :   hahahha.. okay.. link a news headline to the person on the street.   Morpheuse(22:56 PM) :   hahaha..yeah... 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ahh.. bliss! surfing the net with my laptop again... well, maybe not *complete* bliss. i'm not at home. >_ _  anyway... mal and i sort of sorted things out last nite. dunno why i got so steamed to talk to him for two days. he called last nite. and just hearing his voice made me all fuzzy again. heh. hate to admit how i go weak in the knees like that...  Lydia's gone to singapore today -- so no food reviews to tempt you with for the next two weeks. i'm still mad at Sharon. i met with Nick and James last night. and i've got a few projects to keep me busy (and my pocket with enough $, i hope) for the next month. and Wendy's due for her 5000kms check up this week.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i have no idea why it's easier getting mad at him these days.  i hate this!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      dating an alpha male in an LDR is like studying a freaking John Gray relationship course in long distance!!!  urgh! i hate life...  *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      tee-hee-hee... i'm going to be abuzzing with some more writing work the next few weeks. all in the process of pre-pre production. hmm.. just realised learnt there aren't just 3 stages to a production b4 delivery - actually got four-lah! hehe... went to DV today, and i've been handing out some programme treatments around. i feel like i haven't done enough... want to churn out more! O_o all this and no money yet... but i'm still positive. Ken showed my "Open Mic" treatment to Joanna and she liked it. she's asking me to work with her on one of her programmes in dev. at the mo'. then i (finally) got introduced to Carlos (Kopitiam 4's director) and got more opportunities there... hmmm... nothing definite. everything still in discussion stage. but i'm happy! =D  i've been getting pretty interesting advice these two days. yesterday, Ben introduced us (the project Juno team) to Adrian - a Malaysian working as a story editor in Hollywood. got to talking to him about some process of script and ideas and stuff... not very detailed, but boleh-lah. i'll be seeing him again on Wednesday for a team meeting, and he wants to see some of my work. >_ _  also been surrounded by babies all weekend! heh. Angelus on Saturday, then Glen Michael on Sunday. i didn't know about Glen's baptism till Sunday arvo itself. Glen's a family friend's 17-day old son... i didn't even know she gave birth already! the boy was so cute. i couldn't help watching him sleep amidst the noisy dinner hall. really the same overwhelming feeling i felt watching Angel. aiyor... i don't know if its just me and my biological clock or what... >_  i'd skimmed some other blogs over the last few weeks and been wondering... all those sites with so much hits! man, some ppl are just hit crazy! should i? mebbe if i just typed s-e-x... tsk tsk tsk.. no-lar... i like things the way they are. shh...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i just met an angel... >_ _ used  to the world. ah.. but that's another story. babies are little wonders. simple things make them happy or smile, or even fascinate them. Angelus is fascinated by light... and i also adore it when i can watch a baby's attention. they always seem to be watching things and are delighted by it. i believe they're angels playing with them.   i got to catch up a little bit with  Patrick  before his other friends arrived. then got to know his wife Edna as well. =) she's so sweet. such an adorable couple. heheh... amidst Patrick's hyperness!  i'll just stick to the nice things that happened to me today. better to end the day with a smile than a tear.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ugh. i think i'm about to kickstart an unwarranted best friend loyalty struggle. >_  it's like this... Lydia, Sharon and I were supposed to watch Harry Potter today. but Lydia already told me she couldn't make it the night before. so i sms'd Sharon and asked if she could watch it on Sunday arvo, and that i needed to know cos i was going to buy the tickets while i was in KLCC the next day (today). she didn't reply. until late this morning. but her answer wasn't definite, just a "I might have plans with my sister Sunday." okay.. fine... she tried calling her sis, which she couldn't. then later called me and said that Lydia & I should just go ahead. I didn't buy the tickets for some reason. then later in the evening Sharon sms' me "tomorrow's a holiday. tonite lots of places ladies' nite." hrumph. i wasn't in the mood -- thinking about petrol money... drink money... humdrum clubbing again? no thanks. she later asked if Lydia & i were still going to watch Harry Potter on Sunday. i knew where this was leading to. i replied her back "didn't buy tickets." then she asked if we still want to go! ARGH... at that moment, Lydia sms' me and asks what's happening with Sunday's plans... i had to explain it all to her in less than 160 characters... >_ _  @_@ now i know why i hadn't had any female best friends since i was 13, and why i don't mix my friends!!! ugh... what am i going to do?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      bleh... didn't watch Harry Potter tonite. Lydia had to help her mom with a school play. wanted to get tickets for Sunday's show since i was already in KLCC - but plans got a bit messy. *sigh* don't ask. just getting annoyed with Sharon at the mo'...  well, at least lunch at Genki Sushi was good. too good, actually! >_ salmon sluts ! hahah.. those were Lydia's words. first thing we dug into was all the different kinds of salmon servings from the revolving sushi bar. then the manager brought us three dishes recommended by the chef (tempura, a sushi & sashimi set plate and chicken teriyaki) and we ordered another two (udon miso & a japanese satay). gawd! our tiny table was just filled with dishes... and if that wasn't enough, their novel idea of having a tiny hot water tap to refill your own green tea made me unaware how much liquid i was downing! it was interesting too, how they had a tiny bucket filled with their pickled ginger. it helps with the customers not having to keep calling the small busy staff. tsk. and man... was i definitely moaning after being stuffed with their fresh salmon. i'd never had it that fresh at a sushi bar before. they're really good! you should see the line during lunch time! i think i've eaten enough salmon in the last three weeks that i wouldn't have ordinarily been able to afford! hahahah... O_o  i've been thinking of moving to Singapore with Lydia... heh. no, i'm not becoming a lesbian. it's just been at the back of my mind all this while. all the big television production companies are there. and i just thought of it as a goal for me - sort of a platform into international media work. since knowing Lydia's going to try to find work there, i just thought it would be good company. if not competition. >_ _  oh... and while i'm updating this at the cybercafe the last month, Mal's just started helping me get a new blog going on Greymatter. once and when that is up and running, i think i'll keep these entries on blogger as an archive. can't just throw it away on cyberspace. after all, i started blogging so timely on my birthday last year. that should mean something.   hmm... at least now all that webspace would be put to some good use. i hadn't had the time nor chance to work on my website since July! 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm.. i think i feel a little happier... since yesterday. all that running around made me feel a little better - rather than just brooding at home. i had one of those horrid brooding moments monday night. *sigh* yea, me and my "mercurial moods" (Mal's words)... it's not even PMS this time. it was just me when you take the work out of the workaholic! >_  just a few things that gets me in a smile was yesterday's "cute therapy." hahah... since i was in SS2 for dinner with Sharon, i dragged her to the pet shop with me. we saw five adorable cocker spaniels! i wished i could've had them taken out of their cage and cuddled them for a bit. they're so adorable, i tell you! with their short nuzzles, long ears and curly fur... *manja* hadn't done that in a long while. but it helps! =) darn it! i am definitely getting a dog once we move into a house!  hmm... simple pleasures...
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      just done with a VO recording - some banking prompt jobs... its a little money here and there. heh - scraping the bottom. i'm beginning to really feel the life of a freelancer. doing odd jobs here and there. the really odd one for me at the mo' is having to work with my ex, Jon. the complication here is how we had to break up 3 years ago because my mum hates him... @_@ and also how after we broke up, i found out about some of his lies. i met up with Jon yesterday regarding some job briefs that includes writing a 30-min corporate video and doing VO jobs. i'm taking it all with a pinch of salt. and if the work happens, it happens - in a professional stance, of course!  i also saw Adrian yesterday. >_ _  earlier in the afternoon, i went to Melting Pot @ Concord Hotel for another one of those lunch reviews with Lydia. OMG!! we were stuffed like pigs, i tell you! between us we had nasi lemak, Hainanese chicken rice, mixed grill, NZ beef tenderloin, feta cheese salad, szechuan soup, and for dessert a light creamy mousse in an expresso cup, cherry forest cake and peaches & cream pancake/crepe!!! and tomorrow... we're going to a Japanese sushi bar in KLCC... more food! you know, i think it's Lydia's mission to make sure i put on weight... i'm just helping her eat all this! not that i'm complaining. *grin*  yay! also going to watch Harry Potter tomorrow night! yay! 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      *sigh* all this discussion with Mal for his Mass Comm paper tomorrow makes me wish i was still in uni. i get so excited when i get the chance to debate an issue or an idea from a particular school of thought. i guess reading Gaarder's books make me crave that even more... if i was given the opportunity to go back, i'd spend my time studying psychology, philosophy, sociology, more mass media modules and literature - all kinds... American, British, Greek... i want to go back to school...  talking abt Gaarder, i'm reading Maya now... and was just wondering about the part in his book he mentioned about how the western world has made food a commodity. would that mean i could actually live in this world without the need for money? i'd just have to live in some secluded part of the world where i just need to till the land for food. i could actually do away with societal pressure, stress, expectations and the mad herd mentality to feed someone else's greed to survive on a currency... hmm.. there's a thought! how much can a person learn to re-learn and become that tabula rasa that we once were? hmm...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i've been having a number of strange dreams lately. and as much as other people tend to let them pass, not me. it always end up as some sign related to that person in the dream. one of those dreams involved an ex-bf. i hadn't been talking to this particular ex for quite a while, and only met up with him early this month for a drink with another old friend. that was that, didn't think much of it. in the dream, we were in some sort of conversation abt the relationship again. it was strange. cos then, today he sms'd me and asked me about doing some voice-over jobs and scriptwriting. i accepted, of course.  the other dream was probably amplifiying a certain need... hahah.. as a Freudian would interpret!  Mal's on my case for sleeping while in one of our sms chats. *sigh* i only did it once before! and again last night... @_@ but hey, both times i was on medication! its not like i meant to ignore him or anything like that... ableh. as you can see, it's affecting me dearly.  went out with Sharon, Lydia and Lionel Saturday night. this whole clubbing almost every week is getting blase... i'm not complaining for company, it's just the whole thing's becoming tedious... *shrug* or maybe its just me in my usual restlessness and boredom with the all too familiar. ugh.. and Lydia's gone all hyped from my nonchalant admission to Mal's "personality making up for his size"... what was i thinking?? aloud?!! *slaps head* i think i could've been drunk sitting at the mamak that night just going on about Mal being a mere 1 cm shorter than me... oh.. did i just type that? anyway, she's not going to let me see the last of it... >_  have to go watch a movie soon... hadn't done that since "Everybody Famous" with Nick... i've been so confined at home lately that i didn't even realise Harry Potter's out in cinemas already!! argh...  and if that's not bad enough, Seng Kit's gone and confirmed in the doxob thread that it is me in that Anuar Zain music video! >_ 
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      what is this feeling of helplessness running all over me? the lack of control, the inability to hold what is mine, what i want let me be and forget all else.  *sigh*
     
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      went for another food review with Lydia yesterday. yum! Japanese! and more salmon! hahahah.. it must be absolutely sinful to be eating salmon (for FREE) two weeks in a row! we had such a wonderful salmon teriyaki, and a temaki rolled with salmon instead of rice... you wouldn't believe how wonderful the whole meal was! and the japanese straw mushrooms wrapped in beef, the crab miso, huge japanese oysters in chili mayonaise sauce, japanese pancake with green tea ice-cream and pretty little bean desserts. *drool* i'd been to Genji before, and had a wonderful unagi sushi... but i didn't know their other dishes were just as sinful! @_@  
     
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      oh gawd... i got out of bed this afternoon with an sms from Mal saying that there's a very interesting post on doxob today. i asked him what it was... and he said there was a thread about me being in a music video! argh! and i thought no one could recognise me... i mean, who watches NTV7 in the middle of the afternoon?! don't these people have to work or go to college? ableh. i haven't even seen the latest version... i was supposed to get a copy of it off Pete. *shrug* i guess now if i go for any ad castings, i can mention it in my resume! muahah... *choke*   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the cynic is still in the house - tired of life and thinks its a humdrum of nothings. *sigh* i'm in the midst of making a decision about work - my career. and it's quite a pinch. i wish i didn't need to fall in line along with all the drones in life... people who just work till they die, earning cash to buy things they'll only leave behind when they're dead and gone! i'm so tired of it.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      in a less cynical mood... i went food reviewing with Lydia this afternoon. went to this 2 week old place on Jalan Bukit Bintang called Bintang Shack. the place is really nice - they've got this kampung theme going with their deco. its an al-fresco concept with little shacks with tables. there's a seating variety where some tables were low where you could sit on the mats kampung-style as well. the place is nicely tucked with trees surrounding it that you don't realise you're in the city - let alone the Golden Triangle.  the food was mediocre. typical for most middle class targeted restaurants. i liked the Salmon in Banana Leaf i ordered =) it was a nice fusion of Asian and Western. Lydia didn't like the Braised Lamb Shank she had.she liked my salmon! hahah... we also ordered assam laksa and fruit rojak - but that didn't go too well. tasted a wee bit too spicy for an assam laksa... and the rojak, well... i liked that they had pink jambu (guava) it in. that was different. it was too spicy for Lydia. heheh... the half American. we ended with a nice 'homemade' mango ice-cream though. =) Lydia and I both agreed that the shack was a good place to hang out, not to dine. maybe that's why the manager kept trying to promote happy hour! hahah...  she couldn't mention it in her review, cos she's doing it for a friend's Halal (kosher) dining publication... heheh...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the only thing bearing a glimmer of light to my dark shell right now is Fairul having called me today. even if we spoke for a mere 11 mins. gawd, i miss him. he made me remember i have a friend. he seems to be the only one i could always talk to... i wish he wasn't in NZ tho. *sigh*  at least he's coming back for good - on Christmas morning. heh. he said "don't you believe in Santa now?" tsk. yea... two best friends back home from abroad this year. i guess i'm being too cynical.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      bear with me as i blabble like a cynical cow tonite... i'm not feeling exactly on top of the world right now and could just go on with whatever crap that's going on in my head at the mo'... i have no idea what exactly is the matter, all i know is that i've to say this year has been absolutely the most crappiest year i've ever had. it has kind of made me think about what i've been doing all wrong, that futile attempt to actually understand the crap i'm going thru...   i guess i'm putting myself into so much pressure that i'm breaking right now. it's all about work - and the lack of it right now i've had so many good interviews, impressed people and yet NOTHING!!! what the hell is going on?! i don't understand! i keep thinking what i've done wrong, so i won't make the same mistakes. its just annoying the hell out of me... *sigh* just when i get myself calmed and settled... something comes up to throw me into the pits! =(  i just feel terribly alone! and i feel strange how i'm realising things this way... like how come people can be so f**king fake in front of you and just tell you crap, and do nothing later? and how i've no one around who can help me, while i'm always like there for my friends?! i think i've done alot for them. i just don't understand how come i can't get that same shoulder to cry on when i need it?! *sigh* maybe i underestimate all of my friends, and i admit that. and i rarely ever ask for help. it makes them think like i'm strong enough. like i don't need them the way they need me. *sigh* maybe it's just me. maybe i don't say anything... or enough to let people know me. =( i hate how i'm home on a damn friday night... most of my friends are out with their bfs/gfs... most of them have work... i've got no one to turn to... i mean really turn to cos i'm too damn obliging. i don't seem to matter, but others matter to me?? *sigh* i even feel like Mal's bloody useless to me. think he makes all my problems worse. i hate LDRs cos they're bloody f**king pointless at times like these. what's the point of having any relationship where you are there for one another when you can't in a long distance one? i hate LDRs with a passion. just don't ask what the hell i'm doing in one. cos right now - i don't know!!! it's a bloody waste of time. boyfriends - who needs them?! i might as well be single right now. at least i wouldn't have to kill someone for not being there for me!  *sigh*  i just want to crawl into a shell and stay there a while. maybe even build up a stronger wall around me...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm beginning to be too comfortable lazing at home, waking up late that i don't want to work. @_@ tsk tsk tsk... i'm back at the cybercafe again today (amidst all the noise of gamers!!!) trying to get some research done. bleh. client changed some details for the calendar i'm working on. bah! i guess i'll have to decide very soon if i want to go back to production or do more of these little bitty copywriting work. hmmm.... 'elp!
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      gawd, one week without net access at home and i nearly died! i'm surviving tho... @_@ last Saturday, i groggily dragged myself to the living room and dad told me that the desktop had contracted a virus - aaaarggh! no laptop, no desktop... *sigh* worse bit is, after getting the drive reformatted, we had the same problems with the PCMCIA card slot drivers like we did in the beginning. this means waiting for the silly customer service ppl to come and reinstall everything again. they were SUPPOSED to do that today. argh. yes, they have not! so i'm at a cyber cafe right now...  quite a bit happened the last week. including one which i hope means me starting work very very soon. i'm quite 'superstitious' - so i won't tell you what it is until i actually snag it! hahahaha...
     
    
</post>

<date>30,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm no longer here... >_ i've moved.   urlLink http://zona.she.st/blog/ 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      since the year's almost at an end, i've decided to start blogging at a new address. nothing like a headstart to something new and refreshing eh? heheh...  so pay me a visit at my latest  urlLink think.deck ver3  from here on. n_n
     
    
</post>

<date>28,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i found a fortune cookie on the dining table earlier. mum brought it home from the wedding dinner dad & her went to tonite. i didn't resist breaking it open and while munching on the cookie, read the little computer printed paper-- "Life to you is a dashing and bold adventure" with little smiley faces at both ends. >_  i'm driving Mal crazy. he's helping me alot with my new blog site. but i am persistently asking him to change the fonts, the colour, etc... for the header image. i'm just not a happy client. >_  in the meantime, while driving Mal up the wall, i'm procastinating with my own work. Bong wrote me a long email on how i can improve on the two script outlines i've given him. and it looks like i've done quite badly - for my first attempt. >_  i sent Wendy in for her 5000km service today. woke up all lazy, dragged myself out of bed close to 3pm after Mal called me to tell me he doesn't have the car to help fetch me from Glenmarie. bleh. asked dad if he could take me home after sending the car to the service centre and i got a mumbled lecture... whart the?? i can never rely on anyone! i so hate how i can do things for people, but it can't be done for me... it's bad enough dad nearly didn't want me to buy the car. he can even go on about how i have boyfriends to drive me around and my brother takes his car, in a guilty manner.... then finally agreed to the idea i should get my own car! urrrgh!!! he's not so reliable himself! and believe it when i say i'm still left with those stigmas of his unreliability...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      things at  urlLink doxob 's been agitating some of us moderators for a while. especially from one particular character. but i've decided to help Mal loosen up a bit and have a bit of fun in one of the  urlLink threads . with the year's end, lots of things are coming up... y'know, best of 2002 sort of thing... tsk... and they've come up with a mr. doxob contest. so this is what i did...     yea, and i've become his campaign manager... eheheheheh... man, did he laugh when he saw this!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      it's damn humid!! O_o mebbe i should ask for snow, then i can start complaining it's damn ccccold! =P tsk tsk tsk... got stuffed again at Lorraine's. her mum served us so much dessert - chocolate cake, custard, fruit salad, apple crumble, soya jelly, sponge cake, cookies... *burrp* and to think i've still got another dinner tonite...  James, Allen & gf - Felicia, Kenny & his bro - Kevin... were around for lunch @ Lorraine's. it was nice having the old bunch together. well, sort of. one of us - Shirrine is getting married late January. she's got herself an American bloke while studying in Louisiana. so she's having a reception here Jan 25th... its times like these, at this age, when we meet after a long period of time, we'd tend to talk about who's doing what, who's getting married and any kids...? bla bla bla... talk like this that just tells you age is catching up - and blardy fast, too! look! 2003 is next week! >_  it's nice to have Fairul back. although, it's prolly just going to be for a month. he wants to go back to NZ and look for a job. he asked me my thoughts, and i told him it goes both ways -- if he was going back because of his gf Irma, then i hope he thought it out well, cos that isn't good enough a reason (IMHO). i told him about Jerome. after graduation, he stayed on in UK for his gf, and worked at a fish & chips shop for a whole year. he regretted the whole idea when he couldn't find a job and begin his career. it grew to resentment and he was bitter later when he broke up with his gf. the things people do for love... >_  we had our usual drive around town after mamak. only this time, we had Mal in the car and i was driving. it felt nice to have that feeling of letting it all out with someone you could really talk to and not get lectured or judged. even if this time i was just on the listening end. that's one of the things i missed about not having Fairul around. i guess some things can still be the same.  --and that includes my hair! >_ 
    
</post>

<date>25,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      quiet Christmas... with potato salad, a skinny Malaysian turkey and more! >_ . i've already read up to Dec 14th of the book... n_n  Julia's last nite was nice. her dogs, Sweetie & Ebony were quite the hosts, and no doubt Athena - her Scottish Fold cat - was a darling. the food fare was yummy - especially the crispy wan tans, and i had my first turkey with cranberry sauce. although i think i still prefer it with gravy, like dad makes it. n_n not much boozing save for the rum in the punch. but i guess it's saving up space for New Year's eve. hadn't any confirmed plans, but Lionel says he definitely wants to get sloshed! who doesn't? tsk... all i know is, "No Night Train for me, Lionel!!"  Fairul's back!!! going to meet up at SS2 mamak later -- with Gary & Lionel too. Mal's going to meet Fairul for the first time. They've exchanged sms' a few times while in NZ but that was about it. I don't know why i'm so excited about Fairul being back...  tomorrow's back to work - the UTM corp video's been confirmed. got a meeting at 10am at the KL Campus, then it's off to Lorraine's for lunch. James just sms'd me saying she's back from Hong Kong. ooh... then i've dinner at Felicia's (Mal's VHQ colleague)...  now, what's the season without all these food and catching up with friends... n_n
     
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ack... i got my period. right after i got my haircut! >_  anyway, i cut my hair! my long curly locks are gone... no more curly sue. got all jelak (bored) of it. i tend to do that once a year. and its been exactly one year since the perm. now i look like this drawing of me a friend drew 5 years ago.    i went with Mal to 1Utama to supposedly shop for Christmas stuff. it didn't happen. i think i'll just wear something at the back of my cupboard. i'll be at Julia's for dinner tomorrow night before going for midnite mass. just a simple quiet Christmas with family and visiting friends. i guess it's the company that counts.  twas the nite before Christmas... (technically...) Merry Christmas y'all...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      my head hurts.   days are humdrum happening as is -- even as Christmas approaches. how do i get myself into this Christmas spirit? - i'm wunderin again. just thinking i can't get ppl pressies this year makes me sad. i'm really tied-up financially, and digging into mum's resources. i can't go spending her money for pressies. it doesn't make sense. i know i'll return it later, but it's just not me.  i didn't sleep well last nite. i didn't have my little pillow with me. it was drying out after the rain leaked through my room's ceiling... >_  the other thing i don't get is my grumpiness... i hadn't had this month's period yet! >_ and no - i am not preggers...  bleh.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      oh! and just a shoutout - Happy Birthday,  urlLink Patrick ! made quite a boo-boo asking him nonchalantly "what's happening tomorrow (today)?" >_  --just checked out my sitemeter referrals, and saw the strangest things that ppl searched up on google to bump into my page:  urlLink malaysia+klcc+clip+art  ?  urlLink freaky+moving+picture+illusions  ??  urlLink poems+about+pesimistic+guys  ???!  hey... isn't pessimist spelt with a double S? @_@ bleh.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Sandra Bullock  always makes me smile. just watched her in  urlLink ">Two Week's Notice  moments ago. i'm beginning to realise a pattern going on here with her choice of roles. i'm wondering if it's a personal statement of hers with acting in comedies - you know, Miss Congeniality, 28 Days, While you were sleeping... it always seem to start off with a lonely female lead who's rough around the edges, but eventually finds love. hmmm...  don't mind me, i'm just doing a bit of character analysis.  yea, i'm in one of those mercurial moods again. started the day off almost sick and hacking my throat away, grumpy, cynical, fuzzy happy, then finally inspired. all those in just a day. you can only wonder if i'm a manic depressive of sorts.  i can't seem to write anything else right now. the whole myriad of emotions running through me at the moment just by recollecting the day doesn't make me stable enough to tell you anything with sense. so mind my ramblings.  ah... btw, if anyone's interested, i'm actually looking forward to moving my blog to a brand new spot. look out for it - in time for New Year's. urlLink ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      how do you stop from letting what people say affect you? is it natural to want to make people understand you? to let them know what you're really like? what you're really doing? or should we just ignore the careless ramblings of these who don't stop to care? how do you keep from letting these words become personal?
     
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Christmas is less than a week away... and i hadn't done any shopping or sent any cards like i used to. *sigh* this whole Christmas spirit just grows out of you somewhat when you grow up. i remember those years back in high school just preparing for Christmas Nite. those carolling rehearsals, play practices, putting up decors... even putting up the Christmas tree at home hasn't happened anymore in the last five years. i had to suggest to dad to have a nice quiet party with turkey and all that last year. i realise that it isn't just about decor an singing carols, but there's something about being around people who are doing these things that rekindle the spirit in you.  i was with Mal at MidValley yesterday, and a few times this last week... and just watching people go around shopping, and just spending their holidays mulling around made me ask myself why it just doesn't do anything for me. i could just be cynical and laugh at the guy dressed up as an elf (or a funny looking singing dog), and point at a huge purple santa doll. is Christmas a time everyone spend with each other? even if its just taking the family out to the mall?  i had a nice quiet time with Mal just window shopping. went to watch the Brazillian film  urlLink Abril Despedacado  (Behind the Sun). its nice to have company to watch films like that. n_n  and as if that isn't enough, he surprised me with a Christmas present.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      yay! i'm surfing from home now. finally got the antenna fixed. seemed the previous contractor tied up the antenna to the water pipe, and it was unstable. so now i've got signals! woohoo... heheh...  oh.. and i've to finish two scene treatments by tomorrow. psst.. one of them is Kopitiam.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i clinched the  urlLink POSTAM  job! Peter called me yesterday after his meeting with the committee and they like what i had written. so now (as soon as i sign the papers) i'm officially POSTAM's e-newsletter's editor - or something. tsk...  yesterday was an interesting day - had lunch with Arboon,  urlLink Meng Yan ,  urlLink Seng Hau  & Mal, and a nice dinner double date with  urlLink Patrick & Edna . the days are getting busier now that Mal's around, and that i've got work pilling up. Bong's started to push me for scripts already. and todate - he's asked me to comment on five sitcom projects already. @_@ not that i'm complaining. i just feel drained from ideas even before beginning.  ----- it's the year end and i thought i'd lament the bad things that had happened to me this year. all those things just seemed to drown me in depression the last three months. but after Seng Hau posted a thread in  urlLink doxob  for everyone to list their good  urlLink memories  for 2002... i thought it made me feel good. =)  01- had a good birthday  02- holiday in Tioman  03- broke up with bf  04- bought house for parents  05- found new bf - tsk...  06- went to singapore w/ new bf  07- bought new handphone  08- drove to Malacca & saw the most magnificent sunset w/ bf  09- went for Fatboy Slim  10- grandma passed away - went back to Philippines for her funeral  11- best friend came back from Australia  12- bought my first car   13- lost 5kg  14- worked on Who wants to be a Millionaire  15- appeared in a music video - tsk...  16- quit a horrible job  17- drank a lot more  18- partied a lot more   19- made more friends  20- another best friend coming back, frm NZ, on Christmas day  21- becoming baby Angelus' godma  22- got good jobs for next year! (incl. writing for a few sitcoms)  guess life isn't so bad after all - when you look at the glass as half full! ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      spent the whole afternoon at  urlLink Shiroku  working with Pete on the  urlLink POSTAM  e-newsletter. not that i'm tired out. i actually feel like i'm on a roll! heh.   just a moment ago, Wind had asked me to write for him a short expose about someone who slandered Wind at the  urlLink doxob forum . some people just don't have much sense. if you were planning to slander a person because you were affected, then the cause of revenge is understood. but from where i stand, Wind has not done anything to harm this guy. later i found out, this guy is soon to be Wind's web hosting competitor. go figure. the war of words.  Mal's still not back yet. urrgh... he left Penang only at 5pm. and i thought i'd be able to meet up with him for dinner tonite. *sigh* imagine, i'm feeling mad cos he's not here.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      hurr... Mal's still in Penang and won't be back til tomorrow! ho-hum... another night, anticipating another day. *sigh* i don't know what's up with me - and as cliched as its sounds - i think i'm in love all over again. >_ _  Friday night was hillarious. i hadn't met his parents before and neither have they seen me. so we were hoping i'd be able to send him home before they got back from JB. when we got to the traffic light junction just outside his place, he saw his parent's car. i started jumping in my seat that instead of taking the turn, we went straight ahead, as Mal slumped in the passenger seat! hahahah... it sounds really stupid now. anyway, it was obvious now that i couldn't escape anything. but when i drove up the drive way and pulled up the handbrakes, Mal practically leaped out of the car, grabbed his suitcase from the boot and threw them on the porch in a flash! @_@ his mom came out and practically peeked at me sitting in the car. i felt rather rude to just drive off, and just froze sitting there. of course, she went back inside. then he came over and gave me a quick kiss, and i was on my way. heh... you must be wondering why all this cat & mouse. *shrug* all i can say on my part is, its tough getting out of a relationship when you've got parents involved. and on his part, he told me he'd only introduce his girlfriend to his parents if he was sure he'd be marrying her. now tell me that isn't something i want right now? hrrmm?  the weekend was slow and quiet - it was almost agonising. it was just dad and me at home. mom had left for Manila Friday, and bro went to Singapore for  urlLink RHCP . Saturday, i had a bak kut teh dinner with Elaine, KL, Ju & her bf, Pui Wei, Serena, Adelyne, Poh Ching and Pei Lin... the Assuntarian's at a table for 10, which Ju's bf, Sey Chuan quietly paid for. you can imagine the protest all us girls made. this quiet sweet bloke, sitting at one corner of the table, paying for 9 girls? hahah.. i'm not sure if he was delighted at the company, cos he barely made his presence noticed till we asked for the bill. geez... Elaine even tried to threaten him he couldn't join us if he didn't tell us how much the bill was! ahahahah... i left everyone at Coffee Bean 1Utama later that evening, for some rave at Sunway with Sharon, Arboon & Seng Hau - which i shouldn't have gone for. DJ didn't even show up and the place was practically empty!  Sunday, quiet Sunday. i still wasn't in the mood to do much work. but i think the highlights of the day would be Mal saying he has to stay in Penang another night - ableh - and  urlLink Patrick  asking me to be Angelus' godmom! something to be happy and brood about simultaneously. tsk...  it's Monday, (not so) bloody Monday... on a serene sunny evening after the rain.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      the pressure's mounting. @_@  can you hear my heart thumping in anxiety and anticipation?  i just read Bong's reply to my comments to a script. he likes that i've pin-pointed the problem areas. now he wants me and Mai-Ne to work with him to produce "an award-winning script out and ready for production by the end of the month/year." his exact words! omg! pressure! pressure! i'm basking in the attention by someone who could actually be a good script mentor, with the possible idea of having win something. really daunting - but motivating too!  *pause* wow...  i just had dinner with Jeremiah & Jay - regarding the UTM corp video. and gawd am i stuffed! i'm practically a mobile office. moving around where there's a wi-fi hotspot. tsk.. i'm in Austin Chase, BSC - sipping peppermint tea. come to think of it, i've done quite a bit of work the last two weeks alone. hmm... it's definitely blue skies for me ahead. =)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      gawd... domestic disputes in public! @_@ i've no idea what's going on, but this 50+ man is just harrasing this old woman while the couple with them just looks on. i got rather nervous just sitting here...  anyway, i'm feeling so totally out of sync with work! especially without net access at home! i've become so totally dependant on it - its horrible! i'm usually a step ahead of people, now i'm getting people calling me with friendly reminders... =( i need to pick myself up. it's all this relaxation the last 3 months that's got me like this... time to get up and go! go! go! heh... i went to DV yesterday to brainstorm on another sitcom. seems i'm roped in for pre-pro for 4 projects in DV now!! oh-boy... and in a few minutes i've to zip down to BSC for a meeting...  *rush*rush*  *sigh* and speaking of rushing... i'm only getting to see Mal for a mere 3 hours tomorrow when he gets back... his parents are pit-stopping in KL from JB to pick him up and go up to Penang. oh well... then i'll have him again for the next *almost* three months after Monday... =")
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Damien just bumped into me while i'm sitting here at GJ (yea, it's becoming a routine). he hijacked my laptop and said something to Mal that got him upset @_@ but it was temporary. Damien's sweet - like a big brother - when he's not teasing the hell outta me. and this time, i'm not blogging this cos he asked me to. tsk.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      all this looking for rich Tan Sri & Dato entrepreneurs is making me $_$. tsk... i'm working on a list of potential interviewees on this tv program i'm working on with Joanna. it's daunting to think that i'll be taking a camera crew in to intrude on the lives and homes of these Malaysian entrepreneurs... but at the same time exciting and challenging! that's what i love about working in tv production. it's so versatile in terms of its content. you're driven to know more than just master one topic or subject. it's good when you do have a niche in one matter, but imagine the amount you learn on the job. and i don't just mean skills of the trade.  Joanna's practically got me roped in for her project. i've still got to see Bong tomorrow for more. i'm somewhat tied to Double Vision, but i'm not completely committed. tsk.. advantages are more money... they'd work me to the bone for peanuts if i was a full timer! life's grand!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      oh... i'm sitting at Gloria Jeans SS2 today. this time with my own WLAN card. tsk.. got a D-Link at RM230 instead.  welcome to my "office"... heh.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      omg... i'm hyperventilating from being overwhelmed by projects. right now i feel like a scatterbrain. Bong just sms'd me to meet him Wednesday for "other projects" (omg... there's more?), i've to go to Adwise EARLY tomorrow morning to proof the calendar copy once more and do a storyboard script for them, then zoom down to DV to see Joanna on a doco... i'm waiting for Jeremiah to confirm the UTM corp video project, which he just told me once the client gives the budget the greenlight, he'll draw up a contract for RM3k *choke* for me... Peter asked me to handle POSTAM's monthly e-newsletter which i got to do some interviews in the next two days, and he's also asked me to do some research on an expose doco he wants to produce - not to mention two projects already waiting budget approval on his side. not to mention, i've my own show (or two?) lined up in DV waiting for approval...  oh gawd! i've been *almost* jobless since September... then all of a sudden i'm being overwhelmed by projects that don't have a fixed timeline yet. how am i going to go through this? *breathe* i know i can... i've become a one (wo)man show... i tell you, the stuff i mentioned up there aren't all the stuff i'm working on. i've prolly missed out one or two. God help me.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I couldn't resist coming back here. For old times sake. And since my  urlLink present blog's  server's offline. Blogger's got really funky new templates and stuff... So might as well.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been out of commission the last two weeks. First it was an acute gastric attack, then it was the flu. Now it's my miserable blog server and the guy who's hosting it has gone AWOL on me. So I've gotten myself a new server and I'm in the midst of moving whatever archived files I've got.  So if anyone's come back to my good old blogger site, keep  urlLink www.midnitelily.com  in your bookmarks for future references and gripes.  Besides fighting for my general health, I'm quite subdued in the work arena. More so tired and depressed from getting back to work. I guess I've also come to terms with these emotional mood swings as a hormonal problem (read: not PMS). Mal pointed out a poster on depression the other day when I went to the clinic. Might just see if the doc can help...  To be honest, I'm not that keen on being treated with drugs. I just wish there was some other way. But I guess I won't know till I've actually consulted the doc, rite?
     
    
</post>


</Blog>