<Blog>

<date>22,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Yay, I'm just sitting here in the computer lab at JJC trying to think about something interesting to type about.  I was hoping to meet Jimmy here, but he doesn't seem to be around... oh well, I'll just have to give him a call later on or something like that.  Man, I think I'm just gonna go home and miss out on Law class... we're just getting our tests back, and I know that I more or less aced it... it was simply common sense stuff.  Anyway, yeah, I'm leaving... 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Yay, I just ate enough fig newtons to send anyone into insulin shock :) 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, this is just pissing me off.  OK, last night I went to the weekly gay group meeting downtown from 6 to 8.  We had a great time... saw someone I hadn't seen in a while which was cool, and I brought Dance Dance Revolution there (it's a dancing game for the Playstation where you actually have to dance on a floor mat).  Afterwards, we all went to Sara's Place, which is maybe 3 miles from my house.  We got there around 8:30 or so and I called my mother telling her that we were there.  OK, so we all got carried away talking and messing around with Brenn's digital camera and stuff and, well, we were there until around 11:30 believe it or not.. yes, three hours... so when I get home, my mother is sitting on the couch like chain smoking and she totally jumps in my shit.  OK, for christ's sake, people several years younger than me are out there until like 3:00 in the morning getting drunk and stoned and all I do is hang out with some friends somewhere for a few hours.  It's things like this that really piss me off and make me wish I had some way out of here.  I'm skipping math this morning... I want to clean up my room and go through some shit and see what I can throw away... I have too much stuff, and I'm ultimately making my tast of moving out just that much easier. MY GOD!!  I've never mentioned Greg!!!  I just realized that!  Wow, well, lemme tell the world about Greg.  I met him, oh, I think it was Jan. 28th... not sure, I have the theater ticket stub from our first "date" somewhere.  Anyway, Greg... wow, he's so sweet.... probably the sweetest guy I've ever met.  Oh, and he's also the only guy I've ever met that knows how to kiss... OK, my friggin' ex like used to try to lick the back of my throat or something... UGH!  He actually made me gag once and I ran to the bathroom thinking I would throw up... easily the most disgusting thing anyone has ever done to me!  There's another guy I've kissed, and yes, he's into the major tongue stuff too.  Greg, on the other hand, just kisses... like a kiss should be, maybe sometimes with a teensy bit of tongue, and that's OK cuz I even do a teensy bit... just keep the damn thing from going crazy =P.  Seriously, I really enjoy being with him... we don't tend to have a whole ton to talk about, but we really like each other.  We sorta ran into a pothole in things recently, but I hope it's something we can work out.  He doesn't think he's quite ready to get back into a relationship as he's still getting over his ex, but I'll wait as long as I have to for him... he's a rare find in our community (that being the GAY community for those of you without a clue).  I really see a potential for something great with him, but hell, even if we stay friends, that's great... I need friends like him cuz everyone else seems to be ditching me lately. Oh yeah, I filed my fingernails... yay................. and I'm sore from too much Dance Dance Revolution last night........... but I kicked everyone's asses!  WOOT! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I don't really feel like typing a lot today.  I had my first day at Subway and did paperwork... not bad... tomorrow's my first real work day.  I think I'll like it OK.  I got a program for my crappy laptop (it's a Compaq Contura Aero 4/33c... 486/33 with 220MB HDD, external floppy, 8" color screen, and pretty much shitty), and it makes Win 3.1 look and run like Win95.  I love it.  OK, I just ate and I'm tired and full and fat dumb happy lalalalala.... good night. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, every day, huh?  Yeah well, better late than never right?  This weekend was pretty unique, and I'll explain why I haven't been updating.  My friend Dallas, who is in the Navy up in Great Lakes, stopped by Friday night and just left a little while ago.  We had a really great weekend together.  I had never really thought a whole lot of him... I'd pictured him as typical gay... into sex and not into people more or less... wow, I was a bit wrong there!  We had some amazingly wonderful tender moments that I won't soon forget.  We had a good time and he only got on my nerves once, and that was just cuz I got in a huffy mood due to a little episode of "people claustrophobia".  Yes, when I'm somewhere surrounded by people and I just can't move or anything, I get edgy and a little panicky and usually stay that way for a little while therefore making me not-so-pleasant company.  Eh, it goes away after an hour or so.  Did I mention my fingernails?  They're long enough now to where I can sometimes feel them on the keyboard as I type... yeah, time to trim them.  I'll wait until tuesday when I'm home alone so I can like go all-out manicure like some sort of femme... hahaha!  I saw this itty bitty laptop today... like half the height of a normal one with a little camera built in and all... expensive as all hell, like $2100 but man, that'd be perfect for music on the road!  I wanna be able to write music while I'm out and about... that's sorta like my dream.  I think it'd be soooo cool.  I also finally found a copy of Test Drive: LeMans for Dreamcast after searching about a half dozen stores for it.... yay!  Can't wait to get into it!  I also saw the demo of Gran Turismo 3!!!!  Like in person and got to play it!!!  OK, it actually wasn't as spectacular as I had expected, but it was nice.... just a little too shiny and refined to look real though.  Anyway, that's enough for now right?  Gawd, I hope so... =P 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Cool... just watched Who Wants To Be a Millionaire... some nerdy lady was on there and flew up to $125,000 without using a single lifeline... she's at $250,000 with a lifeline left and tomorrow gets to try for $1,940,000!  And what does she hope to do with the money?  Replace her orange countertops... she seems deserving enough.  I'll never forget that one guy... this young cocky SOB lawyer who thought he was all that... he missed the very first question!  The $100 question!  It was something about a nursery rhyme, and my god was it hilarious to see him bite it so soon... he was such an ass. Well, I haven't worked on the nails yet... grr... they're getting long... arguably longer than they've ever been.  I've spent the day doing "dead kitty" checks.  The cat likes to lay on the couch and not move for a long time while she sleeps, and considering the fact that she's at least 15 years old, I always check her when she's like that just to make sure.  I have this feeling that this will be her last year... I hope not for two reasons... one is that I love my cat, and second is that my mother swears that she will never get another cat because she isnt' much of a cat person.  Me myself and I, I'm a cat person... easier to take care of, smaller, and you can leave 'em alone for up to a week whereas a dog has to be let out a few times each day. I went to the GLBFA meeting tonight... that stands for Gays Lesbians Bisexuals and Friends Association.. it's Joliet Junior College's (JJC's) gay support group.  We had some new faces there as well as a lot of missing old faces.  We have new people every month it seems, but the people that were there this time seemed to be about business, which is what we need right now.  Turns out Jenny, this one girl there, is this girl that I'd been talking to online... didn't even realize it until she said something...  it's a small world after all .  This one guy was there too... his name's Jimmy.  He goes to the group downtown on Tuesdays as well... he's sort of a flamer, but he's really cute and seems nice, though I think he's probably a little too, umm, easy =P.  Eh, sometimes I wonder if it's really worth it to have morals... I've got all these horny friends that could be satisfying my every pleasure :) but I'm all moral and stuff so I won't do that, but I sometimes wonder why... is it really something I want or is it something I do for my image?  I honestly do think that I stick with my morals for myself because I think I just wouldn't feel good about sex if it didn't mean something.  So, how am I dealing with my procrastinating?  Well I'm ditching the math homework.... I'll have to work on it bit-by-bit in the next chapters rather than wait until the last minute... grr, and it's worth 20 points too... I hate teachers that do that... I mean christ it's college; we're supposed to be responsible for our actions and if I can not do homework and still get A's on the test, then why must I do the homework?  Some teachers just don't understand what college is about. I'm so happy... I've got a bid in on eBay for a power supply for a Commodore 64 and also for a 1581 3½" floppy drive for the C-64.  I've got some C-64 junk in the basement that I can't use because the guy who sold me my stuff over eBay basically screwed me over royally.  Oh well, I'm not holding out for the floppy drive... the 3½" ones are rare, but the power supply is necessary, a must have.  Then I can start working on converting these 340 game packs I have for the C-64 on my PC over to C-64 disks... what fun!  I grew up on that computer and still really really enjoy the games... makes me feel like a kid again, and that's a feeling that I'm learning to cherish as I get older.  Adults are right when they tell kids not to grow up too fast and to enjoy their time as a kid. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well I just got a phonecall.  I've been looking for a job for a month now and finally got one... at Subway.  Yeah, I know I said I'd never work fast food again, but cripes, for $8/hr I'll do it!  It can't be worse than some of my other jobs.  I used to work at OfficeMax... sorta liked that job because I all but ran the electronics department and was sorta 2nd place in the copy area.  I sorta felt special =P.  Wal-Mart was great too... all I did was push shopping carts.  Yeah, it paid pretty bad, but it was sometimes fun... really laid back too.  Then there was McDonald's.... yuck... I hated that job, but I was good at it.  Granted, I never made the food, and now I'll have to do that, but how hard is it to slap some meat and cheese on bread anyway?  We'll have to see if I can cut the buns... they cut them weird and I'm not the most clever person in the world.  Eh, nothing to worry about.  Point is I'll be able to make enough to cover my insurance bill this summer so now I won't lose my car.  Otherwise, my parents were gonna sell the van and just let me be PT driver on the car, but blah, I'll pay my insurance.  Then this summer maybe they'll bump me to FT... that'd rock!  Money!  My god I'll once again have money!!  Let's hope I don't squander it this time.  Anyway, I haven't bit my fingernails in a couple weeks and they're getting lethal, so I'm gonna go cut them or file them or something. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I've got too much to do before tomorrow.... my procrastinating ways have caught up with me.  I have seven sections of calculus homework due, a calculus test, and a sociology test..... all tomorrow!!  Grrrrrr.... well at least I get a little break today between my math and law classes.  I'm really tempted to skip law, but I shouldn't... besides, there's a pretty good lookin' guy in there :).  Ha, well for now I'll just sit here and chill with my music.  "Is It Love" sure is a good one... I really love it.  It's really emotional too... I wrote that one when I was confused about someone... I didn't know whether or not I was in love with this guy, but I did know that I wanted to be with him more than anything... but he gave me the cold shoulder treatment and won't discuss it, so I guess I'll just get on with my life like I've been threatening to do for months... thank you Nate for putting me through that... as much as it hurt, it helped me realize some shit that I had to realize... thanks a lot (that was only slightly bitter). 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so I finally got in touch with Jim (the guy in Montana)... still doesn't have any new pics (go figure)... still thinks he can sweet talk his way back into my life (yeah right), but eh, I try to make people happy, and it makes him happy to hear from me, so I'll suffer just a little bit.  I just discovered O-Town... I pretty much hate N-Sync and BSB... they just suck bad... I think once I heard 98 Degrees and cringed through the whole thing... O-Town... now there's some damn talent!  They're also a hell of a lot better lookin' than the other groups =P.  Seriously, though, I could like listen to each of these guys going solo, but together they sound great too!  I'm surprised... genuinely surprised.  OK, so it's late and I'm tired and I think I'll call it a night.  I think I'm going to like do a post about each of my friends... that'd be fun.  And christ... I've already got someone IMing me saying "gee, i feel sorry for you" and stuff.. peoples, this ain't a pity thing... there's good stuff in my life, I swear!  I just need to vent on the bad/pointless stuff for a while.  Anyway, good night. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink The Critic  OK, was I like one of three people who liked The Critic?  I thought it was pretty damn funny and yet every channel it's been on kicks it off... even Comedy Central!!!  Christ, they'll show anything... except The Critic!!!  Oh well, at least the show lives on thanks to the internet. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Hmm... you know that guy I mentioned... the one in Montana that I sorta fell for and who sent me the false pics?  Well, now I've decided to get in touch with him again.  I thought it would be kinda fun just to see where life has taken him... I swear, I never seem to hold a grudge... I'm very "forgive and forget"... sometimes to a fault. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Sexuality is quite a topic for me.  I personally like the philosophy of "labels are for jars" but since our society forces us to pin ourselves down in some way, I will go ahead and say that I am gay.  At one point in time I thought I was bisexual, and even before that there was a time when the thought of being gay was pretty yuck.  I've always had a small underlying desire to look at men.  Even when I was a child... when other guys were looking at girls, well, I was too, but I was also looking at guys.  Up until my senior year in high school, the only real area that I had feelings for men was in the physical area.  Simply put, men turned me on...  really  turned me on.  I can remember the last time I was turned on by a woman.  It was my freshman year in high school and I was going to school in Morris, IL.  There was this beautiful girl who was a sophomore, and I would often fantacize about her.  I can't remember a single time since then that I've fantacized about women.  Don't get me wrong, I can certainly appreciate a beautiful woman, and I recognize attractiveness when I see it, but it just doesn't get the juices flowin' any more.  Ever since I was old enough to start thinking about girlfriends and such, I've wanted a girlfriend.  In middle school I had crushes on girls and would always try to impress them.  Even in high school I just wanted a girl to spend my time with.  As far as men were concerned, I just liked to look at them.  That all started to change in my senior year in high school.  It was then that I found myself developing  emotional  feelings for a guy... the first time I "fell in love" with a guy.  It was a guy that I knew online who lived hundreds of miles away in Montana.  He had sent me pictures of himself and he was  very  attractive.  He was also one of the only people who seemed to understand me and knew what I was feeling and thinking even though we'd never met or even spoken on the phone.  I did however find out that the pictures he showed me were not of him... to say so would be an admission of guilt, but for christ's sake everyone does it anyway, and this site is all about me being open, right?  I was looking at porn (come on, who doesn't?) and saw a couple of "his" pics on a couple porn sites.  Of course then he sent me the "real" pics of him, which I also found on porn sites (ok, so I was a kinda horny teenager... sue me!!!).  Needless to say, I ended up writing this guy off because I can't stand a liar. As time moved on, I felt myself starting to wish that I could go out with a girl  or  a guy.  This really hit hard when I was at Western Illinois University for that one semester I went there in the fall of 1999.  I didn't just look at guys as visual pleasure... I started to look at them as potential partners.  I was really freaked when this happened, and that's one reason I came back home (the other reason being my 2.0 GPA).  As time continued on, I still had very strong emotional feelings for women, but it was some time last year that this too started to change.  It was after being in my first relationship with a guy, John, that I realized that I would never marry a woman and would never father children.  I just could no longer see myself in that situation.  I still flirt with girls and kinda think stuff like, "Gee, she seems cool... wonder if she likes me," or whatever, but I know that it won't happen.  I now consider myself to be gay, and with each passing day I become more and more proud of who I am.  I am in no way a flamer... I don't advertise my sexuality in any way.  I am however very open to those that care to know.  I don't care if people know that I'm gay, but I don't run around telling everyone or wear fruity clothes or speak with a lisp or sashé my ass all over the place.  To be honest, I'm not fond of people who do that, but I also try not to be prejudiced, so I try to never let things like that interfere with my getting to know someone.  Anyway, I think that's enough about my sexuality for now... sheesh, my fingers hurt! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I guess I should start with a little info on me.  My full name is Richard James Craig.  The Richard is from my father's side of the family and the James is from my mother's.  I was born on July 19th, 1981 in Ottawa, IL.  Since then, I've moved quite a few times.  I moved to Pennsville, NJ, then back to Ottawa, then back to Pennsville, then to Morris, IL, then to Coal City, IL, then to Macomb, IL, and now to Joliet, IL.  The longest I ever spent somewhere was nine consecutive years in Pennsville (12 total); second place goes to Coal City, where I spent 4½ years.  Needless to say, I can sound kinda funny when I talk with a touch of southern, a touch of "joisey", and a touch of chi-KAAAH-go. From my father's side, I'm of Scottish/Welsh descent and from my mother's side, well who knows, but I know I'm related to John Adams, John Quincy Adams, and Abe Lincoln, and we also suspect that there may even be a drop of African American thrown in there somewhere, but I sure don't look it. I'm just at six feet tall and currently weigh somewhere like 175lbs or something.  I used to weight around 210lbs and then lost the weight fast, so while I'm not really fat, I can look it because of the loose skin I still have.  I have brown hair that wants to be (and used to be somewhat) blonde as well as medium brown eyes.  My skin is pretty dynamic depending on how much sun it sees.  When I'm being my reclusive self and have no tan, my skin is pale and blotchy, but when I'm out in the sun and get a tan (which happens pretty quickly and pretty well for me), my skin takes on a really nice, smooth tone.  I currently have a terrible acne problem... it's not so bad on my face for the most part, but it sometimes gets so bad on my back and shoulders that it is painful to lay down at night, so many times I'll sleep on my side. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       This is the first day of my little online journal.  I never really feel like people understand me, so I've decided that I will just put stuff here and rant and ramble and then people can read it and get to know me better. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Oh gosh, so much craziness... first off, congrats to Marty for coming out to his parents yesterday!  Umm, gosh, don't really know what to talk about... just been going to school and going to work and hanging out with buds at JJC... me and Kristen and Marty were wreaking havoc at Eagle the other day... that was fun... Marty and I were doing the voice of God on my computer earlier today thanks to my sound card =P... Brenn came over for a little while yesterday and then drug me to Glenndale to his friend Neil's place, where we watched half of Abyss, fell asleep, and decided to come home before we got any sleepier.  I have to confess one small thing... the more I'm around Brenn, the more I start to kinda like him... we've got our fair share of differences, but actually we have a lot in common in terms of what we like in a relationship and stuff like that... at first, I really didn't like Brenn =P but it's really weird, the more I'm around him, the more he kinda grows on me, but hell, he's seeing someone and for some reason I have a hard time picturing the two of us together, but hell, I'll try anything right?  Jimmy's proof of that, haha!  Just a little thought... I highly doubt it'll ever become anything, but life has become too dynamic for me lately to rule out anything.  Yes, life is gaining interest for me, some good some bad, but I'll take what I can get just so I'm not bored all the damn time!  For now, I will sleep and sleep well, for tomorrow I set sail for the shores of Daggerfall... err, umm, anyway, g'nite. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, free thought time... Jay just told me he has a b/f now... that's cool... I sorta liked Jay, but we've never met so it's not a huge deal... hope things work out well there.  I'm having trouble focusing on the monitor cuz I'm so SICK! =P  I've been biting my fingernails and fingers and stuff like revenously lately, especially today... I've gotta stop that.  I have four empty pop cans sitting here... yay... ooh, I said "pop"... usually I stick with my east-coast ways and say "soda".... hmm..... oww, after saying I should stop biting my fingers, I bite one again... grr, it's gotta be some obsessive/compulsive thing... driving me nuts!  I'm so tired, but I like don't feel like I could sleep right now because I just woke up from like 5 hours of sleep... ugh... I'm just so bored... and angry... and tired... and upset... and I'll get over it.  Heh, I didn't mention before how Jimmy (my ex) is now pretty much slandering my name... he's telling EVERYONE about..... my "thingy"!!!!!!!!!!  WHAT THE FUCK!  That is SO not public information!  Granted, he's making me sound like I'm hung like an oak tree, BUT STILL!!! (for the record, he only says so out of comparison... I'm average, whereas he's pretty small, mwahahahaha paybacks!).  Anyway, he's also making people think that I'm some sort of awful person, and the fact is that the only person who's making him hurt is himself.  How can he expect me to love him back?  How can he be that selfish and still love me?  How can he defame my name to people I don't even know and still say he loves me?  That little   boy   needs to grow up! 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, this day turned sour fast!  OK, the good stuff first... made a new friend today, Kristen.  She's hilarious... her and I and her friend (I forget her name) were sitting outside JJC just laughing our heads off for like 45 minutes solid (I would've said 45 minutes straight, but for some reason gay people don't do that *grin*).  Then she dragged me off to LARP, which stands for Live Action Role Play... basically looks like a bunch of bad acting based around norse mythology or something... way over my head.  It did kinda spark my interest in acting though... I think I could do that actually... always wanted to try.  Ha, gawd, talk about fulfilling the role of typical gayness =P. OK, onto the bad.  I felt  really  sick toward the end of my math class... felt like I would pass out and could barely move the pencil to write... then started feeling better and felt great during that laughing fit.  Then around 4:00 or so, I started feeling like shit again, and ended up sleeping for about 4-5 hours after I got home.  It's not just my sickness that made me want to sleep, though.  My mom needed some good luck cards printed up for her quartet competition this weekend... she asked me to do that when I got home and she got pissed off because my response was, "I don't feel good."  And it was the honest truth; I felt like shit!  I was checking my email and then planning to go to sleep, but of course she didn't believe me... she thought I was just trying to get out of work.  So then I go on my dad's computer to work on these cards and the mouse starts sticking, so I start griping about the mouse and my dad's like, "Don't start taking out your frustrations on my mouse," and shit like that and I told him it wasn't working right... he WATCHED me moving the mouse down and saw that the cursor was NOT moving, and he still said, "my mouse works just fine,"... he was calling me a liar, something that I WILL NOT tolerate, so I started yelling at the top of my lungs and all but cussed them out (I  never  swear in front of my parents).  They weren't too happy, and we ended up getting in a huge fight and, well, I'm slightly pissed at the moment to say the least.  My father has been more full of anger since I've started having more and more gay friends over... mom says she's "working on him" and stuff, but you'd never know it... he's very cold toward my friends any more, and yet he says he has no problem with it... to which I say  bullshit!   I almost left the house, but if I had, I wouldn't have wanted to come back, and with the van in the shop, I would've had to've come back so my dad could drive to work.  I just really feel like my dad's pulling away from me... we were never that close to begin with, as much as he tried to be, but now he's not even trying any more.  Ugh, I just can't wait to get out of this house and start living my life! 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Oh wow, I feel terrible right now... I'm SICK... my nose is a little crapped up and my throat is a little sore, but mostly I just feel disoriented.  We just took our van in for some looking at... it's been acting odd lately.  Ha, as if I didn't like enough guys, chalk up one more on the list, though this one's a bit different. :)  His name is Sean and man does he have a lot going for him.  He's incredibly smart... so much so that he's going to some like special high school in Aurora that's almost like a college.  He does happen to be only 17, and his birthday is like 8 days after mine, but after talking to him on the phone a couple times and a lot online, I think about the only thing that makes him 17 is his birth certificate... he acts much older, and I like that.  From the pics I've seen of him, he's also pretty damn attractive.  He just seems like a really nice guy, and he's really into computers and games too, which is so a plus... I have yet to find anything that I don't like about him really, and usually I'll find at least one thing right off the bat and several other things as time goes on... hmm..... who knows, eh? On Nate, well, he was MIA all that weekend and I've hardly talked to him since, so that is once again going into remission.  Jay says he's busy for a few weeks, to which I say whatever... maybe I'll someday meet him, or maybe not... not gonna worry too much there.  Now I've got this crazy 15-year-old after me... umm, hell no.  That's just way too freakin' young!  I mean he's a nice kid and all, but he's a KID!  I'm totally not even gonna look in that direction other than just chatting online and stuff like that.  Oddly enough, I've been diggin' Sean so much lately that I haven't thought of Nate in two days, and that's a GREAT sign.  As much as I want to be with Nate, I'd just as soon be over him... this "love" I feel for him is just driving me crazy, and I want it to end.  Maybe meeting some new people will help that happen.  Anyway, if you'd like to see a bunch of pictures of me, some new, some old, check out  urlLink  this page  .  C-yaz! 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Hey peoples!  Not too much has been happening lately, well except this hair thing going on over here.  My friend Brenn just came over and he downloaded like nine million Animaniacs MP3s and then I forced him to watch me play with the Commodore 64 =P.  Other than that, not much has been going on.  I've used a whole ELEVEN minutes on my cell phone =P.  Nobody calls me, whaaaaa =P.  Anyway, I've got some things to do, so I'll be off =P. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so I'm probably not going to AZ cuz I'm gonna go to NIU no doubt.  Check this out!  I wonder if this'll work...  urlLink Picture of Nate ... OK, that's a pic of Nate, the guy I mentioned once before that I sorta fell in love with... well first off, he's WAAY WWAAAAAAYYY too gorgeous in that pic, oh my gawd... I was dumbfounded when I first saw it!  Second, we might get together this weekend, which just makes me soo freakin' happy... wow, I just love being around him so much... anyway... I got a cell phone!!!  (815) 546-1605 if you wanna call it!  I'm also breaking up with Jimmy... I hate to do it, but I just can't really see myself with him in a serious relationship... it's usually very hard to take him seriously =P... honestly though, I do like him, but more as a friend really.  I'm also starting to get to know this guy named Jay... he's really cute and has been on my buddy list for a long time now, and in the last week or so, we've been chatting quite a bit, and now we're gonna try to meet... that'd be so cool, cuz he seems like a really sweet guy... besides, I need someone to take my mind off of Nate since I know Nate won't go out with me, grrrrrrrr.... and now I have this beautiful picture of him to go nuts over!  IT's NOT FAIR!!!    grrrrrrr, I'll get over it!  Here's a  urlLink  picture of Jay  , and thanks to my photo-wizardry,  urlLink here's a touched up version of Jay's pic!   Well, I'm gonna go now... have fun with those pictures.... gawd, aren't they just too cute?  Woot!  I know I'll never be with Nate.... I think I should just move on... I just need the right person to move on with... 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, I'm finally updating this crazy thing... I've had so much going on lately, especially with Jimmy, so I'm sure most of this will be devoted to him.  First off, lemme clarify the list in my last post. -Big fight with parents OK, so like me and my dad were arguing over microphone connectors and I told him I'd plugged this one mic into my computer and he said it couldn't have worked even though I know for a fact it did, and he insisted that I must be lying, so I threw my hands down and started yelling at him... to be honest, I'm sick of putting up with this rudimentary bickering, so I'm not going to stand for it... obviously my father wasn't too thrilled with the idea when he said, "if you don't shut up, i'll fucking punch your lights out"....... yeah, whoah... he's never threatened me like that... I can't say I was scared because he's never hit me and never will, but still, the principle of it... I'm not a happy camper, folks. -Want to move to Tucson OK, it's a dream, but there's trailers out there for like $10,000 or less, so I think I could swing that, right?  Who knows, but Arizona is beautiful, cheap, and FAR FAR from here! -Selling stuff on eBay actually, this is related to the Tucson thing since I need money... auctions aren't going as well as planned, but there's still 3 days left, so we'll see! -skipping math AGAIN yikes!  my teacher told me that if I do again, he'll drop me!!!  holy shit, I totally wasn't expecting that... but what I don't get is that I'm doing pretty well outside of the never doing my homework thing... I think that's so stupid, collecting homework for a grade like we're still in middle school or something.. hello!  welcome to COLLEGE!  it's so infantile and I almost feel like I shouldn't do ANY homework just to prove my point, but he won't give a shit, and I'm the one who suffers. -ME and JIMMY OK, lots to talk about here.  The more time I spend with him, the more he opens up to me... he has a lot of ghosts in the closet so-to-speak... a somewhat sordid past that he doesn't seem to like talking about, and I am starting to see what it does to him... the problem is that the more I try to help him, the further he seems to slip from me... he wants instant gratification like some child, reaching out his arms saying "kiss me" and stuff, and yet he'll turn around and say things like "i wish I was dead" or "i wish i had no feelings so life would be easier"... i just can't handle that... I really like him, I really do, but I can't love him until he accepts me... just tonight, I tried to touch his face and he backed away like I was some killer or something... it was like a knife through my heart!  I just can't love someone if they can't even trust me a little like that... we'll be horseplayin' and stuff and I'll go to tickle him and then he'll jump away and say "no, you're gonna hurt me" in a sort of joking way, but he says it often enough to where it bothers me a lot.  I don't know, I just don't feel like our relationship is really going to go any further, at least not with some effort on his part... and cripes, he's one horny little bastard!  I'll just wanna be with him and he's all like goin' crazy on me and stuff!  I so wish Greg could've been a part of my life... when I was with him, I just felt so great and so free, like the weight of the world had been lifted from my shoulders!  When him and I were getting intimate, it was the most wonderful experience of my life... it was paced perfectly and never felt lustful in any way... nothing but emotion... it was so overwhelming that I was literally shaking!  Anyway, talking about him just brings back all that pain, so I'm gonna stop... gonna stop altogether... g'nite! 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, am I lazy or what?  I don't feel like typing, but I'll try to do a quick list of things to talk about later. -Big fight with parents -Want to move to Tucson -Small fight with Jimmy (who is now my b/f) but we ended up crying in each other's arms (good thing) -I DID ace my law test (98%!) -Selling stuff on eBay, first time -have my hair combed all weird this morning -skipping math AGAIN OK, that's enough... I'll explain more later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, yesterday was fun!  Ezmerelda and Andy and I went to Chicago AGAIN... this time so Ez could go to Gaymart.  Here's the best part!  I met Art!!  We met him at Gaymart, and wow what a cool guy!  He is so perfectly balanced for my tastes... he's very mature, yet playful... he has the perfect balance of masculinity and femininity, kinda like Nate... he's also very attractive... quite the cutie and he has the kind of build I like, slim but defined.  We all had a great time, and I like Art quite a bit?  The downside (there's always a downside)?  He lives in San Francisco and just goes to school in Chicago... he's leaving in two weeks and won't be back until August.  Hopefully I'll get to see him again before he leaves... I just wanna give him a big ol' hug, and I didn't get the chance to do that yesterday (except for the little welcoming hug when we first ran into each other).  He's such a sweetie too... we were all sitting out on the rocks on the shore of Lake Michigan and next thing I know, I'm sitting there and he's standing next to me scratching my head =P.  Then walking back to the van, Andy gave Ez her coat, I gave Andy my jacket, and then I began to freeze, so Art starting rubbing my arm and my back trying to keep me warm... such a sweetie.  Well, gotta run! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       When I find myself rolling in way too much money, I shall open up a port-a-potty company and call it, "The Bushes."  In my commercial, I will have a person walk up to a rather poorly maintained port-a-potty and say, "I would rather go in the bushes," at which time they will turn and see my port-a-potty, with a sign saying, "The Bushes," in tip-top condition.  WHEEEEEEEEEEEEE! 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Damn, once again I find myself in a sour mood, and both times it was because of Brenn.  I'm starting to realize that I really like Brenn, even moreso today after hearing all that he's been through with his medical problems.  I guess what bothered me was when he talked of one time when he was in so much pain that he asked his friend to kill him.  He called his friend over just so he wouldn't be alone during his pain, and I guess I just feel like he should've had someone more than a friend there for him during his time of need.  God, my heart just goes out to people like that, and I want to be there for them... it almost brings me to tears, honestly.  I know that if I'd been in some sort of incredible pain like that, I'd want someone more dear to me by my side, but he didn't have anyone like that there for him.  Now I'm listening to some music that almost has me in tears every time I hear it.  I think it's time I had a good cry... I haven't cried in so long because things have been going quite well for me lately.  I'm just lonely.  I need someone there for me too... I may not have excrutiating physical pain, but the emotional pain is quickly becoming unbearable...... my god this music is so beautiful, and yet so sad... easily some of the most moving music I've ever heard... it's from the Final Fantasy Symphonic Suite, the Prelude, track 5.  It's incredible... so very moving.  It follows my mood fairly well too..... god, all I want is someone to hold in my arms, someone to cry on, someone to cry on me... someone I can connect with on an emotional level.  It seems like all of the people that I match up with never take notice of me... the people that see things the same way I do always seem to look right past me.  Ugh, life goes on, as usual... 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       WHOA WHOA WHOA!  My auction is up to...... $122.50!!!  Damn!  I tell ya, I'm getting that feeling again, that feeling that I haven't had in so long.  Back in like the high school days, I was always so self-conscious, ie if someone gave me a dirty look, I'd think it was my fault.  As of late, I've been more confident in myself, so when that same person gives me a dirty look, I just think that they're having a bad day or just pissed in general.  Now I feel like I'm reverting back to my shy, self-conscious ways again, and I don't like it.  I feel like my friends are all drifting away from me, and these are friends that I've had for like maybe a month or two.  I just feel like things are shitty lately.  I don't know why, I just do.  I hate this, I really do.  It's like some sort of depression that I get from time to time... don't get it often at all any more, but I used to be like this almost nightly, especially in college.  I just really need someone in my life right now... things are starting to feel sour to me and I need someone there for me who can give me something to look forward to.  =/  When will it be my time to fly? When will it be my moment to shine? When will I get a chance to love? When will I be the one who is loved?  When will I find the time for life? When will my heart not feel like a knife? When will I gaze upon endless skies? When will I see with cloudless eyes?  Oh god, I'm writing poetry... that means I'm depressed... I think I'm going to go try and sleep it off... forgive me for being such a downer tonight... tomorrow will be better, as it always is, even if only in my dreams... ok, whatever the hell that meant... now I'm getting all philosophical and that's really not a good sign =P so to bed with me! 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       First off, my auction is up to $76.  Second off, I just realized that like I never was fond of Dodge cars, but now they're all like redesigned and stuff and I really like them =P.  And then we have today... went to Chicago with three gay girls... wow, um, that was an experience =P.  I spent an hour sitting in a bookstore that was full of lesbian books and stuff... we were in Andersonville, the lesbian part of Chicago.  I also finally wrote a new song.  I'm also extremely tired and don't want to type any more, but I will say that Esmerelda and I probably swore more tonight than either of us have in our whole lives =P.  G'nite. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       WOOT!  Auction is up to $70!  Can you say WOW?! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Yay!  Good news on two accounts.  First off, I am auctioning my old Atari and Coleco crap on eBay, and the bid is at $51!  I was expecting like $10 or somethin... check it out  urlLink here .  I've also revamped my pictures page at http://cragman.tripod.com so check it out.  Now for the other good news!  Just talked to a guy last night on the phone... really cool guy, named Art.  That's him down at the bottom... isn't he just damn fine? Wow... and what a nice guy too!  We had a good time talking and I think we got along really well, so maybe him and I will have to meet up or something... that'd be fun.  My only complaint about him is he  really  reminds me a lot of Jimmy... not in any bad way, but just in general.  Hell, if Jimmy hadn't been so phoney and so childish, he would've been fine, and here we have a guy who seems to have a lot of the good things that Jimmy had but without Jimmy's downsides... and I'm sure once I meet Art, I'll see him more for himself and not compare him so much to Jimmy, which'll get rid of that creepiness =P.  Anyway, I hope Art and I will meet some day... I think him and I could get along great as friends, and I definitely see a potential for more, though this is all going off of a single phone conversation and a little bit of online conversation =P.  BTW, I'm looking for a decent little laptop, something that I can write music on while on the road.  I may end up taking back my DVD player just to have that money to put toward this laptop I want so badly.  Anyway, laterz!   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, kitty update!  At the moment, you'd never know anything was wrong with the cat... she's eating and digesting, meowing, running, just being her usual self again, so let's hope that her new diet will keep her with us for plenty of time to come.  Today was BORING... but I had my hair bleached again, and it's a teensy bit different this time.  BTW, that DVD player I bought, an Apex 500W, which you can find at some Wal-Marts for $99 (if they have them in stock), is OUTSTANDING!  The MP3 player feature is kinda dinky, but it's not bad really, and the video quality was much higher than expected... throw in some surround sound effects and zoom capability and you've got a player that does more than a lot of players twice its price!  Highly recommended!  Anyway, c-yaz all later! 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, Kitty's not feeling well, but she's on her way to a minor recovery, so we'll hope for the best.  Now, about today's road trip, lol!  Me and Andrea (Andy) went for a ride.  First we went to Toys R' Us to find her a ouija board... found one, but it was kinda pricey... then off to the mall so I can get rechargeable batteries, found those and now I'm happy.  Then, the road trip.  We took Rt. 30 to see where it led... ended up turning into like Rt 126 or something... then that intersected Rt 47, so we took 47... all the way to Woodstock, which is 15 miles from the Wisconsin border.  We ate at a little family restaurant, and it was fabulous!  Then, we came back via Morris so we could hit the Super Wal-Mart.  Anyway, I must crap now *grin* and go play with my new DVD player and stuff... yay... c-yaz. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Another Kitty update... the blood test is back in, and our poor Kitty seems to be having some kidney trouble.  The vet says that a low-protein diet will help, but our Kitty's days are numbered.  Guess I'll just have to try and spend more time playing with her and such.  At least she's still got some time left. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, here's a kitty update.  She's having bloodwork done, and they'll see if it's anything major.  She's still not doing well keeping food down, and my mom is fearing that she will slowly starve.  It's all up to the results of the bloodwork.  I'm also starting to hate being single... now that I've been in a couple relationships, I can understand why people are so vehement toward being single... it sucks.  BTW, I'm not all depressed like I was yesterday... still BORED TO FUCKING HELL (!!!!!) but I'll manage. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, three updates in one day... this one sucks too.  Our cat is having trouble keeping her food down, and considering that she's 16, well, maybe this isn't a good sign... we can only hope for the best, but for some reason I'm expecting the worst.  Hope my Kitty is ok. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, yeah, the basement... why I'm discussing that is beyond me, but I just got it all set up cool and shite =P and man I wish I could just move in down there... it's so perfect, especially from an audio standpoint.  I was also seriously thinking about taking a road trip to the east coast.  Only problem is that I would have to go alone because nobody else is free to go.  I was seriously going to do it if I had a companion, but even as it is I'm still entertaining the thought... this will no doubt go under the list of things I've always wanted to do but never did.  I can't gush enough about how much I love the ocean, but I want to share that with someone... I'm sick of being alone... even with all of the new friends I've made, I still feel like I'm alone because I never go do anything with them.  Nobody ever invites me to go anywhere with them, people rarely talk to me unless I talk to them first, and I just feel like people shy away from me for some reason, and I just don't understand why that is.  I think I'm a pretty good person and would like to know if people are doing this and why if they are.  I guess I'm just destined to sit in front of a computer monitor and vegetate for the rest of my life... at least my expected field of work coincides with that well =P.  I'm just sick of feeling like shit and feeling worthless... I wish I had friends that could make me feel a little more needed, cuz any time I try to be there for people, they just push me away... any time I try to get a little closer to someone, they just push me away.  Am I that despikable or something?  It's times like this that I wish I could just go somewhere else and start all over, but I know that it wouldn't help any... at least it'd give me something to do for the time being until my existence there became as stale and stagnant as it is here. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       WOWOWOWOW!  Ha, I just talked to my buddy in NJ, Karl Schmidt!!  Whoah!  We were both remembering all of the stupid little things from way back when... man, was really cool to talk to him.  I'm also working on rearranging the basement, which will be nice once it's done.  I hope to some day insulate the ceiling to that it'll be more sound proof.  Anyway, ha, I've been getting kinda "pride-ful" lately, lol... have TWO little rainbow stickers on my work nametag and one larger sticker on my backpack, hehehe.  For some reason, I just feel like doing that, cuz I'm really starting to get comfortable with all of this.  Anyway, I'm outta here..... laterz! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, ok, John and I aren't back together... oh hell, I'm not even gonna try to explain it cuz I don't even understand it, but my intuition just tells me to avoid him.  Ugh, well I'm gonna go through stuff and get rid of a lot of things and clean this place up... my room is trashed, the basement is trashed, and I have my packrat ways to thank for that!  Otherwise, today was just ho-hum as usual... when will I have a life? 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Wow!  I've neglected this poor thing for quite a while... well first off, I just ate a veggie sub from Subway, and my my was it good, and only $2.49 with tax! =P  Big news!!!  Ha, John (my first bf) and I are back together!  I sorta woke up to the fact that it was more my problems that caused me to end the relationship before.  I just need to learn to be tolerant, and besides, and I don't really mean this as a knock to Jimmy, but going out with Jimmy showed me that being with John wasn't that bad at all, and the more I thought about it, John and I really had some great times... he's one of the few people that I'm naturally comfortable around, and I really do think that with good communication that we can work out the few problems we have.  Haha, on a funny note, I asked Kyle, my str-8 but gay-looking friend in Boston how big he was, lol!  And he answered!  Actually, his first answer was, "i'm kinda puny down there, and it's shaped like a spoon".... ha!, I was like rolling on the floor after that one!  Anyway, out of respect to him since I'm sure he wasn't thrilled to have a gay guy asking him about his size, I won't disclose the answer (but he is above average ;) ).  Why I find that so funny is beyond me, but anywayz... I've been talking to a lot of people from Pennsville lately... Hudson Finlaw, Tom Burton, Dale Dobson... kinda cool stuff!  I hope to go out there soon and visit people and stuff.  Ugh, well I overdid some stuff on that sub and it's kinda giving me the willies, so I'm gonna jet!  Hopefully I'll get a good picture of John soon... as handsome as he is, he isn't exactly photogenic, so I'll just have to work my photography magic on him =P. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, how interesting.  One phonecall may have just had a significant impact on my life.  I received a letter in the mail from "Vector Marketing" asking me to call about a possible job.  I called today around 1:30.  They asked me in for an interview at 3:30.  At 5:30, I was offered a job.  Wow.  So here's the thing.  I'm a sales rep for Cutco now... yes, I'm selling knives to people, but thanks to the decent prices and the fact that the knives truly are awesome, they almost sell themselves thanks to word of mouth.  Basically, I set my hours, I set my workload, and I control how much money I get.  I have the potential to be making like $1200 a month... enough to live on my own.  I have also thought that I may put off NIU for now and go to JJC some more.  That way, I keep the van, I get an apartment, I pay my own tuition... I can get out on my own with this job!  I train tomorrow, Fri, and Sat, and I really hope I can make something big of this!  I can finance the van and get insurance for $300/month... rent could be $400/month... I'd have enough left to live off of.  Anyway, the site for these people is www.vectormarketing.com and it's really not bad at all.  I can't wait to get started!  Anyway, that's all really... gotta go... and yes, I quit Subway =P. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Oh, this is funny... some girl at work gave the cashier her number to give to me... I can't believe it, some chick gave me her number!  I might even call it =P just for fun... and I was wearing my pride necklace and everything!  Hmm... maybe I'll call tomorrow... for now, I'm braindead and wanna sleep =P... c-ya! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Hey!  Wanna see what I drive?  http://cragman.tripod.com/van/ is the place to go!  Notice the spiffy wheel covers and the steering wheel cover and the rainbow sticker on the back :)  I love my ghetto van!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Ah, interesting night.  I went to play pool with Andy and Esmerelda... well, Ez couldn't make it, so it was just me and Andy... then when we were done, Andy called Ez and finally confessed her feelings.  It made me feel good for some reason.  Earlier today, Andy and I tried to turn my van into a tent (inspired by the Pontiac Aztek) and barely succeded.  We went into the woods and cut down some stick-like dead trees to prop up a tarp with so that's kinda cool.  I had my rainbow keychain in plain view and my necklace on as well.  Well, interesting happenings with a neighbor from that.  There's this neighbor kid who lives in the next cul-de-sac over... he's always riding his rollerblades and often walks his dog while riding on them.  He's pretty attractive, slim build... typical young guy ya know.  Well today Andy and I were walking to the woods to go get the big stick we cut down and he came up behind us on the blades with the dog leashed... of course the dog had to stop and sniff us, so he stopped for a sec, and I was like "go dog, go!  run!  run like the wind!" being goofy and the guy looked at me and smiled and gave a little laugh... not a smirky smile though... an actual toothy happy smile.  Then since it took forever for me to drag that  log  home, I ended up running into the guy again... he's never really spoken to me before, but he took off his headphones and said, "so, do you usually carry around a stick that big?"  I was kinda like "uh, wait, holy crap is he flirting with me or messing with me?!" and I told him we were turning the van into a tent and laughed and he laughed too and went on his way.  Interesting... I don't know how old this guy is... he seems high-school age, but heck that's no problem... my min is 17... it's mature enough and also legal.  He seems nice though... I'd guess from his clothes and looks and attachment to his CD-player that he's a bit of a metal head, but so what?  Hell, he was probably just fucking with me and probably didn't even see the keychain, but I can hope right?  Damn, date a guy who lives that close?  Sweet!  For now, I must sleep because I had one hell of a tiring day... dragging that log home reminded me of like Jesus carrying the cross on his back... yeah, so I had it much easier, but at least it gives me more respect for the man.  G'nite! 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Nate called again!  Wow!  Of course I wasn't home because I actually have a life now =P... and tomorrow night I'll be out again playing pool with Andy and Ez.  Anyway, I've gotta call Nate now :) BYE 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so now that Art's gone, things between me and Nate are progressing slightly.... gawd my life is confusing.  Turns out Nate called Saturday night and Sunday night... both nights I was at work, but Saturday night he was actually calling to see if we could get together!  Him calling me is rare enough for celebration, but for him to actually call me to meet is like wow.  I called him today and he said some weirdness about how he considers me one of his better friends because I call him and always want to talk to him and stuff.  I'm getting the impression that he's starting to notice the fact that I've been there for him and been after him for 10 months now, longer than a lot of his friends seem to last.  I'm hoping I can ask him out tonight, cuz on Mondays the local mexican restaurant has live mariachis... I figure that'd be interesting at worst and romantic at best ;) .  Anyway, off to work on some music!  C-ya! 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I've fallen in love once before... with Nate for those of you who keep up with this thing... and I have loved another guy, John, my first bf, though I was not in love with him.  The love bug has struck again... I just spent yesterday and today with Art at his place in Chicago.  I feared this would happen, and it did... I fell in love with Art.  Him and I have had a sort of chemistry since we first met, but these last two days were our first opportunity to act upon that.  Art is the culmination of everything I've liked in other guys... he has the charm and cuteness of Nate, the kind and sweet and romantic nature of Greg, and he's gorgeous on top of all that.  He's everything I could ask for, and he's the first guy I've ever been willing to openly display affection toward.  I hugged him right in the middle of the train station and would have kissed him had he made the move.  I would give anything to have him stay around here, but he has to go home to San Francisco for the summer.  I really hope that him and I can maintain over the summer what we've started here, and then I'll just have to take the bus to Chicago once I get to college this fall.  I'm actually tempted to stay in Joliet another year and get an A.S. degree just so I will have a way to see him... I never thought someone could mean to much to me after only meeting them three times... I know I was infatuated with Nate after just once, but I've now ruled that an infatuation... this, on the other hand, is pure.  It's so spectacular, and I had to muster every ounce of energy in me to keep from bawling all over Art when we said goodbye... as it was, I still cried a tiny bit... I think he did too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       School is OVER!  Thank God!  I think I bombed my calc test and aced my econ test... oh well... I can take Calc again when I'm in a real college with a real teacher who doesn't treat us like we're in high school. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Hmm, interesting stuff... first off, I remembered the 2nd funny thing I came up with on Friday's Chicago trip... I want a horn in my van that baaaaa's like a goat when you press it =P.  I'm not real happy at the moment... got back from Tuesday night group... we ate out at Sara's (a restaurant) afterwards... I wore my 32/34 bluejeans just cuz Brenn had griped two weeks earlier that he's never seen me wear jeans... well these are all I have besides my ripped-knee ghetto pants that I never wear.  I also wore my hat and sunglasses, so I was quite out of character... and then me and Brenn and Andy were outside Sara's with this other guy Justin talking and stuff and Brenn instigates a moment of making fun of my pants... I was already a bit insecure about wearing them but did so just to show that I do actually listen to people.  All night people were making little jokes at me, which normally is fine, but these jokes just seemed a little more than usual and to be honest I feel like shit.  I'm sure it was all in good fun, but still... it didn't seem like it this time.  I did get to meet one damn damn damn good looking guy though... damn shame he's already taken.  I can't remember his name, but he was with another guy and they were obviously a couple... he was the shorter of the two with fluffy hair, and my gawd was he gourgeous... he has the most unbelievably gorgeous eyes I've  ever  seen, and I know mom would just eat his hair up... beautiful hair... it was weird, I was checking him out from his neck up... I was so interested in how incredibly attractive his face was and how nice he seemed that I wasn't like  really  checking him out.  Like I said, he's taken, but I can wish can't I?  The guy he was with was nice too, but not the kind of guy I'd look at much =P.  And tomorrow I have a Calculus final at  7:45 in the morning!!   Which means I must sleep now.... good night. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, another week, another trip to Chicago!  This time I went with Andy and Brenn, and I am glad to say that any and all feelings toward Brenn outside of friendship are about dead... Andy and I were at his house waiting for him to get ready and get out the door... thanks to him we ended up running an hour late... no biggie, but it would've been nice to know since we were meeting Art up there... luckily, Art checks his voicemail =P.  Also, within three minutes of being in his house, Brenn starts talking about getting laid... hmm, interesting info... I don't tend to think people should proclaim such things so openly.  I just suddenly became turned off to the idea of ever going out with him, and that's probably a good thing.  Anyway, enough about Brenn... time to talk about Art!! We were all bored up in Chicago, so we drove a bit south down to Harlem Ave. and ate lunch.  Well, Brenn started feeling bad, so we decided to drag Art to Joliet so we could take Brenn home... that actually turned out cool because Art was able to briefly meet my parents and it turned out that he loved Joliet (what planet is he from? lol).  Then on the way back, it hit me... wouldn't it be neat if him and I would hold hands?  So, I took one hand off the wheel and hung it over my armrest wondering if maybe he would do it =P... then he did the same... a few minutes passed and I said something and he smacked me on the leg =P... then a few more minutes passed and I said something and he just kinda tugged on the sleeve of my coat, so I reached up a bit and tried to grab his hand and he took the hint, so we held hands all the way home... it was so sweet!  Now all I can think about is just snuggling with him watching a movie or something... well, he's gonna be here this Wednesday and spend the night and stay all day Thursday, so hopefully there will be some snuggling opportunity in there somewhere =P.  I'm kinda split on what to do... I  really  like Art, but he's leaving for home on Saturday... he lives in San Francisco don't forget.  Then by the time he's back in Chicago, I'll be gone to DeKalb at NIU... of course my little fantasy is that I would have some grand opportunity to ask him if he'd stay with us for the summer, but he's probably rather be in Frisco anyway, and it's not like him and I know each other  that  well.  Eh, I can dream can't I?  He's such a sweetheart and quite a rare find... I really wish him and I had more of an opportunity to develop something... grrrrrr, there's always some sort of barrier!  I did look at what transportation there was from DeKalb to Chicago... no Metra, no Amtrak... but there's Greyhound... $26 round trip... not  too  bad.  I'm just afraid that something might happen between him and I, and I'm not sure if I want that or not.  I guess we'll just see what happens.  Anyway, I just got home from work a half hour ago... had to close tonight, but on the plus side I had my first break ever... heh, anyway, I need some serious sleep.  G'nite all. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, something has happened and that's why I'm not updating this journal any more.  Please email me to find out what happened...  urlLink cragman77@hotmail.com . 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Many people don't believe in magic... they think it's all illusions and superstitions... I am here to tell you that magic does exist.  I experienced this phenomenon of magic last night. I felt something so pure, so extreme, so wonderful... so magical... Those of you who keep up with my journal know about Nate, a guy that I first met back in July of '00, 11 months ago.  I knew right then that I liked him, and those feelings only grew stronger and stronger as time went on.  I met Nate a second time in January.  Both meetings were somewhat  blah  but we had a good time and enjoyed each other's company.  Since then, I've slowly and steadily continued to fall further and further for Nate... Earlier this week, Nate called me and said he wanted to get together... his mom was going to be gone and my parents will be gone until July 1st.  So, Nate came over yesterday around 6:00.  We went to eat at the chinese buffet, rented a movie (Blair Witch 2... not great, but better than expected), and then watched another movie I had (Six Days, Seven Nights).  I then, in person, finally confessed my feelings for Nate.  We were in his car and I tried to tell him but couldn't, so he kept asking, "What is it?  What's wrong?"  Finally, I just thrusted my hand out and held his hand.  After a few minutes, I told him how much I liked him.  Then we got home and sat on the couch... eventually, I grabbed his hand and asked him how he felt about me, to which he responded, "I like you... even in that way somewhat." Nate then leaned over a bit with his head leaned over... I took the next two minutes to muster up the courage and then put my head on his.  He just looked at me, smiled, and wrapped his arms around me... I did the same.  The rest of the night involved wonderful moments like making out to Enya and holding each other until we fell asleep.  Unfortunately, he had to leave, but it took him 15 minutes to get out the door... we kept holding each other and kissing each other... I didn't want him to leave and he didn't want to leave.  He'd said earlier that it felt so wonderful when he held me and when we kissed.  Folks, I think I finally got through to him.  I absolutely hope this leads to something... as it is, I'm on cloud nine.  And for the record, for all of you dirty thinkers out there, we kept ALL of our clothes on (even my socks)... so no...  that  didn't happen, and I'm glad it didn't... though I'll admit there was a certain level of sexual tension there, but I'm glad we both kept our cool.  I can't wait until the next time I can stare into those gorgeous eyes and wrap my arms around him and kiss him softly... I am happier now than I have ever been in my entire life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       OK, that picture from before doesn't want to work... I'll get on that eventually.  Anyway, things have been freakin' awesome lately.  My parents left Monday morning and it's been like one big party here ever since... there has been maybe like 10 hours total since Monday afternoon where there wasn't someone else in my house... it feels great!  And of course there's already been a spot of trouble... one guy drank too much and was praying to the toilet while two other guys got just a bit too intimate... oh well, we're planning the big party for this upcoming Friday night... nothing big, and there won't be anyone getting drunk, especially me... I don't even like drinking a ton... just enough to loosen me up.  Anywayz, so that's that... oh yeah, we converted one of my Dance Dance Revolution pads into a hard board version... it's so freakin' awesome!  So there we go... laterz! 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I just noticed something.... look at the difference in me in the last six months.     Don't you think I look happier on the left?  This is after being out to my friends and not being afraid to express my true self to others... I've finally broken out of my shell and you can see it.  Think of this as inspiration to all of you who fear what others may think of you only to find yourself missing out on life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       PARTY AT RICH's HOUSE!  JUNE 15TH!!!  My parents are gone for three weeks starting this upcoming Monday!  SWEET! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, this is rather interesting.  I need to talk about my new boss, Josh.  Interesting things seem to be happening here.  OK, first off, a little about him.  I'd guess he's in his early 20s, very cute, nice swimmer's build... physically just a great lookin' guy.  He's rather talented too... great with handling people, and he can sing too!  He even used to be a vocal performance major in college.  Now, here's what raises my eyebrows.  2nd day of training, I'd just re-hilighted my hair and so had this one girl, and he said, "Oh look at our two blonde beauties."  Hmm.....  Then that same day I was wearing my Old Navy jacket and he's like "Nice jacket!"  Then, and this one is what gets me... he saw my rainbow necklace the next day and said, "Hey, nice necklace.. that's hot!"  Then, yesterday he calls me into the office and asks me to lace a parking lot with ads.  I do that and come back and he's like showing me pictures of his family and stuff (one of the pics was of him shirtless *grin*)... then he asks me, "How old are you?"  I said 19 and then he's like "Well, do you have a fake I.D.?" as he grins... I say no, so he says, "Well, I was gonna invite you out for a drink, but I guess I'll just have to treat you to lunch some time... how's that sound?"  Of course I say, "Yeah, that sounds fine," while in my head I'm thinking, "WHOAH!!  That's almost like asking me out!  OF COURSE I WILL!!!"  I mean hell, he's damn good looking and a really nice guy... only problem I'd have is the fact that he's my boss, but so what?  I can deal with it.  I just think it's interesting and stuff... that's all =P. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, it's been a while since I've posted.  My new job is going rather well... not as well as I'd hoped, but better than Subway.  I don't really know what to say exactly... I'm taking over the GLBFA club at JJC... I'm staying in Joliet another year to get an associates degree, so you can scrap NIU.  I'm also now a staff member at www.zophar.net which is a pretty big major site.  I'm also VERY tired and want to sleep, so I'll do just that... bye! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       This journal has been continued elsewhere, so email me at rimco@comcast.net to find out where! 
    
    
</post>


<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My name is Richard Craig.  I am currently 21, 22 in just a week.  I live in Joliet, IL, a small city an hour south of Chicago.  I work for Jewel Foods, a subsidiary of Albertson's, in Romeoville, IL.  I am an aspiring musician under the pseudonym, rimco.  I am gay and at the moment single, though I hope I don't stay that way for long.  I am a video game nut, a trekker (not a trekkie, as a friend pointed out), a computer guru, and yet I tend to not be too much of a geek.  My email address is rimco@comcast.net and I am on AIM as ric60431.  To continue back even further than this date, check out my old LiveJournal at  urlLink http://www.livejournal.com/~rimco/ .  If you'd like to go back even further, then check out my original blog at  urlLink http://cragman.blogspot.com/ .  That's it... enjoy! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, I'm looking for a new boyfriend already.  So, how is the hunt going, you ask?  Well, I have my eye on a couple guys from PlanetOut as well as my ex, Joey.  Joey is being a bit of a schmuck though... he won't return my calls... gee, that seems familiar.  One of the guys from PNO is Eric.  He's the coolest!  We actually talked for over an hour just about Star Trek... we racked up over 4 hours total just sitting and chatting.  I'm hoping I can get to know him better... he seems like a really nice guy.  The other guy... hell, I don't even know his name, but I thought he was cute and I said hi and he's one of those people that just kinda muddles through a conversation... eh, he's probably stuck up... s'pose he wouldn't want to date one of those skanky Joliet guys, of course... so now I'm back on PNO looking for more options.  I'm tenacious. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, so needless to say I have been having a REALLY ROUGH time ever since I broke up with Artis.  So I called him, told him what's been happening, and we met up.  We talked, held hands, told each other how we felt, and I realized that none of this agony I'm going through would be happening if I had just stayed with him.  Granted, things weren't perfect when we were together, but it was a hell of a lot better than this dating shit, always second guessing people and whatnot.  So, he wants some time to think about it, so I'm not gonna put all of my eggs in one basket just yet, but I have a feeling things may return to the way they were... not perfect, but acceptable, and that's all I can ask for. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, things totally went to hell in a handbasket... people with less skill than me are getting better positions than me at work... Joey, my ex, totally makes out with me a couple weeks ago and then gives me the cold shoulder and then says "oh let's just be friends", Junior does the same, and I'm just fucking done.  I'm tired.  I'm broken.  I just don't know how I can feel any more with everyone doing this to me.  Maybe it's my fault... I'm sure it is in some way, but fuck, people don't have to make a problem worse by toying with my emotions like this.  It really makes one wonder what the point of it all is... why the hell are we all here?  Why am I here when fate intends me to feel anything but happiness? 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so I have tonight off and Junior is a night owl, so we're hoping to hang out after his rehearsal and stuff after 10... probably won't be until midnight when we're able to hang out, but I'm up all night anyway.  I really hope I get to see him... it's not like i'm obsessed with him, but he really is a neat guy, just the kind of guy I can see myself with.  Anyway, for now I think I will take a nap so I can stay awake later. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, I need to stop planning my days around tentative plans and shit.  I was talking to Junior early this morning while I was on break at work, and I thought he and I were going to work on moving some of his stuff up to his place in the city... I thought that way I could help out and we'd be able to spend some time together.  Well go figure, now his godfather and brother and brother's friend are all going with him and guess who's not going?  Yup, I got the boot.  I wouldn't be bothered by it except I've been sitting around all day waiting for him to call, wondering if he was even going to call at all, and now I find out that I'm not doing a damned thing today.  I guess it just kinda pisses me off a bit, but it's my own damned fault I guess.  I just keep thinking about him for some reason... he has so many of the qualities I look for in a guy that it's hard not to dwell on him.  Anyway, here I sit all dressed up and ready to go somewhere, and I've nowhere to go... aggravating, considering this happens to me all the time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yes!  Rich unexpectedly found someone!  **In valley girl/ fag voice** Soo, lemme tell ya aaalll about him! His name is Bruce, though everyone calls him Junior.  He was one of the people who actually IMed me from my profile on Planetout, which is awesome cuz I love it when they come to me instead of me searching PNO or XY and finding bitches.  So, we chatted a few times online, exchanged pictures, and the superficial side of me said, "Ah, well he's pretty nice looking."  Boy, was I waaay off.  After talking some online, we decided to watch Punch Drunk Love together (which I highly recommend but only if you're well awake, otherwise you'll get lost) and woo, when I actually saw him for the first time, I just kinda stopped in my tracks like oh-my-god... yeah, he's that good looking.  Anywayz, after some pillow fighting and goofy hand wrestling he started petting my hair *shivers*.  Now don't get me wrong, I loved my ex to death, but he never was all that tactile unless we were, well, intimate.  Having someone just cuddle with me and pet my head... it just felt so incredibly wonderful... I'm sure he noticed that my heart was racing *grins*.  Then it went a step further... after a couple nervous twitches, we kissed.  I haven't felt such exhiliration over a kiss in forever, and it was so tender and sweet.  Amazingly, considering my track record, things didn't go further than that, and I'm so glad.  I'm sick of people, myself included, letting their hormones run away with them.  It ended with him having to go home to get some rest... he's working on moving up to the city, though according to him, he plans to come back to town quite often, which is great.  It was just simply one of the nicest nights ever for me.  I am really really hoping something will come out of this... he's very bright, very artistic, and very talented.  He even likes my music, lol!  So, I think it's safe to say that I'll be counting the minutes until we see each other again... for the first time in quite a while, I'm happy. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, yeah, I just realized why I love DeadAIM so much... AIM cloning.  It lets you open multiple buddy windows with different screennames.  What I just did was copied my main buddy list to all of the others.  What happens when I set them side-by-side?  Well there seem to be some discrepencies.  What seems to have happened is that certain people have blocked me... some I get, some I don't.  So here's today's list! Belief14 - This is Tim, the guy I hung out with yesterday and didn't really click with... obviously he agrees, and obviously my guess that he was your typical Naperville bitch was right as well *wink* KoKoKraKah - Maybe this one was a mistake, cuz this is my buddy Mikey who lives out in Washington... there's no beef between us, so maybe he clicked by accident. There's one other person who does show up on my list and not on the others, and that's just cuz he has an allow list, so that's nothing to worry about.  Of course Eric has blocked all THREE of my screennames now... what a bitch.  People simply amaze me sometimes... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, the hunt continues, and we have some updates.  Things with Eric died quickly... he won't return my calls and won't talk to me online... I guess I'm surprised, but men suck anyway.  I met another guy, Tim, up in Naperville.  He's a nice guy, but not exactly my type... we didn't really click at all.  Then there's Darren.  He lives out in NC, but he's going to move here to Chicago.  He's this gorgeous black guy, my height, slender and smooth, just how I like them, lol!  To make things better, he's an awesome guy too!  I've offered to let him stay here a week or so while I'm on vacation from the 4th to 8th.  I'm trying to think of cool things to do around here.  I wanna go to the waterpark, but I need to work on mah belly and get a tan, so Id better get crackin'!  I hope Darren is as nice in person as he is online.  I've actually had him on my mind a lot, which is weird.  I need to stop going gaga over guys I don't even know.  Anyway, I'm off to dinner with the folks... let's hope my manhunt goes well, cuz I'm already sick of being single. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, so it's been over a week since I updated, so here we go.  I've been on vacation all week and go back at 12:30am Tuesday morning.  After more talks with Artis last week, it's obvious things are not going to reinstate, and I think I'm learning to accept that.  Dan wants to, well, go out with me, but that's far too complicated, and I just don't think it's a smart choice to pursue that at all.  So, there I was, all single, not too worried about it, and then I started talking to my buddy Yumi, a guy who contacted me from Planetout.  For some reason, I was kinda hesitant to meet him... I have no idea why, but I was.  Eventually though, I forced myself to... I have to stop being so damned picky and just meet people, and I think meeting Yumi proved that to me.  What I found when I met him was a cute, sweet, goofy, fun guy.  I was actually quite struck by him, so I decided to meet him again.  So that's twice I drove 80 miles round-trip to see him, haha... I'm always the one driving, but I love my car anyway, so who cares.  Both times we had fun, walked around outside a bit, just hung out... ok, well last time we maybe did a teensy bit more than hang out, but yeah... at least it shows we're interested in each other in some way.  I just hope this isn't another one of those situations where someone makes out with me and then does a disappearing act... doesn't seem likely though as he's driving down to visit me tomorrow... can't wait!  It's not like I'm going ga-ga for him... I've done that enough times to know it doesn't do anyone any good, so I'm holding back a bit, yeah, but maybe this time it'll work.  I just wanna meet a decent guy for christ's sake!  Hopefully that's exactly what I've done this time. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Today was a decent day, all-in-all.  Worked from 11-7, got home, called Artis and told him to come get his Dreamcast... when he came over, I barely even made eye contact... I hurts too much to even look at him... oh god he looked so good too, cuz he finally got his hair done.  It was just this kind of afro thing, but he got it braided down... gah... why I ever jeopardized that relationship is beyond me, but if it wasn't meant to be, then I guess this is one way to find out.  So I hung out with Dan... drove to Super Wal-Mart in Plano for a change... sick of driving to Morris for my Wal-Mart madness fix.  We hung out here for another hour or so and now here I am, typing and sleepy.  Gotta work at 11, so it's off to sleep with me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       By the way, that was also not meant as a chastization... err, is that a word?  But yeah, I'm just throwing my opinion out there... not trying to knock anyone.  And also, thanks to going back on my meds, I'm quite stable for a change... it does feel pretty good, but I still don't have to like it!  ::grins:: 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I actually worked during the day today, yay!  I also found the clause in the union contract that says I don't have to work overnights if I don't want to... go me!  Otherwise, it was actually a rather boring day for once... go me again!  By the way, since I know he's gonna read my blog... Chris, I wasn't chastizing you for posting about hot guys... it's just that, well, we didn't just "hang out" that night... I'm sorry if that means more to me than it does to you... like my PNO profile said, these things mean something to me... maybe you missed that part before you decided to IM me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so I totally failed in both quitting smoking and also in stopping my medication.  I had a complete nervous breakdown today... you know, the kind where you're bawling so much you can't stand, where you're so angry you start finding things to break, the kind where you... umm... contemplate your own life... ugh, yeah, that was really scary, and of course not a single friend of mine was there to help me.. I called people just looking for someone to talk to, and everyone was either too busy or not answering or something, so I just had to deal on my own... luckily I won the battle against my insanity.  So yes, my happy little white pills are now dancing in my brain, keeping me from feeling the pain of life and, well, keeping me from feeling much of anything at all really.  I think that's why I hate them so much... they keep me from getting depressed, but they also keep me from feeling really happy or anything like that... they just kinda turn down ALL of my emotions, even the good ones. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yes, I cracked... I'm still smoking... I just can't do this now.  After seeing that things obviously weren't going anywhere with Chris (seeing as how nearly every post he makes in his blogger is each about a different guy he's pining over), I talked to Dan.  As I've said, Dan has issues, issues that I haven't been sure I would be able to tackle with him.  Well, I think I'm just gonna go for it... fuck, it can't be any worse than what's been happening to me lately anyway.  My job is getting worse... my hours have been cut from 48 to 32 this week... come on people, I'm not the one who's on strike here!  I've just had a complete and total apathy for life lately... I feel alone... extremely alone.  I feel as though right now there is nothing that would make me happy... nothing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I was smoking my last cigarette as I made my last post announcing I was going to quit.  Well, I'm getting really really... yuck.  I'm thinking that total cold turkey might not be the answer, but I've made that excuse before and just ended up smoking like I always do.  Bah... fucking things. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As I continue to sit here and ponder what I have just shared with the world, I have decided something.  I'm going to stop taking my medication.  I'm also going to try to quit smoking.  I'm sick of these vices... it's bullshit.  I'm stronger than this, I know it!  I'm not going to let some fucking tobacco or depression get the best of me.  Damn it all to hell, you hear me?  I can do this... if I have to, I'll do it alone.  The world can suck my fucking ass. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yay, I just got back from Chicago a little while ago... went to Market Days, and it was, well, OK.  It really didn't strike me as anything all that special, just another reason for a bunch of gay people to get together and try and look cute for each other... yack.  I'm quickly growing sick of the gay community in general, I really am.  Everything just seems so superficial anymore.  All anyone is interested in is a cute guy they can have a fun night or two with and then that's it.  That's not what I want... I want a man, someone I can be with, enjoy my time with, and not have to worry about whether or not he's just using me.  Is that too much to ask?  I met up with Chris at Market Days... didn't talk much cuz my friends and I were finishing up just as his friends and he were getting there.  It was nice to at least see him and get some opinions from my friends... they think he's a pretty cool guy.  I was horribly tired on the train ride home, and when I get tired, I get damned goofy.  I was making barnyard noises and whatnot the whole trip home.. well, except for that half hour I was knocked out asleep.  Market Days seems to rank the same with me as the parade... interesting the first or second time you go, but for me, I think I'm done with this sort of thing.  I don't know what to do... it's to the point where if you're gay, you're in the scene... you do what everyone else does... there is no individuality left.  I had the perfect man, a guy who was himself and was just what I wanted, and I fucked it up as I always do.  It kills me a little more each day knowing that I ruined something with so much potential.  It kills me even more to remember everything I went through before I met Artis and then to realize that I may have to go through all of that again and then some before I can find someone else just as special as he was.  And no, it's not like I'm trying to replace him, find someone just like him... I just want to find someone that I can connect with on that level again, and it just seems like I can't.  I've honestly been so incredibly depressed lately that if I weren't taking my medication, I don't know if I would be sitting here.  Even that bothers me, that in essence I have to take a fucking pill to keep me from hurting myself... what wonderful self control I have, huh?  It was funny, when I was with Artis, when I was with that person that I felt so absolutely wonderful with, my medication became obsolete, unnecessary.  Now that I'm without him, I have become a slave to it more than ever.  It's terrifying to know what I would be capable of if I didn't have any help... and I know first hand, because I almost took a brush with death when I was in college, for no reason at all other than I was just depressed.  It's times like this, when I ponder life itself, its purpose, its validity, when I wish I had that special someone by my side, someone I could share all of this with, someone whose shoulder I could cry on, someone who would hold me and tell me it will all be OK.  I don't have that any more, and that is what makes life so unbearable for me right now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, yeah, I made an ass out of myself two-fold this morning.  I had read Chris's blog and saw that, well, he didn't mention me other than one line saying he went to Joliet, yet he had a huge post about some guy at the Apple store he went to... well, the post he made about the Apple store, even though it says it was made afterward, was actually saved from beforehand.  So what does my paranoid ass do?  I asked him to call me when he got home and I brought it up to him.  Anyway, he told me that he really did have a good time here in Joliet and that it wasn't just "all in good fun" like he'd said.  I'm very relieved.  God, it's just so hard for me to do this stuff any more, it really is.  So many people have treated me so badly in the past, and especially after what happened with Artis... I'm absolutely petrified to even see guys, let alone consider a relationship with them.  It's to the point where I'm constantly paranoid, and it's just not fair, not to me or the guy I'm involved with.  I start imagining things, and I need to stop doing that... my imagination is way too wild. So, that was at 4:30 in the morning, and I was supposed to get up at 6 to get ready for Market Days.... and I didn't wake up until Ezzy called me at 8:15... the train leaves at 8:24... yeah.  Well, she and her friend David were also running late and not sure if they would make it on time anywayz, so they're just both gonna come hang out over here until the 10:24 train, which does get us there later than we wanted to, but hey, at least we'll still be there. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, so I would say that plenty has been going on lately, so let me clue you in.  Let's start with where we left off... Yumi.  I'll say this, he's a nice guy, he really is.  Things sorta got a little more involved when he came to visit me, and well, I just wasn't feeling it.  It's not that I'm not ready for another relationship, but I just wasn't feeling that sorta thing with him.  I've sorta, well, not avoiding him but not going out of my way to make contact, ya know?  So, then I just recently met Christopher.  He's a really cool guy, rather intellectual, but not too heady.  He's definitely the type of guy I like.  He's been in NC all summer with his family, and he just got back to the city Thursday.  We've been talking online for a good while now, few weeks, and we decided to hang out over here.  We had a great time and all, so I came up to the city tonight to visit him and watch a play put on by his group he's in, the About Face Youth Theatre.  It was really really good.  Things didn't go quite so well afterward, though.  I'd already told him how I don't function well at all at social things, and he still wanted me to go to the cast party afterwards, so I did.  Of course, being the social butterfly that he is, he disappeared off to the dance floor and kinda left me staring at the wall, so I left rather early from that.  So, I certainly don't blame him for that... he was with all of his friends that he hadn't seem all summer, and that was exciting for him, but I'll admit I did feel a little left out.  He walked me to my car when I left, which was nice of him, though I was a little, well not upset, but disappointed that I didn't even get a kiss goodbye.  Tomorrow, Ezzy and her friend David and I are all going up to the city for Market Days, and at some point we're going to meet Chris there, so we'll see how it goes.  I'm not sure if this'll turn into anything, but I'm gonna hope for the best... he's a neat guy, and we have fun together. So, let's move on to the issue of work.  The warehouse employees are going on strike, so that means that our loads are, well, coming at weird times or not coming at all, and seeing as how I"m on the overnight crew, whose sole purpose is to work the load, my shifts have been really thrown off.  I was scheduled last night at 11:30, but they asked me to come in at 6am this morning.  I said fine, but when I showed up, the load was still 6-8 hours from arriving, so they said I could go home.  Well, at 4pm, they called me and asked me to come back in, and I was like "I sorta have plans for the night and also early tomorrow.. I can't do it."  I also basically told them that from now on I don't plan to come in at all of these weird times, because I just don't think that is fair at all... I should be able to show up when the schedule says I should instead of finding out a few hours ahead of time when I should be there.  Luckily, according to the union contract, I have every right to do just that, and I plan to.  Anyway, I'm tired and have to be up really early, so off I go. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My Star Trek obsession is horrible... I've already watched the entire first season of DS9 and I NEED MORE!!!  Wow, I had no idea the show was this good, and the first season is considered the worst?!  My DKC remix is pretty much done... just have to do the cleanup work and the post-production to make it sound nifty!  It turned out really good!  I can't wait to get it on OC Remix and see what people think!  Anywayz, I'm gonna get some sleep... our grocery load tonight is going to be about 1600 pieces... usually it's about 600-800... oh... my.... god this is going to SUCK! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just spent $100 on the first season of Depp Space Nine... oh god, what have I done?!  Now I'm going to have to get them all!  And when Voyager comes out on DVD next year, I'm going to have to get them all too!  This is turning into a really expensive hobby!  Damn you, Star Trek!  Damn you!! ::grins:: 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       First off, everyone loves my new remix... I can't wait to finish it and get it online! Second off, I just put a profile on XY.com, so maybe I'll get some responses there. Third off, considering Dan, I've decided that I won't be pursuing that.  I just really value him so greatly as a friend that the thought of a relationship with him is almost awkward.  He feels more like a brother than a potential boyfriend. Fourth off, I've noticed a growing trend in people talking online... a complete and total lack of away messages.  I'll be talking to someone and then they'll just ::poof!:: disappear!  No away message, no "brb", no nothing, just no response for a half hour.  And being the dork I am, I usually sit around waiting for them to respond back only cuz I don't want to be as impolite to them as they are being to me... eh, I'm stupid like that. Fifth off, I'm back on overnights at work this week... oh goody ::yack!:: Sixth off, Dan's friend Eric is the hottest guy in the world, and I am not kidding.  Whoever said all the cute guys in the world are gay is full of shit.  I just had to get that off my brain ::grins:: 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm sending that remix to some of my fans, and so far everyone has guessed what it is!  See, people like that song! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       "Blah" is becoming my favorite word, ousting "wheee", because that's just how I feel any more.  Fought with Joey of all people last night... oddly enough, I started off in a horrible mood and ended up laughing my ass off at how stupid he is.  I was gonna post the whole conversation on here, but I wasd arguing that he was being childish, and posting that here would be just as childish, and I refuse to stoop to his level.  Everything else is, well, boring.  I'm still alone, blah.  I started work on a decent new song for once... a remix of Aquatic Ambience from the SNES game Donkey Kong Country... everyone says that's their favorite song from the series, and I sorta inadvertantly remixed it, yay!  Anyway, there's nothing much to say really, so off I go! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So yeah, I woke up yesterday at 9AM and haven't been to sleep since... and I'm wide awake... not cool.  Work was HELL today, simply put, enough said.  I haven't been online since yesterday afternoon cuz I've been working on my massive rearrangement of my living room... it's nearing completion, yay!  Life is still biting me in the ass, but eh, what can ya do... I'll just go take some happy pills and sleep my cares away. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As I watch a guy blow a balloon out of a women's contraceptive, I sit here chowing on pretzels and asking myself why I'm still single.  Am I a bad person?  I don't think so.  Like I said before, I'm a blunt person.  Just because other people can't handle the blatant truth doesn't mean I should be labeled a bitch.  Am I too clingy?  Maybe by other people's standards, but then again most of those other people aren't really looking for a serious relationship anyway... they don't even know what a serious relationship is.  Clingy is when you're practically stalking someone or demand all of their time.  I don't demand all of anyone's time, but I think it's fair to demand some of it, and I think it's fair to be aggravated when everything else comes before me.  It's like I'm explaining to my friend Chris right now, I'm not one of these young adults who's trying to "find myself."  I found myself a long time ago, and I'm comfortable with myself.  My need for a significant other has nothing to do with any insecurities I have.  Problem is older guys tend to see me as just another kid, so I'm stuck in this sort of limbo, a space between, and it's a lonely place to be.  I'm wondering if I'm ever going to find someone who understands me... it's not that I'm complicated... I'm just unique.  Uniqueness seems to scare people. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       akarimco: you seem to be the only one awake this morning ric60431: yeah, you too akarimco: so how have you been? ric60431: you don't know? akarimco: well i suppose I do ric60431: this conversation is going to be stupid akarimco: so why are we having it? ric60431: who's we? akarimco: now now, don't get jealous ric60431: well i think i'm going to go akarimco: me too ric60431: bye akarimco: bye  Why is this so stupid?  Because both screennames are mine.  Yes, I was having a conversation with myself... boredom is a terrible thing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Um, yeah... I'm bored.  But I'm special... Christopher says so.  Wheee! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I've been practicing that trumpet of mine off-and-on the last few days, and I'm actually getting better already... my lip is coming back!  Now my lips are so tired though that I can hardly whistle (not that I really could whistle all that well in the first place).  I've had a startling revelation in the last couple days that has the potential to radically alter my life...  I don't belong in Chicagoland.  I've never realised until recently how out-of-place I feel here.  My attitude just doesn't fit!  I'm a blunt, sometimes crass, person, and that seems to offend people around here.  It's like people can't handle the truth!  But where does that attitude fit in?  I know exactly where... where I'm from.  I've spent an equal amount of my life between the Chicago metro area and the Philly metro area, and I SO belong in Philly!  I feel that no matter how long I live here, "home" will always be back on the East coast.  Hell, I was even born here in Illinois, but that doesn't matter... Philly is the place for me!  Lucky for me, Albertson's, the company that owns Jewel, also owns Acme, a prevalent grocery chain out there.  The possibility of a transfer exists, so now I'm left with many hard decisions to make. Obviously I don't really want to move away from my folks, but they're moving to Arkansas in a year or two anyway, and I'm sure as hell not moving down there with them, yuck!  So what else is holding me here?  My home?  I can get a better one for less money in Philly.  My friends?  Friends are important, but I do have friends back home too, friends I haven't seen in ages.  What else is there?  No love in my life... no ties there.  There isn't much holding me here except the effort it would take to move.  I'd have to go through the trouble of selling my home, buying a new one, moving all of my shit, stuff like that.  I'm just ready for a change... a radical change.  My life is starting to feel stagnant.  I need to find a way to breathe new life into it!  So, I'm trying to figure out how I can get away for a few days to go visit friends in Jersey and scope the area out, make sure it hasn't changed too much from what I remember.  The one thing that I need to sort out is lodging... I don't have the money to put myself in a hotel for a few days, so I need to find a friend I can stay with.  I think I can work it out to where I can get like 5 days off in a row and only lose a day of pay, considering my managers would work with me on that.  I just NEED to get back out there, even if only for a short while.  I miss it terribly.  Anywayz, hopefully I can find an old friend to stay with or something while I'm out there, otherwise I'm not sure how I'm going to swing this. In other news, life is boring, as usual.  That's all... just boring.  Blah.  If I had a man, maybe I wouldn't be so up and ready to jet outta here... I just hope that if I do decide to take that path that it's the right path to take.  I miss my home... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Haha, fickle seems to be a difficult word to type... erm, anywayz... ugh. I can't make up my mind about anything any more.  I'm still not sure what to do with Dan, so forget it, I'm gonna stop analyzing and just let things run their course.  I'm not gonna stop looking for someone, but I'm not gonna ignore any possibilities with Dan either.  I'm just gonna sit back and see what happens.  On one side, things are like I'd said, a tad awkward for me, but on the other hand, we're just such kindred spirits, and he has this incredible sweetness that doesn't surface often, but when it does, it's enough to make me cry.  I'm always yelling at Dan to stop overanalyzing everything, and maybe it's time for me to practice what I preach.  I got a trumpet today!  They had some at Sam's Club, and it was $170.. my mom took me there to look at it, and I said it felt good, so she said, "Well, if you want it, there it is." I was like, "I don't have $170... I can't get it right now... but I'll save up for it." "Well I have $170," she says, giving me that look.  I felt kinda bad and spoiled rotten at the idea of her just giving it to me, but she just kept chiming in... "OK, Richard, just pick up the trumpet and put it in the cart." "That's it, I'm not arguing with you any more... you wanna give me stuff, I'm not gonna worry about it any more."  So I put the trumpet in the cart and was happy, lol.  She's always doing that, and that's why I love her... not just cuz she spoils me, but cuz she gets so much happiness out of giving.  I do too, but I have a hard time parting with my hard-earned money, lol. Anyways, it's an awesome trumpet, sounds great, and I love it!  I can't wait to put it to good use! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just started thinking of Artis, but not in the way I have been as of late... I'm realizing that I'm starting to get over him.... starting to, that is.  I'll never be truly over him, but eh, that's life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Oh...... my........ GOD..... I'm watching Celebrity Yearbook on E! and they just showed a couple pictures of Lenny Kravitz in high school... holy fuck... ho-ly-fuuuuuck.  If I could meet a man now that looks like Lenny did in HS, I'd just pounce on him... in public... rip his clothes off... yummmm! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       22 years old, and I need reading glasses... how cute.  I'm using them right now at the computer and wow, my eyes feel nice and comfy rather than straining to see the screen... I never realized how farsighted this LASIK surgery made me.  So now I look like a little old man with my little reading glasses... blah.  I just found that amuzing is all.  Wheee! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       ...I wonder if there will ever be a day when I can replace my medicine with the love of another, for love is the ultimate medicine, the only thing that can cure my condition... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So today is my day off... I'm just sitting here fantasizing about my dream man... realizing my newfound obsession with black men... just wishing some nice guy would pass my way by chance... blah.  I know there's a guy out there that I'd match so well with... hell I've even met some, but they either live too far away, are already taken, or are closet cases.  It's just so fucking destitute, I mean I really think I'm a good guy and that I have a lot to offer someone, but nobody seems to care.  This loneliness is just insane.  I have myself... I'm happy with myself... I'm comfortable with myself... I'm just empty, incomplete, when I have nobody to share myself with.  Oh god... here I go again... I need to take some happy pills before I start bawling all over the place again...  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just met one of the most sparkling people I've ever met.  His name is Rockett, yes, just like the thing that fires into the sky.  He and I spent the evening together hanging out and playing videogames and stuff like that... very fun.  I have NEVER met someone with whom I have felt such a humoristic connection with... we were literally cracking up the entire night!  I have a rather off-kilter sense of humor, and the fact that his sense of humor matches mine so perfectly is just awe inspiring to me.  On top of that, his looks are also quite awe inspiring... he's just a remarkably attractive guy.  He's the kind of guy I could totally fall for in three seconds, and yet once again life is toying with me, and I must do everything I can to keep from developing any sort of feelings for him.  The reason for this is because he's not single.  I honestly didn't know this at first... I found out during our discussion over dinner (at Subway, of course, lol).  I'll admit, it sorta let the wind out of my sails, but he's such a shining person that I would love just to be friends with him... I would be honored just to be friends with him.  He's just a remarkable guy from what I know of him so far.  It's such a shame that when I finally meet someone that I click with, he's unavailable.  It's just another blow to my soul, another round fired into the fabric of my emotions... I'm becoming quite tattered and torn.  I am, however, still intact, and I suppose I should be thankful for that. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just finished a three hour conversation with Mr. Georgy Porgie there in Delaware.  What a crack-up!  He seems like a genuinely nice guy... shame he has to be so far away cuz I'd love to meet him.  Talking to him reminded me of two people... one was my friend Brian from back in NJ, but that's mostly cuz of the accent from the area.  He also reminded me of... Nate.  Yes, the guy that mercilessly broke my heart by trying to convince me that he was dead rather than just say he didn't want to see me any more.  I don't mean that George reminds me of the kind of guy who would do something so dastardly, just that his voice sounds a bit like Nate's, or at least how I remember Nate, considering I haven't spoken to him in over two years and have more or less tried to block out any memory of the little prick.  But yes, George seems really cool.  We had some interesting things in common, like a fondness for Star Trek, we were both in band, and interesting stuff like that... a couple things we aren't in total sync on, like he's the social butterfly type who loves to dance and that sorta crazy stuff, whereas I'm the type who ends up sitting alone in the corner.  He also doesn't like smoking at all, which, well, I'll just have to not smoke around him.  I've always respected people who don't like cig smoke by not smoking around them, with the exception of while driving... driving is my ultimate vice that I can't overcome.  Driving without a cigarette is like driving without a right foot.  Besides, you can just roll down the windows and it's like the smoke isn't even there.  Anywayz, hopefully these phone conversations won't be too uncommon, as I quite enjoyed it.  Now I have just that little bit more motivation to get my ass out to the east coast for a brief stint.  Until then, I'm sure my miserably boring life here will continue as usual... blah... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Today's bit of blah, wheee!  Work was boring but livable.  This afternoon is boring.  Tonight will undoubtedly be... yup, you guessed it... boring.  I work days this week, which rocks my world.  I've strangely found myself thinking a bit about this guy I've met online... his name is George... we've only talked a little online and exhanged a couple emails, but he totally cracks me up... really funny guy.  He's also, well, remarkably attractive from what I can see in his pic.  The problem?  He lives in Smyrna, DE.  Yes.... "Hi... I'm in Deleware."  Granted, I'm considering moving out there, but yeah... blah.  He seems really cool though... hopefully I'll get to know him better as we continue to chit chat online.  Cripes, that's just what I need is to start pining over some guy 750 miles away... resist, Richard!  Resist!  You don't even know him!  BLAAARRRG!  I'm so miserably single... ugh... I hate it! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Whoo... yeah... ain't updated in a couple days.  I'm talking to Andrew right now... we had originally planned to hang out today, but that didn't work out and we're not sure when we'll be able to see each other next.  I'm starting to miss him... haven't seen him in several days now.  Hopefully we'll be able to see each other soon.  In other news, I got in a bit of a fight with my store manager today, and I don't really want to go into detail now cuz I'm still quite upset.  It's just a mess.  I really don't know how much more of this overnight stuff I can take.  Eh, I'm getting in one of my moods, and I don't feel like typing any more, so that's all for tonight, folks. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, so I didn't get any sleep today until 9pm and I proceeded to sleep until 11pm... oh yeah, a whole two hours.... so in the last 36 hours, I have slept two... wonderful... my brain is deeeeep fried.  I suppose I have Andrew to blame, lol... no actually it's my own fault for not sleeping this morning before picking him up from school... I think it was a fair tradeoff though, cuz I really enjoyed my time with him.  He did a little homework, we watched the Simpsons and Will & Grace and all that good stuff... he's such a sweety... I really hope things are developing between us... I think they are, but that doesn't count if he doesn't see it the same way... something tells me he does though :).  So yeah, I'm going to go get all ready for bed, pop a couple sleeping pills, and sleep the day away... wheee! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well first off, I'm sick.  Well I was mostly sick yesterday, but that caused me to get little sleep and so work this morning was hell... pure hell.  I didn't leave early though, and I'm proud of that.  I showed up a half hour late cuz I sorta dozed off, but that's no biggie.  This afternoon I'm going to pick up Andrew from school, and we're going to hang out and get to know each other some more... how fun!  I just read Christopher's blog and stuff about how his church now knows he's gay and is quite pissy about it.  That's why I don't like church, even the gay-friendly ones.  They're telling me what to believe in, whereas I feel that each person should be free to believe in whatever they want.  I feel like blathering for a bit, so...  Welcome to Rich's Personal Theology 101.  Hello class.  Today we're going to discuss three often misunderstood religious viewpoints, agnostic, atheistic, and nontheistic.  Agnosticism is basically another way of saying that you haven't yet discovered your spiritual beliefs.  "Is there a god or not?  Is there some sort of supernatural force that makes the world go round?  I haven't a clue!"  This is what one who is agnostic would say.  They are unsure of what to believe in and are sorta "soul searching."  They do not necessarilly disbelieve in god, as is commonly misconceived.  Atheism, however, is rarely misconceived.  It is quite simply the disbelief in any form of supernatural force governing the universe.  To an atheist, there is no God, there is no "mother nature", there is no spirit.  We're all just a clever bunch of chemicals in a world that just happens to stay so well balanced.  Many people who claim to be atheist are not truly, because atheism is disbelieving in any form of spirituality or supernaturality.  Simply saying you do not believe in God does not make you an atheist.  Then there is nontheism.  This is what I personally subscribe to.  An example of a nontheistic "religion" would be Buddhism.  Buddhist follow the teachings of the Buddha, a man who walked the earth centuries ago in a search for the end of suffering, "nirvana".  When he found nirvana, he proceeded to teach everyone how they too can find nirvana... would've made a great infomercial!  In the end, his teachings formed a method which is followed and practiced today by Buddhists across the globe.  The key thing here is that Buddha was a man.  Buddha is not a god, he is not supernatural, he was just a man like you and I.  He just happened to accomplish something that had never been done before.  So then the question that remains is, "Do Buddhists believe in a God?"  The answer is simple... who cares!  That's the heart of nontheism.  The concept of a God or the question of whether or not there is a God or other supernatural force is quite irrelevant to the life of a Buddhist or nontheist.  These people find their spirituality from within and focus on that, not on exterior supernatural forces, whether or not they exist.  Nontheists do not say there is no God; if there is one, that's wonderful!  Nontheists also do not say that there IS a God; if there isn't, so be it!  It's just not in the interests of a nontheist to spend his or her day contemplating and soul searching and blah blah on and on trying to figure out if there is something there than can't be seen nor felt nor consciously experienced.  I had this on my mind at work, and man, I had it worded to eloquently in my mind and now that it's here, it's not quite as good, but yeah... I neither believe in or disbelieve in God or other supernatural forces... I just don't really care.  It's kinda like the old saying...  What's the difference between ignorance and indifference?  I don't know  and  I don't care .  I suppose it's more of a witticism than just a saying, but the same applies to agnosticism and nontheism... agnosticism is an ignorance of God, whereas nontheism is an indifference toward God.  Anyway, that's enough ranting for now... I need food, a shower, Star Trek, and sleep... the basic four for any healthy lifestyle, lol! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well it's about fucking time!  Yesterday evening, I finally met a pretty awesome guy, and I think that this time things actually WILL develop.  I suppose this is where I tell you all about him :)  His name's Andrew, he lives in the southern outskirts of Chicago, he's adorable, sweet, and actually WANTS a relationship.  He's also pretty stinkin' good at videogames =P.  Here I am, Mr. Musician, and I was losing my ass in Bust-A-Groove.  We still have a lot to learn about each other, but he seems like a really decent guy.  I can't wait for us to spend more time together.  On the musical front, I've just begun work on a song that mixes club-style dance music with jazz... yes, jazz.  Oh man, it's gonna be awesome!  I'm gonna try and get some trumpet in there for good measure.  Anywayz, there's the latest on my life... woopdee! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Why email this when I can put it here for the whole world to see?   1. Full Name: Richard James Craig  2. Nicknames: Rich, Dipstick, Dick (i hate that one)   3. Eyes: Brown  4. Height: 6ft.  5. Hair: Light Brown  6. Siblings: 3 older half-brothers, Raimie, Jaimie, and Toby  7. Do you sing in the shower? Occasionally  8. Do you like to sing? I'm a musician; of course.  9. Birthday: July 19, 1981  10. Sign: Cancer  11. Where you live: Joliet, IL  12. Sex: been entirely too long  13. Righty or Lefty: Lefty!  14. What do you want most in a relationship? Passion, intimacy, committment, honesty, decency  15. Have you ever cheated on a test? Nope!  16. Marital Status: Single  19. Favorite Movie: Goodness, probably Moulin Rouge  20. Favorite Song: Dark Heart Dawning by BT  21. Favorite Book: I don't really care for reading  22. TV Show: Star Trek, lol  23. Actor: Harrison Ford  24. Actress: Not really sure  25. Food: Seafood  26. Number: 2, cuz everything is more fun in pairs!  27. Cartoon: Ren and Stimpy  28. Disney Character: Mufasa!... Mufasa Mufasa Mufasa, woohoohoo  29. Color: Royal Blue  30. Do you plan on having kids? heeeell no.  31. If so, how many? kids are evil  32 Favorite names for your kids? Joseph Leno or Marina Gabrielle  33. How old do you want to be when you are married? Any time will do!  34. Would you have kids before marrage? Obviously not  35 Do you have a b-f g-f? Ha!  I wish.  36. Do you like someone? Kinda sorta, but not really   37 Music/TV: Music  38. Guys/Girls: men men men men... girls are such a turn-off   39. Green/Blue: Blue  40. Pink/Purple: Purple  41. Summer/Winter: eh, both have their ups and downs  42. Night/Day: I used to be a night person until I started working overnights... now I'd rather be awake during the day  43. Hangin' Out/Chillin': same dif?  44. Dopey/Funny: Dopey  45. You know I'm around when you hear: my imitation of Goat Boy  46. What school do you go to? Llama University (inside joke)... actually, none.  47. What year/what are you studying? I was studying computer science, but it wasn't my cup o' tea.  48. What do you want to do with your life? just be happy  49. How far would you go on a first date? More like how far HAVE I gone... and that would be pretty far ::grins::  50 Most blonde friend: Probably Mista Clova, you dipstick  51. Nicest: probably Shanan  52. Funniest: definitely Shanan  53. Tallest: Ryan by far, he's like 6'6"  54. Best personality: they wouldn't be my friends if they didn't all have the best personality  55. Which 6 people do you trust and are open with the most? that requires too much thinking  56 What do you think of soul mates? I've believed in that since I was a little kid  57. Do you have a soul mate? I'd better!  58. What was the last thing you cried or got teary about? Got a little teary while recording for my last song, cuz I tried to really get into it  59. What's something about guys/girls you don't get? I don't get girls at all... they baffle me.  60. Why? Cuz I'm a 'mo, duh.   61. What's an object you can't live without? definitely the computer  62 Love or lust: i prefer love, but lust has its perks (pun intended)  63. Silver or gold: silver  64. Diamond or pearl: diamond  65. Sunset or sunrise: sunrise  66. Have you ever gone skinny-dipping? like when i was a kid  68. Do you have any piercings? one  69. What song are you listening to right now? none... it's so spooky quiet!  70. What's the last 4 digits of your home phone? 4661... that's my cell... i have no home phone  71. Where would you want to go on your honeymoon? Toronto  72. Who do you want to spend the rest of your life with? Heh, will I ever know?  73. What's the first thing you notice about the opposite sex? Geez, what a stuck-up bitch, lol!  74. Favorite sport? Basketball  75. What makes you happy? cookies   76. What CDs are you going to get next? anything by BT or RÃ¶yksopp's new album  77. What's the best advice given to you? "Don't turn right... if you turn right, you'll end up in Indiana."  78. Do you live by it? hoosiers are the bane of my existence  79. Have you ever won any special awards? yuppers, I was a smarty pants and got the Illinois State Scholar award in HS  80. What are your future goals? to be a famous musician  81. Worst sickness you've ever had? chicken pox... at age 16... ugh.  82. Do you like funny or scary movies better? funny!   83. On the phone or in person? in person  84. Hugs or kisses? gratuitous making out, lol  85. What song seems to reflect you the most? Eventually and Lonely Girl by Pink  86. If you died tomorrow to whom would you leave everything you own? I was planning on splitting it all up to specific people  87. Do you have any enemies? I guess Andrea could be one, though I wish that weren't so any more  88. Rich or famous: I'm already Rich(ard)  90. Have you ever been in love? Severely, yes...  91. Have you met Santa? I think Santa is a magical child molester  92. If E.T. knocked on your door holding up a peace sign and asked to use your phone, what would you do? I think I'd cry... yes, I'd cry... and assume the fetal position.  93 When did you last talk to the person that you like? Blah  94. Do you have any pets? Yup, my sweet kitty Snuggles   97. Who sent this to you? I stole the idea from Chris  98.What do you think of this person? Chris is a stitch  99. Do you want your friends to send back? like Chris said, "No I want them all to post it on their blogs so I can read them"  100. Who do you expect to write back first? Probably nobody. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It was about a man named Kurdin.  He approached me while I was doing my laundry here in my condo building, and something about the way he talked to me and acted toward me made me trust him instantly, like he was a friend of mine for more years than I'd lived.  He came to eat with my parents and I that very night and the same happened with them.  Also for some strange reason my mother pointed out a caterpillar by Kurdin's foot and I started sqaushing it and then two centipedes appeared and I kept mashing on them and they wouldn't die!  Kurdin and I started spending a ton of time together.  Things would happen suddenly around him that were unusual, like we were in an airport looking for a flight and suddenly it had arrived early and was cleared for takeoff.  We were in an elevator or waiting room or something, and he suddenly put his hands on the knees of these two black women who were sitting as he knelt on the floor, and he started telling them things from their past, and the looks of contempt on their faces quickly faded to looks of happiness and good-will.  There were many other things, but the dream is already starting to fade.  It's kinda weird... reminds me of Hearts of Atlantis.  I never have dreams quite like that... very strange. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, this is the greatest thing ever! www.freewebs.com/rimco/singing.wma  That's me.  Yeah.  I found some kick-ass software that totally put me in a good mood.  It's Auto-Tune, a program designed to even out the pitches of someone's singing... it totally rocks my world.  Most professional musicians and studios use it to cheat, so why can't I?! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I can't help but be just a little sad today... today would have been Artis's and my 9-month anniversary.  I would've loved to have him here for the weekend away from school, give him a flower, a card, treat him to dinner, something.  Instead, I will probably spend the day alone... not by choice but because life hates me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Wheee!  I'm updating, how nice.  I finished a new song, Please Believe Me, and so far everyone who has listened to it either likes it or absolutely loves it... I'm so excited!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
        I'm gonna have to stop taking naps or something... I was dreaming that I was living with my mother in a condo similar to my own except each unit was shaped more like a trailer, like it was a bunch of brick trailes cemented together... we were on the 8th floor.  There was a storm or something, and we didn't think much of it, until I went in my room as saw the floor was cracked and half of the room was recessed about 2 inches... suddenly I freaked, screamed at my mom to get out, kept telling her there's no time to explain, it's an emergency, get out now... we got out, got to the ground, and each segment started to fall from the building to the ground.  Oh lordy.  I never remember dreams, and now that's two very distinct and odd dreams in the last week.  And on Monday again!  Blah! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       My roommate just got home a little while ago from a weekend back home in Michigan... her car is totaled.  She says she fell asleep in Indiana, didn't say much else but she was obviously shaken up pretty bad.  I'm glad to see that she's OK, but man, her car is just wrecked.  I remember plenty of times I'm been drowsy while driving... maybe I'll be more likely to take a quick nap from now on :-/ 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just spent a good bit of time coming up with a clever way of selling myself on XY... I like what I wrote... --------------------- It's so strange how some of the simplest things in life can be so rare. Common coal, when tempered under immense pressure and strain, can turn into a dazzling diamond. Yet it is so hard for the average person to tell that diamond from the wanna-be cubic zirconia, a manufactured imitation of the real thing.  I have done my time, putting up with shit from guys, refining myself, slowly molding myself from the shy and dull coal I once was and into a rarity to be treasured, not mistaken. I am the diamond.  All I am is real, all I say is for you to hear, all I feel is for you to experience. I have no lies, no secrets, no shame.  Stop digging in the coal to find me. Don't cast me aside thinking I'm just another imposter. I am the honesty you have been looking for. I am your diamond, and a diamond is forever. --------------------  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Oh blah indeed... it's been a while.  So I'm gonna try and be quick.  I was in LaSalle/Peru last week and go back next week helping out an Eagle that we converted into a Jewel.  I had yesterday off and also have today and tomorrow off... wheee!  Dan may be moving in here if we can cram him in.  I hung out with Carlo last night for the first time in over a year.  I think that sums it all up there... now I have to go defecate... I'm sure you needed to know that :grins: 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, lemme update on the "men" situation.  The younger cute black guy called me a couple times... he's a real goofball, and he seems to act his age, meaning he seems a little immature for me, but I'd still like to meet him, if nothing just to look at his cuteness *grins*.  The other more all-around gorgeous black guy who goes to Lewis isn't much of a talker, so I'm already losing interest there.  Haven't heard from the uber-hot white guy in Lisle yet... oh well... just IMed another guy off of glimpse.com... huge-built muscular black dude... he could break me!  You'd be surprised how sweet and cuddly those big black dudes can be though... sounds right up my alley.  Anywayz, I need cigs and I need to stop thinking about men... more DS9 for me! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Wow, I'm bored, so I'm gonna come back to my blogger and try and update everyone.  So yeah... been trying to meet guys... no major luck there yet.  Last night's meeting was quite a fiasco... guy came over, we played video games, and then he blatantly asked me if I was interested in oral sex... I swear, that fucking little troll... ugh, if I wasn't such a nice guy, I would've hit him.  Couple weeks ago, more fiasco... met a really nice, really cute guy, he came over, we got a little innebriated, we made out, he then tell me it meant nothing and then a couple nights later while hanging out with a mutual friend he felt the need to tell me he "slept with" a guy at a party the night before... now granted, it turns out that by "slept with" he literally meant "fell asleep next to" a guy, but he didn't make it sound that way.  Yet another immature boy toying with my emotions.  On the online front, there're three guys I have my eye on, all gorgeous to say the least.  One is a really cute black guy who lives here in Joliet... talked to him once on the phone and he's a real ham, that one... must've sang five songs for me on the phone, which was nice, and he wasn't that bad actually.  Then there's... wow... another black guy who's not just cute but just really really good looking... he goes to Lewis... problem there is one, he never seems too interested in conversation, even though he IMed me first, and two, he plans to go to UIC next year... another guy sucked in by the city.  Then there's this guy I just emailed this morning... oh... my... god... he's like supermodel gorgeous and lives in Lisle... not real close, but at least the drive involves more corn than cars.  Hopefully I'll hear back from him. In other news, I still hate my job.  I'm working on getting a PT job with OfficeMax... I hope that by getting my foot in the door I will be able to try and move up with that company.  I'm sick of being a little peon underling, dammit!  I also unexpectedly was approved for a Best Buy card with a.... gulp... $2200 limit.. I've already put almost $400 on the fucking thing... I hate credit... I love credit... damn you credit!  We finally got rid of our new night crew chief, that bum.  Everyone hated him, so he took the hint and went back from whence he came!  The guy we got in return kicks ass, even if he is a big fat ugly monster... he's funny though, and knows how to have fun along with the rest of us... and he actually busts his ass (when he's not "busting ass").  I'm gaining weight... oh my... my belly is returning... Richard, this is not a good way to attract the boys!  Fuck you belly... fuck you and your little navel too!  Oh my god, my navel is like the fucking Grand Canyon... you ain't SEEN an innie until you've seen the depths of my naveliciousness.  Yeah, I'm in just a bit of a goofy mood... can't tell?  Well obviously you're inept if you can't.  Anyway, I got out of work almost three hours early, and I think I can put it to better use than just sitting here telling the world my life story, sheesh.  I guess playing video games and watching DS9 aren't better ways to spend my time, but at least they're more relaxing, and that's what I need... relaxation... lots and lots of it... and i plan to since i have tonight off of work, yay!  Oh yeah, I'm up to Season 5 on DS9... well i HAVE up through Season 5, but I'm still watching 4... thank you Best Buy card!  Got a new DVD player too cuz I thought the old one was going kaput already... turns out the problem is with some sort of signal degredation caused by my cable signal coming in... in any case, the DVD player I got is major kick-ass and has FULL support for all of the good HDTV features, so when I am able to get an HDTV, man, look out!  Gonna look BEEE-autiful!  Aren't you sick of reading yet?  Haha, when I typed sick i accidentally typed "dick"... Freudian slip?  Possibly *grins*.  Well, you all have yourselves a fine-ass morning and I'm gonna go waste my life in the depths of science fiction... woot! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Fuck em all!  I hate my fucking job, I hate working fucking overnights... fuck.  I'm calling Brenn today to see if he can get me a job with Belkin Tech Support... it'll be a little bit of a pay cut, but fuck it... I'll eat ramen for a few months.  I overslept again last night and it's just like fuck, I can't do this.  I used to be a respected employee at that store, and now I'm dog shit.  I've been dog shit all my life, and I'm sick of it.  I have a fucking IQ of 164 and I'm stocking shelves for a living... it's such a waste.  Jewel can suck my white ass. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       That's right, unlike my other updates on MEN, this update is finally on A man.  This guy emailed me the other day, and so I finally caught him early yesterday morning online.  We talked for a good while, then moved onto the phone for another good hour or so before we decided to meet and hang out.  Well, I just dropped him off back at home.  Yeah, he's been here for, oh, 36 hours or so, lol.  Obviously things are going very well there.  He's really sweet, kinda goofy, a little odd, but I like that.  He's a gearhead, meaning he LOVES cars, big time.  I'm already quite into him, and he seems to feel the same way since he was already talking about the next time we see each other... seeing as how we just spent a day and a half together non-stop, the fact that he already wants to see me again is really nice.  Talk about an unexpected surprise!  Now I have to work... what a way to bring down an otherwise wonderful day, blah. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    urlLink audio post  powered by  urlLink audblog  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Bryant gave me the biggest fucking hickey I've ever seen!  I've never even had a hickey before, and now I have this black WELT on my neck... yes, folks, today is a turtleneck day. But yeah, on that front, we were together again last night... it was both wonderful and a little insightful.  Once gain, we enjoyed each other's company, but toward the end of the night, when I was about to take him back home, he did something that greatly annoyed me.  I always like that last kiss to be a nice, passionate, loving kiss... well, obviously he was still in a goofy mood and totally exploited it.  First, he kept pulling away, teasing me... it was funny the first three times... the fourth, I finally just grabbed his head and tried to kiss him.  He then proceeded to more or less lick my face off... I'm sorry, that's such a turn-off... tongue is one thing, but he was going overboard, and he was doing it on purpose, and for some reason, it really upset me.  I was actually quite down the rest of the night, and I think my sullenness rubbed off on him, cuz on the ride home, we didn't really talk at all.  I tried to hold his hand, but he didn't really hold mine back, and once again I was annoyed.  Then he fell asleep, which is understandable... he has the cutest little snore, hehe.  He said he was just tired, and maybe he does like me and just gets real goofy when he's tired.  I just want to know that he's taking this relationship seriously.  From various things he said throughout the night, I do believe this has developed into a relationship, like the whole "boyfriends" thing... I will probably talk to him about that later... he's supposed to call me today.  Anyway, I have a lot of cleaning to do and then I'm going to buy DS9 Season 7!!  Yay!  By the way, don't get me wrong, Bryant may have annoyed me a little, but I still think he's great... I was probably just in a quirky mood or something.  I definitely see that potential, that spark, that special something that I haven't seen in quite some time.  I'm going to do all I can to hold on to this one. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Oh wow... wow... wow again!  OK, first off, to clear up the thing with the last guy... to put it bluntly, he's annoying... so that post from Nov. 10th... ignore it.  He won't even talk to me any more cuz I didn't hug him goodbye that last time we hung out... this was after we decided a relationship was not in our future.  So forget him... he's a kid.  I have found myself a MAN... and man-o-man what a man!  Shiiiiit!  His name is Bryant... he lives on the east side of the city (a rather simple 45-min drive that I stragely don't mind making), he's 19, he's GORGEOUS, he's smart, very classy... he's actually a lot of things I don't normally look for in a guy, and yet we hit it off almost immediately.  We spent a good 18 hours together yesterday (causing me to get NO sleep between now and 10pm on MONDAY night... yes, I've been up 35 hours with no sleep... yay), and all I can say is wow... maybe that's cuz he says that a lot when I do something like mess up his hair or poke him in his side... it's sorta his response to everything... it's cute.  I'm totally infatuated... is that a good thing?  I can only hope so, and I can only hope that some of these feelings will be returned.  Since I broke up with Artis, Briant is THE first guy I've met who totally makes me forget about Artis... it's an incredible feeling, and it's hard not to sorta jump into things (which we already seem to have done to some degree *grins*)... I can only hope that this will work out.  I can't begin to say what it means to finally meet someone who makes me forget all about Artis.  I actually was looking at Artis's pictures today, and suddenly he just looks like just another face... none of the emotions are attached.  I don't think of our engagement... I don't think of how close we were... I don't think about any of it.  My mind is totally focused on someone else for a change, and it feels absolutely liberating!  But yeah... I've been awake for 35 hours... I should probably go to sleep... I think I will, with the help of my friend Rumpel Minze... yum! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well... I emailed Bryant everything that was on my mind... he emailed back this morning... let's just say that we have a hard time understanding each other, but things are OK, I think.  Hopefully things will get easier as we get to know each other.  What really makes me feel a ton better is that I emailed Jude and told him all that happened and why I didn't hang out with him last week.  He not only understands but wished me the best with Bryant, and even said that he'll be there for me as a friend.  What a sweetheart!  I always feel better when all is out in the open and it works out for the best.  Now I'm gonna have to clean this trash-hole of a room... yuck! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I feel much better, but not exactly great.  Brenn did a good job of keeping me cheery though... I always feel better when I'm around a good friend.  We did a little shopping, walked around the mall, all that sorta good stuff.  Right now I'm listening to some of my songs, sorting through the many emotions in my head, trying to figure it all out.  It's like my life is some sort of intense puzzle whose solution evades me further as I get closer to solving it.  My emotions just rattle around in my head like beans in a can, and the noise is so loud... too loud.  I need something in my life, glue to hold the beans to the walls of the can.  But what is this glue?  Will I ever find out?  I seek answers, I NEED answers, and I have nothing.  At least I know I can depend on my music to work my mood out... it's the one thing in my life that is dear to me and is always there for me... now if only I could find something or someone tangible to fill that same void.  My life may be stable, but I am not.  Help me, please... someone... anyone... help me... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well Blogger is down for the moment, so I'm typing this in Notepad and post it later.  First off, Chris, yes, you are a slut, oh my god!  LOL!!  Thanks for sharing all that with the WHOLE WORLD! lol again!  So yes, I'm in a terrible mood... one of my bipolar depression moments, and I'm out of medication... actually, it's a "supplement" and not a prescription, but it works as well and is safer than full-strength lithium.  So yeah, I don't really know what to say... I just feel terrible... I'm thinking of how I more-or-less blew off this guy Jude that I liked so I could be with Bryant instead... I was with Bryant the night Jude and I had planned to hang out... no, more like I had pleaded the day before that Jude hang out cuz I was so interested, and then all of this unexpected happening with Bryant... and now I'm having sorta doubts about Bryant... no, not doubts... just complications in my own fucked-up mind.  I'm going to my friend Brenn's place... I can't be alone right now... I'm scared. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Just typing here for the hell of it... not like anything interesting is happening... well actually, I did meet a guy the other night.  His name's Fabian... really nice guy, though he was quite shy.  I always get weird around shy people just cuz I used to be horribly shy myself and other shy people bring that back out in me.  He has these incredibly gorgeous eyes though, wow... he's someone I could become interested in, definitely.  For some reason, I keep hesitating on Jude... I keep wanting to call him, hang out, all of that, but it's weird... he was so sweet and seemed like he'd never hurt anyone, and yet I'm more afraid of him than I am of other guys... I guess I'm starting to feel like after 19 attempts at relationships that it must be ME who is doing something wrong, and yet nobody ever tells me... things always just fall apart with no explanations.  I guess since Jude seemed like such a nice guy that I'm afraid that I'll be the one who ends up hurting him... I don't know... my brain just doesn't know what to do any more... it's like a computer harddrive with too many stupid little programs on it and now it's getting buggy... problem is, you can't reformat a brain. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, Bryant is officially old news... he hasn't called in over a week, he's only emailed me once... fuck him... I'm done dating children.  I'm gonna try to meet new people, see where things go with them, stuff like that.  Work is okay.  Life is okay.  I finished Deep Space 9 today... wow... I cried.  Anywayz, yeah... fun times to be had by all, even if I AM single... still... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm still riding high on it all... things with Erik are just crazy!  It's still hard to believe that I've found someone who means so much to me.  It's amazing how alike Erik and I are, and yet we're different enough to keep things interesting.  His friends rock too.  The only complaint I can think of is that he lives up in Chicago and I live down here, and he doesn't have a car yet, but it's an easy drive, and I don't mind making it for him.  I just got back this afternoon from seeing him... I miss him the moment I'm out the door... it's driving me nuts!  I want him to meet all of my friends... the few that I've mentioned him to all want to meet this guy who has stolen my heart.  It's always so wonderful to wake up next to him... if only I could every day... hopefully that time will come, sooner or later.  Until then, I will love every moment I can get! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       No, this isn't me getting all googly-eyed over some guy who will just treat me like shit or that I can't have.  This is the real deal.  It happened.  I found the man I've been looking for for ages.  Forget every other guy I've ever dated, because this one takes the cake.  Love is in my life once again, and this time, I truly think it's for good.  I truly can't remember the last time I was so happy, I really can't.  Erik Uy.  Who would've thought that six letters could change my whole outlook on life.  Just when I thought my love life had hit rock bottom YET AGAIN, I got an IM... from a guy... and I had the usual feeling of "oh gosh, here we go again."  It started as usual, getting to know the little things, like where we live, how old we are... we decided to meet that night... it almost sounded like a hook-up, but I was still a bit burned from Bryant, so I figured what the hell, I needed to feel special, even if only for one night. I got there, and we watched a movie, didn't talk much, and then a little flirting and pillow fighting later, you can guess what happened... but what you didn't guess was that some spark, some magical happening took place... we connected, instantly.  Emotions ran high the whole night and next morning, and we couldn't get enough of each other... I was scared because here was this guy I didn't even know and yet I was already developing strong feelings for him... in one night.  You'd think after 11 other relationships I would've known better, and I did, and yet I couldn't stop it from happening... and it happened, and I realized it, and I didn't know what to think... it was love at first sight.  At this point I would usually freak out, knowing that I was the insane one, that the other guy could'nt possibly be dealing with the same emotional adrenaline I was experiencing... but he was, just the same as me, a kindred spirit that had found his way into my life so unexpectedly and yet so unabashedly.  I have the missing piece to my life... the puzzle is now complete.  A guy who loves me and whom I love, and it's true, honest, and real... I've never been so sure of anything in my life.  I have found my soul mate, among the billions of people in the world.  I have become truly almighty.  Everything I've known in my past, all the love and sorrow and pain and pleasure... it's nothing... it's irrelevant.  My life begins again, reborn, renewed.  My renaissance is here, and I'm running wild, running free, and most paramount of all, I do not run alone.  My sweet Erik, my love for you is boundless, endless, rackless... timeless. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Could it be?  Has it really been almost a month!  Today is my and Erik's 4-week anniversary, which means that this Friday will be the big one month.  Amazing... what a month it has been.  All the laughter, all the warm hugs, all the sad goodbyes, all the tears shed over an overwhelming love that can't be contained.  World, you had better watch the fuck out, cuz we're gonna take you all by storm!  We are unstoppable! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I love you Erik!!  My lover bunny, butt-whisker, cuddle-bug, smoochy butt... you are like an arrow that has pierced my penis!  Well, seriously, all I ever think about is you... and if you had an arrow sticking in your cock, you would probably have a difficult time thinking about anything else, right?  **grins** 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Always there must be this dark cloud over my life... I suppose it's nothing that directly affects me, but it's still a terrible, terrible thing.  My good friend, Steve, just lost his closest friend Keith.  Keith was in a car accident about a week ago and suffered severe internal injuries, and unfortunately he couldn't make it.  I'm so incredibly worried about Steve because I know he has problems with depression, and I know he doesn't deal with it well.  Something like this could very well be a bigger blow than anything in his whole life... I hope he realizes I'm here and that I will be there for him... I don't know what I'd do if I lost a friend like that, and I hope Steve doesn't do anything that'll have me face that situation...  [[UPDATE]] Yeah, so I guess there was a HUGE misunderstanding, because Keith is fine... just hung out with him like two weeks after all of this.  Umm... I'm confused... but yes, Keith is fine, and Steve is too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink PlayerPRO Home Page  I'm just throwing this on my blog so that I can get the link at Erik's place... gotta try this out on a Mac at the Apple Store up in the city!  Fun times! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Erik spent a couple days here... it was so great to come home from work in the morning and find him lying in my bed and to lie down next to him.  If only every day could be like that.  I bought a few things the other day that I've been wanting to get for a while.  I've always wanted a 5.1 surround audio disc of some form, so I found Reanimation by Linkin Park in Dolby Digial and Brand New Day by Sting in DTS... yay!  I also FINALLY found a copy of a Cowboy Bebop soundtrack and also Volumen, which is a bunch of Bjork videos... I've been searching for both for quite some time. Work is chapping my ass... Naperville is hectic, and it's not run well at all.  My manager at Romeoville may have been a dick, but at least he knew how to run a store.  I'm also working 8 days in a row, which I'm about to work #6 tonight.  I need a day off!  I'm going nuts!  I've been really depressed the last couple days too... I'm out of my "bipolar pills" so I just have to ride it out.  Ugh... anyway... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Up until recently, everything has been fine.  I got transferred at work from Romeoville to Naperville, and I'm enjoying my new store.  Things with Erik have been going well... until now. Always, always, ALWAYS there must be something!  The story isn't too different from what happened with Artis.  He's so afraid of his parents and what they'll say/think/do if he defies them that he's letting it cripple our relationship.  Instead of spending a potential two days together over the weekend, we got to see each other for a whole four hours... oh goody... he won't hold my hand in the car, he's kissing me differently... something's wrong, something's different, and someone's not going to put up with it for much longer.  Seriously, if this is how things are going to be... if he's not going to even talk to me when I'm trying to figure out what's wrong, I'm not going to stick around and watch it fall apart from the inside out like it did with Artis.  I knew things with Artis weren't going exactly well early on, but I tried to stick with it, and in the end it hurt me so much that it nearly cost me my life.  I'm not going to make that same mistake again, so if Erik can't even talk to me, his boyfriend who loves him dearly and treasures every moment with him, then obviously we're not as close as I thought.  It's a gamble... I can either try to ride this out and end up making it work or end up seriously damaged again, or I can end it now and just get burned a little.  It's not a decision I have to make right now, nor do I want to, but soon, because I can't wait forever to find love, and if this love is dead, then I'm not going to stick around for the memorial service.  Erik... I still love you so very much... you are the one thing that has held me together during a very hectic part of my life... I don't ever want to hurt you, but I'm not going to sacrifice myself again like in my last relationship.  Don't make me choose between me and us. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I guess this news is coming a bit late... Erik and I have broken up.  Yes, it's official, yes it seems to be lasting.  It happened, oh, about a week ago.  We both just realized that we started our relationship out of a need for each other, but once that need was satisfied, we realized that we were really just friends with benefits.  It's weird going from "oh god I love you I love you I love you" to "I'll talk to ya later."  I'm getting over it, I guess.  So, the hunt then began.  Let's give a little rundown.  -Bachelor #1- Upside - He's cute as hell, he's nice, and his friend that I met is hilarious. Downside - Too young (17) and doesn't seem like the type to want a serious relationship on the level I want. Story: Met him online... he found me.  He lives in Minooka, which is rather close by.  He and his friend and I hung out at the mall and had a decently fun time, but we've hardly spoken since.  Yeah, he's cute, but he's not really my type.  He's an Abercrombie-type guy, ya know, loves the popular thing.  I highly doubt this will go anywhere.  -Bachelor #2- Upside - Spectacular personality, loves many of the same things I do including Star Trek, near my age (21) Downside - lives in Chicago, don't really know what he looks like due to poor picture, always downplays his looks, which makes me wonder if he's somehow unattractive (which shouldn't matter but does), somewhat over-complimentative, like he's going out of his way to flatter me but doesn't really mean it Story: Met him online too, and then we moved to talking on the phone.  Seems like a really nice guy, and I plan to meet him Wednesday.  -Bachelor #3- Upside - Again, cute as hell, very bright personality, seems nice Downside - the youngest ever (not quite 17, eek!), lives in Cicero (might as well be Chicago) Story: I don't know as much about him as I do the others, but he seems like a nice guy.  I talked to him on the phone, and I'm supposedly going to his place later today.  -Bachelor #4- Upside - his self-description makes him sound like he'd be really really good looking, very pleasant, seems interested in me, lives in Flossmore, considerably closer than Chicago, but not around the corner either Downside - only 18, has no pic at all Story: Just talked to him for the first time last night... he was gonna call at one point when he saw my usual "call me" away message on AIM, but was too shy to, seems extremely nice, but haven't had a chance to really get to know him yet.  So there we go... what do you think?  Another quick rundown... Bachelor #1 - wouldn't mind seeing where it goes, but doubt we'll even meet again Bachelor #2 - a definite match personality-wise, but appearance is mostly unknown and he compliments me to the point of annoying me Bachelor #3 - don't know a ton, seems nice, but too young Bachelor #4 - don't know much here, but seems very nice and sounds like he'd be quite attractive  So which should it be?  Well, I'm meeting #3 today, met #1 and have pretty much dismissed him... yeah yeah, I definitely need to meet #2, if only cuz he loves Star Trek!  I also got a raise at work, so now I'm up to $13.95/hr not including my $.50/hr overnight bonus, which tends to add up to about $20 a week.  Dad ran my taxes real quick to get an idea of what sort of refund I could expect, and it could be upwards of $1000!  Wow!  Anywayz, gotta rest up! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Lol, wow, it's amazing how so much can happen in a couple weeks, you know.  First, an update on the runners-up! -Bachelor #1- I've mentioned to him online a couple times now that he never IMs me first, and he just gives an excuse and then continues to never IM me, so like I said before, nothing going to happen there.  Not interested. -Bachelor #2- We met a little less than two weeks ago, and he's a very nice guy, but I just didn't feel like he's someone I could get along with in a relationship.  A friendship, perhaps, but not a relationship. -Bachelor #3- Well I didn't meet him two weeks ago like I said in my last post, but I did meet him a few days ago.  We just bummed around Cicero, walked around a park in the freezing cold, and just talked a lot.  Really sweet guy, but one, he's taken now, and two, he's entirely too young, and three, I've had my eye on Mr. Bachelor #4 since the 6th when I met him... so let's move on to him, shall we? I met "Bachelor #4", whom I can now refer to as Siki (yes, that's his name).  We hung out not this past Saturday but the Saturday before and wow, did we have a good time.  He's actually taller than me, which is a nice change of pace, and he's just gorgeous.  We just bummed around Orland for the day and in only a few hours we created stories that we'll no doubt be telling for some time.  JoS. A. Bank! (no, you don't get it!)  Then this past Saturday, we had a chance to spend a few hours together over here.  After I had my ass handed to me in Soul Calibur (and keep in mind that this game is why I failed college at WIU, so I'm not that bad at it!), we watched The Notorious C.H.O.  After some *mild* flirting, tickling, pillow fighting, and what have you, the cuddling began, and of course we all know where cuddling leads... oh my GOD, he has the softest lips ever!  I mean like pillow-soft!  It was just a wonderful night, and it also happened to be the beginning of what I hope will be something very special.  I'm already dying in anticipation of the next time we see each other... I just wanna throw my arms around him... he's so... umm, snuggle-able?  Snuggable?  I like that, my own new word, snuggable.  So yes, great things on the horizon for Richard... go me! 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So yeah, I haven't smoked in over three full days now, and I'm so proud of that.  But I've been thinking about one thing and one thing only.. well I guess he's not a thing... but yes... Siki...  I don't really know what to do, to be honest.  I can honestly say that I'm developing strong feelings for him, and that bothers me... really bothers me... no, not so much bothers as much as it *scares* me.  I'm terrified.  I have been hurt so much and so badly in the past that I just don't know if I can fall in love again.  Well, I can, and very easily too, but I know that if I do that it will just break my heart again.  Siki is easily one of the most incredible guys I've ever met.  He's gorgeous, intelligent, witty and clever, and caring.  He's also a very independant person, the type of guy who would like to have a relationship but who won't exactly give it priority in his life.  I, on the other hand, give relationships almost too much priority in my life.  This is not a good area to differ on.  What scares me is that first off, I don't see enough of him.  I knew that I wouldn't going into this, but I was so struck by him that I was willing to deal with it, and for now I still am, whether I like it or not... he's worth going a little out of my mind even if I only get to see him once a week or so.  But there's this impending college decision... where's he going to go to school?  Right now, his main choice is in New York, and he just got accepted the other day.  That's great for him, but it's basically death for us.  Neither one of us will be a part of a long distance relationship, so if he goes to school in New York, that's that.  Done.  So how can I honestly give my all to a relationship that will very likely end in a few months?  How can I risk my heart like that again?  I don't think I can... it's something I really need to talk to him about, and I wish I could right now, but he's at Wesleyan touring the college right now and won't be back until tomorrow... now I can't even talk to him on the phone!  I feel so cut off... not just from Siki, but from life.  I feel like no matter what I do, no matter who I find, no matter how wonderful something seems, it will always work out in a way that takes away just a little more from me.  I honestly, truly, do NOT know how much longer I can live like this. I can honestly say that I'm beginning to fall for Siki... what remains to be seen is if he will be there to catch me.  If he doesn't, will I be able to survive another fall?  Should I just keep my feet on the ground and be miserable?  What on earth am I to do? 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'll tell ya how... you get rid of the thing that broke it in the first place.  You know, I never had any of these issues until I started smoking... so I've quit.  No, not one of those half-ass quits where you start back up the next day or try and smoke "just one"... no, I'm done, I'm not doing it any more.  I will not smoke any more. I've been smoke free since 6:20AM yesterday morning, March 23rd.  Remember that day... it's the day I fixed a big wrong in my life. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, enough about men... I do have other things in my life, right? I got my first song up on my website, www.lerah.com/rimco.  It rocks! My mom has been smoking between 1 and 2 packs a day for almost 40 years, and Saturday she quit... the secret?  Accupuncture!  Unfortunately, when she found out about my smoking, we made a deal that if she quit, I'd have to as well. My income tax return yielded some exciting news... I'm getting almost $1200 back!  OMG, now I can FINALLY take that trip to NJ that I've been trying to take for like 2 years now!  YAY! And even with all of this, I feel weird... I feel disconnected... my bipolar disorder is acting up again, and I still don't have any medication to help... I just feel like I want to curl up in bed and cry, not for any particular reason, but just to relieve stress, to try and make myself feel better.  I keep thinking back to when I was a kid, when I could sit at home playing Nintendo and not have a care in the world... not worry about a job, not worry about paying bills, not worry at all.  Right now I'm worried about everything, and I have no reason to be.  Worry is such a pointless emotion because it accomplishes nothing.  It merely cripples us in situations which we have no control over.  I know this is because of those damned sleeping pills I took last night... they always do this to me, and that's why I almost never take them.  I just thought they might help me sleep better, and they did.  It's just so aggravating when you have so much to be happy for and yet you can't feel happy, like happiness has been borrowed by a dark shadow who won't give it back no matter how much I beg.  Whatever am I to do... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So yeah, things with Siki continue to be incredible... I end up missing him so much that I wrap myself around my pillow and wish it was him.  It's so crazy, like I feel like I may already be falling for him, but I'm not sure if that's really what's happening now or if it's like I feel as though I *will* fall in love with him in the future and I'm just anticipating that or... god, my emotions are so confusing sometimes.  Honestly, I just feel like I've found someone with whom I feel so wonderful... he takes all of the good things in my life and amplifies them and takes all of the bad things and makes them feel like less of a burden.  I can honestly say that he means very much to me and that I'm very attached to him... but is it love?  Probably not yet, but that potential is there, and it's so hard to not just dive in blindly.  I only hope that things will work out right for me for once... I've paid my dues, I've suffered enough... it's time for me to shine. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I mean we all have regrets, but your whole life?  One big fucking regret? Here's my list of regrets thus far...  Having EVER fallen in love, because it only leads to emotional disaster. Having quit school to pursue a job that is beneath me. Having spent so much money on things that only bring me short-term happiness. Having so few friends and rarely being able to see them. Having adopted a cat cuz mine is pissing me off as I speak. Having bought a home, knowing damn well that it's as much of an anchor on my life as living with my parents was. Having leased my car instead of buying one, all cuz I wanted to be "unique". Having stayed in the closet in high school, since most people I've told since then don't care. Having been so quiet and withdrawn my whole life, because fear serves no purpose. Having ever started smoking, because I'm still having major issues over quitting. Having ever hidden my feelings for someone only to find that, while they were involved with someone else, I could no longer hide it. Having ever been overweight, because now that I'm much thinner, I still look chunky, even though underneath the loose skin I have quite a nice physique. Having ever been involved with someone knowing from the start that it wouldn't work in the long run. Having the inability to control my hormones, which has resulted in "casual sex" too many times (though I've never just "hooked up")  I don't know, I'm sure there's like ten times that much, but it's warm in here and I'm already sick of typing because I have the attention span of a spaztic squirrel.  Seriously, though, I feel as though I regret everything, everything I've ever done.  What have I ever done in my life that truly made a difference?  That didn't just end in disappointment or end with no good result?  When have I ever made a truly positive impression on someone's life, made them feel like a better person for having known me?  Who am I to feel like I have any value here?  If I were to die, my friends would mourn, but for how long?  A few months and then they'd all be back to normal?  Is that even normal?  So am I abnormal to still have occasional issues over having broken up with Artis, even though it happened 9 months ago?  What don't I regret?  I even regret my current feeling of worthlessness because I know someone will read this and feel pity for me, and I don't want pity. I am not me... I am all of the parts that construct me, but I am not me.  I no longer have the control nor the ability to put the pieces together to make me whole.  I need help, and if I cannot find that one person who can pull me together, I will never be the sum of my parts, and therefore I will never exist... who I am will never be.  I've always been the optimist, but not this time... this time, I truly feel desolate, alone, and afraid. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so the last few days, everything in my mind has just exploded.  I officially broke up with Siki... it just wasn't going to work in the long run, even though the short run would've been so wonderful.  Yesterday and today, I've been thinking about Artis a lot again... I don't know why, because I got over him a long time ago, but I guess it's just because my brain is rather imbalanced.  I haven't taken my bipolar medication in about six months and I started back on it Monday.  Obviously it's causing some small problems, but I probably just need to adjust to it.  I've also realized that all this time, I've had feelings for my friend Steve and have just repressed them.  I've never been involved with someone who was already my friend, and by "friend" I mean someone I'm close to, not just an acquaintance.  The problem is that Steve is involved with someone right now.  I was hanging out all day yesterday with Steve and never did get the balls to tell him how I felt, but I knew I wouldn't, so I wrote a note the night before and then left the note at Steve's this morning when I left.  The weird thing is that later last night, we picked up Steve's bf, Joe, and seeing them hold hands and kiss and stuff... it made me feel something that I almost never feel... jealous.  I was insanely jealous... I didn't even stay this morning... I left before they even woke up because I didn't want to have to see that.  Ever since I quit smoking, everything has gone awry... why?  I should feel great that I quit, and instead I just feel like shit.  I feel more alone than I've felt in a very long time... I just finished sobbing my eyes out over nothing... it's not healthy to cry for no reason.  I can't think of anything I can do to take my mind off of everything save for sleeping, and I'm not tired at all.  I just feel this overwhelming emotion... just emotion in general... I'm angry, I'm upset, I'm sad... just all of this emotion is welling up inside of me, and I don't know how to get it out.  I don't even fell like working on music, which is what I usually do when I feel like this.  It's that bad.  I feel helpless to help myself. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so last night I went to go meet up with this guy I talked to online, Ryan.  Then went to go hang out with this other guy, Paul... turns out they know each other and I had been talking to Paul earlier that day as well.  Then upon getting to Paul's house, I meet yet another person I just started talking to online, Jeremy, and another guy who I hadn't met at all yet, Joe.  Within like a few minutes, I could already tell I was gonna like Joe... don't know why, but I did.  So, after hanging out all night long with everyone, we all started to crash in the basement.  Joe and I were lying down foot-to-foot on the couch, and sorta starting doing some footsie stuff, and then he got up and laid down next to me so we could cuddle.  Eventually it evolved into kissing and nice stuff like that (no, nothing gratuitous, there were other people in the room).  To put it simply, I really like Joe.  Later in the morning, Joe and I were alone in the basement, and we started at it again... and then he got up and said, "I can't do this, I'm sorry."  For the rest of the day, things were a little awkward and then we just talked about it all like an hour or two ago.  Basically, he's the type of guy who won't fool around with anyone else if he's even just interested in a guy... turns out he likes some other guy and felt bad about doing anything with me.  Once again, yes, Richard gets shit on.  I'm so fucking sick of it all, I really am.  I couldn't even go home right away... I sat on Paul's front porch fighting back the tears of disappointment.  Now I have to try and make it through a night of work having only had maybe three hours of sleep this morning and four hours of sleep yesterday... not gonna be fun, lemme tell ya.  I'm so fucking pissed right now, I really am. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       It's hitting me again... it hit me last night, went away for a while today, and now it's back in full effect... I'm so damn depressed right now.  I have nobody to turn to... Steve's hanging out with his bf, Joe is at work, Ezzy is sleeping, and my other friends aren't people I go to when I'm like this.  All I want to do is cuddle up with someone and fall asleep with them in my arms.  Even then, I'm afraid to do that, cuz it seems like every guy I touch ends up leaving Illinois now.  I can't even get XY to load up my profile so I can change it.  Nothing is working... I guess I'll go check the mail since I haven't in days... that'll shed some excitement into my dull life for a whole 3 minutes, and then maybe I'll watch a movie or something while puffing on a cigar... wow, how exciting...  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Apparently it's not OK to break up with someone, date other people in an attempt to get over them, and then find out that you can't get over them.  At least according to Erik, that is.  Yeah, this Joe guy I met is great... he stayed a couple days here, and we were all cuddly and stuff, and it's nice, but it's not the same.  He's leaving for his post with the Marines on June 1st, so why bother.  And once again it comes back to Erik.  I honestly miss him and still love him... I always will, and just like with Artis, I will have to learn to live with it.  I'll never get over it, but it's like a foul odor that enters the room... eventually your mind adjusts to it and you don't smell it any more, but it's still there.  You know who I miss the most?  Me.  Who I used to be before love shackled my soul.  Now I feel like an old man with nothing to live for.  God help me when I actually AM old, if I ever make it there... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Looks like a tornado hit Joliet last night... don't hear about that very often.  About 100 houses around the cathedral district are screwed royally.  Walgreens is demolished.  What a mess, and it happened about a mile from me.  The town of Utica is about 80% destroyed, so luckily we didn't see that kind of devastation.  Maybe I'll go drive around in a bit to see the aftermath. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I've been watching, well, chick flicks I guess... lol.  Well first I watched Dancer in the Dark, and that is THE most depressing movie ever made, but it's an excellent movie... highly recommended.  Then I watched Secondhand Lions... another good movie... and then just now I watched Radio... yet another spirit-lifting story.  God, I'm such a woman on the inside, lol. Over the last week or so, I've been debating on whether or not to keep my kitty.  And just as I was thinking of it again just now, he's rubbing all over me looking more adorable than ever... I don't think I can do it, but I know that if he gets sick again, I'll have to take him to the shelter.  It seems dispickable, but there is a price on this love, and it's not one I'm going to pay no matter what.  Damn cat had better realize that and just not get sick!  His little trip to the vet a couple weeks ago set me back $400... well, actually my parents picked up half the tab, which was insanely nice of them, but they won't do it again.  Anyway, I think I'm going to take out my last bit of energy on some unsuspecting folks in Vice City and then it's off to bed with me.  I still need a bf, but at least for once I can live with the fact that I don't have one. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, so Joey and I have dated twice, we've had our fights, we've said some terrible things... and now we're back together.  Who would've guessed?!  It seems like the two of us have grown up a bit, and I'm really hoping that the third time is the charm here.  I've always been crazy about him, but he'd always do some little thing that really bothered me and then I'd get all dramatic and break up with him and crap... I expect too much out of a relationship, I really do.  If I'd just lighten up a bit, maybe things wouldn't end so crappy all the time... actually, I was just reading some journal entries from a couple years ago, and I was saying more or less the same thing... so when am I going to stop saying and start doing?  Cripes... 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So I bought an Xbox a couple weeks ago and just got NFS Underground... wow... awesome game.  I think what impressed me the most was when I drove the Celica.  My mom used to have one of the newer Celicas, and I always laughed at her because it had this whiney, gurgly sound to the engine... and when I drove it in the game, it sounded just like that!  Fun stuff!  It's just a lot of fun.  Anywayz, yeah... things with Joey are good, albeit a little like they always have been.  Yesterday was one of those "second guessing" days, and I hate when I get like that.  Thursday night, he said he'd call and never did, I finally got a hold of him online around 2 or 3 or something yesterday afternoon, then around 7 he said he was running out to a friend's for maybe 20-30 mins, and then around 12:30 I finally called him.  I know I can't spend every waking moment with him, but a lot of the circumstances seemed familiarly fishy, but that's just Joey... he's always running a rather hectic and spontaneous life... so what if we both had the day off and didn't see any of each other.  It'a really no big deal, even if yesterday I thought it was... part of me wanted to go off on him like I would've a year or two ago, but I held back because I knew that today I'd feel better about it and it wouldn't be a big deal, and I was right.  Once again, I'm getting crazy ideas in my head and blowing things out of proportion... at least I'm keeping it to myself this time, sans this journal here.  Mostly, I'm just babbling... the point is, I'm fine, I trust Joey, and everything is cool... I was just going temporarily insane. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       To put it bluntly, I was downright suicidal last night.  I dont' have the time nor the energy to go into detail, but things between Joey and I are right back to where they always are... aggravating.  I doubt we will last much longer.  The only person I felt like I could turn to was Artis, who stopped by yesterday... his arrival began my downward spiral into a nervous breakdown.  After two hours of violent crying and two hours of Artis trying to calm me down, I tried to sleep and couldn't.  Now I have to get through work in one piece.  If I knew what to do, I'd do it, but I don't, so I can't. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I spent a week in New Jersey, spent the following week loafing around while still on vacation, just recently broke up with Joey, and in an interesting spin, I'm now officially involved with... Bryant!  Yay!  How a plain old-fashioned guy like me landed a gorgeous urban hipster like him is beyond me, but I'm not complaining because it makes me happy, and that's all that's important, right?  It almost makes me want to parade him around in front of all those stuck up little Naperville kids, but that wouldn't be right.  Funny thing, tonight at work I ran into this guy Tom who I knew from QYC... I guess I should be glad that he at least recognized me, but that was about it... typical.  Anywayz, I guess you could say that my mood is decent right now, maybe cuz I took a dose of lithium this morning.  I'm just so happy that things are going somewhere with Bryant, cuz he's the type of guy who likes to confront problems right away so that they don't become bigger problems down the road, and he also seems like the kind of guy who will actually try in a relationship.  He's pretty much everything I've been looking for in a guy... well, except for the distance thing, but for once that's not really bothering me that much.  Having Brenn as a roommate seemed at first to be an iffy decision... I wasn't sure how well we'd get along.  Oddly enough, we're getting along really really well, far better than I'd ever expected.  Even in the four weeks he's been here, it feels like we've become closer friends, and that's important to me because I feel like my other friends are slowly drifting away.  Well, not like severely, but Steve has not only two jobs but also has a boyfriend who he spends a LOT of time with... I haven't even hung out with Steve since we got back from NJ on the 28th.  Esmerelda is ALWAYS busy, but that's understandable considering how much she has going on.  Dan is being his usual hermit self.  I can't even think of any other close friends with whom I spend much time.  I finally got myself a laptop... yeah, I know I went through all of that to pay off my credit cards and then went and bought a laptop on credit, but I swear, it's all I've bought and all I'm going to buy, and I don't even have to pay any interest for two years.  Funny thing is that this little bugger is unexpectedly FAST... like twice as fast as my desktop.  I think over time I'm going to work on getting rid of the desktop and use the laptop full-time.  I've also decided that a morning walk would be a great idea... I'm starting to appreciate my body a little more, and with a little work I think I could have quite a great body.  Anywayz, i need sleep...  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Tears are not enough this time, For no waves of saline Could ever wash away The pain I've felt Nor the pain I've dealt. The truth is clear: To live is to suffer, And to suffer is to be me. Still the fact remains That I am alive, But who've I to thank? Who've I to curse?  Why am I? 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       OK, so here's what all has been going on.  My last post was because I was stuck between a rock and a hard place, mainly Joey and Bryant.  I had assumed that my relationship with Joey was over, so I pursued things with Bryant.  Then Joey tells me that he doesn't want to bring up and we learn that we are in fact in love with each other.  What choice did I have, honestly?  "Gee, do I choose the guy who I've fallen in love with or this other guy who I barely know?  Hmmm..."  So Joey and I ended our little separation.  The main reason I'm explaining this is cuz of what just happened.  I don't know, maybe it's just me, but I'm a very affectionate person.  I like hugging, kissing, tickling... physical contact means a lot to me, and I don't mean in a sexual way.  Joey has to be one of the least affectionate people I've ever dated.  He just stopped by a little while ago, and I knew he couldn't stay for long, but he wouldn't even give me a kiss goodbye.  Seriously, we've been dating again for about a month and he wouldn't even give me a kiss goodbye.  It's extremely aggravating, but more than that, it's a problem.  It's a problem that somehow needs to be solved, because I can't be in a relationship where I feel like the other person doesn't really want me around.  As I've grown up and been in more and more relationships, I've learned that compromise is vital, and I've learned to accept things like when Joey doesn't call or when he says he'll come over and then suddenly plans change.  I don't even get all of these crazy ideas any more like he's avoiding me or he's lying and off doing something else.  I finally trust him, all because I learned to compromise and accept things.  Unfortunately, there are just some things I can't compromise, things that run so deeply in my that they can't be changed.  One of those things is my need for affection.  I threw my arms around him and tried to give him a hug, and all he could say was that he smelled and didn't feel good.  Yet on the other hand, a few weeks ago my shoulders were covered in extremely painful second-degre burns, and in spite of that I was still willing to give him a big ol' hug.  I told him it wouldn't hurt even though I knew it would and did, but I didn't care.  Getting a hug was more important than the pain I would have to endure.  Does he really think I wouldn't want to hug him just cuz he's been sweating a little?  Geez, I mean we all know I'm an asshole like that, right? (that was sarcasm)  I really do have strong feelings for Joey... I really do enjoy the time I spend with him, but when a kiss goodbye is too much to ask, there is something seriously wrong.   On the work front, I, um... am trying to get myself fired.  I think today, being my second no-call/no-show, just may do it.  I know it's a stupid thing to do, but I'm not going to let any person or any company fuck me over like these people are.  Even if that means I have to collect unemployment like some lower-class person, I don't give a shit.  I'll live on the streets before I let someone tell me that I'm inadequate.  Jewel can burn in hell. I've put in applications at 4 different OfficeMax stores as well as at Brenn's work, Telemon.  They do tech support for Belkin and a couple other things... trust me, I can handle sitting in a cubicle on the phone all day.  It may be a paycut going from my $14 at Jewel to Telemon's $11, but it's worth it just to be rid of the stress.  The best part is that there is a good chance I will get a job there, though I'm not going to assume anything... it seems like every time I make an assumption, I just screw things up.  Joey, I know you've read my journal before, and you'll probably read this too... just know that I truly do love you, and the only reason I bring things like this up is because I'm trying to make this work.  By going off and saying, "oh god, don't bring this up again," that's almost like telling me you don't care, that you're not willing to help make this work.  I can't do this alone. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I don't even know where to begin... let's start with work... I've beern unemployed for the last four weeks... I suppose it's been a great chance to spend time with me, myself, and I, but it's really hurting the wallet.&nbsp; I'll probably be able to make my bills this month OK, but even with unemployment, it's gonna be really tight.&nbsp; So yeah... fun fun fun. &nbsp; On the relationship front, let's get the old shit out of the way.&nbsp; Joey was old news quite a while ago... he said his feelings changed after everything with Bryant and whatnot, and well, blah... whatever.&nbsp; Then I was sorta interested in Chris, but that fell throgh after a whole two days cuz he couldn't handle the fact that I was a top.&nbsp; I couldn't be happier with my resulting single-ness, because.... &nbsp; Now to those of you who have read my journal before, this will seem kinda familiar... another guy that I've gone ga-ga over, but there is no possible way for me to aptly explain what's happened... I'll try my best though. &nbsp; I was feeling, well, lonely *grins* and so I decided to check out a rather seedy website, manhunt.net.&nbsp; Yes, I was looking for some quick fun, I'll admit... I'd never really tried it before so I thought I'd see how it went.&nbsp; I talked to a few guys, and some actually seemed interesting... and then I started talking with this guy out in Chicago Heights.&nbsp; I don't know what I would have done if I had realized from the start what was about to happen.&nbsp; You think I was in love with Artis?&nbsp; Ha... that whole seven months of relationship couldn't even hold a candle to the last few days I've spent with the man of my dreams.&nbsp; So this little blurb is about a guy named Jamie. &nbsp; After talking on manhunt a little bit, we started talking on AIM.&nbsp; It started off with a little flirtatious talk... I mean we were both meeting on a hook-up website, and my initial motives for talking to him were his good looks and my hormonal needs.&nbsp; But it quickly became more than that.&nbsp; We talked, and instead of a hook-up, we had a date.&nbsp; We spent that evening together, and already I could feel this incredible pull toward him.&nbsp; It wasn't until that first kiss, that first hug, however, that I realized what I'd just discovered.&nbsp; A few months ago, Jamie has his palm read, and the reader said that some time in the middle of this year, Jamie would meet his soul mate.&nbsp; We both agree that, well, this could very well be it.&nbsp; It seems absolutely insane and irrational to be proclaiming my undying love to someone on our second day together, and yet that's exactly what happened.&nbsp; True love's first kiss, just like in the stories... it really happened, and it's... well, almost overwhelming.&nbsp; I'm not even quite sure what to make of it... like my head's spinning cuz it's going so insanely fast, but when we told each other how seriously we felt, we knew that yeah, it was strange to fall so quickly but neither of us was afraid... that means something, it really does.&nbsp; I've never been so sure of anything in my life, I really haven't.&nbsp; It's like all of my fears, all of the heartache I've suffered through up until now has just melted away.&nbsp; I feel alive for the first time in, well, my life.&nbsp; I feel safe, secure, and loved.&nbsp; I've always had this dream in my head of what the perfect guy would be like, and Jamie couldn't fit that dream any more closely.&nbsp; I have absolutely no doubts that this will go very very far.&nbsp; It's so amazing that it's really hard to believe.. kinda like "what's the catch?"&nbsp; And yet, in the back, I know that there is no catch.&nbsp; I know that I've found someone truly special, someone I connect with on an entirely different plane.&nbsp; I've found true love so abruptly, so unexpectedly, and for the first time ever, I don't feel alone.&nbsp; The feelings I have for him literally bring tears to my eyes, because smiling or laughing just isn't enough... my body is incapable of conveying emotions as intense as these, and all I can do is just cry because crying is the most powerful way of expressing emotions.&nbsp; I've shed tears of joy before, but none like this... never while I held the guy in my arms.&nbsp; I feel like he's been a part of me forever and that we've finally found each other.&nbsp; Whatever I was missing in my life, I've found it in him.&nbsp; I couldn't be any more excited, I really couldn't.&nbsp; Anyway, I'm extremely tired, and I have this wonderful, gorgeous guy lying in my bed all ready to snuggle the night away, so I won't keep him waiting any more... I think he and I both have waited long enough.  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       He's still here!&nbsp; Haha, not that I'm complaining one bit.&nbsp; Jamie and I have spent, at most, 15 hours apart since we met.&nbsp; It's already getting to the point where we're discussing him moving in... yeah, I should probably run that by Brenn first.&nbsp; Yes, it's that serious... already.... wow.&nbsp; This guy is amazing, let me tell you.&nbsp; Incredible.&nbsp; Wow.&nbsp; I don't even know how to put it in words, so I won't even try.&nbsp; There simply are no words to express true love like this.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>