<Blog>

<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Further well wishes come flooding in.  Elena, former employee of  urlLink MCS  is saddened by my apparent oversight in excluding  urlLink Russia   from my planned itinerary. Well Elena, I hold the lifestyle of Mr Tony Soprano in high regard and may pop across the (not so) iron curtain for a few days and see what i can dig up.  Mona, current employee of  urlLink MCS  has dreams of flaunting her thang in and abouts a  urlLink Tuscan villa  in sept/oct... We will without a doubt find Florence's equivalent to the Supper Club and pretend that we are colonial marauders here to pillage all the stocks of spansih sherry this tiny municipality has to offer.  Mona an invaluable resource of the  urlLink world's best bars  has been unearthed, memorise it - and then eat the website.  Yet another  urlLink MCS  employee Agatha has hopes of high drama when she does the Contiki thing in late May. No doubt by then  urlLink Contiki   will have changed their itinerary to include drive by's of the bar I am propping up - so no doubt ag, I and all the other horny bastards aboard the contiki bus will catch up and share tales.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks for all the good wishes people.  Nobody has offerred me a Tuscan villa jjjjjjjjjjjuuuuuuuuust yet but   Josie suggests I rock up and demand to see the accounts at the  urlLink cafe zizzi  in London,.. i think she may be onto something, as they seem to be popping up all over the UK,..   Old friend, celebrity impersonator Mr K Katsieris (who works in an office) has passed on this very sound advice;  1) Stay away from home-made hot lookanika from yugoslavia.. they are real arse burners 2) Goats milk tastes like shit no matter what country you're in!! 3) If someone comes up to you and says "Sucky sucky long time" I think you've gone treking a little too far east 4) "Threating to violate their family" is a means of getting from point A to point B in a taxi while in Greece for under $50 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       To boldly go where just about everyone else except me has gone before!   There comes a time in every man's life where he has to go out there, face his fears, throw himself headlong into an adventure which will take them to places they had not dare dream of.  For many this occurs during   urlLink O-Week   at university, when the nice chick adroned with the ample bosom whom you have been chatting with whilst looking oh so suave and sophisticated (in an undergraduate kinda way) hands you a leaflet letting you know when the next Christian Union meeting is.  Others break free from the ties that bind early in their 20s and leave ma and pa behind to boldly enter the share house and find out what it is like to live in a house whose refrigeratory device carries 6 peoples names written on 6 different milk cartons and each one of the 7 days past its presonal "best"  For I however, for I do things in ways that others do not... For I ... I thought it best to wait until aged thirty and five before leaping headlong into the bosom of my heritage and embracing the opportunity to walk around an entire continent, my most prised posessions strapped to my back and enter small cafes and places of beverage worship and utter imappropriate phrases to locals thus giving them the opportunity to  guffaw .  and lord knows how rare such opportunities are in life.  Today, armed with nought but my good name and hefty visa card credit limit, i did enter the  urlLink Carlton Flight Centre  and within its walls did i commence the negotiations of a worldly contract that would transport me bodily towards my loinage. And within this centre of flight, aided by my trusty and loyal customer service representative i was provided with hefty brochures outlining ways i can part with local currency for exchange of lodgings and transport in the mutterland.  I am choked with fear and images of foreboding but I must go on, as the tickets are ... non... re ... fundable. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The going away party now starts to take shape.  At the lovely 330 Red our "local" for the past 12 months, and a place which will no doubt hold a special place in our hearts for at least a month or two after we move.  Details are available at the  urlLink taxi bus donkey  main site. Stay tuned for pics and other reports from the night.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Jump date rapidly approaching, looks like i can cross baghdad and lunch with uncle SAddaM off the list, shame.  Cant say I have been overburdoned with preparation work,.. have crossed the possibility of getting an EU passport off the list thanks to the shifting sands that is Greek bureaucracy but will set the wheels in motion for the next trip. Its all complicated by the Greeks desire to  urlLink conscript   fit young men for the defense of the realm.  Other housekeeping tasks remain, what to do with all my crap etc etc, but all will fall into place soon.  Best of luck to Esther who is looking for a suitably funky pad to dwell in, and is going for 2 exciting employment opportunities this week at  urlLink CAPA  and  urlLink CERC 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Thanks for the fish!  Well the goodbye bash went down a treat, thanks to everyone who was able to make it all so shpeshall!!  Highlights for me included - My good buddy Sav, who worked the end of the bar that i wasnt working and had a steady stream of inappropriate comments and even inappropriately touched some inappropriate people inappropriately... Sav... we'll be doing more of the same in Europe soon. - The lovely Kim formerly of 300 red who broke lots of hearts, and eventually left at 1:30 am after saying her first set of goodbyes at 10:30 pm - The lovely Monda with her entourage who dazzled all with their collective wit and feats of great alcogolic endurance - Damian and the caring Staff including Istvan the mad Hungarian and the just so lovely Lyndel - Madeleine and the girls ... always a floorshow - Joanna K for letting me touch her bum... well... not stopping me from touching her bum... well... not calling the cops after she realised that it was me that was groping her.. - Kathy and Helen - just for being Kathy and Helen - Chris Ketsa, good to see you again brother  And last but not least - the Great John Fox who managed to pull a band out of his ass and wow the crowds and for delivering that poignant moment during the formalities.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 28 - Apecchio  OK so i am going to owe a lot of favors for this trip, and the karma meter i have been talking about is now so far in the red that i understand a small committee has been formed some place to try and find the most efficient way that my debt can be repayed and the just order of the universe restored.  Apecchio is a lovely small town about 20 minutes drive West of Urbania on the border of Marche and Toscana,.. the fact that it is pretty wont come as a great shock to anyone... the fact that it was the first time i had managed to lay my eyes on the rolling green hills of tuscany certainly did come as a shock to me ... but im not going to attempt to describe tuscan nhills on the fly in an internet cafe... uhuh... not falling for that one.... go read a book do a net search and come back in a few minutes.  On this day I along with 2 other classmates were fortunate enough to accompany 2 of our teachers to a retaurant tucked away in said tuscan(esque) hills, this was an old house on a dirt track off a drt track off a sidestreet, of course there were no students, in fact we were the only people there, in fact there was never any doubt that we were going to be the only people there.  But as I said surroundings arent important, you know those movies where some guy is sitting down at a table eating and drinking all this excellent food that is really simple but you couldn't possibly contemplate preparing or procuring on your own and the women at the table are beautiful with long dark curly hair, the kind of hair that looks like its on its way to some kind of exhibition or is protected by a national trust somewhere, postcard hair, travelogue hair, and she smiles and is fascinated by the fact that you live in this country called Australia because it is so far away and how amazing and exotic it sounds... so you pause and look around, rolling hills, great food, beautiful people and think to yourself... you would rather be trying to find a free carpark spot in chadstone????  Monia, who has been my teacher for the 4 week course and the vivacious Manu dragged fellow classmate and all american rockstar type Mehdy and my housemate and all american top bloke Ben away from quiet Urbania and off to Apecchio for an afternoon of wine, women and song... sure it was all nice and above board, the owner let us loose on his cd collection so a bit of dancing to some really daggy songs including a selection of WHAM classics, he even joined in and spun the girls around a little. The food,.. OK glad to spend some time there... antipasto simple bruscete tomato, cheese, spinach, prosciuto, flat bread with a very salty soft cheese filling,... i didnt dare ask if the cheese was greek. Pasta the varieties always have bizarre names here its not just spaghetti or tagliatelle ... but as i dont recall the technical descriptions subclass and species i will translate it into lygon street lingo we all understand... tortellini woth a very light gorgonzola and funghi sauce, a spaghetti with a basic tomato and basil sauce,.. nothing basic about the taste and some kind of ravioli, spinach and pumpkin with a meat filling pine nuts and more baby basil. Wines, more local red, tasted like a chianti, was absolutely fabulous,.. i know i poo pood chianti back home,.. shoot me if i do so again.. and we rounded it all off with lashings of cherry wine, which is just a knockout... several helpings of a limoncello cream liquour and even yes some more grappa.  But back to action, so there i was in the proverbial tuscan villa spinning my beautiful teacher monia around to the dulcid tones of ''last christmas'' and its not even july!!! sacrilige!!!! i occasionally tear my eyes off her and sneak a glance through a window,.. not a grand window with a terrace just your standard window as you would find in any suburban house back home so abundant is the beauty around here that there is absolutely no reason to make a song and dance about the view.  Again that recuring theme of beauty so heavy so thick that you feel it drag against your throat as you try and absotb it, my mind was constantly on remember this moment mode, and ive got a backlog of memories i am still trying to process. Here is just a sample of them  - sitting in the right hand side of a car driven by somebody you would normally be ogling on a magazine cover - singing along to italian rock songs and mistranslating phrases to her delight - translating english songs on the fly and impressing her with your ability to see things - an old mill in a field of poppies - streetsigns written in a font so small you have to stop get out of the car and walk up to them to read them - a dog guarding the casa we were to lunch at bigger than some ponies i have seen and a bark that would make a baritone blush - walking through the family living room in order to get to the restaurant complete with nonno asleep in the arm chair - learning how to swear in italian like a local - testing it out on the owner of the place who corrects your grammar and pours you another wine - staring at her for so long you think the muscles surrounding your eye will forget how to move - actually liking wham songs  yes, the beautiful, the perverse the timeless the dog, oh my god the dog.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Later that evening - may 17 2003  Tonight several of us dined at the local osteria la cuco, this is a tiny place big enough to fit bench tables along 2 side walls allowing just enough space for the waitress to serve the tables without bumping into you too often. No menu of course just a rapidly delivered series of dishes in no particular order. Being a small not tourist infested town we sat at table which seats about 10, were joined by a young couple from an adjoining town and had another 4 people join the other end of the table.   What did w you eat what did you eat!!! I haer you cry,.. well,.. we didnt go absolutely nuts much to my disappointment,.. we had to find a balance that people were prepared to pay for,.. so we kep it to a good range of anitpasti and 2 pasta dishes oh and desserts and wines and grappa and some stuff that noone is sure about.  Antipasti,.. several salami and pecorino cheese types,.. no biggy around here, but the smaller salami are nice and meaty not too fatty,.. a kind of cold almost canelloni type crepe filled with a mince of mozarella basil and something which was translated to me as capsicum but was something i couldnt quite place,.. a beautiful orange colour,.. some simple bruschetta with (i was assured) truffle oil, although i could not taste or smell any myself (the area around urbania is famous for truffles,.. tartufi,.. but its not quite the season for it yet).  Pasta we had some ravioli containing a specific grade of basil that they grow around here just for stuffing pasta,.. very subtle and cobined with the olive oil that i think i have described earlier made for an intoxicating mix of flavours,.. the pasta itself contained something which we couldnt agree on,.. almost had a pumpkin like aroma to it, slithers of almonds and maybe a bit too much butter dressed it all. I never caught the name of the second pasta dish,.. but these were big plump ravioli, kind of like agnelloti with procini and other wild mushrooms and some kind of meat, topped with a very light drizzle of a cream based sauce.  Drinkies? Several bottles of the rosso connero that everyone washes things down with around here,.. i must say that i am a lot more impressed with the italian wines than i thought i would be, chianti and tosso connero go down a treat and at about 3 or 4 euro a bottle at the supermarket or bottle shop its better value than back home. We also had some god awful grappa which had a wheaty tate to it,.. it was a scuro and really should have trusted my nose and skipped it... but the drinking experience was saved with a nice bottle of vin santo which i described as a noble reisling not because it is a noble reisling.. it certainly isnt, but it reminds me of a swet lighter sherry,.. the locals soak biscotti in vin santo... why i asked as i downed another glass,.. also had some beautfully fragrant and warming cherry wine and a selection of the delci which was nice but the slices were so small it became rather hard to tell one from another.  At 30 euro a head not a cheap night but a pretty unique experience.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 20  - May 19 2003 - inseperabile and vodka  Every monday night the school organises a film screening, last week it was the elephant man which i watched just to listen to the dubbing ... this week was the film inseperable with jeremy irons... this is a painful film made even more so by the painful and hard o follow dialogue (italiano of course), not really interested in talking about the film.  Howevr,.. after,.. dopo,.. the film,.. we ventured to ''bar centrale'' .. now bar centrale is one of the 2 bars that face the main piazza in urbania,.. and although it has outdoor seating and is open late we foreigners tend to frequent it much less than the caffe del teatro just across the street... well on this fresh urbanese night we changed this pattern and stormed the place. Despite what you may think, Italians actually don't drink too much, and the raggazi certainly don't go out for a night of boozing as is the norm back home... This point was made clear to us who leaning at the bar ordered our third beer in the space of about 30 minutes ..  Me: un altro per favore,.. pushing the glass across the bar. her: un altro? brief look of astonishment crossing her face. me: si... un... altro... she looks at her watch and reaches for the glass  oh but we hadn't finished, but we were classy... averna, amaretto, campari and some weird american cocktails that are all the rage over there... and then chris asks about the vodka... Vodka, like most spirits is cheap here,.. a litre of vodka con linone is about 7 euro,.. and its freezable and quite drinkable, limoncello and the like are kind of laughed at but still go down a treat... but like most places the vodka isnt stored in the freezer,.. in fact on the back of most vodka bottles i have seen it says dont put this in the freezer,.. a pox on ye who dont freeze thy vodka i say!  The owner of bar centrale Gianni,.. a man i knew i would like as he reminded me muchly of all round good buddy savvas back home, looked at me when i enquired re the vodka he produced not only ice cold vodka but tres funky little oce cold glasses to drink the stuff from... marvellous, i think he was as happy about it as i was.... further details become blurry.  Oh,.. i had my sunglasses on all night... ah the looks i got from the locals, priceless.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 18 - may 17 2003 - Random notes and musings  In rome, watched an impromptu latin jaz ensemble perform at a piazza along side the tiber in trastevere, they played for an hour on the steps of a fountain, there were at least 15 of them, just the old classics bt each had their go at a solo which was special... and no hat being passed around either... they were probably famous  did i ask if anybody knew if russel crowe was in rome with his new bride around may 1? i am sure i saw him at a table in a small osteria in trastevere,.. i looked under the tabel for a slab of VB but didnt spot one, which is the only reason i am in doubt it was him.  In rome young guys and girls were wearing these odd looking shirts,.. sort of tie dyed but mor elike thay had been used to do the painting, everywhere.  All girls in italia use surgical implements to put their jeans on, the expression  > is greeted with positivity... in fact it is sought after.. and although they are into the tight jeans .. god bless their cotton socks... unfortunately this passion for clothing doesnt always extend to the undergarments they wear with these jeans... the bog catcher is very much in vogue  I need a haircut  Ive managed to avoid familiarising myself with the sweets at the cafes and bars so far,.. doing well,.. have lost quite a bit of wait and im still recovering from the walk to Peglio which i have graphically documented in another post... although i have recovered to the point where i am now contenplating doing it again.  Still cant get over the beauty of the coffee here,.. going rate for an expresso in urbania is 80 euro cents, 85 for a machiatto and 1.05 or 1.10 for a cappuci. Purchased a 4 cup stove top espresso makre the other day, typical italian aluminium model... 3 euro, lavaza crema e gusto same packs we get back home is around 1.90 euro.  Also getting stuck into the sicilian red )we call them blood) oranges... 1 litre is about 1.80 which isnt ridiculously cheaper than back home... but i love the stuff.  I wrote my first italian poem today for class, currently with my delectable teacher Monia, will no doubt post it here when i get it back... lots of cliches and lots of really amateur images,.. but hey at least  i hav an excuse... everything rhymes in italian as well which can be annoying but you end up with some long words when speaking in 3rd person passato.  The sky i blue, unphotographable blue, i thought i knew what blue was, turns out i had no fucking idea.  everyone smokes, my next door neighbours dog smokes, everyone smokes.  You cant tell how old the woemn are around here,.. until its too late... not that i have been in such a position... but my teahcer looks maybe 25, shes actually 34, a girl in the cafe nearby looks about 30, shes actually 40, a women we spoke to at the bar last night looked about 32, she was 48,.. sofia loren has had no plastic surgery looks hotter than most of th scrags walking around chapel street and was born when my grandmother was just a kid  On that note my grandmother is doing fine and waiting for me in Ampelokipi, hang in there granny, got hours of video tape i need to fill with your memories.  Learning the lingua di strada is a lot more fun than learning how to conjugate verbs. Many words that relate to the act of picking up are based on the entire fishing experience... lovely, why mince words.  The italian word for an at sign is a 'chioccola'' which is a little snail... how cute... i picture all these hardass finance dealers and shit swaping email address......  >>
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 15 - May 14 2003 - Forza Juve  Urbania is very much a Juventus town, kids wander around in their black and white striped shirts quite often, in fact the region of marche in which urbania finds itself is the only region that doesnt have a team in the italian first division, hasnt had one for some time but they do have some hjope that Ancona which is in seria b will get promoted this year.  Wednesday night was a big night for Juve tifosi, the second leg of the semi final against the fierce Real Madrid. Real had won the first leg 2-1 in spain and the return leg in Torino ha dbeen built up to incredible heights by the local pres and fans. AC Milan had qualified for the final the night before and so Juve were expected to rise to the occasion and make it an all Italian affair for the final in Manchester in a few weeks  But of course this isnt a sports column, as i will now prove... Juve won 3-1, rather triumphantly with 2 splendid goals and parried real's last ditch efforts to make it rhough to the final, forza Juve.  This piece is about getting to live one of those fairy tale evenings for any soccer fan, sitting with the fans in a small town which totally comes toa standstill for big games. We watched the game from one of those bars that are so small nobody knows their name,.. i asked the owner and even he wasnt 100% sure, but the concept of the big screen isnt alien to these guys so we sat or leaned in my case and watched the game unfold, the fans were hopeful but not arrogantly so... Real Madrid is a real powerhouse of a team and coming from behind was a tall order.  One of the great things about Football in Italy is that everyone talks about, including the chicks, and on a big night like this the crowd is mixed, guys girls, husbands wives kids, all together screaming, throwing their hands in the air.  Spirits were lifted early when froggy star Treseuget scored for Juve, an opportunistic but well taken poke past the keeper, the crowd went as they say in the classics quite ape shit, everyone leapt up and hugged anything, beers hit the floor there was even tears,.. and this was only the 10 minute mark. The excitement picked up with the 2nd and 3rd goals to the point where nobody seemed to mind that zizou managed to sneak out a bit of his own patented magic to keep the scoreline respectable for the spaniards.  Following the game we walked around the streets of Urbania waiting for the sreams of cars and vespas to descend on the city, horns blaring flags waving, we watched them stream down via Roma (every town has a via roma) and around the town square, people hung from windows clapping, very much looking forward to the final.  Post game we caught up with Danilo, the PR guy from the italian school, mad juve supporter, he tod us how to get to one of the small underground pubs in urbania ... what a find... its called the ''new inn'' which isnt really funny until you realise that it is actually in the basement of a 500 year old building... Danilo broke open a bottle of champagne, and the bar owner also shouted us a bottle of a sweet white which was great because it was feree... wonderful little place to which we will return to watch the final.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 13 - May 12 2003 - Peglio - i think i can i think i can  In class in the morning chris heard jan, one half of the elderly dutch couple say  ''Ieri pomeriggio sono andata a peglio a piedi'', which I translated as ''yesterday afternoon i went to Peglio on foot'' well by the end of this story you too will know how important those little filler words are and that Jan did not say to peglio but he said in Peglio as the journey to peglio from urbania on foot is only done by the insane... lock me up sister.  From the terrace of my casa rumorosa we can see a castle perched atop a nearby mount, looks very impressive and if the wind is blowing right you can actually hear its bells a second or so after the bells from urbania. A breathataking structure which would have made it abundantly clear that the people that inhabited this town kind of liked to be left alone and had some pretty good technology and money backing up this desire.  I left for peglio with a small bottle of water, a book, my camera stowed nicely in my daypack, the first part of the journey went swimmingly... a wrong turn started things off.. well not technically a wrong turn just a hope that it would connect with the road to peglio... a false hope.. But not even the wrong turn dampened my spirits it gave me the chance to walk through a poppy field and say hello to some old ladies who were very surprised to see me walk past them, and not quite as surprised to see me return.  Finally on the real road to peglio the existance of a bike track completely seperate to the road made me think that yes this is a well thought out walking track and that many tourists and locals make this journey regularly and it would be pretty and scenic and local girls with arms full or local produce would greet me along the way... bzzt  about 1 km along this scenic pavement the road started to climb,.. not so bad i thought,.. i mean it's got to climb... it's not too hot and the climb and the resulting view is the reason i am here,.. i have my health happiness and a hunger for adventure..yadda yadda yadda   Another kilometre down the track, the road was still climbing and the tree canopy was becoming sparse, my water bottle half empty and the sign i just passed said winding roads for 3 kilometres. Of course the nice bike path had stopped and i was walking on the shoulder of the road with most drivers giving me a what the hell are you doing look with one of them laughing as he shook his head.  I paused after walking uphill at a fairly good pace for an hour, the views were getting better all the time but it wa hard going, i had walked for about 2 hours, taking out the efect of the wrong turn means i should be just about there,.. but i wasnt, as it turns out the 3 kilomeeteres i was told was as the crow flies, the distamce was closer to 5 kms, i didntt know this at the time. )remind me not to seek a carer as a suspense writer)  A further hour of walking uphill and afternoon sunshine and i reached the outskirts of Peglio, it was just the idea that ''i have come this far...'' that kept me going. Thew view from the top .. yeah it was good,.. but not that much better from the view from the nearly at the top... beautifull patterns of different fields, streams, mountain mists blowing across the valley and finally a cool breeze flowing across the top of the mount that i had scaled.  Peglio being a small town everything commercial was closed by this time,.. its 3 shops not available to offer me refreshment but a fountain near the bus shelter appeared to give me a chance to refill my bottle and cooll down. Certain rumblings in my stomach were nothing to worry about it was just the exercise... i had a good lunch of bread tomato tuna and ... ahh.... beans... lots of beans... hmmm  With the rumblings growing stronger i searched the town for an approriate receptacle for my ... post lunch offerings... niente, i tried speaking to two old ladies who sat near the church.. the church goddamit but nieither of them could help out.. one used the word purtruppo which i took as her saying sorry but i cant help you.. one pointed towards a bush... a small bush mind you... and laughed... i took my leave...   A large hotel loomed on the horizon,.. it meant climbing a bit further uphill,.. but hey it's a hotel, i can even see a pool dammit i can probably have a shower and have those local damsels feed me those grapes they had been peeling for the past hour. Well the size of the carpark made me believe that this is a popular spot,.. but not at the moment... the place was fenced tight and looked like it was waiting for the high season, it actually looked like the whole hotel existed somewhere else and this wa a backup copy.  With my rumblings keeping me company i began my descent, obviously much swifter than the ascent, i passed places i hadn't noticed in my approach to Peglio, a beautiful lush green field a small villa clinging to the side of the mountain, the sign indicating deer over the next few kilometres is obviously there just to keep the tourists hoping.  The rumblings had turned to cramps, but urbania was now visible my oohs and ahhs were a combination of breathtaking vistas and ass clenching fear.. i walked past that same poppy field this time wishing it wa a grove of bushes, walked under the sign welcoming you to urbania one final clench and double timed it back to casa rumorosa.   Flatmate Ben couldnt quite read the expression on my face as i approached but he has gotten to know me well enough to open the doors for me and laugh ... my shirt and jeans soaked through with perspiration, my posterior entrance surviving the ordeal and the camera in my bag capturing the moments that i will tell more often... i think.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 9, 10 & 11 Siestamatic  Getting into the morning school afternoon rest routine. God bless these crazy europeans and the afternoon siesta, why the heck should people do anything between 12:30 and 3:00 anyway? What could you do during that time that cant wait until 3:30 or the next time, may it live forever i say.  I am having to structure complete sentences now in Italian, this is challenging, i told my teacher today that my Italian is like some dangerous wall,.. i have a lot of bricks and it looks impressive,.. but there is no mortar holding the thing together so if somebody sits on it or interacts with it in any way it will fall on top of them crushing everyone in its path. I am hoping that will change by the end of next week,.. i have certainly come a long way in the pat 4 days, just need to speak more and make as many mistakes as possibl but the class structures arent quite right just yet, early days.  Friday evening we returned to what is becoming a personal favourite in Urbania, the enoteca Vin Italy for several bottles of the local plonk, three reds, going to make notes of what we are drinking next time as the range is enormous but the quality has all been of a standard higher than expected. We followed this up with a trip to a local pizzeria, wasnt very adventurous this time as i just had to get some food into me.. one of the group ordersed ''faro'' which none of .. the waitress included, were totally clear on... turned out to be some kind of wheat pasta, riche shaped but a bland grey colour,.. i can half remember something similar in greek but have probably blocked it out of my mind, any italian speakers who want to help out please do so.  Later the group returned to another local bar, one of those hole in the wall type places that only locals seem to go to...there were some great photos of the town squares and typical urbanian scenes on the wall which nobody but me seemed interested in speaking to. Mehdy, one of the students in my class had befriended a local gent who goes by the name of Bardo, yes alarm bells did ring for me too.  As always the young english speakers gather together on these things so the inner circle of the under 30 english speakers is 4 americans, Mehdy, Jessica, Jennifer and Ben and another Melbourne boy Brian who for good reason goes by the name of Stefano in italia. The youngsters occasionally allow me to tag along and try not to make it too obvious that i dont quite fit the young and beautiful criteria... i pretend to be appreciative and not aware of this... it's a balance that matches the most intricate that mama nature has tossed up from the hellfire.  They are an interesting bunch of guys to be honest, which is a pleasant surprise, my roomate Ben is an all round great guy, but its the southern belle jessica that has captured my imagination, she just makes me feel warm... i mean all over warm not specific body part warm, not that she is difficult on the eyes, on the contrary but there is a fire in her that i cant quite put my proverbial finger on... unfortunately she seems about as interested in me as... well as something that doesnt have a lot of interest,.. like that analogy you know the one, the really good one that always slips your mind when you are trying to remember it.  The posse kicked on to Urbino to hang out in one of the local bars, a great time was had by all,.. One of Bardo's buddies managed to roll his car on the return leg from Urbino, he apparently wasnt quite drunk enough to drive as fast as he was... nobody was hurt... turns out that Bardo is one of the Albanese that smother this part of europe, not that theres anything wrong with that,.. im no racist, some of my best friends are Albanian... actually no they arent... none of my friends are Albanian, this is probably because albanians would stab you for your dandruff, but you do some crazy stuff when you are on holiday.  Oh this didn't happen today but before i forget,.. there's a swedish girl who started class today,.. who looks uncannily like the bitch from ipswich Pauline Hanson,... must acquire photo soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 12'- Ravenna  Ravenna is most famour for its mosaics, and although many italian cities make that claim there is some pretty impressive stuff here... but... for me.. im not really into going into some massive monument to see a whole heap of intricately constructed objects places so far from you that you cant appreciate their intricasy or the efforts of the craftsmen. One of the new sites is the Domus dei tappeti di peitro, which was a site unearthed during a mundane demolition, this exposed rouhgly 50x20m of beautiful mosaic work including some murals, mix of greek and roman influences but the sheer geometry of it is stupfying, if you are going to Ravenna in the next few months be sure to check it out... its not on the tourists maps as yet as it only opened a few months ago... everything ele is chruches.  The city being near the coast si flat and easy to get around, their paved streets habe a smooth section in the centre which i quickly realised... mi scusa signora,.. is for people riding bikes... it was only after 5 hours of walking around that we discovered that there were bikes for tourists available for free... probably a good thing i didnt see it... id be a statistic.  On the way to ravenna we paused at S.Apollinaro in classe, impressive church again... yeah ,... mosaics... but there was a first communion service going on which was great to see,.. kids on the big stag with the padre, proud parents watching priests asking kids questions about their faith and simple bible quizzes and the kids answering proudly or shyly turning way from the mass and whispering their answer into the priests ear... i got to tell off a german who was using a flash camera, everyone loved me.... well aside from the tourist... but i had a shirt on and looked impressive.  On the minibus ride on the way back i discovered exactly how sore my ass can get .. and also discussed the intricacies of the german and italian recycling programs with my class mate Rupi... man those germans know how to party.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings tranSport fans. Ziz's reporter on the ground here in Melbourne is making sure that the Taxi - Bus - Donkey site has as much to offer as this fast-paced edge-of-your-seat Dolmio-grin blog.   To view the images from the farewell party, go to  urlLink the Taxi - Bus - Donkey "taxi" page , where you'll also find a link back to here. Got your own pix?  urlLink Send them to me and I'll put them up.   Multicultural Australia not slapping you around hard enough?  urlLink WogLife is still up and running  and a few new articles have appeared this week. If you're not wearing a WogLife tshirt,  urlLink ask yourself why .  Ziz - love your work. May we all live the next few months vicariously well!  End transmission.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 8 - 7th May 2003 - Urbino  This afternoon around 18 of us piled into a little bus, the kind of bus you usually see at the bottom of a steep ravine on the 6 o clock news and headed of for a few hours in Urbino with a few stops along the way ... the first of which being .. you guessed it... a ravine.  The river Metauro that slowly winds its way around Urbania combines itself with several other rivers in the area and has forged a valley in the vicinity of Urbino. Steep high cliff faces of various coloured stones rise suddenly up from the river forming a cathedral of stone, at the opening of this fiorgo a small church stands we piled out of our bus and into it's cold dark space with the sounds of kids playing a rather energetic game of soccer at a park directly opposite bouncing off the walls, again the clash of the ancient and the utterly modern is everywhere. The slab in the chamber below the pulpit was cold, i lay down for a few seconds when nobody in the group was watching.... somebody had carved Juve Merda on the stone above my head.  During the afternoon we had the opportunity to spend a great deal more time in  urlLink Urbino , once again the youthful effervescence of the town during school days is its most prominent feature but we had time to walk some of its ridiculously steeply sloped streets. It was only recently that cricket jumpers became all the rage in Europe, one of the sports clothing stores in urbino still had a good range to choose from... my favourite were the mockups of rugby league jumpers,.. with my favourite slogan being ''The frontier spirit of the australia'' the 25 euro price tage took it beyond the souvenir bracket but i had a good laugh at the shopkepers expense,.. which is good as it is usually the otherway around.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 7 - 6th May 2003  Im not getting paid for this plug, but as it so happens, all the teachers in the school are absolute dolls. We were greeted with their beaming smiles and round sof Buongiorno when we first entered the doors and it was just impossible to not be lifted by their youthful enthusiasm and breathtakingly tight pants.... a la italiano.  MY teacher is Monia, a lovely girl from the nearby town of  urlLink Apecchio , long text book italian bombshell black curly hair, dark eyes and a smile that breaks hearts at 50 paces. The classes are conducted entirely in Italian albeit it with the odd word or two in English from Monia to help us know the meaning of a new verb. My fellow class mates are - Mehdy a young American guy from University of South Carolina who has an Iranian background a good sense of humour and your all american type, Rupi, hailing from Germania and who is certainly the most vocal of our classmates, i mean that in a technical and sensible sense,.. i would definitely be the one who craps on the most. Jan and Helder an elderly Dutch couple who are devoting the rest of their lives to travel, Jan has a wicked sense of humour and he and I have been getting along rather well and finally Chang Chang a chinee girl who has the best diction and grammar skills in the class but who closes up like the proverbial clam shell when its her turn to speak.  I on the other hand would easily have the worst grammar skills in the class but launch into long soliliquies when asked to speak, ive never let grammar get in the way of an opportunity to speak shit. Per sempio when asked to introduce ourselves to the class and tell them what sort of place we liev in back home i asid something along the lines of 'I am the duke of melbourne, well actually i am the son of the duke of melbourne i am just a bum who travels the world spending money. I live in a grand palace with approximately 30 bedrooms a few swimming pools a church in which we play tennis and 3 pink dogs' Its great what you can do with a rudimentary understanding of a language, a dictionary and a few spare hours.  We haev classes mon-fri from 8:50 to 12:20 conversation classes in the afternoon from 2:30 to 4:30 special lectures organised in the afternoons of Monday and Wednesday and a revision class on Saturday mornings from 9:00 until 11:00. The school also organises excursions on wednesday afternoons and all day sunday, tomorrow afternoon we go to Urbino with a few stops along the way.  Tonight however i figured that study was my best option, although i am glad i have been placed in the elementary group, i have a great deal of catching up to do, the course i completed in melbourne was very conversation based and though this made it possible for me to land in rome and be able to feed myself and gain shelter I have to start plugging the gaps.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 6 - Back to School  OK well my mum didnt pack me a lunch and i didnt cry when i was waiting at the front door of the school waiting for the first day to begin, but the place has a bell that rings between classes,.. so i guess its flash back time.  Monday was the beginning of my 4 week course at the  urlLink Centro Studi Italiani  here in Urbania. The course commenced with an entrance exam, th only italian i had studied was 10 x 3 hour classes )level 1 and 2) in Melbourne, after about 20 seconds reading the entrance exam for the course i figured that the standards here would be significantly higher. I fumbled my way through the exam stuffing up what i thought were fairly basic things and then had to inflict the oral component of the exam onto one of the teachers. I guess i did better than i thougth at the oral component, because eventhough my grammar was pretty abismal and you could drive several 3 wheel APE through the holes in my vocab i managed to get into the elementary group and avoid having to go through the beginners course again.  That Afternoon Danilo, one of the school admin staff and all round cool dude took the new students on a bit of a hike to a monastery with great views over the whole of the city, a good chance to shoot the shit with the other students and for the younger and more adventurous amongst the group to designate shagging targets. Student numbers are down this semester due to the travel precautions that have plagued the world over the past few months so there are only about 25 of us.   Later that night we were guests at a local enoteca 'Vin Italy' where we sampled several local wines while the store's proprietors Alessandra and his wife Maria Grazie discussed some of the finer points of the stuff we were shoveling down our throats, some of the highlights included a Vin Santo which was a sweety ... smells and tastes like a Noble Riesling, several sweeter reds, served chilled just how i like em and some wines from Puglia. The drinks were accompanied by serveral antipasti parmesano and salami from the local area and an absolutely magnificent olive oil which i will definitely be sending back home, golden and light with an effervescence that i have never ever encountered before, yeah top night.  I returned to my wog palace in via dante alighieri to an interesting night listening to the trio of dogs in the area, the upstairs neighbour who insists on walking around the tiled floors of her apartment in what must be steel tipped stilleto boots and the neighbours on the other side of our bedroom wall quite happy to allow their nippers (nipoti) to have some very professionally coordinated tanrtrums. Classes start at 8:50 Tuesday morning
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 5 - Hungry in Urbania  The apartment I find myself in is a fairly typical Greek or Italian family apartment block. The parents have a largish block located near the town centre, knock down the shack and build a two storey concrete slab structure which houses them and their children and has other seperate apartments which their children will move into when they are old enough to marry. Most of the apartments in the via i live on are such structures,.. on the streets name is of course Via Dante Alighieri what better name could there be for a travelling scholar such as myself. The place is noisy, even for a Sunday morning, i find myself up with the roosters letting the cool mountan air hit my face at about 6:30 am, I figure time for a shower and a walk.  In the brief encounter with landlord guy i had some detailed instructions on how to operate the hot water system, this involved the highly technical flicking of the switch on and waiting... in fact the intructions were difficult because i wasn't familiar with the italian verb ricordare which has nothing to do with making a note of something, simply means remember,... don't forget that... maybe record it somewhere.  So switch flicked, pants off and waiting... and yeah... even after several glances at the watch.. niente aqua caldo.... figures i say to myself,.. its that bloody taxi driver Karma coming back to haunt me... a cold shower for me in a cold apartment on what was thankfully not as cold a morning as it can get around these parts.  So, with a slight shiver in my knees and having checked that i have the apartamento keys on me 3 times i head off for a better look around Utbania.  Urbania like Urbino is located within mountain range peaks, Urbania is reasonably flat, ... absolutely flat when compared to Urbino but hilly when compared to ... Noble Park. (noble park being the global standard for determining the hillicity of urban areas). Urbania's old city is walled and surrounded almost entired by a river (the Metauro) which is rather dank but makes for good photos as long as you keep smellavision features off.  I paused for some time at the eastern bridge into the town, an old bridge with a large single arch, rising about 40 metres from the river, the banks of the river crammed with very sensibly arranged vegetable gardens and a rather new but quaint looking shack. I sat on the stone wall and pretended to read whilst actually watching birds swoop playfully down the sides of the valley and under the bridge their chirpring echoing crisply off the stone walls. I figured I would read for a while until the town started to wake, luckily i wasn't serious, as it was now about 9:00 and apart from one old lady who sported that the °what the heck are you!° look on her face as she passed me and the odd old man driving around in his APE it was only me the birds and several slowly growing vegetables that were moving.  I returned to the town square to find several people out and about, the road through the centre of town had been blocked just to make me believe there was going to be a market or something that involved the exchange of goods and services for slips of paper but it wasnt to be, the barriers were purely to divert the 1 car per minute which would have used those streets on a sunday and given them something to tisk tisk about.  There were 2 Gelateria open,.. so... my diet for the day  10:00 breakfast - a un espresso e uno piccolo gelato tiramisu 13:00 lunch - un espresso un aqua minerale e uno piccolo gelato fragole 17:00 afternoon snack.. felt like something different - una grande e un gelato con tiramisu e caffe e panne (thats cream not bread folks) 16:00 for the long 3 minute walk home ... another grande with tiramisu and vanilla, hold the panne.  In betwixt gelati i had ample opportunity to perform several giri of Urbania, beautifully laid out, narrow cobbled streets with all streetfront places being 1 or 2 storeys and a great mix of adornments made to the houses, signs of life on every door and window, the strung up laundry the odd well fed cat stores selling fresh produce nestled behind simple doors a good mix of churches which have a politely coordinated bell ringing hierarchy and even a small church where mumified remains of long dead significant people are visible, certainly never seen anything like that before.  I tracked down the location of my school and all the other essential services i would need, including a pool table in one of the bars and headed badk home to digest my gelati. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 4 - Rome to Urbania  One of those journeys that takes longer the closer you get to your destination, I left roma at the beautiful (cough) Termini Station on my 3 hour train ride to Falconara on the Adriatic coast. In Termini I was that guy that always gets those looks from yourg girls or ladies who are having trouble freeing up a baggage trolley... and being the all round nice guy that i am i helped out, even though I had a rather large backpack strapped to me, ... and to answer the question... no,.. not all the ladies who looked to me for assistance were good looking... some of them were great looking, i think one of them may have been a model, but there was at least one who was rather plain. maybe So if you are looking for trolley loosening tips see me when i get back cos i had that shit sorted after an hour standing around the departures board waiting for my Ancona train platform number to appear. It's all in the bounce ... the same theory applies to many things not solely trolley related.  The train road to Falconara was reasonable, sat next to an italian woman reading a Wilbur Smith novel,.. it seems crap literature knows no boundaries... Got to see some rather picturesque scenery, it felt good to see lush green plains augmented by the brilliant european springtime sun.  At Falconara i disembarked gracefully and got a lungful of Adriatic air, as most of you hardened travellers will know the train line along the east coast of italia runs along the shoreline for quite some way, so my trip from Falconara to Pesaro was spent mainly looking over my left shoulder at the expanse of blue and the meeting of sky and water.  At Pesaro it was time to use the italian and sort out the buses,.. A bus to Urbino was the second last leg of the journey, ... ask ''dove la bus per urbino'' at the train station, walk to the °piazza° (I have learnt now that Piazza usually means the place where the rubbish bins are located ... or ... carpark)... stand around waiting, ask the guy in the ticket office when the bus comes, he tells you when the bus comes but doesn't tell you that the tickets are for sale at the bar at the other end of the piazza, so when the bus arrives you do a mad dash across the piazza and meet the bar owner at the door who has a handful of tickets awaiting the oncoming masses... anyway... i am now on the Bus  Urbino, is a university town nestled in the mountains about 45 minutes off the Adriatic coast, fairly unique mix of architecture and humanity, very youthful due to all those pesky students but right up there on world standards of significant buildings with the palazzo ducale and other highlights certainly making the place worth a visit,.. I had a quick stroll around but the very steep hills, my backpack and already 8 hours on the trip clock combined with the fact that it was only 18kms from my ultimate destination made me figure... come back some other time.  So I parked my ass under the portico in the very tasteful carpark and waited for the Urbania bus to arrive... much to my surprise after about 60 minutes of squinting at oncoming bus signs... 1, or 2 or 20 steep climbs, breathtaking turns and with me the only person on the bus the doors are flung open at yet another car park along with an enthusiastic cry of °Urbania° oozing from the drivers mouth.  But Im not there just yet,.. I am in Urbania to do a 4 week Italian course, accomodation at an apartment has been organised, i have the apartment address but dont really fnacy my chances of finding it,.. i have the owners mobile number which i assume i had been given with good reason.. so i call it.. an old lady answers the phone...   me: buona sera signora, signore davide passeri per favore signora: 30 seconds of uninterrupted italian shouted down the telephone line me: mi scusi signora ma parlo un po' italiano signora: repeats what i assume was the same passage but slower and louder,  she then drops the phone, I figure i am supposed to stay on the line... she returns... and rattles off a series of numbers... i am a clever guy and figure this is probably a phone number... I hang up and ring it  The phone is answered thusly yes yes si si aspelte arrivo a cinque minuti.. i have one car grey I knew what that meant so ordered a coke and sat down at the bar near the bus stop.  Several cars pull up, none of them grey, one rather nice silver hatch appears,.. i recall the difficulty my father and i had over the years understanding the subtleties in the translation of things are silver in colour grey in colour white in colour or transparent and figure thats my guy.  I stand up backpack in my hands,... I am trying to look as touristy as possible ... i am pretty sure i even had a map in my hands... he walks up to me doesnt give me a second look... into the bar ... out again and into his macchina and off. After what I know now would have been a lap of the town the silver car returns, he gets out walks past me again ... °Davide?° I say... he turns to me as if i just fell from the sky... °Yes... chrisa!!!° we go.  He takes me to what will be home for 4 weeks.. its a combination of typical melbourne suburban construction methods,.. with that added elemtn of euro wog chic, the place is newish but seems to have been constructed using salvaged parts and the remains of what used to reside at that address, different tiles in each room, differrent door knobs on each door, strange mixture of light fittings, but it was reasonably clean and i was ssured that it was just two one hundred metres from the centro,. this could have been 2100 metres, 102 metres, or 200 metres. A brief tour of the facilities and my new landlord Davide disappears and I a tired and weary traveller on the new leg of a journey stand in the kitchen listening to two flies bounce off the window.  Its probably no where near as bad as it seems, i say to myself.  I unpack my bags, lie down for 30 minutes and test out this two one hundred metre theory, the directions were good and i find myself in the centre of town... once again turning heads.... the sole objective was food, but some of the buildings and the old bridge i literally stumbled across just made me stop for an oh wow moment.  The smell of wood fired pizza dragge dme nose first into La Loggia pizzeria, i had an insalata Caprese with some very generous slabs of fromaggio de la name escapes me, fat juicy pomodore and basil leaves that cover your palm.. and pizza boscaiola, the pizza was super thin, crisp and still had charcoal specs from the wood oven on it, it hung over the plate, big but not very bready so it hit the spot, luckily my good sense told me that it was unlikely that i would find something to eat on sunday in such a small time so i loaded up... wise choice.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 3 - May 2 - Central Rome  Rome basically shuts down for May Day, so in my travels i came across several shops that i had been looking for, the local supermarket, tabacchi , post office, phone shop... so i started my day with a mission, purchase a few things, including bus tickets and head into termini station to purchase tickets i would require to travel to Pesaro on Saturday ... tomorrow on my way to Urbania.  The bus whisked me off to Termini and it was all rather orderly... Melbourne has been plagued with public transport ticketing problems ... looks like rome has had a taste of their own.. each bus has 2 types of ticket validating machines... 1 old one and 3 new ones... but there is no ticket selling on board,.. you have to buy tickets from Tabacchi,.. but not all Tabacchi sell them because they dont make a cut on them that they are happy with... The newstands sell tickets but they are the old ones that they purchase via rather dodgy means apparently... they are still good, just not new fangled ones. fangled doesnt necessarily mean better,.. its just has added fangles.  I was trying to stick my old ticket int the new ticket slot much to the pleasure of the romans within sight of yet another hapless tourist doing this... they didnt offer help,.. it wasnt life or death.. the whole system seems a bit slack, turns ourt that the old validators are at the back of the bus only,... i knwo this now... this i now know.  Acquired tickets ra6ther swiftly at Termini,.. i had prearmed myself with keywords to lubricate the transaction,.. solo andate, posta, diretto, bigletto... done... hopefully wi ll actually find the train tomorrow morning...26 platforms and people wandering around everyhwere, rose sellers and beggars again yeah yeah.  Came across a fangled )refer to repvious definition of fangled and fanglisation) inernet access point in tyermini, it was ridiculously expensive but as i hadnt touched the net for 4 days... it was my duty... the fanlging of this net access computer meant that the keyboard had various dodgy keys, these were the seldom used letters °e° and °d° and space bar... so i apologise to the people i emaile during that time... ill decipher when i get back.  From Termini,.. a subway ride or two got me to Spagna... which i figured was roman for Spanish and the steps of the same name... well all those years at university paid off cos goddamit i was right... The Spanish steps was a suriprise actually, interesting beautiful and functional,.. and not just because i like looking at chicks... ok.. well maybe it was just because i like looking at chicks... but it was interesting... took the vide camera for a 30 minute stroll from piazza di populi to spanish steps and up the suckers... after which i needed a drink.  Now the restaurants etc near the tourist attractions are notorious for rip offs,.. so i sat at one just so i can share the story with you.. all prices in euro espresso 2,30 large 1L mineral water 2,90 small mineral water 1,90 sandwhiches around 7,00 pot of beer, 5,00 pint of beer 10,00 )thats 20 bucks for a pint of freaking no name la spina beer!!) So i order an espresso and a °grande° mineral water,.. but i receive an espresso and a °piccolo° mineral water.. and yeah you guessed it .. was charged for the grande... luckily for me the cashier spoke quite gopod english so she understood the abuse i poured on her establishment,... bring on the next victim i think she uttered.  From there, spring in my step delivered by roman espresso i headed off to the trevi fountain, i didnt expect to beimpressed,.. i wasnt... its just a lot of statues really,.. i mean yeah its impressive.. if you like that kind of thing,.. i came here becuase of a recommendation for internet access,.. from which i have been typing these updates.. and where i have spent the last 3 hours... simple place on via luchessi directly to the left of the fountain,.. typical narrow street overcorwded with gift shops and this lovely net point crammed with people from all over the world doing what we are all bound to do at some stage... think of those we have left behind.  cheers for now.... arriverderci roma domani,.. on to new experiences further north... i didnt toss a coin in the trevi but i think im coming back anyway.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 2 - Trastevere yeah yeah  I spent most of today in Trastevere, the place has me hooked.. it the cliched image of a narrow lane, a small dimly lit cafe at the bottom of a run down building, cobbled alley with garbage, cats, beggars and locals enjoying a chianti,.. family discussions flowing from the windows in the uppoer flors and washing strung on lines betwee the buildings... but its real and there is street after street of it just waiting to be seen. Alley after alleys spins into a web of discoveries and suddely bursts forth onto large piazzi or churches, fountains with cool clear water.. its a dream    I got blissfully lost this morning, even though that meant long uphill walks past walled villas, there was just delight after delight and i literally stumbled across one of the best views in rome.. somewhere i planned to go to but didnt think i was doing so just at that particular moment.. i hope to get some pics on soon.  Walked to the vatican in the afternoon along the Tevere, San Pietro, its all about magnitude, picutres cant capture it, you just feel small,... you are supposed to, its very effective..What impresses me more about all these ancient wonders are the fact that at the time of their construction there were so few people that would actually see them... today with easy access to affordable travel every wog and their dog has gone to the Trevi fountain and it is still magniicent,.. but 100 years ago and more,.. the magnitude ... thats what its all about, we cant capture that devotion today, no government could build a monument to equal these places, because they would be uilt knowing that millions of people from all over the world would visit it, places of work of such magnificence will never be built again.  No it aint federation suqare.  But why are there so many locals on the streets of rome flocking to piazzas and sipping drinks or just riding around on their vespa_ Why cant we capture this same spirit in some of the communities we have in melbourne.. Fitzroy, Carlton, St Kilda,.. there is something missing. I guess it comes back to necessity, housing is cramped and cities arent allowed to sprawl as much as they can back home... people need the space and desire interaction with people who share their lifestyle,.. its not climate, ours is comparable, its not public works, our public transport, cleanliness etc surapss what i have seen here, there is a willingness to participate that we dont have in Australia, a spirit a culture a feeling that you are a part of something and each person plays a special part in the tapestry of life, multicultural life as its meant to be not as we have constructed it back home... there is an evolution a rapid evolution a vibrancy which we lack.  The afternoon was spent gettling lost on the way back from the Vatican, not that good a lost this time, through baically residentlial new developments ... iwaslked the wrong down a very long alley and a man appeared before me.. i was wondering which newspaper would come to cover my murder, because i really like the fact that repubblica has 2 b's... but turned out that he was there to help, i didnt understand a word he said but he got me back onto the road that lead to San Pietor and away from the dreaded roads that wind around the walled Villas... and when i saw walls im now talking about a 5 foot red brick job,.. im talking walls,.. 50 feet of granite... i couldnt understand a word the guy said... i think he spoke italian but not any italian that i did... i brought him a beer at place that was open even though we were at the ass end of May Day and stumbled back towards home.  One more detour took me across the river, in a half assed attempt to get to Trevi fountain before nightfall and make a day of it... i stumbled across Via Giulia a straight lane flanked by old houses, the odd embassy, a palazzio and a beautiful fountain covered in roses, I sat there to check my map whren a large family on their afternoon passegiare walked past me, i didnt catch everything the protagonist of the family said but he looked at me and my map spinning between my hands and said... °Roma,.. via fontana,.. via la fontana... via la fontana° to which i replied... °si,.. via un altra fontana,.. via un altra fontana... via òa due fontani° they laughed,.. the old lady that walked with them gave me a rose.  A Trastevere pizza, topped with sausage, cheese, tomato oven baked on an irregular shaped dough,.. i could taste the ash from the oven ended the day for me..
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      day 1 - Trastevere - Colosseum - Forum  I awoke feeling naked,.. oh,... well i was feeling naked more importantly... stop distracting me with what i was wearing... which was nothing... anyway... the sink or swim approach to this holiday had definitely started, i knew precious little about the city i was in ... i had a map but wasnt sure exactly where i was, wasnt sure which way the river was so wasnt even able to just wing it... but i did have very comforbale lodgings at  urlLink Hotel San Francesco  in trastevere, so its not like i was camping or anything... lordie lordie  spent the first few hours of the morning gethering food and working our where i was,.. i kind of worked it out... did some road crossing practice,.. literally almost got killed the first step i placed onto a road... even though i was trying to remember to look to the left... my brain just said what the hell are you doing and made my head look to the right.. it wasnt a bus,.. and it wasnt even one of those crazy 3 wheeled cars,.. just an everyday fiat ... its driver said something to me which i will have to take up with my Italian teacher when i get back.  A bit more road crossing practice and i was feeling better,.. made my way to the river, back to the hotel and sense of direction (one of those things you cant buy at the tabachi) had been acquired.  Most of you know i dont like crap movies.. in fact some of you probably think i only like crap movies.. thats because its you who like crap movies and dont yet know it.. But i watched the movie gladiator all because of this strange obsession i had with the colesseum,.. i have never been able to explain it... but the place has captivated me since a fellow student showed me some photos of it back in 1978, Well todayed i walked it touched it smelt it etc, and although cliched and reasonably crowded it still meant something, the scale of things, the scal of human ability to both build something magnificent and yet use it for something so primitive .. and the need to preserve these structures as places of importance even thought the tastes and beliefs have changed.  Tourists will be pleased to note that the gladiator clad dickheads who try and make you take pohotos of them were gone, that was nice, although i had learned several swear words just for their ears,.. but knowledge is a good thing,, i am sure it will come in handy one day soon.  From the colleseum it was onto the Roman Forum just a bunch of old stuff really,.. nice place for a block of apartments, i had read a comment on a website about Circa Massimo once,.. which just read °why dont they just concrete it° and figured i better go and work out why for myself... well its got me stuffed... i think melbournes italian australian community should each send 1 kilo of pebble mix over to cover the place,..  Back to my bed in Trastevere for more efforts at de-jetlagging myself... i have hayfever,.. i never get hayfever,.. crazy roman pollen i guess... jasmine everywhere, sweet smelling,.. but eye swelling.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 0,5 ' first taste of rome   Im shagged i say to myself,.. i walk out the gates at Flumininco and didnt realise i was past customs until i was already on the street, dodgy people offering me everything from hot showers, to roses to °drivings in most comfortable of car°. whats the go with the rose seller? hey I just got off a plane,.. how about a rose to celebrate!!!   The intersting signage at rome leads me to the train station conveniently located near the station via a series of up and won excalators,.. they should just replace them with sheets of aluminium make you sit in a bag and give you a big push so you can go wheeeeee all the way to the ticket office.  Now the bulk of yoursist catch the express specifically designed train to take you direct to rome's Termini central station.... but no... i like to do things differently,.. im not staying in central rome i am stayin in Trastevere, anybody who knows rome will be oohing and ahhiong about now... but that meant i had to catch the local °regionale°... i accomplished this and was feeling pretty proud of myself... even got off at the right station, remembered that uscita was exit and walked out into romes brilliant sunshine at trasteverre station backpack, carry on luggage including the bags under my eyes.  I had some excellent instructions on how to get to my hotel however and set off... ok so i didnt have excellent instructions,.. in fact .. i had this map which looked reasonable if you have never beedn to rome,.. well it turned out to be a useless piece of shit and i didnt even notice when it blew out of my back pocket.. the map that is.  I somehow manegd to get back to Trastevere station after a good 45 minutes walk in full sun... yeah i love rome i was thinking... oooh what a great day... collected my thoughts and figured i would need a drink... go to the °bar° at the station and ask for a chinotto... asking for a chinotto in melbourne is greeted with °what the?° which means we dont have such an item ... or °yes° in rome however, there are several types ... so i had to go through this pointing exercise but finally got what i thought i wanted.  And then despite my hours of training,.. forgot that you pay at the cashier and not at the counter,.. anyway i think i walked into the only bar in rome where the owner doesnt have at least a rudimentary undrestanding of what theyt have been led to believe is english... i gota  drink,.. i think it kept me  alive...  I collected my trhoughts and headed back out the front of  Trastevere station, i started to lose it,.. albeit in a really cool and interesting kind of way. Trams buses, ladies with prams, beggars )polite beggars) all started to whirl into a crazy cacophony with me in the middle and a shower and bed visible on the other side of a chasm... yeah dn there were frogs in that chasm and everyone is scared of frogs... and they were croaking and all.  But the specil powers of the chinotto plant kicked in, i saw a group of white cars arranged in some kind of weird circle as if they were taking part in a seance, staggered towards them,.. an older man walks towards me and says ?taxi!? i say ?siiiiiiiiiiiiii? he says ?stanco eh?? i say aha... and mutter the name of my hotel... he says ?ah yes i take you straight there? it wasnt literally around the corner, but it was literally around 3, the fare was 3,80 and in my stupor,..i didnt tip the guy, and even after i didnt tip him he carried my bag to the front desk and said thanks  But that lack of tip will come back and haunt me, taxi karma man, thats bad karma.  The rest of the day involves me showering and expresing deep feelings of love towards my bed and pillow and the comfort it provieded,.. i dont ythink internet publishing laws in italy allow me to go any further... i slept for 12 hours from 3pm to am...  Oh i did manage to slip in an hou of late night ityalian television... see this is why these people are so sensible,.. freelay available soft porn,.. it has to be good for everyone.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 0 - Melbourne - Singapore - Frankfurt basically a day on bloody planes or around them or within the centres that cater for them  Most of you know that i am not petite,.. i may prefer bra sizes that are, but they arent for personal consumption... i am rather large so the prospect of sitting in confined space for some time is a bit hard to deal with. First leg was melbourne singapore, blessed by SARS Iraw and all that othe good stuff the flight was empty .. i exchanged pleasantries with the guy sitting near me and enjoyed 7 hours fo lounging around empty seats everyplace... watched °adaptation° several more times,.. great movie ... glad it won zero oscars however.  Singapore wasnt quite as SARS crazed as i thought, lots of people wearing masks but not everyone.. i didnt bother, 3 hours kicking around singapore airport,.. they dont call it changi quite as blatantly as they used to i note... is enough for anybody,.. so got back onto the singapore airlines flight for frankfurt.  Now i was supposed to fly direct to rome, but singapore airlines in an effort to save people from the dangers of SARS had the great idea of dumping everyone onto the same flight (egnius) and therefore cancelled the rome direct flight and moved us all, hosts and carriers alike...  onto the Frankfurt flight..  The frankfurt flight was full,.. not a dry seat in the house...i sat opposite lots of lovely people of asian persuasion wearing masks... sat next to an interesting young german couple returning from 4 weeks in hospital in bali,.. turns out that they had a motorbike accident on their first day... so they had a great time!!! he deserved it .. she was nice.. dump him, dump him i say!!!!  12 hours and 30 minutes straight on a plane full of oddfellows... it was supposed to be 12 hours and five minutes but we had to go up hill a bit more than expected.  Frankfurt airport is a hole, don't go there,.. its sprawling as this makes german people feel more important,.. you get to have a good look at the planes that actually fly you around, trust me this isnt a good thing... dont fly Thai whatever you do, their plans are held together by recycled noodle boxes.  Sav had mentioned that I should count the dots at frankfurt airport,.. had i recalled this important tid bit of information i perhaps wouldnt have gone insane... alas... 2 hour wait, 1 hour delay, and the final leg to Rome on a bloody Lufthansa flight was underway.  The flight left at 10:30am so it was a °snack° that landed on my tray, here is the exchange  Lufthansa boy: You will be having of the snack? ziz: yes i will be having of the snack?... iw ill also be reading of the newspaper LB: reading of the newspaper? ziz: yes reading of the newspaper LB: reading of the newspaper? Being the first time he had met me i let him off lightly, he probably didnt know that i am a lyrical gangsta and also didnt know that i had spent 28 hours on in or around planes... ziz: yes please LB hands me a newspaper... its german, i hand it back LB looks at me ziz: do you have an english paper? LB an english paper? ziz; yes an english paper LB an english paper? ziz ya un auslander newspaper fastunkerden )i dont know what fastunkerden means but stevie b made the word up a few years ago.. it had the desired effect) He brings me ... the financial times... If i had any stocks... i would know just how they were doing ... on April 12th, but i was sitting next to americans after all, so i appreciated his efforts.  We landed in Rome, and as per usual, my luggage was the absolute last to come out of the carousel, I'm standing there, nobody around the odd left behind bag spinning around thge carousel,.. watching the little flashing light on the end of the conveyor belt that has delivered everyone else their sock and jocks... thinking wwell this is grand.... and suddenly it appeared... plopped out the chute and sat ther staring at me... it didnt look opened,.. but had it contained anything other than my undergarments i dont think i woul dhave seen it... obvioulsy nobody in the rome airport baggage handling department has a prefernce for XL sized mitch dowd cotton lycra boxers, fools.  The interesting outcome was that my luggage was so late,.... nobody was interested in my passport... so i dont actually exist,.. i can stay forever,.. but that's a lot.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Memories are real, only the facts have been changed to protect the justification of expenditure   Alfredo, knowing that family is a good source of free and reasonably reliable, but more importantly free labour played his part in the production of child. His son, now approximately 30 years old... maybe more.. maybe less, is regularly seen around Lucca steering one of the various forms of Le Torre branded means of transportation betwixt the various areas of lodging they manage.  Number 1 son is often seen accompanied by a rather tall, dark, slim attractive woman, very similar to the many italian tall dark etc etc women in the area... similar except for the fact that she happens to be venezuelan.  Today, once again partaking in the now traditional afternoon activity of doing othing in piazza carmine with alfredo and the missuz we were joined by number 1 son, his girlfriend and his girlfriend's sister (I can wait while you go get a whiteboard but there arent any new characters in this tale so if you have your heard around the players so far you are sweet)  The sister carried a large black briefcase, lawyer style with a large flap across the top, she sat down in the once vacant seat that now contained her ass opened her case, i half expected to be served with some kind of summons, and removed several small glass plates, a small table and several small pots. She arranged the small pieces of glass on appropriately small stands, even with my pointless eyesight i could see familiar images, ponte vecchio, rialto bridge, etc etc. She took our a few brushes and began applying paint to an otherwise bare piece of glass.  I leant forward took a closer look, i picked up one which depicted a fairly anonymous row of houses along a tight slightly curving street leant back and examined it for a few minutes.   "why do you like that" she asked in reasonable english. "I like it because it doesn't exist" I replied, she smiled waving her brish over the table. "None of them are real... in fact out of all of them that one" she said pointing her brush towards my hands, "is the only that exists, its the street that I lived on in Firenze when i was learning how to do this." She continued giving me a brief description of the various businesses, local oddities and details that she had captured.  "Do you sell many of these ones?" I asked, she shook her head and returned to her work.  "I've never sold any, that's the first one i finished and ive had it with me for almost 2 years" "It doesnt sell because it's not the image people want to construct in their minds" "All of these are fantasy, they are ... highlights" "postcards"  Exactly i thought, text book tourists will buy trinkets the same way they take photos.always tring to reconstruct the photos they saw in the brochure their travel agent gave them several thousand dollars ago. But even though those look like photos, they may as well have been painted onto glass by my venezuelan friend, as they have been reconstructed, touched up, improved, they are fantasy. The road signs, telephone and electricity cables, traffic lights, overflowing bins have been extracted. The conversation moved between English, Italian and hand gestures as we struggled to find a common level of communication.  "Why dont you paint what you see?" A strange question i thougbt considering what we could see was a narrow service avenue behind a row of houses lined with cars, vans, packing crates and Alfredo rather enthusiastically playing with his dog. She chuckled and pointed at the frame in my hands  "I did, ... nobody bought it" I examined the image and passed it back to her, "well even this is the highlights, you have left out a whole lot of stuff,... Paint this but include the bus stop, the zebra crossing, the communcal bin, traffic lights, tourists and people will buy it" "people dont want to see those things, they dont want to remember that" "I do, i can still see the beauty in a scene like that... I cant be the only one." "Maybe you are" she laughed almost victioriously "is that what you right about... you write about rubbish bins?" "...yes..." "you think the bus stops and television antennas are more beautiful than the duomo?" "maybe... or a girl on a bike talking on a cell phone, or an old lady looking into her empty mailbox, or a tourist trying to find the right bus,.. yes they can be" "Hmm... then maybe you are the only one"
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Crumbling in Lucca   The flu whose seed i had sown in the storms of Bologna, the aching left foot I had soveniered after a week of 10km a day walks through venice, the stabbing back I had twisted out shape in the air conditioned mirage of a hotel room in Firenze, and a sore throat aggravated by a night's of talking and laughing with friends in Lucca have joined forces and clouded my ability to experience.   My will to travel and experience was still strong, but the need to rest reflect and capture wayward thoughts was now speaking louder to compensate for its relative lack of importance.   Sunday morning in Lucca began with a throat so sore that I only dared swallow shen the phlegm had collected so badly that my throat had completely closed. This was accompanied by a dry cough that seemed to come from nowhere, last for several minutes at a time and leave me quite near passing out. In those wee small hours of sunday morning two things were decided. Firstly I had to seek the attention of some form of trained medical professionals and secondly, once i had attained this advice and hopefully some relief, I needed to make plans to head to Greece and the sanctuary of my grandmother's home in the family village in Kastoria.  The first part of this quest was accomplished after 30-45 minutes study of my inadequate but transportable dictionary in order to get my head around several ways of describing aches and pains. The farmacia provided me with a spray for the throat and a syrup for the cough. In the pharmacy's doorway i seriously overdosed on whatever active ingredients these products contained and rather rapidly found myself able to function with some form of normality. Sure i couldnt eat anything that had corners and didnt risk anything not at room temperature, but i felt human.  I returned to Le Torre allowing the symoathetic words of the signora to further heal me and ended up not surprisingly back in bed my medicated state now making sleep a possibility.  The supermarket below my window was open for business, the rhythmic beep beep of products being passed over the scanner lulled me to sleep, a soothing postmodern lullaby of commerce, progress, globalisation, macroeconomics. The beeps burst out of the doors of the super, bounced off the walls of the old markets a few metres away. The entrances of the two halls of trade; ancient and modern, faced each other in an arrogant "time will tell" way, the arrogance of the young against the seen it before slowness of the old.  The barcode symphony was the first recognisable sound I heard when I awoke at about 10 am. Dry cough and sore throat still my bedfellows but neither as crippling as earlier that day. I got up shook the sleep from my eyes with a quick shower and joined the Rizutti at the local segafredo, i even think i managed to down an espresso or three.  We squeezed in another tour of the centre of Lucca with the Rizzuti, the craft markets were in full swing and contained some interesting trinkets but none that forced me to loosen the purse strings.  We returned to the Rizzuto family fun vehicle which they had pacled, ready and waiting to transport them onto the next destination.  "Beach!!" the women folk cried, "whatever" the men folk replied, and west they rode, albeit a little too early in the day to allow me to say into the sunset.  Thanks Rizzuti, may the sun never set on the Ligurian Sea of your collective happiness.   As I watched my friends disappear into her streets, I wooed by Lucca's ample charms decided to make this my last stop in the first leg of this fantastic journey.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Lucca - try say slivovitsa ater three shots of the stuff   It was still rather early in the evening so we took the opportunity to walk Lucca's streets and attempt to achieve the "are we lost yet" heights of touristic utopia. It was a postcard tour of about 2 hours duration, the amfiteatro, piazza napoleone, churches, puccini's birthplace and even stumbling across the (its actually pretty big) aquaduct that supplies most of the town's drinking water, and it seems most of the town's empty beer bottles and other general refuse.... yeah but at least it was clean garbage, god bless italy.  We returned to trattoria gigi for another round of great food and bevvy, this time accompanied by good and varied conversation. The rizzuti were also kind enough to allow me to swallow a few red wines and then crap on at will uninterrupted about my "on tour" thrills and spills, my gesticulation factor and volume rose in direct line with my consumption of red wine and grappa,.. ahh... sobriety,.. who needs it,.. the aching left foot, the sore hip, neck and chest,.. whittled away to nothing by the wonders of grappa.  After dinner we returned to the streets of Lucca and stumbled back towards Piazza Napoleone, so great to see a public square, simple but functional being used just for that purpose, people standing around talking in groups, others promending and pretending not to enjoy the fact that people are looking at them, others in cafes or restaurants,.. Having soaked in the locals rich pageant we returned to the rizzuto compound and experienced more culture clashing. Papa rizzuto has some family in Slovenia, and had managed to head up there for a spell during the rizzuto family does europe 2003 tour. Amongst the no doubt fascinating souvenirs the family acquired during the slovenian sleepover was a real treat, a few flagons of the slovenian "vodka" as they cheekily refer to the rocket fuel they like to allow to slide down their throats. Papa rizzuto had even managed to secure the traditional serving vessel for the slivovitsa,.. the 1.5 litre plastic water bottle... a true classic.  A balmy night drove us outdoors with our nightcap in hand, much to the anti delight of the neighbours who at least had us to blame for the fact that they couldnt get any sleep. Papa rizzuto passed around the plastic cups we had scrounged from within the Le Torre megaplex.  It was smooth, it was hot, it was hot and smooth and hot and hot all at the same time. Ben and I exchanged "what the fuck did i just do to my body voluntarily" glances as we sipped the experimental beverage that the slovo-rizzuti had passed onto us. papa rizzuto was quick with the refills and we continued past midnight once we had bid buono notte to the women folk.   We decided that this self flagellation had to end and I, clutching a hefty sample of the evil brew in my hands waddled off towards my allocated room. The walk back to Le Torre 1 seemed swift, yes I was stupid enough to have another swig on my way back home... i was thirsty!  I arrived to the front door to find the 3 dutch girls from room 1 fumbling with the rather dodgy lock protecting us sleeping LeTorrians from the rest of the world. I offerred them a drink and to my surprise they took the bottle, sniffed and took not pitiful sips as i skilfully opened the gateway to beds and slumber for all. Yes I was stupid enough to say goodnight to 3 cute, pure alcohol swilling dutch girls and head straight to bed...   At approximately 4:00am, the health giving properties of alcohol had worn off and i awoke in a coughing fit with my throat almost completely closed.. I staggered towards the table were i had placed my water bottles,.. yes my four 1.5 litre plastic water bottles, o reached for the fifth of these four bottles and took 3 large gulps before i realised what i had managed to do to myself... buono notte.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Lucca con rizzuti   More positive tourist Karma at work with my fortunate choice of lodgings at Le Torre deep in da heart of Lucca. The owner Alfredo and his loveleeee wife are absolute characters. He spends most of the day sitting around Piazza del carmine talking to the other locals, making smalltalk with the tenants that he likes all the while sporting a rather well worn pair of black trousers, the government issue dark brown sandals and a shirt (please note the use of the singular) which he, like a skilled catwalk model or experienced seamstress, transforms into various "looks"  When in idle mode (this is his default mode), the shirt would be draped over the back of his chair or similarly draped over one or occasionally two shoulders. In the one full afternoon I spent with him, testing my Italian as we watched the shadows lengthen across the piazza his establishment Le Torre happened to be full, so Alfredo's interaction with passing tourists seeking shelter didnt extend beyond him pointing with an outstretched index finger thrust forth from the hand he happened to have laying on top of his head at the time to an A4 piece of paper on which he had cleverly scrawled the word "FULL". I, after watching his interaction with some of these tourists unsatisfied with the information barrage that this one word conveyed to them arose from my chair, removed my trust Pilot V2000 pen from my pack and added the words "until monday" to the sheet, after which Alfredo barely had to move a muscle until the aforementioned day was upon us.  It was during this relaxed mode that I received a call from all round great guy and urbania roomy Ben Rizzuto. He was kicking around toscana with the rest of the Rizzuti and was somewhat keen to head down to Lucca for the evening. My eyes turned to the A4 information system hanging from Le Torre's sign moved across to Alfredo who was so magnificently slouched in his chair that his feet would have been a good metre in front of him, he looked like some meaty brrom stick someody had leaned against a chair and then forgotten. I felt compelled to tell Ben that the place i was staying in was "full -- until monday"  Wanting to help the wandering rizzuti further i left the snoozing alfredo and took a quick tour of some of the other b&b's in the immediate area. There were a few places with vacancies but nothing overly inspirational. I returned to Alfredo to find that he had enhanced his feats of reclinational gymnastics further by somehow crossing one leg over the other, he had to slightly shift his upper body weight in the opposite direction in order to minimise the number of fundamental laws of physics he was openly defying by arguably remaining in the vertical plane. One of his many unearthky senses must have detecetd something as he arose from his chair and buttoned a button as i approached him.  "Alfredo... quatri amici,.. ahh... arrivera sta sera .. alfredo... e possibilie per loro restano ... qui ?" I utterred "Quanti???" he skilfully enquired... "Quatti" came my succinct reply, he raised his index finger in the universally recognisable sign of "ignore me for a few seconds" and swept into the office of Le Torre.  A phone call and a rather animated conversation with his housekeeper later he emerged to make sure he hadnt misunderstood the information we had previously exchanged and to seek my blood oath that these amici were definitely going to arrive and arrive soon.  A quick call to ben and I had the promise of an honest man in my possession which i passed on to Alfredo. he returned to his office barked out some more instructions and sat on the steps of Le Torre with his button still in the engaged position. This concerned me, and rightly so for all the pieces of the puzzle that alfredo had conjured to accomodate the wandering band of rizzuti now streaking towards Lucca aboard their trusty steed had not yet fallen into place.  Minutes later emerged american backpacker guy, Alfredo waived him into Le Torre, looked at me and pointed with his thumb back over his shoulder. A gesture which I took to mean one of three things 1) You Fuck off! 2) Im going to kill this guy and you have to help me get rid of his heavy heavy body, or, 3) I would be most greatful if you could assist me in my business with this gentleman as he speaks no italian.  To my disappointment he meant the latter, a few mudge mudge wink winks later and american backapacker dude had been convinced to take lodgings at another no doubt similarly beautiful institution run by a friend of Alfredo's. He departed, Alfredo made it clear to me that he had performed what we in the west refer to as a "favour" and we returned to our full... until monday positions.  The rizzuti arrived seconds after Alfredo had to dash off to retrieve his dog which had taken leave to stray from his home in an unauthorised manner. My part in the vicious cruel murder of poor Mario in the canals of venezia seized me bodily turning me to stone ensuring that there was no way my instinctive need to assist in the rescue of wittle puppy dog would bubble to the surface of my cerebellum. Alfredo dashed off on his bicycle and returned just after ben introduced me to mum, dad and sis rizzuto, puppy safely stowed in the girly handlebar basket.  Alfredo took care of business with Italiano parlaing Ben and whisked the rizzuti off to their pad in Le Torre 2, (another cornerstone of the Alfredo empire)  an hour or so later I was pleased to hear that the lodgings werent like robinson ca-ru-soe as primitive as can be and that the rizzuti were poised for an evening of Luccafication. (gee i hope that's not a word) 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Surrounded by Lucca   Lucca didn't need fireworks, men on horseback or architectural feats to grab my attention, What people stay in florence when lucca is only 90 mins further up the train line i dont know... why anybody would dram of staying in pisa when lucca is only 20 mins up the train line is something that will baffle e for quite some time, but it is to my gain so why worry.   urlLink Lucca  is immediately recognisable by the well preserved walls that suround the old city, these are impressive not only beacuse of the fucntion they served but simply due to the size of the undertaking, Lucca isnt a small city and it has been surrounded by a set of walls wide enough to carry a road, parks and treelined avenues along its top. The 4.5 km walk around the city walls give you great views of lucca itself and also of the surrounding countryside.  I arrived in Lucca from Florence after a gruelling 1 and a half hour wait at santa maria novella train station in florence. Made my way into the city and wandered around for a while looking for a room, there were plenty of places available so rather than take a chance i figured i would go down to the tourist centre and use their booking service. Everything went swimmingly and i soon found myself at Le Torre a small affitacamare very close to the centre of the town centre, comfortable room with bath. The rooms are owned by an interesting couple who i was pleased to find out where quite happy to have their guests sit down and talk to them and also didnt speak much english at all, i made use of the free italian language lessons a great deal over the next few days.  Lucca's town centre had a very interesting mix of residential, commercial, ancient and not so ancient areas, The balance was quite pleasing for me, dotted with narrow streets arranged in a way that you somehow find yourself back where you started from even though you thought you had travelled in a reasonably straight line.  Great views of and from the town walls, lots of locals still living and working in the town centre, tourists sure,but i never felt like i was about to drown in them, and staff in shops and restaurants that are and speak .. italian... yes florence was behind me.  My initiation of the wonders of Lucca was complete by the end of the night, after walking into the amfoteatro in Lucca the afternoon sun bouncing off the walls of some of the buildings that surround the oval shaped piazza, I hadn't seen anything quite like it before and was happy to pay some inflated prices for a beverage or three. After i had soaked in the sights i wandered off to Trattoria Gigi conveniently plonked just around the corner from the hotel i was staying in.  My entire experience at gigi was terrific, great food, daily menu, very reasonable prices, wine, service with a smile,  urlLink hey they even have a great web site , test your italian and find the daily menu. Gigi also delivered Elena to me, my words for her aren't for public comsumption but elena, if youre out there... grazie, tu sei belissima, ci vidiamo.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       June 25-27 Firenze second time around   Hacing promised myself to return to Florence and try and find some love for the town the whole world bar me seemed to worship was... unsuccesful. I did my best, stayed in a better hotel, went to the sights and wandered the streets, but there was so much I didnt like about this town.  There were several things i did like. Most of these moments happened when i walked to the outskirts of the town centre to areas like Santo Croce where the Calcio Istorico was played, here again the crowds were incredibly passionate thugs but you felt you were in the midst of something unique. The game itself is more brute force than brutality, not openly violent but men did whatever they could to stop the guy with the ball from getting to where he wanted to go, there werent too many moments of random violence... there were plenty in the crowd mind you, and a lot of them between the "women" i enjoyed a half of a game and headed off to listen to the cheers from the steps of the santa croce church whos piazza had beeninvaded by the game and its supporters.  I also returned to santo spirito and spent an afternoon sitting in the piazza, drinking at the small local bars and rounded it off with a meal served to me by an australian girl who at least didnt lapes into english, but the 5 or 6 places i ate at whilst in florence were all somewhat disappointing even before the bill arrived.  By Friday i was ready for new adventures, decided to pick another smaller town in which i seem to feel more at ease packed my  urlLink fairydown  and headed off to Lucca.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       June 23- 25 Chilling with the Arezzo crew   As i mentioned earlier Arezzo is Roberto Benigni land, and although he no longer lives there he has left many relatives behind. Walking the streets can be something of a head turning experience if you happen to be a fan of the man.  My favourite roberto lookalike was a guy who ran the newsstand near the station, one of the first people i saw in Arezzo and had the whole johnny stechino look going for him. I never asked him if he was related, it was just so unnecesary, but i did take to asking him stupid questions just to get a free of charge roberto benigni type response,.. he didnt have the lines ... but he had those million dollar expressions down pat.  Some of the questions I asked him included   Vorrei parchare mio dischi volare qui... va bene?  I would like to park my flying saucer here... ok?   Vorrei il giornale per domani perche io preferisco pesche fresci  I would like tomorrows newspaper because i prefer fresh fish   Hp bisogno una caramello due chilogrami pesante  I need a 2 kilo lolly.  By the end of my stay he was giving it a go and would great me with a wink and a buongiorno principessa ... 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       June 22 - World Series Jousting   Arezzo had gradually whipped itself into a frenzy over the giostra that was to take place this saturday night. I had watched the various pageants parades and also watched as they constructed the jousting surface across the centre of Arezzo's Piazza Maggiore.  Arezzo's main squre is fairly unique as it is neither flat, nor rectangluarl and doesnt really have a monument of major interest. So the physical engineering of creating a surface for somebody to run a horse along without risking himself, his ride or the spectators was interesting enough. The feat was accomplished using fauirly simple methods, mud and various mud soaked materials were placed along a diagonal strip along what is the flattest part of the square. The track was around 5 metres wide and began in a sidestreet that fed into the bottom right hand corner of the square. Once the rider had complete his attempt he had to make a fairly tight left hand corner between the palazzo alomg the top end of the square and the church along the left hand side.  The joust had been reduced to a task of skill rather than a life or death situation. The rider would approach a dummy, which was sporting a target in place of a shield, the rider would attempt to strike the target in the centre, and would earn points for his team based on the accuracy of his efforts.   Ticket prices varied from 5 euro for standing room right up to 60 euro a ticket for the best seats located to the right of the dummy's outstretched arm (i know i always like to spend time around dummies). Well i got the standing room tiket so i can rub shoulders with the locals,.. wise choice.  There were 4 teams battling for the prize of the golden jousting stick. These were named after the various Porte or gates to the city. During the last few days i had befreinded a young kid who had shaved the symbol of the region he supported into his hair and died every visible part of his body red or green. He supported porta crucifera, i purchased the appropriate red and green garb and headed off for a good nights jousting.  More fanfare and pageantry, including about 20 of the wonderful flag tossing dudes and we crammed ourselves into the square, the crowd was incredibly spritied and vocal. The event was reasonably well organised and each of the four teams supporters were allocated a section of the piazza to support from, i took up a good spot at the oustkirts of the porta crucifera supporters about 5 metres away from arch rivals santo spritio.  I doubt that they were as arch as some of the kids were making out, but there was very colorful exchanges of chants, most of which revolving around the other teams main rider and the virtues of his family and his abilities to satisfy a woman sexually.. if i am to believe some of the chants, the rider from sant andrea really has a tough time with the ladies....  The jousts begin with 3 rides from each team, after which the top 2 teams are left to battle it out for the prize with 2 final rides. Santo cricifera started well with a 4, but followed it up with two 3's, this meant that we needed some serious fuzzes by the other teams ... these didnt eventuate and the golden jousterama was held aloft by the riders and supporters of the green and white sant andrea after a quite triumphant victory.  There were tears, there were some great scuffles, there was a whole lot of pushing and shoving to the point were even i was lifted of the ground one point by the sheer swell of humanity pushing into our group of supporters.... a great time all round, even managed to get a punch in, much to the joy of my fellow cruciferi.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       June 21 - what's italian for stolen generation?   True to form after 3 days in a town the local bums and regular faces started saying hello to me, and me in my effort to be conspicuous placed myself in one of the main town squares and happily "buona sera"d passers by.  After a while a local gent came and sat on the wall near me, didnt say hello, but sat so close to me that it would have been rude of me not to make the initial effort.... "sssseeeera" i said... dying to be taken for a local. "Sei straniero?" was his reponse,.. hmm.. guess that pretend to be a local approach lasted an entire 0.0 seconds.. but he seemed to be ok with the idea of me not being frrom these parts and so i gave him my abbreviated life story.  He was interested in Australia but much to my surprise was more interested in New Zealand,.. i mean arent we all!!!?.. he knew a fair bit about australia, and even knew the prime ministers name... you know who i mean... the short guy you voted for. We spoke of the nature of the people, i told him how australia has large numbers of european migrants but the system is fairly english and this includes the way the people interact with each other. I said its possible to live next door to a family for 20 years and not know their names.  He said in italy thats not possible, within 20 minutes everyone knows everything about you.... he then asked if they would help if you were in trouble.. I responded in the affirmative and told him that Australians were pretty much always interested in lending a hand... he interrup[edt me with.. i would rather have my neighbours not know my name but help me if i needed it rather than have them say hello to me every day, buy me a christmas present, remember my daughters birthday but pretend not to be home if they see somebody breaking down my front door.  My homework for the evening was to learn more vocab which would help me describe the "stolen generation" to the locals. I was unsuccesful in my attempts to fuble my way through it with my new buddy, i think i left him with the belief that in ancient times the government of australia would form a religious community and it would share children from different families with local priests and they would bring them up according to white ways... i guess that was close enough.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Arezzo woodstock revival   The next morning the sun was out, the sky was once again that science fiction uncapturable blue, i had spotted a few places for some photo opprtunities the previous evening and made my way to them before the crowds, the crowds I refer to being the crowds I would later find out don't actually exist.  I walked to the highest point of the town where the fortress walls that were once used as a convenient spot to pour burning oil on attacking hordes have now been converted to a cute little playground for the kiddies and a series of oval paths focusing on a simple piazza complete with a statue the purpose of which i couldnt quite get my head around.  I snapped a few typical steeple sticking out of a bunch of trees, misty mountain village type shots and then moved onto the lovely looking star shaped bastion that remained in the northeast corner of the wall. Again the roof of this bastion was large enough to now hold a small park complete with benches and even a few tables... gasp... moving up a litle bit higher didn't really add to the views of the surrounding hillside but it gave me a good look down on some of those trade mark sunflower fields and even a view of a war cemetary of some kind,.. I was the only person up here, I made the most of the space amd tranquility, i think i even nodded off for a while,.. in fact i know i did i just wanted to pretend that i was more actively enjoying the tranquility.  I awoke, wondering what local animals had made use of my person over the past 30 minutes or so and saw a nice little spot which would probably yield a few more postcard shots and headed that way. As i moved from what i thought was a simple journey from a brick path to a gravel path i raised my camera to my eye and considered snapping a pic of the expanse of blue just to test my cameras capabilities.   My eyes previously uninterrupted view of blue sky now shared space with what i quickly recognised as my left foot.. this was joined not surprisingly by my roght foot, the camera decided that it was time to leave the area immediately in front of my face as my arms flung themselves into the "what the fuck is happening to me" pose, ... yes kids i was falling, and i was seriously falling, i had a good second to consider what was happening to me, before i landed on what i had thought was a gravel path but was actually a beautifully formed mud pool, a good 30'40 cms deep and quite clean and consistent, it was as if some giant had been making chocolate brownies and i had fallen into the mixing bowl.  I peeled myself out of the mud, apart from a 20cm wide stripe of identifiable clothing near my shirt i was covered head to toe and in some places heavily caked in tuscan mud. I laughed, l iaughed again and took another look around me... I had managed to somehow slide right off the path and land on a small embankment, about a metre to my right was a fairly sheer 10m drop to the rock floor of the bastion, about 10cm from where the impression of my head could be seen in the mud was a large pointed rock, most probably made of more sturdy stuff than the back of my head.   But why worry about that now, what's a holiday if you don't cheat death every now and then.. and hey,.. i think the fall fixed my back.  I climbed back on the relative safety of the gravel track and took a better look at myself,.. my camera was coated in 3 inches of mud, aside from the shot of my foot against the blue sky i don't have any permanent evidence of the occasion, but that images speaks volumes.   Every part of me i could see was covered in mud, it was a good half hour walk back to my hotel ... most of which through the centre of town, i figured i would try and clean myself up to the point where i wouldn't be mistaken for some ancient town legend.  I scraped the mud off myself, this went quite well,.. to the point where all i had on were dirty clothes, i got as much of it out of my hair as i could, i only had a small bottle of water which i didn't even bother using to clean my hands in case it was more useful for other purposes later. I noticed that the mud was drying fairly quickly in the heat and decided to take off my shirt, pants, shoes and socks and lay them out in the sun.  I sat on arezzo's ancient walls, in my least favourite pair of jocks, staring at the distant hills, blurred now by my absent spectacles. and waited for mother nature to have some impact. 20 minutes later the oven bell rang and my clothes had been transformed into a nice khaki colour, almost fashionable i thought. I picked up my jeans and belted them against the wall,.. dust and chunks of mud floew of them for the first 3 or 4 whacks after which i was surprised at how presentable they had become,..  the same couldnt be said for my shirt. My body wasn't quite wall smashable either and despite large amounts of scraping i still looked like i had rolled in mud.  I put my clothes back on and headed back towards the rest of society to try and find a tap or a bathroom of some kind to clean myself up further. I took a good look around the place and didnt find any water source and decided to head back down to the gardens and see if there were some facilities.  As i descended the ramps from the bastion I saw a puppy turn the corner and head in my direction, the puppy was attached to a lead which is normally followed by a human, but this lead just kept appearing from the corner ahead, they must have had a mad sale on 20 metre dog leads at the local  urlLink supermercato  or maybe this guy doesnt like his dog much or vice versa,.. but ... eventually, he turned the corner his dog had already passed me i took a step towards him,.. umm the man him i mean,.. I'm not sure what the sex of the dog he was reeling in was. Before i got my initial mi scusa signore out he had started reeling his pooch back in, the dog seemed to understand this manouvre and was cooperating, he picked it up in his aarms and clutched it to his chest as he awaited me to speak... true to the local legend ... i did.  The itialian word for 'fall' is one i always have trouble remembering... so i thought i best try and explain my appearance and said "ho soltato non buono" whuich loosely means... "i jumped not well" he nodded .. i went on"sto bene ma vorrei pulitare dove il bagno in vicina" again i took some liberties with the langauges and i think invented a verb for clean myself but he focused on the meat of my question... "where is the bathroom" and gave me a series of hand gestures and comments ... it seemed that all i would have to do is walk past the odd statue oin the gardens below and i would find an outdoor bagno  I only had to walk past about 20 people, all of whom had a good laugh at my expense,.. including one of the town bums... i found the bagno,.. which was a rather strange looking cube of a building with no signs and a door in the centre of one of the walls... I opened the door,.. there was no ceiling and referring to this place as a bagno was rather odd as all it contained... was a toilet, no sink, no taps, no bidet, no towels, no servant handing out mints... none of the essentials.  In my pack a carry several things that people are surprised by, one of them is a sponge/scourer combo thing. I examined the toilet, opened the top of the cistern and found that the whole thing was quite new, very new in fact and remarkably clean... i turned off the tap feeding the water into the unit and ran through a couple of flushes until it was empty...  the water feeder had a small hose at the end of it that just reached over the top of the system so i wa able to wash my hands and scrub some of the mud off my face and hair using fresh water,.. lovely... but it was just a trickle, wasnt going to help with my clothes.  I used my scourer to give the toilet system and crapper a good cleaning, some of the more popuòlar restaurants in arezzo are now using this toilet as a seat for the saturday evening rush it was so clean. I undid the modifications i made to the cisternm and turned the water back on.  I loosely draped my shirt across my hands, held it in the bowl and hit the flusher with my head... it was an excellent flushing system, very powerful, within 3 flushes my shirt was looking dandy. The jeans i tackled similarly but one leg at a time, also quite succesful, about 10 flushes in total for them ... it was only the fear of unlocking hidden childhood memories that stopped me from sticking my head in the bowl to give my hair a once over.  The rooflesness of the room now did its work, the jeans weren't going to dry but the shirt was a drip dry travellers best friend type garb and was ready to go in minutes.  I got dressed, squelched my way out of the bagno and headed for a park bench to dry off further. After an hour or so i was feeling so nice and fresh that i even conidered going out to lunch rather than returning to my room.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       June 20 More Arezzo   With the number of anti inflammataries in my system graadually on the decline and the town of Arezzo returning me to an environment i found somewhat appealing I found my spirits once again buoyed.   I had spent some time yesterday afternoon wandering the streets, found a little place for dinner which seemed to have lots of locals in it, fumbled my way through the menu and ordered way too much but was also just as overindulgent on the compliments i bestowed on .. the cooks, the cook's parents, the people who taught the cook how to cook, the waiter, his apron,.. his shoes, the colour of the walls ... and the eggplantiness of the eggplants... yes it was one of those stick a litre of the local red in me and i wont let poor grammar get in the way of me having a good time kind of nights.  During the night we had a most wonderful storm, sheet lightning and rain that is more like a sea making its way back down to earth than the showers we are used to, i sat at my window and watched it for hours, i opened my window... and then spent 3 minutes trying to force it closed again before i drowned the inhabitants of the rooms below me, my enthusiasm dampened along with my scantily clad  person, i hit the sack early tucked up in bed watching the new zealand soccer team make fools of themselves on the world football stage at the confederation cup in france.... it shoud have been us there, making fools of ourselves on the word football stage.  The german words for ''absolute underdog'' are very similar to the english... yes its a cultural exchaneg at every possible level here.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      June 19 -  Arezzo  Having licked my wounds clean enough to parade before the public, and attempting to keep an open mind about Firenze really being as good as people say it is... I packed my bags, left my humble lodgings at la Giaconda and headed back to the train station to make my suave departure.  I used the 10 minute walk to Santa Maria Novella to decide on where to go, although I have had a rather organic time table for this trip, I have almost managed to plan at least a few days ahead, this was the first time I was looking to hop towns without having some klind of lodging waiting for me at the other end. No sweat, had several options and most of these tuscan towns are well serviced by the rail network that has carried my ass all over the place thus far.  I was tossing up Arezzo, Cortona, Lucca, Siena. Cortona and Siena and Lucca are on the must see list, but as I planned to come back to firenze i figured the direction of Arezzo was a safer bet as it was kind of a dead end trail in Cortona. I figured I would get off at Arezzo have a quick peak around the town attempt to find a room and see how that fell together.  Arezzo is an easy 90 minute train ride from firenze, the train weaves its way through a few picturesque scenes before leaping across the border into Umbria. I arrived just after the tourist office had closed for the lunchtime break but there was enough information plastered on the walls to give me a feel of what was going onj and a list of hotels with a map in the window... what all round nice folk. In a complete about face, the first hotel i walked into which was a really nice looking 3 star located close to the station, close to everything and on a piazza which wasnt a makeshift car park or rubbish dump,.. half the price of the firenze hotels and the room was huge, 2 beds a sofa, big tv and a real shower with like a door .... a door!!! and tiles and stuff,.. big windows, yeah this would do nicely.   urlLink Arezzo   is famous for lots of reasons, I had heard of it as it is the home town of all round nutter and film making type  urlLink Roberto Benigni , he used the town as the setting for his movie " urlLink Vita e bella " (life is beautiful for you challenged folk). The town had a great combination of views, lifestyle, hills but not back breaking ones and as it so happened I landed there a few days before their biannual festa, the giostra del saraceno urlLink  , which as the name suggests is a joust, now if I could only get my hands on a cheap set of jousting sticks.  Took a breather in the pad to read up on the town and wait for the tourist office to reopen to get my hands on a map. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       June 15 - June 18 Firenze Fashion Victim   My trip from Bologna to Firenze was reasonably uneventful, aside from the nagging heat, the only point of excitement was on platform 3 in bologna station where ... having managed to secure a patch of shade i sat and watched the other passengers arrive and fumble around like fools just like i did... when suddenly,.. he emerged from the underpass,.. the last of the great exploreres,.. this was an american tourist who had obviously spent some time studying old tarzan movies before selecting the appropriate garments to accompany him on his no doubt adventure packed package tour of italy... i dont think kontiki stop in bologna.. maybe he is a scout for future expeditions. Now he wasnt wearing a pith helmet,.. but if you were thinking along those lines you would have been rather close because i would wager florence's coldest beer on the fact that he had forgotten the helmet on a bus somewhere because the outfit was screaming for it. I managed to keep the amusement internalised until, in a swift well practiced manouvre he turned moved both hands behand his back and opened the vents that ran along side his outdoorsmans jacket allowing the cool breeze which would no doubt soon emerge as predicted by his instruments to cool him down... this guy was tall too, and this is mne telling you he is tall... and im tall... the unzipping process was swiftly executed but still took a good 2 seconds to complete. Immediately after this i had moved into a reclining position and threw out one of the best belly laughs i have unleashed on this continent, ... i was alone in my outpouring of emotion  but that didnt hold me back, his eurostar train should be just about pulling into some rugged tanzanian station about now.  Arrived in Firenze on Sunday afternoon and quickly tracked down my lodgings Sense of direction was spot on this time, room was ok, shower wasnt a shoe box, usual 3 star fire trap rabbit warren of buildings. As it so happens my roommate from Urbania Ben would be in Firenze and we had planned to meet at the you guessed it duomo, I of course4 waited nearby not wanting to give the japanese schoolgirls too much of a chance to photograph me... Ben swaggerred towards me, the confidence of a loca, having spent 8 months or so here as a student and even working one of the god damn souvenir stands on the ponte vecchio of all places.  Ben gave me a guided tour of the sites, we didnt venture into anything other than the odd gelateria but that suited me. We made it to a little bar in sant spirito ... which is on the (gasp) other side of the Arno and met with Samir and some other locals, Samir works the souvenir stand at the middle of the ponte vecchio and was an all round top bloke brought me a beer and all, now thats just top.  After 3 or 4 ales the 20 minute walk to the shack Ben had picked for din dins that night became a 35 minute stagger, i know this muich.. it was in santa croce, behind the church and the piazza. The regular  urlLink calcio storico   games take place on the piazza in front of santa croce church and yeah we had missed it... calcio storico is the italians justification for claiming the right to call themselves the originators of the game of soccer. Now calcio storic occasionally looks like soccer, but more often resembles an organised beating  Dinner was ok, but i started to get bad feelings about this towm, when the waitress who turned out to be Irish, was commenting on our Italian Having surviuved the tourist throngs in venezia i thought that florence would be a sinch, but alas no, it had found my weakness.  The next 2 days helped reinforce this thought in many ways. Sure venice is a tourist town, sure its hard to find people who are native italians and speak to you in italian. But the city itself has a spirit that has endured and which mocks the tourists that come there stay for 3 days and think they understand what makes the town tick. I havent sensed such a spirit in florence, yes there are stupifying landmarks and no doubt the worlds best art, but the city is sparce and the spaces between these highlights are to me totally demorialising.  Adding to my bitterness were 2 things,. 1 a bi-annual fashion extravanganze happened to be running in firenze on the days in which i wanted to find accomodation. The  urlLink Pitti uomo  is the mens fashion event and therefore every stick of accomodation in the town had been snapped up by some gutter dwelling industry type. Of my 3 days in florence i spent at least 1 walking around looking for accomodation or on the phone asking about it... what a treat.  The second of my 3 days in firenze was spent in my bedroom in bed. The heatwave broke with a ferocious storm on Monday afternoon, i stood in the rain watching steam rise off everything, it was a truly joyous 30 minutes or so, not an umbrella in sight, it even took the moroccans a good hour before they started trying to sell you little fold up brollies,.. actually at 3 euro a piece they were probably providing a public service for a change... but then again i didnt buy one.  I returned to my bedroom soaked to the skin, opened the door ro my personal space and was greeted by a strong blast of cold air courtesy of my air conditioner, i switched it off, opened the windows squelched my way onto the bed and actually slept for an hour happy to let the mozzies feast on me. I awoke feeling good, feeling better about the town, had a shower and went about the usual process of appropriate attention being giving to various body parts. I bent down to search for garments when an almighty force tore into my back, suffering chronic backpain i know all about the occasional tightness and spike of pain but this was a new world, i slumped to the floor, .. not an easy feat in itself in this bathroom and let the pain organise itself into a committe and write a declaration of wart on the back of my brain.  I think i used my finger tips to drag me along the floor and to a space in which i could stretch out. I couldnt move my back at all, but felt no pain when stretched out flat so i was able to laugh... laughter is the best medicine,..  pigs ass it is. I could see the phone cable makes its way to the top of the bedside table,.. i reached for it and gave it a good tug, the lamp that landed on my face made it immediately apprent that this wasnt the phone cable. I could see the phone cable make its way to the top of the bediside table,.. i knew for sure it was the bedside cable as the lamp was now sitting on my chest... i tugged at it figuring what else could go wrong.  I dialled reception and in my pain found that my italian had improved, i dropped the odd swear word, told the guy i couldnt walk and used some of the phrases the beggars have used to appeal for assistance. He explained to me that all they had was aspirin but he would bring that up to my room ''pronto'' that means fast in this town.  He emerged complete with cup of water and a look of grave concern covered his face, yes i had not had the opportunity to put my pants on... thats makes 2 unsuspecting italians i have exposed myself to, way to go. Turns out that the word voltaren translates directly into italian, they change the pronunciation of course... typical,.. but i had to procure some of the goodness that only voltaren could provide. Signore from reception couldnt help me as he was the only person running the hotel, and the only farmacia that would definitely be open at this time was back at the train station.   I swallowed the aspirin, waited 15 minutes gritted my teeth and made my way down 4 flights of stairs to reception, he wished me luck, apologised again that he couldnt help more,.. i lied and said oh youve done so much.. and walked out into the tourists. Next door to the hotel was a 24 hour bar, these are handy as they serve alcohol... i walked up to the counter and said ''grappa'' she replied with about 5 words .. i replied with '' non lo so,... grappa!'' she placed one before me... i swallowed it and said '' un altro''  she saw it coming so had the bottle in her hand, i repeated this process once more and now found myself able to mmove my head back to the normal working angle and yes feet could be placed one generally in front of the other without too much ball tearing pain.  I swaggerred my way to the farmacia at the station and up to the counter, hey i was so lucid i even remembered that i had lost my toothbrush during the exods from my last hotel in bologna and looked through the vast array of brushes they had availabel and selected my appropriate weapon.  The pharmacist helped me out, got me my vol-ta-ren but just as i was about to pay she asked me if i had been drinking... i explained to her that i wa in a great deal of pain, this was made apparent by the fact that half of my 3rd grappa was actually located between my goatee and my shirt. She was well trained and refused to give me the pills if i had just had a drink, i got a bit upset, she said go get some food and i will give you the pills... and o i procured the worst 2 slices of pizza any person has paid money for from one of the bars on the platforms came back to the window of the farmacia, tapped a few coins aginst it to draw more attention to myself and chowed down on said slices. She kep her end of the bargain,.. gave me the pills i had 3 at the counter and went outside to let the lovely volatern cloud come and sweep all the bad stuff away... 10 minutes later,.. it did... right on cue, i toook the opportunity to head back to the hotel and prepare myself for a night of motionlesness... oh yeah.. the tv remote doesnt work either.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      June 12 - June 14 Bologna  The heatwave that has swamped this part of italy continues unabated, it gets to about 40 on most days but the humidity and the breezelessness of it all make it hard to deal with. Despite this i have managed to do more wandering but as the days passed this has become rather aimless. There has been some interesting indulging in the food and bevvy departments however.  The highlights were, a simple gnocci gorgonzola, with walnuts, a single layer of home made gnocci coated with a thick gorgonzola sauce covering 2 thirds of a large plate with a sprinkling of parsley and basil scattering the portion of the plate closest to its consumer, marvellous,.. followed this up with salsicce grilliata, which translats as grilled snags,.. but these were magic, char grilled and hefty.  Another massive highlight in both the financial and flavour stakes was a roasted scallop dish i had at the  urlLink NU   Big scallops roasted in shell with basil and a sprinkling of cheese,.. biggest scallops i have ever had which is usually a bad sign but these were full and flaboursome,.. there were only 3 on the plate and the pire was 19 euro... ouch.  Also at the NU managed to scvoff down a carpaccio of octopus, ultra thin slices of pussy surrounded by bolied taters, olive oil and balsamic on the table and lemon and basil in the dish, have never had octopus served this way, probably doesnt beat several slabs of the stuff on the barbie with a six pack of beer but it was excellent. Also knocked back a Bologna specialty their torta riso, which was nothing like i expected, mor elike a flan, savoury with a dusting of icing sugar, tasted very greek, didnt mention this to my host. As this was my last day in bologna i bid farewell to Toni and his crew at Nu Hotel, top bloke all round, he plans to head down to australia and gave me his email address. Toni spent 20 years in France and the menu and his knowledge show it, has friends in noumea and knows he will visit them one day and promised to make the journey further south, i convinced him to stop over in melbourne for food and wine once he had gotten sick of the harbour bridge and the sights of sydney.  Tonight bologna is holding a massive concert in piazza maggiore along with fireworks at 21:00, I told them not to go to too much trouble, but they insisted .. these crazy italians.  Tomorrow its off to Firenze for at least a few days, as it happens my roomy from Urbania Ben just so happens to be in Florence for a few days, which is good for several reasons, but mainly it gives me another chance to see the guy before we move continents and also the fact that he knows Firenze very well hasnt escaped me, wouldnt mind setting up base there for a few weeks whilst i explore the area.  
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      And finally some pics  Courtesy of relatively cheap and speedy net access in Bologna plus a few tricks on my part to get past the security they have setup on the workstations.  Rome:  Took a lot of video in Rome and i wont bore you with long shots of the colloseum  urlLink colloseum slab  |  urlLink Internal collosseum  | view from trastevere hill  urlLink -1-  and  urlLink -2-   Urbania:  urlLink that bridge where  | I urlLink  spent a lot of mornings  |  urlLink thinking about shit  |  urlLink and who can blame me  | Urbania  urlLink  view -1-   and  urlLink -2-   urlLink  AND -3-    The Stranieri hanging out at Bar Centrale  urlLink Ben Jess Jen  |  urlLink Jess Mehdy and Jen  |  urlLink  Mehdy and Jen   |  urlLink Goodbye Urbania    That day in Apecchio The crew  urlLink  Manu Mehdy Ben and Monia   |  urlLink Ben and Manu discuss what a cool guy i am  |  urlLink Getting down with the insinianti  |   Venezia  urlLink will i fit?  | Piazza san Marco  urlLink portico  --  urlLink Florian  |  urlLink paint shop  |  urlLink A steal at 20,000 euro  |  urlLink these things are everywhere  |  urlLink Piazza San Marco at night  |  urlLink Battle of the tourist bands  |  urlLink they didnt know any guns n roses  |  urlLink  Pretentious shot of door   |  urlLink Gondola chunks  |  urlLink a tourist was photographing this   Thats it for now kids, sorry about size and darkness on a few of these,.. dont have the tools to fart about with them from here... fiddle with knobs on your monitor for now.. blame it on the IT department.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      June 11 Bologna -  I drive better when i am drunk.  The heat wave continues but the desire to feast upon the local food and bevvy is still strong. The other day i wandered into the nizzarely named ''nu lounge bar' which is right up there with the strange english names for businesses, My other favourite in this category is the ''PIZZA UP!'' in Urbania but the winnder has to be Italian mobile phone company called ''WIND'' thats wind like the breeze not like the clock, they have large banners around the place which simply say ''avete wind?'' translating, without need for massaging into '' do you have wind?''  At the nu i dined on carpaccio with carciofi and rucola, its the second time i have had carpacio here and both times its more like a slab of raw meat that gets delivered to you rather than the thin shavings i had become accustomed to in australia, but accompanied by the local oil and cheese it went down an sbolute treat, knocked down a couple of glasses of (gasp) semillon and one of the local semifreddo with chocolate specialties and i was anyones.  So nicely sloshed and with no real desire to head back out into the sunshine i outstayed my welcome to the point where the owner tony came over and asked me a few questions,.. most of which i understood and was able to respond to... i made the mistake of asking about one of the waitresses, he said ''that would be my wife''  but i managed to weazel my way out of it and suggest that i was referring to the other waitress who obviously wasnt italian... ''ah yes she is german'' and he invites her over for a drink... her italian was better than her english but also better than mine so we sat and talked about how she managed to wind up in bologna... again they all seemed fascinated by australia, despite my efforts to tell them that there really wasnt anything to be fascinated by other than the physical landscape of the place... but they all seem to yearn for empty space, where as we seem to yearn to spend time crammed into tiny interesting spaces wondering why the locals dont appreciate the culture that surrounds them.  It's kind of like Tasmania,... which is intersting because so few things are... We mainlanders think of tasmania as this beautiful untouched paradise a treasure which must be preserved at any cost in todays dollars, whereas the locals have to live there and after a few years of waking up to views across the mountains you learn to build houses facing away from them because thats the direction the cold winds come from and you dump your rubbish in the river because the council want you to pay extra to have the rubbish collected from outside your driveway.  I passed a few hours with my new german italian english speaking friends, she took me to the public which houses an old anatomy lecture theatre complete with wooden statues of skinned blokes and 3 rows of wooden seats arranged arouind a cold marble slab ) i didnt lie down on this one ) she asked if she could take a few photos of me, cant say i blame her cos i am freaking gorgeous... will have to keep an eye out for her exhibition when i make it up north to deutchand.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      June 10 - Bums and Bombs  It usually takes around 3 days for the town drunks to start to speak to me. This formula held true in bologna. I was sitting in piazza maggiore early on sunday morning watching the shandows grow shorter across the town square, the bums and beggars circling the square holding their neatly printed cards asking for money for a whole host of causes, they would come close enough to confirm their suspicions about my origins and them move away.  Three days later and a few 1c coins cast into eager receptacles its waves and tipping of hats to the wandering Mr Ziz. My favourite,.. well if i had to choose just one i wouldnt id list them all... thereùs the guy who has a very neatly presented full beard and an uncannily steven wright like delivery, hat in hand he approaches passers by and im a perfect monotone says osmething along the lines of ''help me with something for the purposes of eating'' which sounds somewhat more poteic in italian. Unlike the Roman beggars he hasnt bothered gettiong a grant to translate his plea into other languages and also unlike the roamn beggars he doesnt throw 1 euro cent coins back at you. The beggars here are very mobile, i swear they must run down the quiet lanes in order to swing back for another passage along the tourist strips, this is a opposed to the venetian beggars who think they are competing for some kind of human statue award,.. in fact there is a rather famous human statue in venice who operates only 50 metres away from one of these motionless beggars,.. he leans against a wall in a long robe which allows him to move his hands and scratch the odd nbut, whilst the beggar sits on his knees one hand stretched out carrying a heavy cup in which to receive coins... and yet the tourists are paying the busking human statue full euro coins and turning their noses up at the beggar... where's the justice.  Along side piazza maggiore is piazza nettuno, so called because of the rather large and ornate statue of neptune and attendants in the centre of the fountain... impressive... but near this fountain is the standard wall of honour for those who gave their lives to world warr 2, these are usually quite impressive displays complete with small photos of those who died either in action or in complete inaction during the war. Near this memorial in Bolgona is a smaller, less ornate glass plaque paying respects to the 80 or so people who deid in the bombing of the bologna train station in August 1980 urlLink  .  After a few minutes attempting to translate the inscription on the plaque i was joined by an elderly local who looked me straight in the eyes, pointed at the plaque and rather angrily suggested that i had no business reading it as a foreginer because i couldnt understand the significance of the event. I looked at him, subtracted 23 years from his life and saw a man who may well have been closer to the incident than first seemed,.. i tried to be polite but strangled by the language barrier i may have come across rather abruptly.   He asked me to read the plaque, whcih was lucky for me because i can fool just about anyone with my italian pronunciation as long as they arent too many pesky letter c's... so i turned on my best exaggerated italian and read the plaque back to him. This seemed to calm him down somewhat, but also managed to attract the attention of 2 or 3 other gentlemen who would otherwise have simply passed by another tourist pretending to read something which they dont understand. They stopped and started a conversation with the gentlemen, they (obviously) held a different view to himself and believed that it was good for foreigners to come here and be interested in the history of the town and who show respect, he agreed but found something to disagree with and the hand waving increased along with the velocity of the conversation which combined to a sharp drop in my comprehension of what was being discussed,.. as the gestures in my direction grew less frequent I made my way further along the piazza.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Bologna  Despite the heatwave I managed to haul my ass around this town several times. Assisting me in this endeavour was several centuries of sensible town planning. The entire centro storico of bologna is made up of porticoed buildings which allows for plenty of shade and places to sit and also maufactures pleasing breezes which tickle the seat on your brow and somehow trick you into thinking that 25 degrees aint so bad after all.  In contrast to this is the town's main square, piazza maggiore, a slab or concrete big enough to have a footy match in.   Bologna is home to Europe's oldest university, formed about 1000 years ago to argue about how to split up the cash the church was making... gee so glad they sorted that problem out once and for all... Bologna is also home to just about every left wing political movement and lobby group in italy and the town is not too over the moon about italy's current political saviour... In fact Mr Berlusconi os mocked quite publicly and i challenge anyone to find a copy of one of his newspapers for sale in this town, i have seen one copy of the  urlLink corriere della sera  whilst staying here and that was in the corner of the breakfast room in the 4 star hotel i was staying in when i first landed in this town. Most people that prefer their news on dead trees get to a copy of  urlLink La Repubblica  and its certainly the only paper you see advertised at the edicole around town.  The other advantage of the uni town is the fairly active nightlife and spirit of the town itself. Young, smart people wandering about arguing the point or just being pretty, lots of languages and culture all trying to hammer themselves into something that can loosely be called italian society. I am over the cobblestones and ancient walls, i look into the eyes of the poeple now and allow myself to be washed away by their passion their anger, contempt, joy, conflict, pessimism, hope and contradiction,..  this is what makes a culture, its not a formula, it's a cacophany of choices which when viewed from a distance all point towards the one destiny. This destiny isnt corruptible by the desires ofa  single person, sure each person has their say and can influence others but you cant sway a culture just because you dont like something about it,.. it takes numbers, it takes time as much time as it took to develop the thing in the firstplace.  I have always been amazed by how impatient australians are to manufacture a culture for our country, i am certainly in no hurry, yes i think its important to discuss these things but not so we can come up with a consensus on where our cultural identity lies, to do so would mean to take a vote on which cricket player best captures the australian spriti... none of them do... none of them can... we cant decide how many australians need to die in a war before we can feel that we have contributed to the worlds development,.. thats a ridiculous notion, we cant conjure up history, conflict, resolution peace and tension, we just have to get throught it like every other society throughout history.  Hmm... back to Bologna now.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      June 7 Off to Bologna  Caght the train from Venice to Bologna on Saturday morning thinking wow what agreat little trup to bologna this is going to be... peaceful, i dont even have to put my pack up on the rack, calm, tranquil,.. i can even hear the birds in the trees as we pass them by... and as we approached mestre,.. i could spend a few seconds trying to recognise the strange noise which was getting louder it sounds like... hmm.. i dont know... oh yes i do.  It sounds like about 1,000 soccer fans making the trip to bologna for the last of the serie A games for the season, 1,000 hot and sweaty, smoking, horn blowing fans, most of which chose my carriage from which to abuse the anto smoking policy that the italian train system had in place..  The horror quickly subsided however, they were young and raucous but by and large a good bunch of people... chanting, waving flags,.. comparing flares (of the non panteloon variety) and generally being a good way to pass the time whilst travelling through the otherwise flat and relatively uninteresting countryside between venezia and bologna. The other bonus was that the girls who frequent soccer matches have taken to imitating brazilian soccer fans, the yellow brasil t shirt tied just below the jubblies, whistles, hot pants and dancing queens... yes one wasnt game to get the camera out in the confines of the carriage im sorry to say sports fans, but i am happy to give those interested a minute by minute description.  I brought the weather with me to Bologna, arrived at around 2:30 to 35 degree heat and figured the 2km walk to my hotel wasnt going to be a good introduction to the town, a quick tour of the bustilng and apparently very dodgy train station and i taxied my ass off to 4 star luxury. Was greeted by an indian receptionist who spoke lovely italiam amd better english than most of the english i have met,... she was a pom of course and laughed when i suggested that she had never been back to india... she wasnt into banghra so we quickly ran out of things to discuss until she asked me what i did for a living.... i dont remember the batch oif lies i extracted from my ass but they began with me asking ''which name i had booked my room under''  This seemed like a good idea at the time,.. smalltalk with the staff and all,.. but i recalled my encounter with the carabinieri in venezia,.. i dont think i was game to mention it here but suffice to say that the piazza san marco was subject to a ''credible'' terrorist threat... i didnt ask whether the terrorists or their threat was the credible bit,.. i uess both. But the  urlLink carabinieri   were interested in speaking with solo non italian travellers who had changed hotels within venice on or about monday June 2. o yes on the thursday evening my time had come and the nice carabinieri types sat me down in the bar of my hotel with a few other stranieri to have a chat... i was the only one who asked for an espresso,.. i foolishly thought this would impress them... some german kid started to cry... they asked me what i was doing in italy, i told them i was here to meet chicks.. they said... no seriously... i said, yes seriously .-.. i didnt say i was going to be succesful.  They have some fabulous uniforms them carabinieri, once again i didnt think this was a photo opportunity, but they did take the chance to have a look at the holiday snapshots i had taken,.. i guess passing up the chance to take a few snapshots of the guy selling mussolini posters and cufflinks was a good call after all.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      June 3 -June 6 - Venezia  Tips for being alone in the city of love  Venice is not the city to head for if you are on your own and the type of person that enjoys the company of members of the opposite sex but is unable to acquire said company and the drop of a gondola... however, it is a pretty place so for those loners like there that plan to spend some time here, learn from my finite but poignant wisdom  You will generally get by without breaking down into tears as long as you dont spend too much time on dimly lit canal bridges, or frequent restaurants that people who would otherwise be spending tiem on dimly lit bridges eat at.  Saying the words ''sono solo sta sera'' may sound poetic to the foreign ear but they are a sad combination of parole italiani ... in this town when you utter words to this effect after entering a restaurant you are immediately ushered away from the eye gazing couple which adhere to the street side tables and are usually sent to a seat where you can usually at least see the outside world but usually are part of the ashtray or napkin storage area,.. i guess this is to minimise the pain that you may undergo by having to watch people being happy sharing expensive cocktails deliberating over whether cozze are mussles or some kind of mushroom or arguing about why the fella always refers to the map... ( i ditched my map days ago,.. im not bragging.. its just rather useless)  Once you are seated various adjustments are made to your personal space,.. firstly the waiter whisks away the glassware, cutlery and napkins from the vacant side of your table, this is to remind you that there is something missing in your paultry existence, a void, an aperture which you have neglected and which may become infected and lead to serious harm unless you do something about it. Everyone else is now aware that you are alone, you cant pour a sip of wine into the spare glass and pretend that your beautiful dinner partner has merely popped out to speak to the amassed throng of foreig journalists or deal with a problem the chef has with tonights souffles.  No buddy, you aint gonna fool anyone.  But you have the chair, the chair, it sits there staring at you, a constant reminder of the fact that yuou cant manufacture shared experience despite how seasoned a traveller you are, how refined your tastes or profound your knowledge of local customs, ethics and culture.  The shape of the chair will vary, some are short and stout, motherly, the kind of chair you would turn to when you needed advice, a hug, or got your thumb caught in a blender again, others are tall and slender and have southern accetns, they knock you off your feet and make you think of a world you never knew existed, these are the kinds of chairs you pass by thinking i will sit with that chair next time i see it,.. but of course that day rarely comes... Other chairs are a flamboyant aray of angles, material colours and form, you keep hoping that they are just shallow but you keep wanting to be with them and learn more about the simple complexity of their world.  But the shoulders of the beautiful chair are always there, peering back at you over the top of your table, waiting patiently for you to come up with a witty anecdote, say something inspirational anout the things you have seen today, the smells from the fish market intermingling with those from the pasticerria, the sunlight reflecting off the canal and onto the ceiling off the casa on the bank, the things americans say to people they think cant speak english.  You can say this things, you can think them up, you can write them down, but nobody will be there to understand them.  This is not necessarily a bad thing, but a thing you must come to terms with.  For me this is the end of the line in Venice, tomorrow I am off to Bologna for at least 3 nights and then will probably leapfrog ,my way through Toscana to siena, but then again thats one advantage of travelling alone, i really dont know where i am going, but for once .. thats a good thing.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink whats wrong with you people down there  they should just arrest the guy who thinks his fridge magnet tells him how to analyse people.  imagine having mud on your boots, there could have been an atomic bomb in that mud... you can cover just about anything with mud... ive seen them do it..  If you cant be a mindless dickhead in Australia then where the hell am I supposed to live!!!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      June 1 -2 - Venezia  All i wanted to do was get lost in venice, it didnt take long, in fact i am typing this right now thinking hey its dark out now... how the hell am i going to get back to my 159 euro a night cupboard for a nap? But what better city to get lost in, wandering past rumbling doorways that you swore you just walked past a few minutes ago and which you probably did. Doing stupid things like using the armani store in san marco as a marker,.. aha... yep.. there are 3, or the even more sutpid mistake,.. following the tourist reading the map.  My first 2 days were spent in the Hotel Hesperia which is far enoguh from the station to be quiet but doesnt require you to lug your luggage over canals ... clever hey.. and it was a nice place,.. interesting rooms,.. nice people... real coffee for breakfast... so my first 2 days were spent walking through the jewish ghetto and making the trek on foot from ferrovia to rialto and piazza san marco.  It was on such a journey that I met mario and his care giver, whose name i never caught.  Mario had some issues, he was short and stocky, he was fat and really hadnt kept himself in good shape,.. but it seems that today was the day that mario wanted to break free from the shackles that had bound him, and I played my part.  Strolling along the canareggio canal towards tourist land i saw a small dog appear from a doorway, its little legs only barely keeping its belly from the pavement, it looked to its right saw nothing .. looked to its left ... saw me... figured i was the safer bet and sprinted madly towards me, seconds later the frantic screams of mario mario mario expolded from the sam doorway from where emerged a woman who although a difference species did resemble mario in stature and certainly in speed... mario shuffled headloing towards his destiny, she shuffled like a madwoman after him,.. mario mario mario... i had time to assess the situation and thought... aha... i can help this poor hapless local who has lost her dog, surely the only source of income for her and her starving... err...sparrows...i moved swiftly into position... stepping in front of mario and his dash for freedom,.. mario took onle last look at his prize amd moved his gaze towards me, the expression puppy dog eyes is a cliche but cliches become cliches for a reason.. this was the reason.  However stumbling care giver was not satisfied with merely a distriaction she wanted mario in her posession, custody she wanted him back in the chains which he had lived all his life, she even had the keys with her i could hear them jangling during the pauses in her cackling... she continued ... mario mario mario.  Mario leaned one way and moved the other and implanted the thought that he may have rabies into my mind to make a getaway,.. but he didnt count on another australian traveller who had also scouted the situation and saw a chance to impression the locals. He lunged at mario forcing him backwards into the path of ... of that woman... mario had no choice... h had come this far and was going to be free without second throught he plunged.  We leaned .. over the edge of the canal ... a drinking straw, a piece of miscellaneous plastic,.. some patented veneziano floating scum... but no mario... still the mad womans screams continued... mario ... mario.... mario...   We waited for at least a minute ... but mario was free,.. my companion turned to me and spoke a few words in his honour ''lets get the fuck out of here man''    I am for 6 days, lets hope i dont kill ... again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday May 31 Urbania - Pesaro   On saturday morning i packed my worldly possessions into the old fairydown and headed off for more adventures,.. i was kind of looking forward to leaving the sactuary that urbania had become, although there was still much to experience and we had put together a nice little posse the sands of time theory was always going to win and i whisked myself away while the stranieri slept in their uncomfotable beds.  The last time i was in Pesaro was the weekend before the course began, so i was familiar with the layout of the town, the bars near the station etc... and now i had a bit of italian wih me as well... the experience was much more appealing.. i bounced up to the ticket ounter at the station,.. booked my ticket for venice got snappy when the girl behind the counter told me i would have to go to anopther counter for a seat reservation... went to the bar and ordered coffee, mineral water and yeah why not a focaccia and i could sweat the girl had the gee he doesnt look italian look on her face.  Yes some progreess had been made,.. the guy who stumbled into that roman bar in trastevere makign every error possible 5 weeks ago had died and left the planet.  Pesaro, lovely town alongside the adriatic,.. it aint Fano and it aint Rimini but buggerred if i can tell what on earth the difference is.. there is what they pass as sand, sea and sun... but i realise i am no espert on the subject... so... i sat in bar in the shade of a dot dot dot tree... sipping some kind of bevande watching the chicks walk past adjusting themselves like the trained proffesionasl that they are, had enough of that and was about to leave when some goddess type thing landed her spaceship next to me and came into the bar, she stood next to me talking to the barman... the heat radiated off her body ... and i didnt even have my face that close to her.. ok i moved a little closer... but not too close.. really... i mean ... yeah.  My confidence evaporated after her third, ''this smile is brought to you by the city of pesaro'' moment and i headed off to find that caffe, and yes... my sixth sense kicked in,..turned off the main road,.. turned away from the church and there it was... darn i almost told you its name... cant do that... this is gold... the sounds of coffee cups being stacked and the coffee grinder at work,.. 6 tables all under umbrellas a small piazza complete with leafy trees, sleeping dogs, vespa and an old woman sitting in her first floor window singing or praying or doing something noisy.  If nothing else happened in pesaro and you can bet your ass it didnt! i would be happy and take fond memories into my head long plunge into that tourist land where italian is rarely heard... venezia
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Day 30 - Friday May 30 - i never could count  Friday was the final day in my course in Urbania... whenver somebody has stopped long enough to listen i have ben using the analogy of a brick wall to describe my grasp of the italian language... how so you ask? Well,.. having been around italians italianness and italianism for my entire existense i have picked up loads of vocabulary which i stoed in a large pile,.. we shall call these ... bricks... after some basic schooling i have managed to arrange the se words into simple phrases, sentenses or what i like to call... a wall... or more correctly a garden edging... now this wall looksed ok,.. people would pass it thinking yeah theres that wall again, seen more like that one somewhere ah yeah just over there... as long as nobody leaned on it, played soccer against it, attempted to construct a swimming pool grandstand using it as support it basically worked as a wall... oh,.. water management was also right out...  my wall had lots of bricks but nothing holding it together,...sheesh do i have to spell out everything for you people...  well now.. after some intensive schooling... which i refer to cement... parts of my wall are kind of secure, parts are patchy,.. and others have had the bricks broken down and bright yellow and red tape used to keep tourists away from the area...  I am pretty happy with how the course went, dur to the fact that my conversation teacher was a bit of a tool ... actually he is a tool, a sidchrome 12'' shifter, my conversation skills arent quite what i hoped they would be, but you dont want somebody like me randomly going up to the locals and actually communicating with them now do you... see they had it all planned.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       July - Taverna "Barba Yiannis"   My cousin's taverna had changed since i last visitied, but there was still many echoes of what once was. His Father Yianni opened the tavern in 1975 serving small snacks to the townfolk who would promenade for several hours each evening during the warmer months. The tavern was small with about 5 tables inside, a small delicatessen style freezer beyond which were the heavy cast iron grills on which my uncle would place the number of souvlakia i felt capable of eating each night i was there. Each summer the front yard of the house would accomodate a further 8 or so tables, in the open lit by candles and lanterns. I remember trade being brisk, people would come in and sit at a table, the waiter, usually my cousin Diamandi or his brother Tzortz would lay a piece of grease proff paper down on the table whilst telling them what was on, there was rarely more then 4 dishes, 3 meat and one dish from the kitchen such as stuffed vegetables or "yiyantes" beans. The souyblakia ordered would be placed onto the grease proof paper along with half a lemon, and a piles of dried oregano and salt. The meat on the stick would be dragged through these and into the mouths of the patrons.  The tavern had now grown, the indoor portion now occupied the entire old tavern had been extended forward into the butcher shop that the family used to operate, the kitchen had been moved to the rear of the place and been twice expanded since those days.  The menu had also expanded and the practice of using the grease proof paper covered table as crockery had also been replaced by knives and forks and white plates, much to my disappointment. But the meat was as i remembered, the flavour, smell and the way they pulled off the skewer took me back.  The old man no longer worked the taverna, Diamandi now stood behind the grill, his wife Mairi oldest daughter Hrisa (18) and son Yianni (of course) (15) shared waitress and kitchen duties when they were around and Diamandi's older daughter Elefteria was the full time waitress. Full time for them had become 7 nights a week and Friday - Sunday lunches, plus one other lunchtime session when busloads of greek "kapi" would be bussed into the village to eat at one of the traditional tavernas that had sprouted up in the houses surrounding Barba Yiannis once they saw his success.  The rivalry between the taverns was fairly apparent, with families electing to shift their efforts from working the land, and into converting their homes into a sutable venue for food and drink realising that this would also mean the end to any friendships or blood ties between them and the other tavern owners. Although these newer taverns purpose built from scratch were more comfortable places to sit in, the people that came to the village were looking for an opportunity to experience things in a more traditional environment and so barba yianni's stayed popular and most *but certainly not all) of the town's inhabitants stayed loyal.  So it is in the tavern again, amidst the company of family members i could actually talk with and dare i say it enjoyed the company of that I would again sit during the morning and evenings passing time, joking, reminiscing and sharing hopes, gossip and ... the occasional souvlaki or ten. 
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        kept you hanging there didn't I?   "they can hear you through them you know" Aryiri whispered to me, i couldnt answer but did manage to look in his direction expected more information "your phone... even if its off, they can still hear what you are saying" "they?" "eh they... you know who i mean... the government" "why would the government want to listen to what i say?" "why? because they can... and they want you to know they can" "it wouldnt surprise me and i dont really care... they can come over for lunch if they want" "youre right cousin... a clear sky isnt afraid of lightning" "you said it"  Aryiri straight down the guts of the village... at the old town square near my grandmothers house but didnt come to stop, he turned the steering wheel full lock and allowed the car to do a few laps crunching the gravel on the shoddily paved road outside my grandmothers house. "where should we go... we need to talk about some things cousin". He released the steering wheel and we dizzily drove through the back of the village and down the hill towards the river.  Next to the old bridge near the river now stood a small church, this wasnt there when i visited in 1978, it was a small shrine type construction... barely cat swinging room inside. Aryiri pulled over and got out, i hesitated but followed.  "do you believe cousin?" "in God?" i replied, a question he didnt enjoy hearing "yes... in God, why else would i ask you if you believe" "I believe in something... " he interrupted "wrong" Aryiri had moved towards the back of the church and was looking inside another small shrine in the wall, this resembled your typical roadside type windowed shrine with a few icons and an oil lamp. "faith is more important than anything cousin" he takes out a small icon, crosses himself, kisses it and hands it to me as he reaches for another larger icon. He was watching me, i figured that I have done a lot worse to avoid offending people, crossed myself kissed it and placed it back into the shrine, we repeated the same process with 2 more icons. Whilst this was going on Aryiri spoke of how his faith in the Lord had kept him alive and helped him to stay aware of what he had to do to do the rigth thing by his family, wife and children. He spoke to me of how my faith must have manifested in various ways i wasnt aware of, eventhough i dont go to church he said, my interest in, knowledge of and thirst for knowledge of greek history, and my ability to speak the language well were all evidence of a faith.  We walked towards a small bench near the church, a fountain had been placed behind the bench drawing water from the river, there was some off cuts of pvc pipe laying across it, i picked them up and placed them behind the fountain so they couldnt be seen and then cleared some dried leaves from the its concrete floor. I turned and Aryiri had raised his palms towards me and was crying, smiling..  "You see cousin,.. you see... you have faith, you believe" "yes, i believe that there shouldnt be junk lying around" "yes, but each day you walk past junk in the street and you dont stop to clear it up... " "how could i... i wouldnt have time to do anything else" "yes,.. but here... in this place you found the time, you moved and cleared the area, made it more respectful" i started getting a little annoyed, the whole do you believe argument had been forced down me a few times before and although i dont think people who call themselves believers are fools,.. i dont think im somehow lacking because i dont call myself one of them  "Aryiri, listen, i believe in a power, a strength, a source of hope etc, but i really believe that this is human spirit, i respect this space because you obviously do and I want to show you that I respect you" Aryiri listened to the words as they came through my lips and reached for my hand, he twisted our arms together, his hands were rough and dark never knowing a day without work, mine soft and white 35 yaers old but brand new. "My cousin our lives are very different, you live in a world surrounded by thought and knowledge, I live in a world where taking time to think about things means that there is something wrong with you." I guess he was speaking relatively when he referred to my intellectual world, so i let that one go through to the keeper. "You are greek, I am greek and we are blood, you cant deny that and you cant find anything stronger, we all live today because of what our family did in the past, and what makes us the same is that we have the same people to thank for it." This notion of a weight of gratitude for what happened in the past, what my grandparents and parents had to endure to simply make it possible for me to walk the earth was something which i had been unable to avoid during the short time i was back in town.   "We both have strengths, i am luckier than you in one way, one big way" I didnt see his next sentence coming. "I knew our grandfather, the man whose name you have,.. you never met him"  Speaking to the old timers is alsways something I enjoy. I like listening to the stories they care to sahre, the way the say them and just like watching the way they go about their daily shit. I had been soaking up any tidbits of information about my grandfathers, neither of whom I met. I ama fairly proud individual and believe that I try and do whats good not just for myself but for others, I always consider what impact my actions will have on other people abd whether to my credit or detriment have made changes and decisions based upon the fact that doing otherwise may hurt, disappoint or upset those around my life. My Grandfather Chris was such a man, but he makes me look like a sinister swindler in comparison to the deeds he regularly performed for strangers. My father inherited much of this, I have to but walking down the street and having complete strangers top you and say 'your father built my house,.. we didnt know hi, we had no money, he came here one day and built this!" ... makes me realise where I stand in the global good samaritan rankings.  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       We are all a little bit insane at times   Having settled into village life, found my way to the city and even located comfotable albeit not super economical internet access i was silly enough to think that i could switch off parts of my brain that i had been using to absorb and analyse events, people, places spaces etc and just relax for a while. But the big guy who pulls the levers of life figured one more "point of interest" on the calendar of my travels wouldn't be inappropriate as it would make me realise that even in relatively small towns, shit doth happen and it happens fast.  On this fine tuesday morning i had spent about 2 hours digging into my email inbox, amidst the offers to sell me viagra, without pain or weights lengthen my penis, allow me to collect prizes that have been waiting for me and informing 10 billion US dollars which was about to be forwarded to my bank account, there was also the odd messaage from  bona fide  human beings whom i have actually met... imagine my surprise.  When suddenly! My phone rang, OK maybe that jump cut was a bit harsh as in this day and age a phone ringing isn't necessarily worthy of fanfare, if i was some kind of viking up to my neck in a pillage and i suddenly received an SMS then yes,.. but the phone did ring suddenly as they often do. and as I had only acquired my Greek phone number a day or so ago, and due to the the fact that nothing at all can ever possibly happen within 24 hours in Greece I was pretty well confident that I was about to receive my first Greek wrong number...  oh my god how wrong was I ... hmm yeah i did it again there didn't I? The reference to our Lord and saviours old man was probably again inappropriate, i apologise if I offended anyway.  I answered the phone in the traditional manner, albeit in greek, but greeks have traditions too and these extend to communications via telephonic device. A conversation took place, to save time i have translated it rather cleverly into a language we all claim to understand.  "yes! cousin? ahh yes, who is it? its your cousin Aryiri cousin, how are you going,.. where are you? Aryiri is my first cousin, his mother is my fathers sister and he is the oldest male cousin on my fathers side who lives in the village. We share a grandmother, you get me? Yeah well... him calling me out of the blue or... suddenly as i previously erred,  made me immediately shift my thoughts to my grandmother, more specifically her life or possible lack thereof, which although would have been sudden may not have been out of the blue although the expression i didnt even know she was sick! would definitely been appropriate. With this in mind i continued the conversation.  whats happening cousin, is anything wrong? no cousin, dont worry, nothing is wrong, for once i have some good news to share bravo aryiri, these are the sorts of things i want to hear, tell me this is actually a really nice expression in greek but translates rather cheesily, shame.  Yes chris, i've had some good luck and i want to share it with you today what do you mean? Do i need to bring a bottle of champagne? yes why not, ive never had champagne, its probably good... cousin i won some money today in a lottery and ive called all my friends here today and i feel empty without you here knowing that you are so close by.. i want you to come here as soon as you are able great news cousin, ill come as soon as i find a bottle of champagne come come soon cousin, il be waiting  The conversation ends with me hurriedly ending an email and wondering where i would find a bottle of bubbly in this town, fortunately the consumption of alcohol has always been a national pasttime and somethin appropriate was bound to pop up. A fine bottle of asti ricadonna was purchased for a ridiculous amount of euro and the nice lady at the super even had a recycled piece of blue cellophane to wrap it in, ah yes. Clutching my cliched wog bravo bravo gift i bounced into an awaiting cab and headed back to the village.  Aryiri lives across from my first cousin Diamandis home and taverna, Dianandi is the hub of village knowledge and as i was in need of a fresh bulletin i ducked behind parked tractors so the amassed well wishers in Aryiris front yard wouldnt spot me... like hell they didnt!... and walk into Diamandis kitchen to get the scoop. The details he passed onto me didnt differ greatly from what Aryiri himself told me over the phone, no amounts were known, but the expression a lot of money was used.    I crossed the street and walked into Aryiris front yard, about 6 tables had been arranged on the 2 grassy rectangles in front of his family home, people from the village some of whom i knew, others whom knew me and others who i didnt know from a fence post were all sitting around sipping beers, eating food acquired from one of the many tavernas that occupy this part of ambelokipi and generally wishing it was them.  Aryiri stood to greet me, he looked like he had just won the lottery *note to literary critics, this is not a cliche if it relates to an event that actually happened.   "cousin, its good to have you with me today" "aman cousin, im glad to be here, congratulations" "dont congratulate me cousin, we have all won, im going to share my treasure with everyone"  OOh did you hear that? yes... those bells,.. not church bells, not jingle bells, not as foreboding as hell bells.. just plain old alarm bells, yes folks alarm bells they are ringing but when i look around me and see people sitting around when they should be working eating food and bevvy smiling in the face of adversity it looks like o am the only one that hears them. and then he says, actually thats a lie... he whispers to me.  "Cousin, sit and let me offer you something to eat and drink before you go, i know you have to go back home to see our grandmother but I want to talk to you ... alone... ok?" I nod, take a seat at one the tables knowing full well that nobody has won a red cent and waiting to see what cousin Aryiri has in store for us.  I didnt know whether to laugh or cry, didnt know whether to stand up amd knock over a few tables and tell people to get the fuck out of here. I looked acros at his wife and children obviously believing in that their painfully poor existence had come to an end, his sons had already devised new and interesting ways to spend money and even had a roster as to who could come and play on their playstation 2. But my hunch was still nothng more than that, so I sat there, riding the wave of happiness that everyone else was surfing along hoping that I was just being a sour old fart and that my humch, sparked by the look in my cousins eye and the words that fell from his mouth immediately after was nothing more than that.  We sat for several hours in my cousin's front yard, he used phrases like "this treasure i want to share with you all", "this gift has been given to me and no figure can be put onto its worth" each double meaning cutting into my concsience. My cousin Diamandi had arrived and was sitting opposite me, he reached for one of the souvlakia on the tray between us, i grabbed the other end of the skewer and caught his eye, he laughed thinking i was stuffing around until he saw the expression on my face. Seconds later he announced to the crowd that he was going to get some more wine for the group and asked me to come and help him.  He shut the door to his kitche after we entered, i didnt even know the kitchen had a door, he realised something was wrong, he opened the conversation with; "tell me" "i dont know whats going on cousin and i dont want to get you involved but... i dont know aryiri very well, i dont know the kind of person he is so I cant be sure about what I am thinking but.." "tell me .. what!" "I dont think he has won any money,.. i dont think he has" "how do you know?" "he said something strange and he keeps saying these things that could mean anything" Diamandi's hands blindly lit a cigarette, he walked away from me and stood by the grill looking into the glowing coals. "what do you think diamandi,.. im sorry but I dont know who else to talk to" "no cousin you did the right thing, ... yes... your cousin aryiri, has had a lot of problems,.. you know them as well as i do.. and hes capable of anything, a joke,.. but to his own family? I dont know..." "no neither do I,.. he said he wants to talk to me alone, before I go and see my grandmother" Diamandi turns and looks at me, his daughter Hrisa opens the door and pokes her head into the room. "alone? about what? "He didnt say, he said something about family and sharing and how he needed my help with something important" "Be careful cousin" and as soon as the words left his mouth I realised that yes, yes I had to be careful as if he was lieing and was quite happy with deceiving his own children and wife then what he had in mind may not be totally logical,.. or safe.  I was scared, it was a strange feeling, one i didnt expect to have to deal with within the boundaries of my parents little village.  Diamandi told me exactly what had happened when aryiri walked into his kitchen and announced what happened. Aryiri was holding a "laiko" lottery ticket, told them he had it for some weeks but hadnt checked the number, and was waiting in a supermarket queue this morning and saw the ticket in his wallet, he checked it in the newspaper and knew that he was holding the winning ticket as he turned the pages. he had no idea how much he had won, and would find out later tonight.  I walked back to Aryiris house holding 2 large jugs of red wine, Aryiri stood as I approached the table cleared some room to allow me to put the jugs down, announced to the group that he had to take me back to my grandmothers house and that they were to "treat his house as their home" until he returned.  Aryiri doesnt own a passenger vehicle, his family move between villages on the tractor and the platform that it tows "like gypsies" as he says. He had borrowed the keys to a friend's car, I sat in the front next to him, he asked me to switch off my mobile phone before we drove off, he took my bag got out and put it in the boot of the car, he returned, told me how much he hates mobile phones and drove off.  I looked around me thinking, wow, could this be it? Is this as b grade and straight to video cheesy as things get? As we drove off I saw my cousin Diamandi sitting in the front seat of his car and realised yes... yes it does.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey who's the new guy?   25 years since i last walked her streets, chatted with her locals and rubbed shoulders with my family who live there i found myself as i had done as a 10 year old child standing in the centre of Ambelokipi's town square early in the morning watching the town wake.  Just as then, kids on cycles would ride up to me and stop and stare, conversations would end and turn to whispers and knowing nods, some of these familiar strangers would come up and welcome me, or simply say hello as if it was yesterday or the day before they passed me on their way to buy bread.  The zaharoplasteion (cake shop/coffee house) that used to occupy the building across the town square from my grandmother's house had now become the bakery so although there was still some activity there it didnt have the buzz that people sitting around drinking coffee and sticky sweets can bring. As a result the town square had also fallen relatively silent. I went for a quick tour of the streets surrounding the house, the old school replaced by a relatively new one, a second church builkt in what was the ruins of the old part of the village, in the area where i remember my grandmother Konstandina telling me once had the illegal school for children teaching them something other than the official language of greece. The road out of the town on my grandmothers side of the village hadnt changed, a steep decent to the river, all the roads where now paved but several houses were recognisable. The old kafeneio "rouska" was still there and showing its age.  I sat with my grandmother on the plastic outdoor furniture that have swept across greece on the back of gypsies trucks like some kind of prickly pear infestation. We shared stories old and new in between interruptions by the various close relatives who had been told of my arrival. My Father's sisters arrived, My father's family has always fascinated me as their characters tend to cross an entire spectrum, in melbourne my aunt Frida was serious and aloff, whereas my aunt evdoxia was always happy despite living a life of struggle, they were mirrored by my aunts olympia and afroditi in the village. Afroditi was the family clown and a quite talented one at that, Olympia although sweet and reliable probably hadnt said or done anything particularly amusing in her life, it would just waste time one could spend working.  Around midday my cousin Diamandi and his father Yianni arrived. When i was last in the village it was Diamandi who took me in as such, his father ran the only taverna (psistaria) in town "Barba yianni's" and Diamandi and I wouild spend each morning placing chunks of meat onto skewers, large numbers of which legend has it i would also consume that same evening. Diamandi was several years older than me, but we talked pretty much non stop during the times I was with him, he helped me learn a great deal abiout greece, language and culture that I otherwise would have not seen. He had changed no more than I had, and I felt this bond immediately snap back into place, into a small notch in my heart that i had forgotten existed.   The next few days were spent walking the town streets, meeting relatives and family friends, few of which introduced themselves but all of which ask me to give my regards to my parents.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       A grandmother's embrace   I called her name so as not to shock her, or to at least minimise the shock, or prepare her a little for a moment of happiness. I had been warned that she was weak, hard of hearing and needed lots of help around the house, in the moments I had to myself in her personal space i didn't see any real sign of that. There was the general clutter that accumulates within a lifetime, several objects that she uses regularly within reach, the fly swatter next to the fruit bowl, her pills in a small bowl with a photo of me and my first cousins at my cousin Pauls 12th birthday, her oil lamp and small collection of religious icons kept between the sponges and the television set, but the house was clean and cared for, lived.  As the swishing of her screen door died away my grandmother entered her kitchen and walked towards me, slowly raising her arms up to reach my shoulders, dusko mou dusko mou she whispered as we embraced, my hands moving over her shoulders, which had become narrow and delicate, to think that it was only 20 years or so ago that these same shoulders would take me on endless piggy backs around the lounge room her hands reached for mine and closed firmly, their liver spitted skin now draping the easily identifiable  bones the same hands that years earlier would clinically grab chickens from the ground that I as a child would deliberately let loose in our small east hawthorn backyard.  We embraced for several minutes, my grandmother smothering me in motherly type phrases delivered in a variety of languages and I unable to do much more than tell her i love her and try to resist the urge to pick her up bodily and swing her around the room. I dont often get the opportunity to experience joy, lets face it we rarely get the opportunity to feel joy nowadays, life can be happy, jesus christ it can be wonderful and big and all encompassing  but joy is an indulgence few can afford. Today i was hoarding the emotion in bucketloads, the years of anguish i experienced when i felt too trapped in work and other commitments back home to be able to travel and come back to see my grandmother who helped make me the man i am, the gut wrenching days i spent when she was on the brink and i looked back on the simple decisions i would have had to make to allow me to break free of these self imposed responsibilities and travel the distance to see her, more importantly to give her the chance to see me again, all that pain melted away in her embrace. The awesome weight of times sands slipped away gradually but each grain could now be cherished and remembered as it falls.  The frail old woman I was told to expect was there, but she lived in a way that defied her age, she remained quite proud and simply capable of living, communicating and understanding, she had obviously thought about our reunion and had prepared several little anecdotes, some i also remembered some i had forgotten.  One story which she repeated many times in the first hours of our reunion occurred not long after she first came to Australia. My parents had taken the opportunity to go out to a dinner dance and i stayed home with yiayia, from the events she mentioned i must have been around 7 years old. My parents had just brought a new bed and I asked dad if i could sleep on it while they were out. I remember lying on the bed many times when i was young, wondering what on earth these grown ups did with that much bed, i loved the way the patterns on the bedspread would fade away (in my eyes at least) into the distance and the gentle curve of the middle of the bed. Of course more cliched trampoline like qualities where also enjoyed, memorably resulting in the untimely death of a prancing stallion figurine.  On this particular evening however, as I fell alseep i told my grandmother that when i grow up, i was going to buy a house, not a big house, but a nice house, and i was going to buy a big bed like this one and put it in the biggest room in the house so that she can come and live with me and we can play and talk all the time. She repeated this story to my father after they came home, she was obviously moved by it and recalls it clearly almost 30 years later, from her description I was unable to make out what my fathers impressions of it were, and any psychologists out there are probably also reaching for your text books. But who cares, growing up with 2 mothers arund me has had impacts on every essence of my life... Im not one to dwell on the negative.  Thanks for everything yiayia, i cnn never repay you, you will never want to do anything that give, this i have learnt from you and as much as it makes me a "good" person it also plagues me, but its a gift i will always cherish.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       home   During the long, slow, traffic jammed trip to Athens' new shiny airport in the back seat of my friend sav's rental the fact that i was moving from the uniquely energised state of a city doing its best to reach the standard necessary to host the modern summer olymipc games to a region of greece that my family have lived in or around for as long as anybody can remember let along record. The trip was from the unashamedly pulbic and intrusive calamity of the coty, to the totally personal and intimate reflectiveness of return to my grandmothers home.   Some more background, my grandmother lives in ambelokipi kastoria, she is 94 years old and lives alone but has 2 daughters and several grandchildren and other relatives in the village with her. Her health has been somewhat up and down as you would expect, high blood pressure, heart problems and all those things we can all look forward to one day. But her mind, memory, eye sight and hearing are all pretty good. I have tested her resolve by constantly putting off my plans to travel and see her, but today we would put all that behind us, as by about 6:30 pm this afternoon i will make my way back to the village i last walked around as a small boy in 1978, i doubt much has changed, i doubt anything at all has changed really.  I made my way to the bus terminal in salonica via cab, a drive straight down the main street of a town that even though it is largely comprised of multi storey apartment buidlings manages to maintain a cosmopolitan flavour that many larger cities lose in the smog and mayhem, The cab driver made several attempts to convince me tat his kind offer of 110 euro to drive me to kastoria was my best option, i disagreed very politely which made it very clear to him that i wasnt actually Greek,.. this meant that the remainder of the ride revolved around him giving me a long list of relatives he has living in melbourne, pausing each time to look at me in case i happened to know any of them...  The bus terminal in salonica was a refreshing surprise compared to the shambles of a shed that purports to perform the same function in athens. A short wait and I was on the bus to Kastoria. The bus sped through tghe plains to the west of salonica and then headed for the mountains through Veria and Kozani, as we approached the kastoria border the town names and road signs brough back more and more memories. During our trip to the village in 1978 my uncle who ran the only tavern in the village (at the time) would take us on day trips each monday, he had a massive blue opel station wagon and we would pile into it together and head off to one of the nearby highlights. 25 years ago, as i get closer i choke harder and harder on the fact that i let such a long time pass before returning, and despite years of denying or rebeling against the notion of heritage, here it was staring me in the face.  I wasnt sure what to expect in the village, my father had told me that my grandmother (his mother) seemed ok and had been anticipating my arrival with a great deal of pleasure, this seemed to make my father happy as well, an emotion iu am not used to receiving from him. The bus moved through the villages near kastoria and i heard people on the bus talk about them using the old slavic or maco town names, a few people boarded the bus at koustarazi and an older man recognised me as ''tou tsakou'' an expression i would have to start getting used to.  We passe4d the town of dispilio and i got my first glimpses of the city of  urlLink kastoria  itself. Perhaps i am biased coming from there, but there are a whole host of reasons why i believe that this is one of mainland greece's most beautiful cities, and i say one of not having the knowledge of a city more beautiful but realising that there is a chance that one exists.  As you approach the city from the east you see if resting along the side of a lake, lake orestias, the coty seems to occupy a hill facing due east and to its noth lies a large green mount beyond which the lake takes a run west.. however once you get into the town and climb some of those steep slopes... the true beauty of the location becomes (slowly) apparent. Lake orestias is a large basically round lake with a keyhole shaped peninsula piering into it from the western shore, the coty of Kastoria straddles this peninsula at its lower part with  large green knob of a mountain extending some way into the lake immediately next to it. Very hard to describe, but have a look at some of the pics and get your hands on a map, and if you are heading to greece, go have a look.   The city looks like an italian seaside or lake town, and building a town on such a peninsula obviously made practical sense in times when people rode around with spears and shields, a natural barrier to the marauding herds that have visited the area over the centuries. The green mount immediately next to the city is totally undeveloped and houses many byzantine, the fact that it hasnt been developed i think has more to do with greek laziness rather than an example of sound planning, it is quite steep and rugged and anybody who lived there would have to backtrack through the main part of the city to go anywhere anyway... but to be fair the locals pooh pooh this idea saying that the area is sacred and even building the road along the waters edge to allow people to more easily visit the churches was an enormously controversial move.  My bus journey ended at a large carpar at the city's edge, the view of the city and the surrounding mountains from here hadnt changed and i immediately remembered the many trips into kastoria i took with my older cousin diamandis holding my hand as we moved through the crowds of people at the bus station.  A short cab ride into ambelokipi was the last leg, the cabbie turned off the main road and down the main drag of the village, we passed my uncles taverna, now surrounded by other copy cats, turning the village into a bit of an evening hotspot, continued down the road to the main square and my family house which overlooks it... in fact in the years that have passed the square has been rather neglected so it is a good idea to overlook it all together. But as i expected the payout of the streets hadnt changed, the main road had come a lot closer to the village, the roads were now paved, the tree lined street on the outskirts of the village was gone but it was still immediately recognisable. My grandmothers simple 3 roomed house invited me in, the high roofs, the overhanging eaves, complete with the older style shingles, the basement and the double slanted doors that lead down into it, the old house in the property to the right which used to house my uncles pigs and other livestock when i was here last still standing but now not holding life of any kind, waiting for its time to return to the dirt which it has covered for almost a century.  I climbed the stairs and entered the house, calling my grandmothers name, i was earlier than i had throught, she may have been asleep, i pushed past the butcher stop style fly screen door as if i had just returned from a trip to the shops letting the plastic slap against the steel door, i walked into her kitchen, saw the bedsitter which she now preferred to sleep in, a wood stove, tv, table, dozens of photographs of me and my first cousins at various stages in our lives adorned most of the falt surfaces and the walls, some kitchy australian souvenirs including a coat of arms thermometer and 2 melbourne arts centre wall hangings. I looked through the other rooms but couldnt find my grandmother. I dropped my bags and sat on her bed to wait, her glasses, medication, salt and pepper shaker lay on the table in front of me, on a scrap of paper she had written my mobile phone number and the word ''Hristaki'' which is of course the way she would remember me, her little chris. A few moments later i heard some shuffling at the back door and my grandmother clear her throat, a sound she passed on to her son and he in turn passed on to me. I stood up walked slowly towards the door calling yiayia ... yiayia, this was home.  
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Shooting the shit with sav   Reunion achieved on Sunday afternoon, hugs exchanged, european style now as we are in a country where it is ok for guys to actually touch occasionally. Sav, Effie and I climbed into the back of their suitably dark coloured car and whisked ourselves off to a bar. And yes, I will say, a very nice bar, and not too far from aforementioned prison, but local knowledge wasnt within my possession, anyway, greatful to receive sea breezes comfy chairs and the posibility of receiving vodka the way i like it... orally... the afternoon and tales of travels washed over us.  We were joined by effies cousin marina and huby angele and wined and dined the evening away, they took us to a just right fair dinkum turkish restaurant in the burbs between central toilet athens and glyfada and a smashing night was had by all.  The following morning i sat in the bar of my prison drinking 4 euro espressos watching a german lady move into and out of the pool glancing occasionally at my phone to see if my friends had bothered to get off their asses. Note to self, dont wait in future, call em and wake the f**kers up.  Afternoon drive to posedionas in souli, fairly impressive cliff face relics but the walk through its centre which we had all hoped to see was no longer possible, we returned for frappe and club santouits in glyfada and headed off for more drinks and merriment.  The vodka was flowing freely, we were in a second storey bar looking over the impressive beach at vouluagmeni and I looked at my cardiac friend savva and for the first time really, being in the company of friends i know from back home, fully realised that it took time, effort and planning to be happy, even if there were points of bitterness studding that happiness. I raised my glass and not for the last time utterred "aint life shit"... all agreed and drank along for the ride.   Tuesday 8th July saw me on an 9:30 am flight from athens to thesalloniki, the trip to the airport being dogged by amaxing single lane traffic, athens is as i mentioned a toilet. Bid farewell to sav and effie at the terminal and headed off towards the olympic terminal which for romantic poetic licence purposes i will refer to as the gateway to my parents village, ampeolikipi kastoria, a place which i have large slabs of memory dedicated to all dated and wide lapelled as the last time i walked its streets was in june 1978.  I boarded the former crop duster which was to ferry me to salonica, watched the entire passenger corpus cross themselves and even saw somebody with a small single use parachute on her lap. I wasnt as well prepared, my bag contained a well thumbed but not finished copy of Italo Calvino "on a winters night a traveller" my camera and the paraphernalea you end up with when trying to get on a plane, i chose not to cross myself, realising that if we crash it would be me who would carry the bulk of the blame.  Despite these massive odds, we landed in salonica safely, the wait for the luggage to appear took almost as long as the flight itself. I burst out of the ever not so bustling salonica international airport to macedonian soil and sunshine.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       July 5th and 6th - Five star prison   My good friend Effie and I are wonderful sparring partners, she knows i love her, she doesnt know how much (yes this can be taken either way) but we rarely see eye to eye when it comes to... hmmm.... lets say commercial items.  For example, she refers to prada handbags as handbags, i refer to them as a corrupt economy or just laugh, she calls gucci loafers -  shoes whereas i refer to them as ... well refer to prada... So i did take her desription of the hotel she had teed up for me with several grains of salt.   The little hotel ,.. i think they had 110 rooms, 80% of which with sea views.  Simple breakfast ,.. well the only thing not 5 star about it was that you had to get it yourself, but there was pretty much any human from any ethnicity would need to survive.  Basic rooms  - Well they were ugly but had all the stuff humans from any ethnicity need to clean themselves and rest during their preferred hours.   The price  - yeah well, those were alarm bells ringing in my head not mid summer tests of sleigh bells.  But anyway, rest was what i wanted to do for the first 2 days of my stay before i was reunited with my dear buddies sav and effie, and lordy ... rest i did... vouliagmeni is ok if you want to hit the beach, but its fairly apparent to most who have shared a table with me that this isnt the highest possible priority for me.. and having little local knowledge i was able to unearth anything worth doing. My few walks of the hills overlooking the hour allowed for one postcard shot and the unearthing of a nearby supermarket which stocked everything a human being would need that wasnt otherwise stocked at the hotel. The owner of said super was a greek who had lived in sydney for 30 years, running delis and cafes in the sans souci area, had a nice chat about the celebrities and political figures that he could remember, including several "whatever happened to" segments which included a detailed description of his meeting with Paul Keating during those crazy sans souci days.  Comfortable, fed, rested, beach viewed, but imprisoned for the first time in my trip, i slept, ate, drank, watched, did i mention slept, MTV'd, late night porned my way through the next 48 hours until the moment that my friends returned from their uninterruptable visit to their borthplace.   Harsh aint i? 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Pisa to Athens   Friday July 4th early am, managed to sneak in a little breaky courtesy of the Le Torre family, receive a firm hand shake from Alfredo and administer a promise to return.   The travel to Pisa Aeroporto wasnt very eventful, chatted with an Alitalia pilot whilst in the check in queue at the airport, they have to queue up with the rest of the plebs if they arent actially flying a plane, something which he wasnt over the moon about, whinged about cuts in salary and benefits.. all this adding to the general im about to go into an airplane anxiety.  All went swimmingly at checkin, i did tell the girl that I was not going to return on the return leg and yes she gave me the same what the hell did you go and tell me that for kind of expression... shoot me for being nice.  Passing through the scanners at the departure lounge italian metal detector yeidling part time armani model made me remove my belt as it was the only metal object i had on my person but was upsetting his instruments. For a few seconds there i thought he was going to retain the belt, which concerned me as my pantaloons are becoming less pant and more loon as my trip progresses, but after some more purposeful scanning and examination by the guy behind the glass it was handed back to me without protest.  Underpants safely covered and chance of performing impromptu calvin klein underwear model poses greatly diminished i waited to board the plane to roma. Pisa is a small but reasonably busy airport, so you are ferried to and from planes via thoe big wide beautiful tarmac buses, this still didnt stop people pushing in front of you when it came to getting through the gate and onto the bus. Once guy actually protested that he was in front of me, i replied with "absolutamente principessa!" and let him through, the super clever, a club which i will join the next time i pass through such airports sat about waiting for everyone to board the bus and then made their way through the gates.  Flight to rome, no real incident, passage through rome, also smooth, absolutely no customs formalities to deal with, a few scanners some passport waving but no stamping of any sort of offical seal. One source whilst awaiting departure in rome was a group of peasants who were going back to there q goat village, one young lad within this group was carrying a 1980s style VHS video recorder and was attempting to ever so sneakily video tape some form of sculptured blonde model type who was quietly looking for herself in a copy of Vogue. The fact that 2 people had to support him while he was in super stealth voyeur mode and that the machine made so much noise that the security personnel kept casting concerned glances his way didnt reduce his joy at succesfully capturing more prey on his 180 min long play TDK.  Flight to athens, yeah, we got there, landed at about 3:00pm very very hot, in the city that most greeks love to hate.  I spent over 2 months in italy, witnessed the occasional incident that the tourist guides watn you about, pickpockets, baggage thieves, shonky accomodation peddlers... within 20 minutes in Greece i had covered all the options. 1 guy tried to steal the used tissues i had left in the open pocket on my backpack, luckily i managed to watch him for 10 seconds whilst he pretended to be scratching his leg. Several guys selling accomodation, one guy came up to me and started speaking to me in greek apologising for being late and saying the car is this way... nice try sunshine.  And I was still in the customs area!  Outside i got myself a good blast of athens polluted hot air and joined the rapidly moving but enormous queue for cabs, as i approached it from the wrong side there was some dispute that erupted between 3 or 4 cab drivers, apparently one of them had order a medium frappe with milk and was given a bendy straw rather than a straight straw as is the tradition from his village. I neared just as fist hit face and two hugging cab drivers tripped over the curb towards back pack carrying chris. I fell under them, several others joined in, one of the guys who "manages" the taxi queue came over and asked if i was ok, as soon as i spoke half a word of greek, the concerned look he was trained to use in such moments was replaced with the more common, "go to hell" glaze that greeks share between themselves. I got up checked to see if I had left any limbs behind and joined the queue.  In a B Grade movie I would purely by chance become a passenger in the taxi of one of the purpotraters of the above act,.. close but no cigar. I stood in the middle of the road, threw my pack into the back seat and sat in the front, saying the usual niceties to the driver, in greek, even asking him if it was ok for me to sit in front, in greek, which i dont think is a standard tourist phrase book comment, told him i wanted to go to vouliaymeni... again.. not a standard tourist response... yet it took him about 10 minutes of bumper to bumper oppressive heat traffic to ask "ellinika omilas?" yes i replied.  Athens is a toilet, more correctly athens was a toilet, now it is a toilet whose walls, floor, ceiling and entire toilet making experience is being reconstructed, adorned with olympic rings and given new names. My driver dived down dirt roads trying to find the most experience crammed journey to my destination. After we had gotten to know each other (cough) he even took me on a detour of a very nice beach where all the "mora" hang out, he even stopped for a quick chat, had he asked me how i take my frappe i would have glanced at the meter, but alas he realised he had a traditional role to perform and eventually after pulling the faulty meter manouvre, dropped me in front of my resort style hotel near the beach of vouliaymeni.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Pisa - The things tourists stop to look at   Feeling at leat a little better and with the "you are in italy" meter ticking ever louder I decided to indulge in that great tourist with a plan activity "the day trip", several options were available, but as i would have to do a reasonably early morning passage through its centre I figured going to Pisa would help achieve two goals.  Oh the things I saw in Pisa.  I am starting to learn how to read your run of the mill "Lets go" style tourist guides. Find the write up on the largest town in the area you are in, go straight to the back pages and read the "day trips" section,.. get your ass to one of those day trip places, pick the one with the most difficuly to understand instructions or that require a connecting bus or train and the words "infrequent service" within its description and stay there for several days making the large city the "day trip"  The piazza that contains the leaning tower of pisa is so appropriately named, miracles occur there every day as busload after busload land in this pointless dirty little town with really nothing of any spiritual or inspirational interest and take photos of an engineering error and ooh and ahh.  Dont go to pisa, if you want to see mistakes, go down to your nearest factory seconds outlet and marvel at jeans with malfunctioning zippers, shoes with mismatched stitching, stand in front of a pair or boxer shorts whose colours have run and get your friend to take a picture, stick that in your album, just dont go to pisa, skip it, go somewhere else.  I shant go on, trust me my camera stayed well and truly tucked in my bag during the 6 or 7 hours i was dragged away from Lucca.  Dont go to pisa, get the t-shirt.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Lucca - Soak it up while you can boy   On Monday I sorted out my travel plans to Greece, flying direct from Milan to Salonica was the best option but due to something which nobody was able to adequately explain to me, tickets for this journey were approximately 560 euro one way. A visit to the travel agent and some explanation of the nuances of the way that airline ticketing works in this country meant than i walked out with tickets from Pisa to Rome and Rome to Athens at about 200 euro, these were return tickets, but i was not going to return,.. the one way tickets cost twice as much as the return tickets (that makes sense) and some poor sod would miss out on a flight from athens to rome because they had allocated a seat for my ass even though I would be several hundred kilometres away in a village.  I asked the travel agent chick whether i should tell them that I am not going to come back on the return flight. She fired back the bloody tourists stare and said "why do you want to do that?" Why indeed.  The rest of my time in Lucca was spent revisiting the places I liked, some of the benches along the wall, where you could sit, read, write, sleep and enjoy the breeze and shade, the tower and its not torturous 300 step climb, puccini's piazza and birthplace, although not a massive fan of the guys work, i really liked the statue in the piazza, which is simply the man sitting in a typical parisienne style cafe chair with one leg crossed over the other.  I also spent time with some new friends, at the segafreddo and of course my new buddies at Trattoria Gigi.   Time was ticking away, my flight was scheduled for July 4th, not my first choiuce of date for air travel but its done now, no point in dwelling on it.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       July 2003 - Bitsa   Bitsa is old, well she is now anyway, bitsa is also the town gossip merchant, political activist, cultural advocate and she walks with a really big stick.. which as we all now demands respect.  Bits if she ever stood up straight would be taller than she is bent over, but bitsa is as bitsa is and wel love her curved up ball of a self. I heard a clear crisp heavily macedonia accented voice booming across my grandmaothers back yad early on a day which felt like a sunday.  I looked across her window and saw her arm stretched up in the air peeking over the top of a row of string beans... her hand clutched a walking stick easily a foot taller than her curvy fine self, and she waddled her way through the town, recognising people as they approached by the sound of the shoes and the type of shit that coated them.  I love bitsa, for many many reasons... but it was the way she spoke, the way she structured her sentences, her mix of very modern and ancient cultural reference within the one mixed metaphor that will have her with me for ever.  I started writing down some of the things she said one day and rapidly realised that this wouldnt be necessary as the level of repetition of theme was so intense that she could probably develop a new learning method, write a book adn be rich beyond her wildest dreams... her wildest dreams would probably mean having about 300 euro more than her phone bill, which she carried with her everywhere in case anybody wished to discuss it further.. they often did.  here is a typical conversation, my grandmother plays the role of grandmother and bitsa, and old hand at playing ... herself.  I see bitsa through my grandmothers kitchen window... my grandmother is in her chair starung at the spot on the wall opposite that she has been so captivated with lately. B. Saddam! my grandmother doesnt respond B. Saddam!!! still nothing from my grandmother... but she sees her walk past the back door. G. ah... bitsa is here again,.. shes going to bust me about something again... hopefully its not lazaro... Lazaro is... ahh... let let bitsa explan. B. Saddam.. dove sei yes bitsa speaks italian... she knows how to ask where you are but if you were to respond in italian she wouldnty have a clue what you were saying.. she actually thinks shes speaking german... maybe she is. G bitsa, im in here, come in...  she will anyway. Bitsa emerges cane first and sits down at my grandmothers table... i sit on the divan opposite her, she sees me out of the corner of an upturned eye... i must have ben upside down to her... but thats normal... for both of us. B. saddam hussein,.. ah saddam hussein... the americans are still looking for you, but you are safe here they wont find you. My grandmother has been dubbed the saddam hussein of the village by bitsa, dont tell colOn powell. G. whats happening bitsa. B did lazaro come and see you? G again with the lazaro... who is lazaro bitsa!!? B he will come, he told me he will come and you should tell him. G tell him what? B huh?  Bitsa wasnt deaf she just was keen to make sure details were clarified... at least incoming details anyway.  G Lazaro!!! tell him what... what do you want me to tell him? B did he come? G who? B Lazaro!!!! G. there isnt anyone called lazaro bitsa, who are you talking about? B i say him yesterday, he was asking me and i said you have to talk to athina he said he would come. G. yes good but who is he? B Lazaro... i spoke to him yesterday. G what did you speak to him about bitsa! B huh?  now i was begging my grandmother not to bite, but shes hasnt seen enough abbott and costello to see it coming.  G Lazaro!!! B. ah... you told him? G no bitsa, i dont know what you are talking about, there is nobody called lazaro in this town, i dont know anybody called lazaro. B hmmm for 10 years... and he has never asked for a cent... not once... not ever... 12 years... never asked for a cent not ever. G who asked for a cent... for what? B once a year he comes and pays me the rent,.. i see him every year at the same time around now... october  yes it was august.  G. are you talking about Lefteri Bitsa? The boy that works your orchard? B. every year he pays rent never asked for any money.  Bitsa crosses herself for reasons im not sure of.  G. bitsa his name is Lefteri not lazaro,... why do you call him lazaro. B. did lazaro come... good... i told you to tell him... you did the right thing! G. i didnt speak to anybody bitsa ... about what! B. your grandson .. he doesnt care about you... all he wants is the land... dont give it to him... lazaro will work it and pay you. G. yeah yeah good. B. hmm you listen to me. stick a 10 drachma piece on your tit and see how many people come around pretending to want milk! G. oh bitsa lefteri you are talking about lefteri, he came around months ago. B well hes coming back, i spoke to him yesterday, he came to pay me, he'll come.  she looked towards the door and i almost expected this two headed farmer to walk in the door,... and suddenly... he didnt.  This went on for some time... bitsa moving between descriptions of conversations with lazaro, her income stream and the likelihood of my grandmother receiving visitors  She would repeat the issues but never quite word for word, things would slightly change, expressions, dates, the amount of money my grandmother should stick to her tit. After an elegant sufficiency she would mount her walking stick again and drag herself out of the room, my grandmother would normally need a lie down after she left.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>