<Blog>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        s: mommy, ang sakit ng paa ko. bakit masakit yung paa ko? m : kasi kinagat ka ng langgam s : eh bakit ako kinagat ng langgam m: eh kasi dirty yung feet mo s : eh bakit dirty yung feet ko? m: hindi kasi hindi ka naka slippers s : eh bakit kinagat m : kasi akala nya yung dirt sa paa mo, food, kaya kinagat s : eh bakit masakit?   sam has been asking so much questions lately. from why ants bite her feet to why i am her mommy. it amazes me how she never  runs out of questions that we oftentimes end up with her first question.  and for some reason, i look forward to each question she'll ask and treat it as some sort of exercise... reasoning exercise.  it's like our own version of a conversation.   time flies fast these days that soon i'll be having "girly"  conversations with her and then "career" conversations and then "women" conversations. i know we'll have lots to talk about and that our conversations will never end that there will never be enough time to talk about everything we want to talk about.  i'd be happy for that day to come. but right now, i'm content with "our conversations".  s: mommy? bakit kita mommy? m : =)
     

    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      friday is definitely the best day in the week. for some reason, i wear my better clothes on a friday. when bestfriend was here, friday is "our day". now, though, bestfriend is not here, friday is still special...i loooove friday because...  ... i can stay up late tonight ... i get to wake up late tomorrow ... people are more free spirited and you can feel it ... i can relax at work (i'm a believer of don't-start-anything-you-can't-finish-today-anyway) ... and for crying out loud, it's the last day at the office  yeah, i've had BETTER fridays than today. before, fridays meant looong and faaar lunches with my absi friends...it meant survivor and american idol...it meant movies and the fort and g4 and mega with bestfriend... it meant fun fun fun...  things sure have changed but a friday will always be a friday to me. it kind of...restarts or ends the cycle (depends on how you look at it). life has been a routine and friday is my refresher. it reminds me that however difficult the week maybe, a friday will always come and save my sanity.  so what else can i say? thank God it's FRIDAY! 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i sooo miss that feeling . it has been a year since i had it and it changed my life. hehehe. no seriously, it's like falling in love the first time. it makes you feel excited. when you think of it you'll experience how it is to sleep smiling and wake up with the same smile. it's amazing. really amazing. it brightens your morning and completes your day. it stirs up all kinds of emotions... love, envy, anger, lust. it occupies your mind and takes all your worries away.  haaaay....i sooo miss hana yori dango.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm sooo jologs lately that i sometimes amuse myself.   last night, after a two hour shopping. note: for me shopping doesn't  necessary mean ending up with stuff you bought most of the time it  means attempting to buy stuff and (for some reason) ending buying  nothing at all.   anyway, i felt really exhausted and hungry, that when i passed  by  Hansarap  at the MRT station, the 10-peso lugaw looked like  the most delectable lugaw i have ever seen.  i hurriedly lined up the turo-turo and ordered that tempting lugaw plus tokwa't baboy with free gulaman for 16 bucks. after getting my food,  i sat beside an old woman who looked as hungry and as harassed as i am. sweating, i devoured on the hot food on our small red table. pouring all the tokwa't baboy on the cup and overfilling it, i wanted to laugh at myself  for what the sight that i was. i don't remember finishing a cup of  hot lugaw that fast in my entire life.   after swallowing the last spoonful of lugaw and my  mouth barely wiped, i rushed to the trains and participated in the everyday  mrt wrestlemania . whew. as i saw my reflection at the train's glass walls i couldn't help but smile. i looked pathetic but i had a great time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      whew! it's finally friday tomorrow!! my favorite day of the week. today has been...let's just say...a lot better than the last 3 days.first, because i finally got my last pay from my former employer and second, work has been more manageable. i really miss life in absi. as another absi alumnae said, it is in absi where you can earn money the easiest way. i miss the royal jamaican patty (my fave is beef jerky) i used to buy almost every morning. i miss working while watching cable...i mean...watching while working...hehe..i miss the loooong lunches with the loooong coffee breaks...that was really fun...and i definitely miss the people. i think, the best thing in absi is the people, sadly, a lot of them is now gone already...which, in more ways than one, prompted me to follow suit. but then, as i read from another blog, you can only grow through change. so here i am, on a totally different show playing a totally different role. honestly, not once did i ponder if i made the right decision and not once did i realize that i am missing a lot. but slowly, i realize how i have changed and became better in such short time.  so what happened there? i was actually planning to write something refreshing because of the good news about the money and here i am going all mushy and reflective...this is what i hate about blogging...it brings out the stuff that shouldn't be out in the first place.   
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;today i'm missing a big part of sam's life. i'm missing her first day in school. it pains me like hell to leave for the office when sam in about to enter a new stage in her very young life. i will always wonder, how it would be like. to dress her up , prepare her things, send her to school and watch how she is with other kids. will she say her name when asked? will she fight with her seatmate? will she like her baon? how many stars will she get? here i am in some office in makati, waiting for the 5th hour. now i would have to content myself with stories of how her first day in school was and traces of star on her hand. argh. life sucks big time.    
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it has been exactly 27 days, 6 hours and 17 minutes since arizona took my bestfriend away from me. here's just but a few reasons why things are not what they used to be : i miss the endless talks about anything and nothing. i miss how we analyze and dissect every single movie we watch. i miss the three of us. i miss his smell. i miss his hair. i miss how he carries his dirty old lunch bag. i miss our fights. i miss greenbelt and the fort (and go nuts donuts) and up. i miss how he sings maroon 5 songs as if they're his own. i miss watching initial-d with him and sam. i miss the happy tree friends. i miss holding his hand while he's driving. i miss feeding him while he's driving. i miss mcdo drive thru in nlex. i miss dreaming with him. i miss how i was when i'm with him. i miss his shoulders. i miss him. sigh.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i miss you 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      first. it's a monday. speaks for itself. second. the traffic at nlex is just terrible. third. the driver driving the fucking van got fucking summoned by the fucking mmda police. fourth.the mrt was flooded with a swarm of people ready to kill for a fucking mrt space. fifth. the fx line at buendia was looong...not that i was expecting things to get better at that point. sixth. as if i haven't had enough police crap for the day, again, the driver driving the fucking fx got fucking summoned by the fucking mmda police. seventh. had trouble at the office.in deep shit. neck on the line. all nervous and wrecked. eighth. and definitely the most unexpected. after telling somebody I wished he was here to ease up all these, he tells me that he's sorry but it's my fault.   and to think that it isn't 5 o'clock yet. life sucks. big time. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       sino ba naman ang mag aakala na ikaw pala... ikaw pala na payatot at tibak na tibak... ikaw na masungit at parang matandang binata... ikaw na striktong nagbabantayat nagpapaalis sa ECR... ikaw pala... ang magiging pinakaimportanteng tao sa buhay ko...    sino ba naman ang mag aakala na dahil sa isang SM City sale ay makikita kita  "in a different light."  mantakin mo yon...sweet ka pala. masarap kausap. hindi masungit at lalong hindi parang matandang binata. at higit sa lahat  gets  mo ko. gets mo? sabi nga sa philo1 we have the same language game.    parang kapag kasama kita pwede kong mag mura...pwedeng umutot...o kaya tumahimik na lang basta...galing mo nga eh...you bring out the me in me...    tapos yun na...with you everything feels right...effortless and free flowing.    kaya nga pag may friend ako na hurt in love...sinasabi ko parati...kung sya na yun...everything will fall into place...naturally...walang complications...    hindi ako naniniwala sa soulmates the way other people define it...na parang hindi sila nag aaway,iisa ng paborito, iisa ng pag iisip. more often than not magkaiba pa nga tayo ng point of view pero if a soul mate is defined as someone who complements you and your soul...someone who does not necessarily have to think like you but respects how you think...baka maniwala pa ko...kasi alam kong ikaw yon.    Ikaw na nga si Mr. Right (for me).&nbsp;  &nbsp;&nbsp;  *&nbsp;  Tangina ang mushy.  &nbsp;&nbsp;  &nbsp;   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it was three years ago when bestfriend and i went to see Atlantis, the Disney movie, at SM City not knowing that the next day would be the start of the best days of our lives.   with a belly so big you'd wonder how i was able to walk, i prepared the  munggo  which was our baon for lunch that day. the plan was to visit our OB and head to work. but all hell broke lose when the doc said i'll be delivering the baby that day. i thought, wow...really? today? are you sure? where's the tremendous pain every one was ranting about? this was too easy than i expected. well... that was what i thought until 5 hours later.  having heard the news, we went to the office to...guess what...file my maternity leave. everybody who knew i'd be having a baby later and saw me all smiles and filing my maternity leave were either baffled or scared. Scared for me that is.  and the nightmare began, excuses to all singles and virgins out there...but the pain...can i just tell you that the freakin pain was just unimaginable. i mean, i have psychologically prepared myself of the greatest pain i can imagine but no...oh no...when i say unimaginable...i mean it.  and then she came, no, there was no "pang-tender-care-baby-powder" scene, where the mom would touch the baby's finger and tears will just roll down her eyes. actually, the first time i saw her, i still couldn't believe she's mine. i read in books that a mother has to talk to her new born to bond them but honestly, i felt awkward doing it. i just talk to her in my mind where nobody has to hear. our first conversations were like that...and now...we just couldn't stop talking.  happy birthday sam and thank you for giving me a purpose. that is, to be a friend and a mother to you. and i thank Him for making it all happen. and when you read this, say...five or six years from now...remember that mommy wants you to be happy all the time.   note. the title of the article is what we should have named sam had we not changed our minds at the last minute. 	  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my eyes want to shut. my back hurt. i want to sleep. i want to rest.  good thing it's already friday. for the past 8 weeks of my life there are two things i miss the most. one is having bestfriend  around and the other, sleep. A five hour sleep these days  is already a luxury for there is just so much to do. been quite busy with work and sam being sick and then there's her upcoming birthday party. but i can't complain. i'd have to say those waking hours are hours well spent...really. but then there remains the fact that i am still a human...with all its limits and vulnerabilities...  i sometimes wonder why God made do with just 24 hours a day. i mean, it's just not enough. if only he made it 30 or 32 maybe... then i'd..   ...read a new book for it's been a while since i last read one ...watch a two hour movie on cable ...have longer conversations with my sis and mom ...write ...draw ...play more games and read more books with sam ...plan for a business concept ...study reading and speaking Jap ...work out with Billy Blank's Taebo VCDs ...clean our room ...have some sort of beauty ritual or something ...comb my hair more often ...go shopping ...take pictures  believe me, i can go on till midnight listing the things i want to do but can't. oh well, enough of that, my optimistic self mumbles something like being thankful for what i have or something to that effect. ok ok i'll shut up. which reminds me, lately i've been getting confused on what and  how i should look at things. one moment i'm all frustrated of how things went and another minute i realize it's selfish thinking that way. Talk about self censorship on the mental level.   something tells me this is not good and that i'm thinking too much and that i should stop writing already.   "All night Hearing voices telling me  that I should get some sleep Because tomorrow might be good for something"  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>