<Blog>

<date>18,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        PAYDAY    It's payday, YEA!!!!. Happy Happy Joy Joy, Happy Happy Joy Joy, yes it is payday, and even after I pay the 2 bills I have I will still have a substantial amount leftover to spend, hehehehe.  Well I gotta go  Ta Ta for Now  
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Robbie Williams    I'm litening to the new   urlLink Robbie Williams  cd  urlLink Escapology  and it is really good, great vocals and music, I would recommend it to anyone who likes Robbie Williams.   
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Morning all  I downloaded a new tool called  urlLink w.bloggar  v3.00 and it is a really cool tool to use, it lets you edit all your posts locally and then you can upload them to blogger 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       For a little fun, head on over to  urlLink Emode , they have all kinds of tests, fun ones and serious ones.   Ta Ta for Now 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Games   Well it seems Rockstar Games is giving away Grand Theft Auto for the pc all you have to do is go to the website and sign up, they give you a link and then it yours, only slight problem is the size of the game, it is a 330 meg download, so all you 56kers out there, better find your geek friend with a cable modem to get it for you.   urlLink http://www.rockstargames.com/classics/    
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Well..   As usual I am at work doing something else other than working, I am working on my blog, this will be my home from now on and I might just mirror this onto the other site I use, I don't know yet, I still want to keep it around.  Ta Ta for Now 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Testing 1 2 3 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Hehehe   Well I think I will now start blogging here, I was using another site, but it lacked some features, mainly the feature to edit my blogs template which was the biggest for me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        This is a test  
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Good Morning!   Well I have 3 websites for ya if you want to find something funny or sometimes gross on the web  1)  urlLink MadVille  2)  urlLink Zug  3)  urlLink Fark   These are all great sites to visit and to laugh your ass off.  Ta Ta for Now  
    
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
         Time for a Change 
</post>

<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Wow   I haven't posted all weekend, well it is becuase I usually do not get on the 'puter for very long on the weekend is why, I mostly try to live in the flesh and blood world, not the cyberworld, but soon they will be merged and be one in the same, hopefully within the next 10 years or so.  No links right now, maybe later after I get home.  Ta Ta for Now  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Hi   Things are working weird, well maybe it's just me, lets find out, sooo away weeee go..    
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Test 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       This is a test.   
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Test  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
        Test   This is a test. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        hi there,   been awhile I know, but it happens. I got a new car, it is a 1992 Cadillac El Dorado, this car is sooooo sweet, my grnadmother owned it before me and kept it in perfect condition, she had everthing done by the dealer she bought it from.     I will also be moving soon to a much better place, it might even be a little closer to my house, I'll let ya know after I move there.  I had a little medical scare oh last week or so, I had been suffering from this headache, and I thought, well it felt like the headaches I would get when my blood pressure was really high, and I had been going through a lot of that lately, so I made an appointment, and the doctor said my blood pressure was undr control, but he did give me some pain pills for my headaches, he also had me get some blood drawn and x-rays of my chest, he is also talking about getting a ct scan of my head, but my insurance company needs to approve it first.  Gotta get back to work, later 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well I am trying out an online game, it is Star Wars Galaxies.  Now this seems like a pretty sweet game, much better than sims, and everquest in my opinion, well its at least science fiction whic is much better than fantasy.  The character creation is pretty nice, not everyone has to be beautiful, you can be a gross fat overweight looking thing with tattoos and horns all over your head, or be hairy all over, yes you can be a wookie, haven't tryed this out for a character. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well I got the results of the ct scan of my chest. It was negative, they then went over the x-ray and decided it was a shadow.  What a bunch of freaking morons, they scare the crud out of me for 2 weeks, I was thinking the worst, ohh great I have cancer, sheesh.   Dave  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>