<Blog>

<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    "The Beginning Part One" aired last night on  urlLink Cartoon Network  in the  urlLink Toonami  block. Was it an improvement on the original, well I can't say any thing about the plot yet because it hasn't gone any where yet.   The animation is a huge improvement using the style first made popular by  urlLink Batman: The Animated Series   and most recently  in  urlLink Justice League . Still with the improvement to the animation the is much lacking in this recent remake. Fans of the series have grown up and are ready for ah well shall I say a much darker Eternia.  On the other hand the voice acting while not as horrid as the original series is still a disgrace to the He-Man franchise.  I still love the fact that  urlLink Cartoon Network  has brought back  urlLink The Masters of the Universe  given all it's short comings I still give it a 4 out of 5
     

        
</post>

<date>07,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I've finaly finnished Lord Tenchi's Blog after two weekends of work. Check out the board for the latests on my Gnomedex videos and photo album links. I should have David and Leo's rendision of "You Don't Bring Me Flowers, Anymore" up in the next few days.
     

        
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Can't find that perfect card try  urlLink Cynical Greeting Cards!   Send 'em to those you love, those you hate, and those you love to hate!   urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>08,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      So you thought you were to good for Poke'mon. How fast we forget that you collected the same thing as a kid the only difference was yours only came in one color, Pink. That was until they came out with the colored versions.  Thats right M.U.S.C.L.E.s Millions of Unusual Small Creatures Lurking Everywhere. I stumbled across this site tonight while wandering the net  urlLink M.U.S.C.L.E. Revisited . They've got all 233 figures in detail.   Only a few of mine survived moving around the country as a kid. Who knows with the popularity of bringing back 80's toys maybe these will be the next we'll see on the store self.           Name  : Dinky Data Dookie    Number  : 138   Description  : Here's a cheery little fella. Dinky Data Dookie loves it when opponents try to punch him on the chest, because it just makes the keyboard type letters on his face. Then the opponent is distracted by what letters appear on Dinky's face, and that's when they're most vulnerable. Dinky also loves to do &quot;The Dinky Dance&quot;, which was a move that Michael Jackson later stole from him and renamed &quot;The Moonwalk&quot;. Dinky hates Michael Jackson for that.    
     

        
</post>

<date>22,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Don't you hate it when you lock your keys in your car? I do. Saturday morning locked my keys in my Explorer.  I tried to unlock it, I made my own slimjim wedged the door from the window and finally had the lock moving when the window shattered. Talk about sucking.
     

        
</post>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I've tried mozilla on an off now for the last year and it done ok but, it's nowhere close to I.E. 6. pages still don't render correctly  it loads extremely slow, customization was limited at best and, worst of all some DUMB ASS decided that I don' need a Home button.   But there may be hope after all that some day there may be another browser that can co-exist with Internet Explorer. A browser that loads just as fast, has customizable tool bars, and doesn't come bloated with all sorts of extras like chat, e-mail and, oh yeah Sign up for  AOL NOW!  What is this browser you may ask Opera, no. Netscape, no. Mozilla, well kinda. Its form the Mozilla org project and uses the mozilla code, just allot less of it.  Now I know it's not a replacement for I.E. but hey it's a start.  urlLink Phoenix 0.1 
     

        
</post>

<date>27,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Tonight, well I guess it would be yesterday now. My room mate meat this girl from out of town and she agreed to set him up with friend so I got stuck with the other girl he meet.   I had no intentions of enjoying the night after meeting this girl the week before when Chad, my room  mate brought her home just smashed of some cheap ass Vodka, you know the kind that comes in the plastic bottle and the plane label. Well while she was here he told her he'd set me up with her if he got her a date and that's not even the worst of it. Every day for the last week she's been hounding me on instant messenger, witch I can' stand to begin with. I tried to be rood to her so she'd go away with out ignoring her completely bu I guess she never got the hint.  So anyway they come over Friday after I get home from work and we go up to Chucky Cheese and eat and I run in to one of the guys I work with so the trip wasn't a complete waist, not to mention the fact that I avoided her most of the night.  Later when we got back to my place Chad thought it would be a good if we played a drinking game. Boy, was he ever wrong! First of all the girl he was with spent the whole night sucking on the same bottle of  Mike's Hard Lemonade. And, second the girl that I got stuck with gets just plaster drinking mixed drinks and decides to start hanging on me. Finally both of us had enough and managed to get out of the house and hid around back of the house. After about  fifteen minuets of this, not to mention pulling the breaker to the house they came out side looking for us and we were able to get back inside the house and ran to the basement grabbing the door knob, which had fallen off a few weeks earlier and locking our selves in. There the two of us spent the next half hour arguing though the door. Finally the girl that my room mate was with had one of her friends came and picked her up. Umfortunatly the other one was suck behind. Once every thing had calmed down I though all her stuff of my room and tied the door shut.   With nothing else to do stuck in my room I turned on Cartoon Network and started to blog.  PS Happy birthday  urlLink Chris . How cool is that to share your birthday with Google.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,September,2002</date>
<post>


           
        It's 2 A.M. and I just got back from Oktoberfest and let me say tonight went far better than last night.  Oktoberfest is kind of a big thing here in La Crosse. It's a week long celebration that starts on with the Maple Leaf Parade and ends the next weekend with the Torch Light  Parade. My old roommate from college showed up Saturday and a few friends of mine met down at the South Side Fest Grounds at about 6. We promptly found our way to the beer garden and got a few pitchers of some fine Wisconsin beer and one of my favorite  urlLink Leinenkugel's . Even though the ten dollars per pitcher was quite steep, and that's ten dollars American if any Canadian's happen to be reading this, they did have a fine German polka band where I learned that the  proper German beer toast or "rrroast" is not pronounced ziggy sacky witch was so basterdised by The Man Show, but diggy sacky, pardon my spelling. After about five pitchers we made our way though the rain to the bars downtown were I ran into a friend from work in the line at Brothers so he joined our party for bar hopping.  Overall I'd say the night was quite the hoot!
     

        
</post>

<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    Ever once in a while you come across something on the net that' just damn funny.  Actually I found this a few month ago but for some reason one of those Apple ads made me think of it again.     
     

        
</post>

<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink    I got my new digital camera Friday and man does it take some sweet ass pictures. It is far better than any of the other digital cameras I've had in the past l. Sure it maybe it's because it's the first one that I've actualy spent any substantial amount of money on. I first had a chance to use one at Gnomedex II last August where I got a chance to use Richard Woo's Canon Powershot S200 Digital ELPH. I had been watching the price on Amozon for a while now and after a $100 price drop in the last two months I figured it was time to buy my own.
     

        
</post>

<date>10,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Man I hate the klez virus. for the last few weeks I've been getting hammered by some moron infected by the klez.h virus. for the last week or so I've been trying to track the bastard down. I figure in couple of days I should have their entire address book.  Tonight they managed to slip trough my fingers but I have a much better lead on who it is. It's actually the first time mail server error with their IP three minutes after it was sent,  so I quick telneted into my modem banks and did a show all conn but by that time they were already logged off. Son of a....!
     

        
</post>

<date>13,October,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Maybe it's to early to wright about to night but I might as well try  while I still remember some of it. Where should I start, While I guess First we met up with room mates X-girlfriend, Who has put on at least a hundred pounds. And we went downtown La Crosse bar war hopping. My guess is to run in to our friends bachelorette party? Well that never happened. we hung out downtown at the "Library", yes it's a bar and started drinking there. After  a few minutes a few a my friends from..  Got to go check the pizza.  Ok so where was I, oh yes I ran  in to some of my friends from high school which was pretty cool. We hung out for the the rest of the night aboot four hours when after my room mate had left us we left us we went down the street to some bar that I hadn't been to before, this is where a perfectly good night goes to hell. Well we walk in the bar and their playing the theme to Smokey and the Bandit, ok seeing I probably like that movie better than most people.  Eating pizza.  So any way as so as they started playing the next song I knew where I was and completely flipped out. Where was I you ask yes that's wright the worst place one can imagine a county bar.   Nothing worse than listening to hey seed music man can that crap fuck up a good night.
     

        
</post>

<date>17,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Ok here's the  urlLink photos  form last months party I hope your happy.
     

        
</post>

<date>20,November,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I'm still here even though I bolged in a while. I guess its becauses I've been buissy lately but more likely its the fact that I'm just lazy.
     

        
</post>

<date>04,December,2002</date>
<post>


           
      Last week I bought Battle Field 1942 and man does that game rock. But, theirs always some asshole that's got to be screwing around shooting their own planes when they appear on the runway or throwing dynamite on the ground and detonating it to see how far they can launch them self up in the air. And if I ever find out who Default_Player_Name is I swear I'm going to KICK YOUR ASS!!!
     

        
</post>

<date>15,December,2002</date>
<post>


           
      I'm not sure what got into my cat this morning but think he was trying to take a crap but he couldn't. When I herd him start crying it must have been about 5 A.M. and I got up to see what was the matter. I found him running circles around the house and then sit in the litter box then go running around the house again this must have went on for about 15 minutes before he finaly got the damn thing out.
     

        
</post>

<date>05,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Last week I scored a ticket to the Packers Falcons game in Green Bay. I left with my co-worker Jason Saterday morning at eight o'clock for the four hour drive across the state. after checking in to our hotel room and stoping to eat lunch we got to the stadium around One. When we arived we still had about six hour before game time and after a quick stop at the Packer Pro Shop to pick up two cheader heads for the game we headed over to the Stadium View to have a few beers or to be more accurate alot of beer.     urlLink Photos 
     

        
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>


           
          I found this over on  urlLink This Modern World , apparently it's the latest in jPOP.
     

        
</post>

<date>27,February,2003</date>
<post>


           
      It's a beautiful day in this neighborhood, A beautiful day for a neighbor. Would you be mine? Could you be mine?...  It's a neighborly day in this beauty wood, A neighborly day for a beauty. Would you be mine? Could you be mine?...  I've always wanted to have a neighbor just like you. I've always wanted to live in a neighborhood with you.  So, let's make the most of this beautiful day. Since we're together we might as well say: Would you be mine? Could you be mine? Won't you be my neighbor? Won't you please, Won't you please? Please won't you be my neighbor?  Fred McFeely Rogers (1928-2003) 
     

        
</post>

<date>10,March,2003</date>
<post>


           
      Tonight the anti-drug ads linking drugs to terrorist and I don't understand why. I thought that the last time they did this after the 9-11 incident they got all sort of crap about the false ads. And what's even more confusing is that the 9-11 attacks were mostly funded by the diamond trade wouldn't that make every one that bought a piece of jewelry terrorist.
     

        
</post>

<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>


           
      1. You've ever ended a sentence with the word "PSYCHE". 2. You watched the Pound Puppies. 3. You can sing the rap to the "Fresh Prince of Bel Air" 4. You wore biker shorts under your skirt and felt stylish. 5. You yearned to be a member of the Baby-sitters club and tired to start a club of your own. 6. You owned those lil Strawberry Shortcake scented dolls. 7. You know that "Whoa" comes from Joey on Blossom. 8. Two words: M.C. Hammer 9. If you ever watched "Fraggle Rock". 10. You had a banana seat bike. 11. You can sing the entire theme song to "Duck Tales". 12. When it was actually worth getting up early on a Saturday to watch cartoons. 13. You wore a pony tail on the side of your head. 14. You saw the original "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles" on the big screen. 15. You got super-excited when it was Oregon Trail day in computer class at school. 16. You made your Mom buy one of those clips that would hold your shirt in a knot on the side. 17. You played the game "MASH" (Mansion, Apartment, Shelter, House) with friends at school. 18. You wore Jordache Jean jacket and you were proud of it. 19. L.A. Gear..... 20. You wanted to change your name to "JEM" in Kindergarten. 21. You remember reading "Tales of a fourth grade nothing" and all the Ramona books. 22. You know the profound meaning of "WAX ON, WAX OFF" 23. You wanted to be a Goonie. 24. You ever wore fluorescent clothing. 25. You can remember what Michael Jackson looked like before his nose fell off. 26. You have ever pondered why Smurfette was the only female smurf. 27. You took Lunch Pales to school. 28. You remember the CRAZE, then the BANNING of slap bracelets. 29. You still get the urge to say "NOT" after every sentence. 30. You remember Hyper color T-shirts. 31. Barbie and the Rockers was your favorite band. 32. You thought She-ra and He-Man should hook up. 33. You thought your childhood friends would never leave because you exchanged friendship bracelets. 34. You ever owned a pair of Jelly-Shoes. 35. After you saw Peewee's Big Adventure you kept saying "I know you are, but what am I?" 36. You remember "I've fallen and I can't get up" 37. You remember going to the skating rink before there were in line skates. 38. You ever got seriously injured on a Slip and Slide. 39. You have ever played with a Skip-It. 40. You had or attended a birthday party at McDonald's. 41. You've gone through this list occasionally saying "This wasn't from the 80's!" 42. You remember Popples. 43. "Don't worry, be happy" 44. You wore, like, EIGHT pairs of socks over tights with high top Reeboks. 45. You wore socks scrunched down. 46. "Miss MARY MACK MACK MACK, all dressed in BLACK BLACK BLACK" 47. You remember boom boxes vs CD players. 48. You remember watching both "Gremlins" movies. 49. You know what it meant to say "Care Bear Stare!" 50. You remember watching "Rainbow Bright and My Little Pony Tales" 51. You thought Doogie Howser was hot. 52. You remember Alf, the lil furry brown alien from Melmac. 53. You remember New Kids on the Block when they were cool. 54. You knew all the characters names and their life stories on Saved By the Bell", the ORIGINAL class. 55. You know all the words to Bon Jovi's "Shot thru the Heart."  PASS THIS ON TO ALL YOUR FRIENDS WHO GREW UP IN THE 1980s!!!
     

        
</post>

<date>14,May,2003</date>
<post>


           
      I've been working on setting up a battlefield server for the past few days and tonight I finally got all the bugs worked out.  Its pretty sweet now that I lag and the remote console up and running. I even got to to ban my first player tonight some fucker on our team kept destroying all the vehicles at our base. It felt soooo good!!!  If you play check it out "CV 1942 Dual OC3"
     

        
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink     what's your cowboy bebop theme song?  
     

        
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink   
     

        
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
        I am Frylock from Aqua Teen Hunger Force!  urlLink Which Aqua Teen Hunger Force character are you? 
     

        
</post>


</Blog>