<Blog>


<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, it's not a total disaster, but I learned a few things this go around with the bikini bottoms. My butt is not quite as big as I imagine it to be. That was nice to know/learn. Bikini patterns from Brazil are in fact risque and, well, Brazilian.   I have an idea in my head of how to alter the bottoms to fit properly, not gape in the back and show that crack and not be incredibly indecent in the front and show ANYTHING. However, I am a little burnt out on it since I worked on it all weekend like a madwoman. This week: FRIDA PONCHO. Nuff said.
      
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I started with the top from Cleo and left out the band around the bottom of the top and just made it a triangle top.      I should have the bottoms finished this weekend I will post them either Sunday or Monday, depending on when they get done.  
      
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi There,  &nbsp; Just want to introduce myself to you all. I'm a pattern designer and I'm interested in joining the bikini knit-a-long to see what people are doing, problems they may encounter with patterns and fit so that I can both help and use that info to improve the fit of my own designs. You can see my designs on the link that Jocelyn attached to my name to the right- the bikinis are at the bottom of the page. &nbsp; Tina 
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      
      
</post>

<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've finished the cups and the lace border at the bottom, and I am now beginning the flap that goes in front of my tummy. Since all other projects have been put on hold for this one, I'm going pretty fast on it. It's really exciting. I want to finish it ASAP so I can wear it this summer on a day trip with my boyfriend. &nbsp; Must go to Joanne's today as I need a liner for the bag I knitted for Jen, one of my bosses. &nbsp; Happy knitting. Rachel in NH 
      
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thanks for all the technical help, Jocelyn. I've finished one triangle for my Cleo top. Very exciting!!!!  Today I was able to parallel park PERFECTLY for the second time in my life. This has nothing to do with the bikini except that I was parking to go to the bank so I could get money for yarn for the bikini.  Happy knitting. Rachel in NH
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Shansu, S. Colyer and Grace.  Glad to see you joining the fun!  Jocelyn
      
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Some of you may have been following the discussion on the Ample Knitters list about converting the  urlLink Thong-th-Thong pattern  found in  urlLink this season's knitty  into a bikini top for amples. Joan, from  urlLink White Lies Design , and the author of said pattern, wrote to me the other day:       Hi Jocelyn,   Since I suggested turning the Thong-th-Thong upside down, I thought a photo of what&nbsp;I had in mind&nbsp;might help clarify what the cup will look like. See it on my D-cup sized mannequin.          I do also carry Fixation yarn and anyone having trouble finding it at their LYS can have a look in  urlLink the yarn section of my site . I'll have a color card there in a day or so.    urlLink Joan M-M    So there you have it, the great 2004 Bikini Knit-Along is gaining momentum (and support) from the most respected names in the knitting community. Thank you very much  urlLink Joan , for this sample picture and your help. This knitter is eternally grateful for all you do to further the cause of beautiful knitting patterns for the ample sized woman.   urlLink Jocelyn 
      
</post>

<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm heading off to LYS in about an hour, and I'm taking the pattern for the bikini with me. I've decided to go with the Cleo pattern from knitty.com (give credit where it is due). I'm going to write to Amy Swenson, the designer, and ask her some tips on how to size up.  I'm off! Rachel in NH
      
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Welcome Bikini-Alongers! If you would like to be an active member of this blog just  urlLink send me an email . You can share your progress, pictures, questions, frustrations, etc. with us. Feel free to post here if you like, and follow along with the Bikini-Along as we knit up some Summer fun! 
      
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I've put my bikini on hold because I need to figure out what to do now. I ran out of yarn, so I won't have a long flap in front of my tummy, just a little flap. Hmmm..... any suggestions? 
      
</post>



</Blog>