<Blog>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night after I posted my blog my sweet mate Salia and her brother Justo came and kidnapped us to go to dinner and the mall.  We went to one of the most amazing italian restaurants I have ever been to.  It was called Italliani's and it was muy bueno!  Justo and I spent the evening talking about theatre.  He is a communications major because his dad wouldn't let him major in theate.  I think I learned more spanish last night than in all of my classes so far.... They are such great people! and they have a car which is good because the public transportation scares me!  Salia is a handful!! she is 18 and has just finished her first year at UDLA... She is so great!  she got so upset when she found out how old I was because I look younger than all of them.  I probably look the youngest in our entire group and yet with the exception of the 2 in their late 40s I am the oldest.  And so far I feel it.  I have a hard time keeping up with these kids!!    We had our second cooking class today.  It was alot of fun.  We learned to make frijoles charro and chilaquiles verdes... es sooooo yummy!! I like chilaquiles!! and it is so much fun to say!!  When I get back we are definately having a dinner party.  Tonight Salia is taking us to the supermercado so we can do our grocery shopping.  It is very exciting! that way we don't have to eat out all the time.  I leave for Oaxaca at 6 in la manaña.  Everyone else is going clubbing tonight.... I am going to bed.  Maybe the dorms will be quiet for once.... 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was nice and relaxed.... After class and lunch I came back to my dorm put on some laundy and took a siesta! After my nap Alysa and I went to Salia´s room and watched some TV.  American TV is so bland in comparison!!  Salia is helping us with our pronunciations and Mexican slang! She is fabulous!! Tonight I have alot of homework so that is probably how I will spend my evening.  I have two papers to write and some stories to read.  I am really looking forward to this weekend and the trip.  I also found out today where to get the settings for my wireless card.  So now hopefully I will be able to use my laptop to access the internet.  I also added new pictures so be sure to check them out!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a much better day! Classes went well. I really like my teachers.  They are very patient and understanding.  The group is starting to try to talk in spanish amongst ourselves which has lead to some very amusing spanglesh episodes... today at lunch we had little white potatoes as a side dish.  One of the girls tripped and they fell off her plate and went everywhere.  She yelled out... -Oh no! I have spilt mi papas all over me!!- I probably shouldn't have laughed at that but I did.     I had my first cooking class as well today! ... I am going to love that class.  We get to eat what we make at the end of class.  It was sooo yummy!! Today we made chalupas and rice pudding from scratch... I don't like rice pudding so much but the chalupas were amazing.  After class we headed back to the dorms.  I got a shower and took a nap... I know it was very exciting... and now I am starting on the mounds of homework I have.  This weekend I am going to Oaxaca!! I am very excited!! 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      FIrst day of classes.... Not too bad.  The teachers are very patient and I wasn't the worst person in the class so that is good I think.  I haven't felt very well today... mostly lack of sleep and dehydration.  I hope. The native students moved in for summer classes yesterday and our dorm is no longer quiet.  If I thought the noise was bad in the dorms at UH... at least there was carpet there to absorb some of it.  I don't think I have ever seen so many people who talk so much.  They make my girls look like quiet subdued little people.  I am going to have to find time to go into Puebla and find somewhere with earpulgs.  They also all smoke and there are no rules about not smoking in the dorms.  Not real fond of cigarette smoke but I suppose I will get used to it.  Ok enough complaining.  You guys might get the impression I am not having a good time.  At lunch they served a soup that was amazing.  One of the best things I have ever tasted!!  I signed up for my extra cultural classes as well today.  I am taking cooking and ballroom dancing.  I am very excited about it.  Now I have to walk to the store for dinner before it gets dark.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We went to explore Puebla today. The three of us chicas from houston hooked up with a group from New Hampshire for dinner last night and again today for the tour.  They are so much fun!!  Our Animadore (Host student),Geraldo, showed us how to use the public bus into puebla... if I thought the plane ride was scary the bus.... a million times worse... fun but scary.... It goes like 60 70 miles an hour on these tiny winding cobblestone streets paying little to no attention to the enormous speed bumps they have all over Chaloula.  Better than that, the seat that I choose to sit in happened to not be bolted the rest of the bus.  It was exciting...   We got to Puebla and walked to the main square.  It was only 9:15 on Sunday morning so everything was still closed so we wondered around til 10 looking at chuches... so many churches...more and more churches... Then we found a bookstore and I picked up some books in spanish.  It was starting to get hot and we were thirsty so we headed to an icecream shop Gery knew about.  Ice cream is very different here.  Not really all that sweet... with a little tartness thrown in.  It was time for our bus tour about the time we finished, which worked out nicely. (Gery is a good guide) The tour was about an hour... which was fine except it was very very sunny, very very long, and when ever the bus stopped HOT.  But I got the general overview of the city and added some places to my list of must sees.  After the tour we were all starving so we went to a little resturante off the square about 4 blocks... The food was very good!! However about 1/2 way through our soup course Jen hollers out ¿Que the f#@! is that? after we had all finished laughing at her... interesting... mix of spanish and english we found she had discovered a worm in her soup.  It was very diappointing because It was so good... A Tomatoe type broth with broccli in it.  None of us could finish ours.  But the rest of the meal was good and bug free.  Luch made us realize how increadably tired we were so we decided to make one last stop to show us how to get to the local walmart (muy importante tienda) and then we headed back to the dorms.  Tomorrow we start classes so wish me luck.  I am very nervous about them.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hola todos!! Well I managed to get to Mexico safely.  It was quite an adventure!  I am at the terminal waiting to board and the tinyest little airplane pulls up to the gate.  I turned and looked at my professor and my concern was obviously written all over my face.  He laughed and said it would be fun! I doubted him.  But he was right!  It was noisy it was bumpy... the comparison I came to was it was like spending two hours on the serpent at astroworld.  (The serpent is the kiddy version of the viper.)  The flight went by so quickly though! I was sitting next to a lady that lives in Puebla but is from tulsa and so she spends half of her time there and half here in Mexico.  Her name is December (yes, like the month) and we really hit it off.  We talked... welll yelled is a little closer to it with how noisy that plane was... the whole flight.  She gave me the names and locations for several restraunts to try while I am here.  We are going to try and get together sometime next week for dinner.  Out flight got in at 11 pm and we were one of 3 flights that had come in all day at the airport so getting through customs was mostly painless.  we were at our dorms and checked in by midnight and I finally managed to get unpacked, settled, and to bed at 2ish.  6:30 came very very early this morning.  Breakfast was an exerience... With our eggs they served a side of black beans (which I was somewhat expecting) and a vegtable medly tye dish with green beans, peas, corn and such (which kinda threw me)  It was quite tasty however.  I then spent the rest of the morning doing placement tests.  I actually managed to get placed in the level I am needing... which suprised me a little because everyone else in our group placed below where they were supposed to be.  Lunch was very fun they had a banquet for us. Mariachis serenaded us for our first two courses.  It was very entertaining.  Now I am off for a nap before spending the rest of the evening studying.  I hope you are all doing great. I will be sending you links to two websites sometime this week one will be to the pictures from the trip and the other to my blog.  Feel free to write me it will be great to hear from home over the next seven weeks.  I miss you all already!!  Wish you were here 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Laundry... Lisa and I decided to go to the mall.  It ws good because gravity was begining to keep my pants from staying on my butt... I got a couple of really cute outfits.  I love shopping here!! lots of clothes for curvy women!!  I am very excited!  We got back and I have taken the evening easy mostly.  Gotta go finish my homework now.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok so we got back from Cuetzalan and Ana invited me o go out with them.  We went to this great little bar called Pulque Para Dos.  Soo awsome!  I loved it.  It was very tranquil and layed back.  Full of hippies.  Me gusta mucho!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is the most beautiful... amazing city I have ever been to!!  I want to live here too!!  First we went to La Gloria.  It was a waterfall... it was pretty but i have seen lots of waterfalls... however I took my sketch book and got a few really good drawings in.  Ana and David (the other camera guy)  hung out some while waiting for everyone to get back on the bus.  I sat with Alejandra one of the animadores... she is really sweet I like her alot.  We then went farther up the mountain  to the point that we had to get out and walk to the city because the bus wouldn´t fit down the streets.  It is a beautiful town!! I cannot even tall you how amazing it is!!  We checked into our hotel... also beautiful... an then had free time. I found my way to the zocalo and drew for a few hours.  Then headed back to the hotel to change for dinner.  We went to Jarritos for dinner and to watch the voladores they are dancers that go up this telephone pole looking thing then spin back down to the earth on ropes suspended from the top.  By the time we left it was close to midnight.  Ana, David, Lisa, Ellen and I went to the cemetary to film us wondering around there.   We then went back to the hotel and dropped off the cameras and walked arround the city for awhile.  It was alot of fun.  We told ghost stories in spanish.  hehehe.  So it is like 2 in the morning now and I am still not tired.  So I sat out on my balcony drew til 4 decided to try to sleep... gave up got up at 7 took a shower and went out to find something for breakfast.  We had a good bit of free time and Ana, David, Lisa and I went to the market so they could film us shopping.  On the way back to the school we stopped at some ruins... and an artiesians market... It was lots of fun!  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Went to class... packed for the trip this weekend... still feeling a little queasy so I think I will go to bed early.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was sick in the clinic hooked to an IV drip.... Had a throat infection and an intestinal infection all at once.  Fun fun fun.... Don´t really remember much from the last few days.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Slept in.... did laundry and homework.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok so I was very disappointed with this trip.  However I got to spend alot of time with Ana and Abram... They are the camera crew that is filming the documentay on our program here at UDLA.   I am going to be a movie star! hehehe!  Ana is great!  She is alot like Nan and Paige if you shoved them into one person.  On the way to Veracruz we passed a cactus farm.... it was the funniest thing I have ever seen.  All these cacti in straight lines.... We then went to Xapala.... I want to live there!! it is beautiful!  We went to the anthropology musem.  Temo walked around with me there and explained anything I didn´t understand.  It is a beautiful musem.   He has beautiful eyes... I love being a girl!  Our hotel.... BEAUTIFUL!!  We were right on the beach... SO amazing!!  We changed for dinner and dancing and met the group downstairs.  I had a hamburger for dinner and we walked to the zocolo where we were going to go dancing.  But the place had a dresscode and there were some in our group in shorts and sandals.  We ended up taking a taxi to Senor Frogs.  What a waste of time and realestate!  I understand that it is a popular place but it was so.... Gringo.  However I had one of the best amerreto sours I have ever tasted.  We got back to the hotel at like 2 and had to be up for breakfast at 8.  We went to wonder around the zocolo and explore a little.... It is SOOOO touristy.  And not very pretty in compairison to the rest of Mexico.  If you crossed Texas City with Galveston and then had the entire population of Houston and its surrounding areas to live there... you got Veracruz.  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to school today.... I packed for leaving tomorrow. Thats it.... fun fun
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Classes classes and more classes... but after class... we had a party!  We went over to Gerry's house for dinner.  His apartment is really cute! could use some decorating... but hey....He and his friends made dinner for us... we had a meat medley on blue corn tortillas... and the best Guacamole I have ever put in my mouth.... come to think of it it was the best food I have ever put in my mouth... that is saying ALOT because I usually don't like Guac.  This stuff was amazing! I had a manzana lift with my dinner... Mmmmmm Manzana lift is like a carbonated liquid apple jolly rancher... It is candy in a bottle.  We then played a game of I never in spanish... which turned into a game of lets find out what Erin has done.... I don't know who they thought I was but it was pretty funny watching them find out about me.  Then we caught a cab home and now I am going to go crash.  Night night
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Happy June!!  Classes... apearantly I didn't miss anything yesterday because they were all pretty much doing the same thing they were on thursday... after class I was starting to feel bad again so I went and took a nap.... can I tell you how much I love naps! Then I went with Selia to her physical therapy appointment and the mall.  I had McDonalds for dinner... It was a nice change of pace and nipped away that twinge of homesickness.  Then I fixed Selia's computer did homework and now it is off to bed 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok so at like 2 ish I woke up with a migrane... spent most of the morning lying on the bathroon floor in pain... about 9 I was able to fall asleep again... slept til noon so needless to say I didn't make it to class today.  This afternoon I went to walmart with the girls we got groceries and I bought yarn and crocheting needles... I left mine at home and have missed them the whole time I have been here.  We got home and I cooked dinner for us and finished up my homework and I am going to bed early!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      REsting... recovering and homework.... that was the theme for today.  I did laundry I slept alot and I did homeork... It was wonderful... I did nothing.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So it is a 5 hour bus ride to Oaxaca... we all knew this but none of us quite grasped the magnitude of 5 hours on a bus... Although I am glad I made the trip with the school and not on my own... the state border crossings were really scary!!  The have tons of military guys with machine guns and angry faces glaring at you.  not something I would have wanted to face on my own!  At 12:30 1 ish we stopped for lunch at El Patio, a retaurant that serves authentic Oaxacan cuisine.  It wasn't too much different from the other mexican cuisine I have had here.  They brought out a plate of fresh tortillas and a plate that had two types of cheese and some chilipepper looking stuff.  We passed the plate around and everyone started filling their tortilla... I opted for only cheese as my stomach had been a little on the queasy side and we still had 2 more hours on the bus.  They served Jaimca (really not sure if I spelled that right...)juice, which is really tasty.  After a few minutes of munching and talking Rachel looks down at her plate and says -ummm guys, thish chili pepper has eyes... and legs...-  Turns out it was cricket that had been sauteed for awhile.  The rest of lunch was good and bug free.  We had a chicken soup and a skirt steak of sorts.  Ot the way out of the restraunt I noticed that the fence around the restraunt was mae of these tall vertical cacti that had two horizontal boards nailed to it. Turns out the majority of the fences we saw were like this.  Our next stop was the villaga of Mitla.  We did some shopping there and wondered around in some ancient tombs... it was pretty cool... there were some amazing views from the tops of the tombs!  However the inside of the tombs... especially the parts that were underground... were quite stinky and dirty... the anchients need a better cleaning service.  My stomach was begining to rumble as we got back on the bus to head to Oaxaca City, where our hotel was.  As we pulled into the mainpart of the city you couldn't help but notice the huge numbers of people.  We had to park 3 blocks away from our hotel and walk with all of our stuff, the busses just couldn't get through all of the people.  Our animadore told us as we were getting off the bus that there was a teachers strike going on in the square and that we all needed to remember the name of our hotel incase we got seperated from the group and got lost.  But he said not to worry because all the people were teachers... and "what is a teacher going to do with you? give you homework?" We made it to the hotel safely.  And got to see a good bit of the strike on the way.  After we checked into the hotel Hillary (my roommate at the hotel) and I wondered around talking to the teachers about what was going on and why they were striking.  Turns out teachers from all over the state had come to strike for higher wages... better school programs... adn better facilities for the kids.  They had been living in the square for several days and planned to stay as long as it took.  It was really facinating!! Some of them had brought tents but most of them had just strung up tarps between trees and buildings and signposts and were living in sleeping bags underneath them... It was amaxingly well organized too... they had walkways and cooking areas and places where they were giving talks and where they had entertainment going on.  Jason (Hillary's friend) finally found us and we went in search of a restaurant.  We headed away from the strike... somewhat to just explore the area and somewhat to find a restraunt that wasn't crowded.  We turned down one of the side streets and fireworks caught our eye.  We had waled smack into the middle of a parade.  We watched it go by for a miute when some little mexican ladys grabbed us by the arms and suddenley we were in the parade!  We walked along for a few blocks when a little restaraunt above a shop caught our eye.  The sign said La Olla... live music inside.  It was the most amazing restraunt I have ever been in.  The service was supurb and the food was amazing!! The waiter asked what we were doing in Mexico and we told him we were here for a language imersion program.  He got very excited and spoke to us very slowly in spanish and then explained anything we didn't understand in English.  We then spoke back to him in spanish and he corrected any mistakes we made.  There was a cello player in the corner playing bach... the windows were all open and there was a delightfully cool breeze blowing in... It was a very surreal experience.  I had a drink that was a lime and mint juice!  (My mouth is watering just thinking about it!!)   After dinner we met back up with the group and went to a salsa club called Azucar.  It was alot of fun but HOT... SO HOT... I cannot tell you how amazingly hot it was.  We only stayed about an hor and then couldn't take anymore.  We caught a cab back to the hotel showered and crashed... Ok so it was so hot there that when I wokeup in the morning the clothes I had worn were still wet... The alarm went off at 8 and we trudged to breakfast... packed up and left at 9. The morning was spent exploring the ruins of Monte Alban.  Monte Alban was a religous center situated at the exact point where the 2 north american mountain ranges intersect.  It was HUGE! and beautiful! Our guide was great... such a character! I could have spent all day listening to his stories.  but our animadores kept us to our time schedule and hearded us back to our busses.  Our final stop in Oaxaca was at a workshop where they make this black pottery... the clay itself is black and once they fire it it is some of the most beautiful stuff I have ever seen.  We watched a demonstration on the pottery techniques used and then we bought pottery of our own.  Between the market and here I spent sooo much money this weekend!!  The last 5 hours on the bus were miserable.... I had worn my contacts all day and My eyes hurt... I went to take them off and my left one got stuck in my eye... it took like 20 minutes to get in seperated... I was tired and couldn't sleep... and I was very very cranky.... luckily they turned off the lights and put in a movie... we watched Freida and Daddy Day Care.  It was a strange combination of moves but hey it helped the time pass a little quicker.  We got back at midnight and my dorm never looked more like home!  
       
    
    
</post>


<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know how to take this. I was informed last night  by my exboyfriend that I was acting weird. He didn't know how to deal with me. And the reason I'm acting weird is... (drumroll please) that somehow since we broke up, I gained self-confidence. And he wanted to know why. HA. Maybe its because I'm not worrying about whats going on with him anymore. Or maybe its that I broke away from only hanging out with his group and got my own. Hmm...  I guess it doesn't really matter much. I guess I just thought it was funny. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I Love thunderstorms! They are the best things when you're not out in them. You get to curl up in a  blanket and be a dork with a book or a computer. Its not quite cold enough, although close, for hot chocolate, but you get the idea. I can't go anywhere because my parents would freak, and thats ok, I don't really want to.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have proof that me trying to raise a child would be dangerous. At least at my current life stage. I have managed to raise two codependant cats. I've had them since I they were three months old and aparently they act very strangely when I'm not around. But I haven't noticed anything weird until today, because they're afraid of my parents two cats, who are very possesive of me and my time. But today I spent the entire day in my bedroom, where only my two cats venture... and they can't let me out of their sight for more than 2 minutes. Its weird. Note to self: no kids  until I figure out how I managed to warp cats.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Obviously, last night was interesting.   Not only did I get to go out with my best friend, her husband, and his friend, I got to work on  a survey that will coming out soon and pray to god that Cole got home ok. So that last part wasn' t fun, but it did add to the interest.   Why are people So silly? If you're going to get drunk stay where you're drinking. Or notice before you start drinking that you're getting annoyed at the people you're with, so you can go home and get drunk there. And leaving the place you were drinking at, on foot, without you're keys (because someone you're annoyed at took your keys) is not a good idea either.   Everyone went to sleep while he was walking around, so he got locked out of the apartment... but he could still drive his car because he had a spare key. So the poor boy couldn't go home, but he could drive while he was drunk. yea... and call me at 330. yea.... hopefully cole won't look at this page again anytime soon. :) If there had been anything I could do for him, I would be less annoyed. But as it stands, I couldn't offer him the couch here because my mom was sleeping on it (nothing wrong with my parents, she hurt her ankle and can't do the stairs) and I was so tired that it would have been almost as dangerous for me to drive to get him as it was for him to be driving himself around.  OK I've ranted, I feel better.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After little to no sleep, I've decided to change my answer from duck to platypus... I mean, who wouldn't want to be proof that god has a sense of humor? AND have all the characteristics that the duck has?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I remember being asked when I was little, besides the ever popular what do you want to be when you grow up: if you could be an animal, what kind of animal would you be? Back then I probably said something like a horse or a cat or even more probably, a unicorn. My opinion has taken a dramatic turn. I would want to be a duck. They're silly, get to swim all day, and everything slides off their back. I wish I could let more slide than  I do. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In studying art history, I have realized something that may mess with a few minds... or may not... it all depends. What if the Rosetta stone was written to throw people off track? Could it be that the Egyptians didn't want people to know what they were saying and decided to write something that looked like a key. I hold that what ever the Rosetta stone says in Greek is not comparable to what it says in hieroglyph and that the other writing says something else entirely... all probably meaning nearly the same thing though. They probably each say that they are duplicates of the other two writings.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that perfectly normal people, with semi-decent love lives, ask advice from people who are not in a relationship, and possibly wouldn't know one if it fell on them from sputnik?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was driving home from work and looked at the moon. I don't always notice the moon, but it was screaming for attention tonight. It was really low, big, and Yellow. Thats when it hit me. I can no longer see the man in the moon. Its not that he's not there, its that my mind has been so destroyed by corporate crap that the man in the moon now looks like a really big energizer bunny.  That makes me sad.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is fun. Although I have no idea what I'm doing. I wish I knew anything about html coding.. but I don't. Or at least, I don't remember. Hopefully Shaun will help me out and I can make it possible for people to leave me messages. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I've decided that if there is a cupid, he has an incrediably demented sense of humor. My closest friend met and is in the process of falling for, a good guy at my best friend's wedding. However, she lives in Indiana and he lives in Topeka.  I don't know how they're doing the distance thing. .... oh well.... fly on cupid.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to see George Carlin tonight, and I would love to say that he was awesome.... but I just cant. Its not that I was offended, because I wasn't. I was a little sickened by some of his material... and I was just sad. He's such a nice man offstage... but then he gets out on stage and becomes this freaky person that thinks everyone in the world should be dead.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now, I'm not one to watch sports, with the exception of soccer or hockey. So I haven't really had any exposure to cheerleaders in the last several years (since I graduated highschool and was no longer in marching band) This is my question about cheerleaders now: How do they do all of their stunts and jumps in those uniforms? I remember the cheerleaders that I've seen wearing loose pleated skirts... but the cheerleaders of Iola U are wearing uniforms that I would find it hard to walk in, let alone jump around.... oh well... time to put in another movie so that I don't have to think about it anymore.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its not that I want to live in clutter. Or that I am by nature really a sloppy person. I am not a neat freak either. So when it comes down to choosing between going out or cleaning my room, I'm going to go out. Thats the problem. I have been so busy going out, or posting on here, or working so much that I never unpacked from moving home. Whenever I needed something that was in a box, I would dig it out, not put everything away that was in the box. That was ok when I was sleeping/eating/studying in my parents living room. Now that I've moved back into my bedroom, however, its a problem. I've been working on it all day and it still looks like a whole bunch of packing boxes exploded.  Could be that I've been doing the preliminary work of cleaning out dressers that haven't been looked at since I left home 4 years ago. I have NO idea why on earth I would have that many pairs of tights, I don't remember ever wearing that many skirts that I would need that. I don't know. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't want the show to end. But I never do. I get attatched to the cast and crew and even though with this group I'm pretty sure I'll see most of them around again, I don't want to take as much time as I'm going to have to away from them. And it'll never be the same dynamic between each different combination of people. The next show that I KNOW I'm doing won't start until late Febuary. Until then I'm going to have to be content with just working as a local crew for the touring shows... one piece of interesting news that goes with that is my boss gave my phone number and name to another local venue. They pay better, but the reason for that is purely the hazard. There's a lot of runnning around on catwalks HIGH above the floor... thats right, its an indoor arena. Maybe I'll get to work a hockey game... THAT would be cool.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm feeling just a bit squiffy. I've been awake and doing stuff for nearly 20 hours, and I don't eat nearly enough to keep that pace up. (I didn't know that until my dad made me start keeping a journal of what I eat when to figure out if I'm starving myself of if I'm diabetic.) I just got home from an impromptu cast party that was just really fun, educational too. Finally figured out someone was gay that I just couldn't guess about. yea, he's gay, I don't have to think about it anymore.  I don't really have a lot to say, I just really wanted to post the word squiffy.... I like it... even if I made it up and its not British like I thought.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Paranoia is kicking in. I have no idea where any of my chat buddies are tonight. Maybe I pissed them off.  My friend Critter totally knocked me off course last night by challenging the Target creed of "Guest Service." He doesn't think that if you have to pay for anything, you're a guest. I had Finally got myself to call them guests, at all times, until today... where I screwed up about 6 times, twice in one walkie communication to the store team lead. ACK! They're Guests... guests.... !! 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK. I have some issues with the age restrictions in this country. You're an "adult" when you turn 18. But only because you are now legally set free from your parents and can be charged as an adult for any crime you commit. Oh, and you can vote. whoohoo. They give you the privilidge of driving a car when you are 16... so you can control a large veghicle when your'e 16, but not flip a voting switch. K You can fight and die for your country at 18, but you can't go to the bar and have a drink with your buddies til you're 21. So, you're an adult when you're 21.... NOPE! You can drink, drive, fight, die, vote....all at 21, but not rent a car! That you can't do until you're 24. OR you can, but you have to pay a whole lot more. Which makes a hell of a lot of sense. Because young people sure do have a lot more money than older people. GRR! I don't know if I can afford to rent a damn car for my trip to Houston.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trainwreck, thy name is is late night tv. I realize I've been talking about television a lot lately, but when I don't have a lot to occupy my time, I watch tv. Obviously I have been really busy since tv is kind of scary right now.  Anyway. The worst of my generation is on latenight tv on the shows, Rendez-view (extremely funnythough), Blind Date, Change of Heart, and the worst of all... Street Smarts. Its like Jerry Springer, without the violence. And just like Springer, if you happen to turn it on, its nearly impossible to turn off.   Street Smarts is by far the worst. They go out and pick the people who look the most likely to be an idiot and ask them general trivial questions, then bet on which one is the most idiotic. But last night, they picked wrong. The girl looked like an idiot, bright blonde hair, big sunglasses, and a willingness to do almost anything to get on tv... but she's a math major. Not to say that she got everything right, but she was better than anyone else on there... and one of them was an ivy leager from Cornell. Ha.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YEA! I think I passed my art history exam. Although, I know I didn't ace it, because I have a major problem with memorizing dates... yea, I should have a problem with dates as I used to be a history minor... haha. Anyway. That was the only thing I really had a problem with. That and the professor told us that she would only test us on the slides she told us about in advance, and she make one of the biggest questions about a slide I hadn't seen before and just had to guess on. Oh well
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm evil! I can't figure out what to do about this poor little guy that goes to school with me. He's really nice, and if he wasn't I could figure out what to do. He's got a bit of a crush and I'm just not interested. But I can't come out and tell him that because he's nice and he hasn't said anything about us going out.  His friend told me that he liked me.... Which didn't help my feeling that this was straight out of the 9th grade.  ... ACK!  Takes me forever to get him off the phone when I'm trying to do something and he calls.   I guess until I get the courage, or the bitchines, to squash him, I'll just have to deal with having a human puppydog.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just saw something rather disconcerting. I'm trying to study for my art history test tomarrow, so of course I have the tv on. And let me tell you, daytime tv on the major networks is freaky.  There is a new (or new to me) show called The Other Side. It appears to be a take off on The View, with 4 men of varying ages...  Danny Bonaduchi, Dick Clark, Dr Jan ?, and Mario from Saved By the Bell. They are showing women's life through the eyes of men. ... They were talking about hot bath's and loufa sponges... and its a double standard that I need to work on, but EWWW! I don't care how masculine a man might look, if he talks about how much he likes the lather from a loufa, he's going to freak me out.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok. I realize that my post yesterday might have sounded a little anti- afghani actions. Which, I'm not. I agree that something needs to be done. I wish that there was a way to get the Taliban out of power and Osama Bin Laden... um... dead with out having to bomb the heck out of people who have litte or nothing to begin with.  I don't doubt that the collateral damage that the Afghani government is going to claim is going to be nothing like the truth, or if it is, its because they corralled civilians into the training camps and militaty installations to up the numbers. Yea, I'm not cynical or anything.   I hate war. I think anyone normal does... but I felt really guilty yesterday for doing what theater practicioners have done for ages. The show went on, even though we had just declared an operation (not fully at war yet).  I think alot of the cast and crew did too.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't get it. When I was 12 I passed for 17. No one thought that I was actually 12... which was fun, but I was sure I was going to hate myself for it when I got older. And now that I'm 22 people all think I'm 17... or actually today it was 16. I just don't get it.... not that I really mind, mostly I think its funny.... but it could explain why I can't get a date... everyone thinks I'm jail bait.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Operation Enduring Freedom. Hmmm.  Well at least this time we have the support of most of the world and there aren't going to be as many official condemnations of our actions. And I don't doubt that this is necessary, but I don't have to like it.  But thats what I get for being a pascifist.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why do people assume that they're too good/ not good enough to be around someone with out really giving themselves a chance to get to know them?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight was rough. The show was really good, but the aftermath was insane.  Someone broke into the dressing rooms and stole a bunch of stuff during the show. No one knows when it happened, but we do know how. They jumped up and pushed open a window in the mens dressing room and took off with a couple of wallets, a couple of purses and a watch. I didn't lose anything, but I felt so bad for the people in the cast... they felt so violated. Its such a happy upbeat show, people shouldn't take advantage of it.  Besides, we're theater people... any theif with any sense would know that no one would have all that much to steal.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I bit off WAY more than I could chew this time, and around 1am, it started to show. This weekend was the closing weekend for Starmites...so there were a couple of cast parties to attend. Which, of course, I did. And on neither night did I get home before 3am. Then after the closing party I had to come home and type out some notes, because I forgot to take them with me to the show for my friend to copy.... which put me at going to bed around 4am Sunday morning. Not too terribly unusual.. if I hadn't had to be at work at 745 Sunday morning. Ooops. Got home from work at TPAC at 230am Monday morning... not feeling terriblt heathy today. oh well que cera cera.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a new favorite quote. This one doesn't seem to have the staying power of some of the others, but I still like it. And for now, it replaces both Dean Martin and Einsten.  Nequaquam vaccuum.------ the void does not exist.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Delerium is an intersting time to look at the world and thing.... what the hell is going on?  I feel like I'm stuck into some sort of half rate movie. The plots ok, but they couldn't afford real actors, so there are puppets.... or something equally odd.  What do you do when you realize that the person you're attracted to isn't unattainable? They actually are attracted back. This is new. And also when you realize that even though there is mutual attraction, that like magnets when the two parts are 400 miles apart the likelyhood of them coming together is faint. I'm not saying that it can't work, just that I don't know how, and that I'm so tired I'm coming up with really ramdom things to say.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Proof that I'm not growing up: Why do I keep doing this to myself? After 4 years of college you Think I would have figured out that procrastinating on studying does little to no good. Yet, while I knew all week that I had a math test on Friday, did I ever stay in to work? Of course not. Even tonight, when I actually got off work at 1030, and I had all of that evening time stretching out before me.... I stayed to help out Cole and went to get a snack with him. Its so late now that I know I won't retain anything... maybe I'll just take a nap and work on this in the morning.   I only have myself to blame........ but I don't regret a minute of the time I've spent with my friend who is visiting from out of town this week. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have an odd addiction. I read the engagement and wedding section in my local newspaper to see if anyone I knew from highschool is taking the plunge. And to me, a horrifying amount of people that I used to know are now starting their own famillies. My normal reaction is to freak out and yell about how we're all too young and what not. This weekend's edition was different.  The wedding was between two of my friends in highschool... I really didn't expect that they would last this long, since they started dating the junior year of highschool. They've been married for a year today, so they didn't put their picture in the paper until today. I'm really happy for them. Maybe I'm growing up, but I kind of doubt it. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love history. So why is it that I dread researching the history of The Globe Theater?  The paper is due on Monday evening, and I just don't want to do it. The only thing I really want to do right now is sleep. I don't even really want to post today, but I feel like I should since it might possibly wake me up and make me write this damn paper. I hate apathy.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that thinking can be dangerous? I'm not talking about thinking that leads to terrorism or mass murder, but thinking about relationships. Why is it that something that should be pleasurable, like thinking about your significant other can cause terror and paranoia? Oh yea, right, because thinking and paranoia are about the same thing.  Poor Kirk.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was sent a posting about a job that is now available. This job represents the end of my goal.. its where I really want to be. Here's where the niceness of having been sent the posting and the reality of life take completely different directions. I don't have enough experience to even think about applying for the job. If by some odd miracle I got the job, I wouldn't have the knowledge and ability to hold onto it. Which would ruin any chance of me having this job when I Do have the knowledge and experience to control it.  What is this job, you might ask? The head audio engineer for the Steppenwolfe Theater Company in Chicago, Illinois. ::sigh::
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate being sick.  I don't know exactly what's wrong with me, but I do know that its not anthrax.... ok ok, not funny, but still. I am of the opinion that I really need to go to sleep and not wake up until Thanksgiving. Not that I would stay asleep that long, but at least the cold/flu/sinusus/whatever would be gone and so would a big portion of November..... whoops, I would miss my birthday.  Ok. Maybe a nap for a couple of hours.... or I could work on my paper that is due on Monday 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've gained another enemy. And this time I might have sort of deserved it, but it was more through lack of knowledge on both parties sides. I didn't know that someone that was hired 2 weeks ago was my superior and she didn't know that if she was watching the jewlrey boat, she can't go  work on a checkout lane.  She has been working at Target, literally, for about 2 weeks. She decided that I had only been hired the week before she was, so I shouldnt' be telling her anything. I'm only a level one.......... I dont' think she's going to last very long, as she's pissing off people above her. She's now a level 2 (which annoys all of the level ones that have been there for very long) but she's telling everyone that she knows everything there is to know about the store.    As a sidebar. I think the reason we dislike eachother so much is that we're a lot a like. I'm just not as loud and obnoxious about it.... and I also figure out who my friends are and who my enemy's friends are before I open my mouth about how annoyed I am..... dumbass. Its just a personal thing with me, if you say something about someone, its going to get back to them.... especially when they tell someone that the person is really good friends with.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       OK. I think I'm ready to post about this now.   Last night after the show  I went out with my exboyfriend for a drink.  Its just really weird now, because before we dated we were really good friends... and now we can't talk about anything but went wrong with either our relationship or any of the many others he's been in... oh yea...and that he's sexually frustrated. Yea. That was sure my favorite conversation ever. At least I got to call him on the obnoxious condom thing. hankfully it wasn't for me... it was for someone else that is in a bad relationship that he wants to rescue.... jeez, where have I heard that before?  Ok, this isn't my normal kind of light hearted post... and it really wasn't all that bad..... We did eventually get back to normal conversation, and I think we may weather this storm and be able to stay friends..... I just don't think I'm going to mix him into my new group of friends.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should stop reading top 10 lists. The ones that think they're being serious anyway... and especially ones that deal with  urlLink 80s music . Its an absolute travesty. The songs they claim are the very worst of the 80s are the ones that I love the most. Grr..... Who are they, the technogeeks at msn, to judge fun, happy, silly music.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to see a production of Dracula (as redone by a local high school theater teacher) last night. It wasn't as hokey as I thought it was going to be. The person who played the count (Shaun Marcott) was good although he had a very odd resting stance, where he made kind of a W with his arms and had his hands  in loose fists... kind of like a weird exaggerated shrug. The performance would have been largely forgettable if it hadn't been for one actor, Carl Peckham. Carl just really needs to leave Topeka and audition for something bigger than the Topeka Civic Theater. As Mr Renfield he was funny, insane, and in the end Extremely painful to watch die.  I'll grant that you're not supposed to be happy that Renfield dies. But Carl's portrayal of a man fighting his inner demons while asking the people around him to pray for his soul would be heartwrenching anyway...but Carl also made you See that Renfield's neck was broken and he had been ravaged by the vampyresses. Carl is just too talented to be wasted on the Topeka stage.   The ending of the show was mediocre at best and used the deus ex machina escape route.... they had a rope that would open the shutters over Lucy's tomb? And Dracula can be banished with mere sunlight?  Somehow, I don't think so. Although they did address the fact that they didn't kill the count by having him raise his hand out of the ashes of his cloak right before curtain call. What they didn't address was what he did after he didn't die..... Would he just leave the Harkers and the doctors alone because they knew that sunlight was an anathama.... hmmm... he seemed to like revenge a little bit more than that.   Anyway. It was a fun show aside from all of the mistakes in Dracula lore (I know better than to say vampyre lore, since Kirk and Critter will both inform me otherwise.) I couldn't think of a much better way to spend Halloween.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Updates: Cow's gone. Mailbox isn't.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, should I worry that my ex-boyfriend has called me 4 times in the past two days wanting to get together, with the excuse that he's bored?  I'll admit that he has no idea that I'm seeing someone... and thats not because I don't want to tell him... its more because there hasn't really been a way to work it into the conversation. I just don't know...... something I do know is that in only spending 3 days with the guy I'm currently seeing, I know I couldn't ever go back to Willie. I just deserve to be treated better.... I just kind of want to know what's going through his head.................. that and he bought (Willie) bought "supplies" (condoms) while I was at the grocery store with him the last time we hung out... which was just a Little bit disconcerting.  He should know better.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really really really hate distance.  Went out with the boys tonight... actually, oddly enough, the person I'm being silly about's boys to be exact.... and while it was a lot of fun, I probably missed out on talking to him... again. :(
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If anyone can tell me who my family has angered, it would be greatly appreciated. In the last month someone has killed two mailboxes. They were poor little defenseless mailboxes and weren't even strangely painted or decorated to attract attention (unlike the extremely strange florescent yellow mailbox down the street from my old elementary school) And yet, two of them have had to die.  The first one had been through several other attacks and even been shot a few times... but it couldn't survive being pelted with a cinder block. And the last one didn't have a chance, it looks like they possibly hit it with an ax and a baseball bat, killing both the box and the stand it was on. ... my dad's starting to talk of revenge. He wants to pound the dents out of the first mailbox, place a smaller mailbox inside of it, and fill the rest of  the space with cement. Then he wants to place the box on an oil pipe that has also been filled with cement...... I told him he should also paint a target on it.   I wasn't all that worried about it, until last night. I assumed it was some bored kids from Meriden that were out attacking mailboxes and that ours was the last on the stretch of road between Meriden on Topeka Blvd that they wanted to hit.... but I drove to Meriden yesterday to survey the damage.... and there was none. Our mailbox is the only one thats been hit.   So, if you have any information about who one of us has angered, please contact me. Thank you :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I talked to my art history professor today. She hadn't even noticed that I had been missing an unusual amount of classes until I asked when she had mentioned that the class was taking a field trip to the Nelson Atkins museum. They went last Thursday, and when I showed up for class, there was no one in the room.  She was very understanding and gave me the assignment sheet and advised me that there were a lot of people in the class that hadn't gone and I should get together with one and make a day of it.... I think I'll pass.   She also told me and a fellow classmate that they should outlaw 8am classes. I agree.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw the most random thing this morning on the way to class.  While I'm used to people having hit cats or dogs or deer on the road, a cow is a first. How do you manage to hit a cow? I recognized the cow as being one that tends to escape from the fence, but it was still on the same side of the road that the fence is... and it was definitely dead. Yet, there was no car left in the ditch along with the cow to say who had been stupid enough not to swerve around a cow. They are big and can do a lot of damage, I would expect, to something as poorly defended as a moving vehicle. There weren't even any tire marks that would explain that the driver tried to stop or get out of its way. I just don't get it. I wouldn't hit a cow... the only things I've ever hit were a hawk that really hit me (rather than the other way around) and a rabbit that I couldn't see.   Poor cow.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its an oddly satisfying feeling when you realize that someone who once could control your opinions, time, whatever no longer has that over you. And that the person knows it. At one time, I would run whenever this one person would call.... and he called today. It took me 5 hours to even return his first, of two, calls and that I didn't jump and run because he wanted to see me.  HA! He sounded really disconcerted. I know, its bad to have a victory over this kind of thing, but so what. I love it. He never deserved the amount of control I let him have.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YEA! I finally fixed my good computer. Not totally though, because I think the subwoofer is broken so I'm not getting any sound out of the speakers. Oh well... at least I can play online and watch good tv (not stupid late night crap on public access) again. Whoohoo!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a complete slacker. No questions asked. I finally pulled out my notebook that contained all of my course syllabi. And after the dust was cleared away I found that there was no mention in my art history syllabus about a trip to Kansas City (whew) but that I have a project due in my intro to theater class on November 5. For some reason I assumed that it would be due much closer to finals. Eep! I haven't even really chosen a topic. At least I don't do presentations. I hate them.  Jeff's probably going to kill me anyway. I haven't turned in anything on time in that class yet... mainly because I've been so concentrated on other stuff..... which reminds me, I have a paper due tomarrow in his class that I was supposed to turn in two weeks ago. Oh well... guess I'll write it tomarrow (just kidding, I wrote it the day it was due, I was just having printer problems, and now I can go back and edit some more.)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate it when, through close association, you know when someone's hurting and can't do a damn thing about it. I've been reading my friend Shaun's weblog and I can tell that there's something really bothering him... but I'm so far away that there's nothing I can do or say to make him  feel any better... not that i could to begin with.  But since I know him so well, I can almost feel his pain... and thats just reading his words, not being in the same room with him.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What do I want? Do I want the stability of a real "normal" job, and the time to participate in local civic theater.... or do I want to  try for the life of a professional theater practicioner? Do I want to be a leaf in the wind my whole life, or do I want to settle in at least one state, if not one city?      I always thought I wanted the professional theater life. I really don't think I would mind the travelling around, except that I would miss my friends that aren't in that life. I never realized how important my real friends were until I had to leave them and come back to Topeka. It took me 9 months to find another set of really close friends, and to figure out that I can keep the ones in Houston, but not as closely.... and the idea of having to start completely over again just doesn't appeal to me right now.  Who knows.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been thinking about my educational goals/ career possibilities problem... and I've also been thinking about my problem with jobs in general (that I don't last at one for  more than 9 months) I've nearly come up with the perfect answer. I should teach. I would only be teaching for 9 months out of 12  and I could use the 3 remaining months to travel.  I do see an Amazing problem with that plan though....... I don't WANT to teach. I've said my Entire life that Iwould rather starve. blah
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phones are interestingly annoying creatures.  They allow instant communication across vast distances.... but are the most frustrating things on Earth when the person you're trying to connect with is already on the phone and doesn't have call waiting...  Not that I'm allowed to complain all that much... if anyone tried to call my house when I'm at home, they would be faced with endless busy signals as well. I'm just frustrated.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not the most observant person in the world... I thought I was... but I am wrong. I just realized today that a friend of mine is pregnant. This wouldn't be a big deal if I never saw her... or if she was less than 4 months along. But I have been hanging out with her a decent amount for several months... and today I was informed that she is 7 months along. YIPE! I see it now, but jeez!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that when you don't want to sleep, you do, but when you want to, you can't?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have one thing figured out. I put in my two weeks notice at Target. They're going to love me for that, as the end of my two weeks is Thanksgiving.  Now there are other problems: What classes to take next semester? When am I going to graduate? What major am I going to graduate with? What school am I going to graduate from? Why don't I just chuck it all and go backpacking through Europe?  Oh well.... I think I have the last one figured out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its quite possibly the strangest thing. Two people that don't like talking on the phone will get caught up talking to eachother on the darn thing for Hours. Two nights in a row.  The world is an odd place.  I guess thats why there are platypi.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish I had something positive to say today.... I just . don't.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't think I'm ever going to settle down. I'm not talking about marriage and kids at all. I'm talking about becoming anything less than restless. I don't know that I've ever stayed in one job for more than 9 months. And I've just gotten to that mark with Target... and I just can't stay there anymore.... maybe I'm not meant for retail... maybe I need to have some incentive to stay that goes deeper (either in the pocketbook or mentally) than any of the jobs I've had until now... I don't know. All I Do know is that I don't want to be there at Thanksgiving. ... They're not all that upfront about store policies..... can't take days off between Nov 1 and January 15th... store stays open for "extended hours" starting the day after Thanksgiving (I still haven't been told that officially, I found that out from someone else that works there. Maybe thats it too... I just don't trust the store. Weird thought.  I'm looking for a new job already. But I'm not finding anything that interests me. I don't know if anything non-theater would interest me for very long. GRRRR!  I'm going to see if an accessory store in the mall is still hiring assistant managers, because that would be higher pay and some sort of responsibility that I don't have a Target....... and I did officially get my hours for my teaching job in the spring today.   Which brings me to another problem. If I take the teaching job in the spring I won't be able to take any of the theater classes that I need to graduate.  I don't think I really need anything but theater classes to graduate. I really wish I had never transferred back here... because I would have been graduating with the degree I WANT in less than a month. I hate this.  yea yea furbs, this one wasn't funny
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I was able to see the most beautiful site ever. I walked out of my front door to view the aurora borealis. The sky was nearly a neon red with a blue green ribbon  below it. I have never before see the northern lights except in pictures. Its just awe inspiring.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Update on the research paper. I changed my topic. I had submitted two, because my work on the Globe theater had the probability  of a huge snag. That snag was not being able to get an interview with Dr Sydney Burger at the University of Houston. He was the historian for the rebuilding project in London. He is a very busy man, and when I was at the University the only contact I was able to have with him was carrying some donations into the building for him. Therefore, I'm writing my production notebook for the Edward Albee New Playwrights Workshop. It was a painful experience, so I have to milk it for all its worth.  YEA! no research involved!!! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I must really hate my job. I wasn't able to work because of other problems, that were well forseen, for the last month. This week I was able to get my hours back up from 9 to probably 25..... yet now I'm having unforseen problems. I have strep throat, or maybe tonsilitus... so I'm not at work. But because I took a semester off from school, I am also not insured and can't run to the doctor to get better. BLAH!  I could get insurance through work... but I really don't want to stay there. I have a new idea.  I think I'm going to start sending my resumes to local radio stations to see if I can secure and internship position for the coming semester as an audio engineer intern. That way I can start getting real experience with the equipment, and possibly radio personalities that can write me recommendations.... the only problem that this doesn't answer is that I don't have insurance. I guess I'm just not going to get sick ever again.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Could someone introduce me to this sleep person everyone's been talking about? He sounds really cool and I would like to make his acquaintance.   I need to find a place in town that I can take a nap while I'm killing time between class and work.......... oh well... it'll be a mostly moot point in about a week.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The only thing that sucks about finishing a paper at 1am is the realization that you have to get up in 5 hours to turn it in.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been thinking a lot about the protest rallies around Topeka lately. I wish I could jump on board with the people who are trying to get Fred Phelps censured in our city. But I can't. It has a lot to do with the idea that while they're hiding it under the guise of the local obscenity laws, but its still censure.   Then, there is the tactics they are using. While their signs aren't obscene, they are still hateful. Not to a large group of people, or even one who is undeserving of the hate... but its still hate none the less.   People were injured in the protests this weekend. A member of the Phelps clan assaulted a member of the Unity Blvd people. A member of the Phelps clan was assaulted by a person that wasn't involved with either group. Someone went to the hospital. They are using it as a propaganda ploy. They are turning the people from Unity that were injured into heros and martyrs (can't be a martyr unless you die, but who knows how far this could go)   I firmly believe that if Unity Blvd hadn't arisen, the Phelps wouldn't have come back. We would ignor them into oblivion... its not as fast or as active, but I think its more effective.  But what do I know. I'm just a simple person who would like to believe in something, but fails miserably.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Things that I don't like, today: 1 Colds 2 being cold 3 media personalities 4 space between two points 5 extremely random non-sensical insults  so I'm a bit whiny today, but I'll live
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I'm starting to get over my personal paranoia. And the reason for that is that I see how miserable other people who are paranoid feel. They come to me, seeking advice and assurance that their significant other really does like them/ isn't seeing someone else/ didn't have a horrible time on their last date. I guess its just perspective, that their problems actually seem worse to them than the ones I have do to me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Frustration is the truest word to how I feel about my current educational brickwall. As far as I can tell there is only about 26 hours I need to graduate. but. They don't offer those classes in any way that would make a difference to me. I REALLY want to take the teaching job at TPAC, actually, I already have so I can't back down from it. But there are two classes offered at Washburn that I need to graduate, and neither are offered at a time when I could teach and take the class. This is rather distressing.  I will probably find out tomarrow what nonmajor classes I still need because I'm having a convrence with the dean of the honors college. He will probably tell me that I have to take junior level English (and possibly freshman comp) because this is a business and not a place where you let people go because they've already had the damn class under a different name. GR. But anyway, at least I will know something more than I know now, which is that the theatre department doesn't know what to do with me. I've taken more classes than they offer. I've taken design classes that they wouldn't know how to offer, but they still want me to take an introduction to design. BLAH!  I might talk to Paul and see if I could just take Design 2 rather t han both design 2 and design 1 because I've taken so many other design classes that have taught me the exact same things.  OK. done whining. I should really be in class.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My art history professor is so cute. She is worried that we're going to think that she's trying to convert us to either Christianity or Judiasm because she's showing us art work from the Early Christain, Jewish, and Byzantium period. Its all based on religious themes, and I really don't think she has control over it.  However, she is unrepentantly Christian, and possibly isn't tenured, so it might be a concern. Oh well... at 8am its kind of funny.  And she was trying to chastise us for being bad students. Of the 40 papers (or so) that were turned in over our class visit to the Nelson-Atkins museum, only 7 were on topic. Meaning that they covered an art piece that is in the time peroids that we are going to cover in the class. Those periods are primarily western and all fall in earlier than 1500. Aparently there were papers on Chinese Art and 1800 British Masterworks. I do happen to know that my paper was on a Classical Greek statue of a lion, so I'm one of the 7. I'm still not confident that it wasn't a piece of crap.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my boredom I decided to create a semi-ficticious neighborhood containing all of my closest friends. To see if the fictional people would interact in the same way they are in real life... so thats not happening. Aparently, the person I'm seeing and I hate eachother... as do my friends who are married...... oh well. Actually, thats not the point.  The point is that I got bored as soon as I finished building and furnishing the houses. That was the truly fun part of the game, because I have very little intrest in controlling the actions of other people. And when I do start enjoying that part, some random neighbor will show up and I can't do anything with them. Grr. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have an answer to a question I was asked extremely late on Saturday night and I couldn't answer. This will seem really odd, but I still feel the need to give an answer anyway.  Critter: the downside is probably my lack of patience.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This was the best possible weekend, for the most part. Very little could have gone better.... although the Harry Potter movie fell short of expectations. For some reason I don't think I'll be posting very often now. I have very little to complain about anymore... odd. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have since been informed that I had no reason to apologise. Oh well.   Today has been rather uneventful. I like it that way, because yesterday was quite busy.   I got to work at TPAC as a local stage hand on the tour of My Fair Lady. I love my job, because I get to work with the most interesting collection of people (the tour's sound engineer was really funny and cool... and he had a blue-green mohawk.) The down side is that its really demanding physical labor and today I don't really feel like moving much... and can't wear shoes because I was run over by a marly (dance floor material) cart.   I have never seen so many people look at me weird because I was wearing socks and sandles before... maybe because soccer season is over... or maybe because it was too cold for sandles.... oh well.... got some christmas shopping done (oddly enough, I wasn't shopping for what I was buying other people, but buying something for my grandmother to wrap and give to me) at least I  knowI'm getting something good this year :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so anyway, megs and kirk, I'm sorry.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Honestly, I don't know who all reads this, and because I can't figure out how to make the comment things work, I probably never will. But still, I have to hope that there are a few of my close friends who read this, because I can't get them on the phone and I need to apologise.  I honestly shouldn't have said the things I said. Not, that I didn't mean it  but it really wasn't my place to say. And now I'm afraid that I've done some permanent damage to our friendship.... or she was just really busy this week and hasn't had a chance to call me back. But I feel really bad. I should keep my opinions to myself when it concerns other people's relationships, but that gets really hard when those in relationships are asking me for what they should do... and then not getting anything out of what I'm telling them..... if it goes on too long where I feel like I'm talking to a wall, then  I get frustrated and say things I shouldn't.  I think I am officially out of the advice business. There just isn't anything I can say to help some people so I'm not going to try.  Maybe I shouldn't say I won't give anyone advice, because that would just go completely against my nature, but giving people advice about my friends when they are dating my friends is just weird.  So, if you want to know a good book, or what you should do to get the attention of the pizza delivery boy that I don't know.. then sure.... but nothing thats going to cause me to freak out or possibly hurt anyone else. BLAH. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like explaining something that I really should have last night on the phone, but brushed off with "but that was a lifetime ago" Matt and I were talking and somehow we got on the subject of tatoos. He has one, I don't.... and I said something about how I almost killed Dave for getting one. I guess I half explained it because Dave was just getting it because of peer pressure and my reasons for not wanting him too.... but its more than that. At that time I thought I needed to keep control over everything, not just myself.  And that was something I couldn't do at that time, so I was being really immature and not going with the flow of life, and accepting that Dave was doing what he wanted. I was immature at that time, I admit it.  I was still fairly fresh out of highschool, so highschool behavoir was second nature to me. I could yell and storm out as well as anyone. I must emphasize that I'm not that person anymore. What someone wants to do to themselves, as long as it causes no lasting damage, is fine with me. Tatoos do not consist of lasting damage, neither does piercings... its just something I chose not to do. So, I guess I just really hope I didn't run Matt off by showing that I did have a controlling side, at one time. ::sigh::
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm very proud of myself today. I stayed home (mostly) to get the living room decorated for Christmas. And with the exception of the video clutter on top of the tv and all the cords near my computer, I think it looks damn good!  Too bad mom will probably destroy it tomarrow. Not through ill intentions, but because its not Christmas with out the tree being over loaded with cheesy Hallmark ornaments. Right now it looks extremely Victorian with white lights, burgandy and gold velvet ribbon, burgandy and ivory velvet bows, and cream and gold glass balls.  The mantel is framed with white/silver velvet ribbon with a large burgandy bow and two burgandy stockings. Its topped with candles, angles, my love music mirror, and my mom's silly christmas pig tea pot (had to leave some of mom in the room)  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You REALLY can't go back. And in all honesty, I don't think its a desireble thing to do really.  So, this comes to what I did last night. I went to see a play at my old highschool. I knew someone in the cast and had heard that it was an interesting script. Ya. The script wasn't too bad, but it left a whole lot of loose ends, but that wasn't the players fault at all.   The set, however, bugged me. It was a drawing room set with five doors, but the walls were shorter than the doors by about   six inches. It didn't really do anything about the script or the playwrights intentions.   The lights also bugged me.  I am aware that the school just bought an new lighting system and they wanted to play with them to their fullest capabilities, but turning on isolation spots, that were too wide, to allow one character to talk to the audience about his work with the other four. Three of whom were retarded and the fourth a sciczophrenic who thought he was a golf pro.  If there had possibly been some sort of a fade division between the different lighting elements, rather than feeling like someone had flipped on a light switch, it might not have bugged me quite so much.  The thing about the production that bothered me the most had nothing to do with the actors, costumes, or any other element under the artistic staff's control. It was the audience. They were not the well trained audience of the civic theater that I have become accustomed to, it was an audience that would have been much happier at a sporting event. They were actually whooping at the appearance of  certain actors. Very disturbing.... That and I'm completely convinced that the fact that I was in the same building that I still refer to as a prison. I was never happy there, and even though there is a different director there than when I was part of the program, I still don't think anything of value can cross those footlights.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't get it. While a lot of things that people should take extremely seriously they don't, like other people's feelings. And then there are a lot of things that people shouldn't take seriously, like the meaning behind the song choices in s mix cd, that they do.  The mix cd thing is driving me nuts right now. I told Matt that I was going to send him a mix cd so he would have something new to listen to on the way back from Denver. So he asked me how it was coming the other night. I had to tell him it was a work in progress, because I don't even think about it really until I actually make it, unless a song I hear on the radio especially strikes me for some reason... oh well. I'll finish it tonight and get it into the mail for tomarrow.  That way  it will definately get there before he leaves on the 22nd.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shoes. I'm not sure what the attraction to them is... and I kind of wish I did, because I love them and continue to buy them, even when I no longer have space to put them... or when my dad is quoted as "you have so many damn combat boots that you're never going to wear any of them out."  ... but its a weird addiction that many women have and most don't think about, and are probably happier for it.  Oh well... they'll look really cute with my skirt and sweater.. it'll give it a bit of an edge. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK. I officially hate people. Its not as if the things that happened on September 11th weren't bad enough, but now there are people suing the airlines that were hijacked. Right.... its the airline's fault that this horrible woman's husband was scared before he died. Its obviously their fault that he died at all.  Right. so as if the airlines aren't having enough problems since the attacks because the sheep in this country are too afraid to fly. And now they're going to be bankrupted by people wanting to profit from all the goings on...... yea, I hate people.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well. The holidays have come and gone without too much of a hitch. Although I'm starting to wonder about why I even bother getting half of the people on my lists anything at all. Not that the Gizmo Furby  wasn't much apreciated, or the box of sharpies, but when it comes down to it, I get so paranoid about whether or not anyone's going to like what I got them that I don't really enjoy anything about the days that we exchange gifts until that part is over with and I get the reaction (god(s) forbid that the person doesn't like what I gave them).  Anyway. Spent some time with the family, and managed to miss the one holiday tradition that I really like. Which is left over turkey made into turkey and noodle soup by my grandmother. again, oh well.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What have I learned today... and this past two years for that matter? Nothing matters. You can live a completely clean and healthy life (not eating a whole lot of red meat, not drinking, not overindulging on sugar or anything else, excercising daily, etc) and you're still going to get cancer, diabetes, and heart disease. I'm thinking that I might take up smoking and become an alcoholic, because then I'll at least deserve to get all of these wonderful things, rather than just be sentanced to them because of my parentage.   Reason for the rant: it appears that my dad is going onto his second bout of cancer. The first was colon cancer and this one appears to be located in his liver. I've never heard of liver cancer before, or even the possibility of it. Not that my dad needs his liver all that much... he has a drink of wine every.......... two or three years, and tonight was supposed to be that one time for this year... but no more. Its insane.   I should be really happy that they've caught whatever this is really early. They still don't know what they've caught, that'll involve lots more painful and debilitating tests. Then probably another round of chemo. At least this time I'm here to get in everyone's way and for the general population to pity. whoooo.  Oh, and my favorite, to be talked to like a 9 year old when the diagnosis are explained to me by my mom. The only reason I know anything about what the next round of tests is, is because I walked in from getting groceries when my dad was explaining it to my mom.    I guess I really am made of porceline and should be kept in a plastic bubble. At least then I wouldn't have a clue about what was going on in the outside world and it wouldn't matter because I wouldn't be expected to live very long.  
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Growing up I was (and mostly still am) the perpetual Peter Pan. I Won't Grow UP!.... but this has created some sort of problems for me. I really don't want to grow up and as such, don't have the capacity to look out for myself. I can't hold on to a job for very long, because I just get bored with it. I don't want to continue to do the same things over and over, but I can't find anything that I enjoy at all.  I've been in school for so long that I don't want to give that up. I haven't graduated, even though I've been in college for 5+ years. and I can't even settle on major anymore. I was a technical theater major for a very long time, but with my move to a different school, I've had to give that up. So for now I'm a theater major (have to take the acting crap) but I want to have a job (teaching tech theater to third graders) and can't take any classes that are offered from the theater dept. So I'm adding a major. History.   Do I want to teach highschool history? I don't know.  Will I be able to get my teaching certificate? Don't know that either.  Am I staying in Kansas simply because I really like the person I'm dating and don't want to leave him? Too scary to really think about. Why am I still stuck  in this weird rut letting my parents take care of me, even though I'm 23 and should be able to do it myself?  If I could answer that I would have most of this problem worked out.  ACK! I don't know what to do, but I have to make $2500  + to pay off my credit card debts, plus cell phone bills and other things... then I have to start to make enough money to afford and apartment and food and all that stuff. I have no idea how I intend to do that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that relating to people is so hard? They are, afterall, basically the same amalgamation of little bits of matter. But each amalgamation sees whats going on around them in such different ways that its basically like trying to have an intelligent conversation with a goldfish. No one can see what the others are seeing, or can come to an agreement that while we're both looking at a tube of chapstick, that it will not definately turn into something dangerous.  Now all that was a silly way of talking about  how differently people see relationships. Who gets to decide who is in and who is not in a relationship? Do both people have to agree that it is, indeed, over and there is no reason to try to continue before the relationship is in fact over?  I remember that the character George faced this problem on Seinfeld once. He tried to break up with the girl he was seeing (or possibly engaged to) and she said she'd think about it. This was laughed at by the general population, but I'm seeing that it is a definate reality for lots of people in society.   Then you add into the mix the problem that children are created but the parents don't like eachother, or rather, maybe one parent loves the other and won't go along with the fact that the other parent is only in the general vicinity of the other because of the child.  One more layer of crap to this is: yes divorce is hard on children, but what happens when not only were the parents never married, but they broke up before the child was out of the first trimester.   Sadly, I already know what my reaction to this situation would be, but I wish there were other ways to react than yelling at the parent that doesn't want to be in the relationship that they should still sleep together, even though they can barely stand talking to eachother on the phone, because it will increase the mother/father bond and make them better parents. I just DON'T get it.   And somehow, I know that by being the significant other of the parent that no longer wants to be in  the relationship, I'm going to make something harder for someone..... but who that is and whether or not its worth it has yet been seen.  And I'm completely aware that this is probably not the best venue to talk out my issues with it, because someone might not want others to "know her business" god forbid that the other person involved think they had anything to do with it.   
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am a punching bag. I think I always knew this, but I am now completely aware of the fact. When I don't tell my mom things going on in my life, I get yelled at. I would possibly accept this more if I was still in highschool... or maybe if I was still in my teens... or if I wasn't nearly legal to rent a car! But, I do live in her house so I suppose I should tell her damn near everything.....hmmm. nope. because when I do I get yelled at for what I do tell her.  Tonight I told her that my boyfriend thinks I need to go to a chiropracter to get my spine straightened out. Its not scoliosis, but I can't stand up straight. And I have a cavity and need to get my eyes checked.... so I'm obviously trying to sabatoge myself.  I understand that I don't have full coverage health insurance anymore. In fact, I barely have insurance at all. I'm Still a STUDENT! I don't have a big job that pays for my health care... so I don't care about money... its not that I'm trying to take all of it, I just don't pay attention to it.  I almost wish she would say the same damn things to my dad, since he's retired and doesn't have insurance from his job anymore either... and he was smart enough to wait until he was retired to get cancer. Its all our fault......... ok, so when I pointed that out, it wasn't as wel recieved, but still.  I really want out of this house. I hate having to live off of them as it is, os I don't know why she has to make it harder. Its not as if sehe wouldn't be extremely hurt if I should try to leave and strike out on my own.  So basically, nothing I can do is right.yea
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My boyfriend's ex-girlfriend had her baby today. She went into labor at .... oh who the hell cares! She was in labor for an Incrediably long time, and I'm pretty damn sure that there's something wrong, because I still haven't heard from Matt... no one has. He's been at the hospital since 6 yesterday, and I drove by his house on my way home from rehersal (down the street from his house) at 11 and he still wasn't home. WORRIED! The baby's really small, and I have no idea what's going on. GRRR!!!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its over.   Not life in general, but the part of mine in which I can go to my dad with really dumb questions, like, "where did you put my w-4s?" or why Did you want to keep every tractor that you've ever owned... in the yard where everyone can see them?... fortunately I got an answer to the first question, unfortunately I will never know the answer to the second.   He finally let go today at 6:30pm. And honestly, he's more popular than I ever would have thought. All the nurses really liked him, and several of them were crying when they found out he wasn't going to make it.  I think I'm almost out of tears, but not quite. I think I can muster a few more while writing this.   My mom isn't handling it well at all. She might be better tomarrow, when the effects of severe sleep deprivation are lessened, or she might be worse, because when you're extremely tired, a chocolate milk shake does seem to fix some of your problems. I guess I'll find out tomarrow.  I have the best boyfriend in the world. He's now asleep on my couch because he wouldn't let either of us drive home from the hospital, so he can't get to his car until tomarrow. He's been there for me and my mom for the past several days, pretty much as soon as I found out it was hopeless for my dad. I don't think I've gone a night without him since Sunday, which doesn't seem to be all that long, but it is when  you realize that he's a new daddy (and a damn good one at that) and spends most of his free time with his  baby  but has been coming over to my house after putting her down for the night so that I wouldn't be here alone.   I should sleep.  Tomarrow is going to be awfully hard.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I guess its been a really long time since I've had time to post, and now its about the only thing I can think of to do that will keep me from losing my mind.  The last post was inconsequential. Nothing really changes. Catlyn (Matt's baby) is doing really well. And it didn't make any real difference on our relationship, so I guess thats going well.  But.  I'm sitting in the basement library of the hospital waiting for my dad to die. There isn't anything anyone can do for him, besides make sure he's comfortable and clean. He's been here for more than three weeks, and up until Saturday, we thought he was going to be fine. He had 2/3rds of his liver removed because of cancer. And while he was recovering from that, because the liver regenerates, it wasn't functioning. I guess he's the only one who really knew how bad it was, but when the doctors found out on Saturday, they kind of gave him permission to give up. He's been in a coma since 9pm on Sunday. Its deeper now. And whats weird is its not the liver thats going to kill him. Its his lungs. They're filling up with fluid, and when they're full, he'll go. So now we're just waiting.  Mom won't leave the room. She hasn't been home in five days. The nurses felt sorry for her last night, so they let her take a shower in an empty room down the hall. She keeps kicking me out though, because she feels like she's protecting me from something if I'm not in there. So I get to go home and feel helpless there... and call his family that he's not talked to in several months. That was fun.   You know, there is nothing that causes fear in a person than from hearing from your brothers child, who you haven't seen in about 10 years calling for him.  I said goodbye yesterday, and the day before, because they didn't expect him to make it through either night.   I don't know what to do.  I had better go back to the room.  Mom's going to try to make me go to my Anthropology class tonight... I don't think thats going to happen.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm aparently not dealing with this as well as I thought I was. Its not as obvious as I would have guessed, but the loss of my dad is affecting my interpersonal relationships. I'm not entirely sure how to deal with people right now. And I'm kind of afraid that I'm going to lose the best guy I've ever met because of it. He thinks I'm dealing with everything that is going quite well, but isn't sure why I'm acting funny. I don't even think I noticed it until this morning. I Know he's not doing anything that would make him deserve me to distrust him, but thats what it feels like.   I really hope that he's understanding about this. If I can, I'm going to talk to him about it tonight, but he might be able to see his daughter tonight. For his sake, I really hope Ginger lets him. She's going to ruin that poor little girls life by telling her, right from the start, what a horrible man her dad is. Just because the little princess didn't get what she wanted. She thinks that because she got pregnant, he should be hers for the rest of his life. And at one point in time I would have agreed, I guess. But it would be worse for all of them if he was still with her, because she would be telling him that he's worthless and needs to sell out to support them. She makes him feel bad enough about himself with the little time he sees her and Catlyn, let alone if he was there all the time.   I wish I could do something to help him, but he won't take anyone's advice that he needs to enlist some legal aide. I think I'm going to research some past cases to see if I can convince him that he's going to forfeit all rights to his little girl if he waits too long. I also think that the fact that he was raised by a singe mother and isn't completely (if at all) sure who fathered him, is hindering him in trying to take some control away from a psychotic mother. I don't know, but research is about all I can do, even if he doesn't ever use it.  To that end I'm starting another blog.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Update on my sick kitty.  She's staying at the vets office for a few days so he can observe what's going on with her. GR
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I saw something completely and randomly offensive on my way home from work today.  I passed a church, which while I don't agree with their tactics aren't normally blatantly offensive, has now sunk to new lows. I happened to read their events calendar while passing.... and on one of the days in the next week is something called "Jews for Jesus".  Now, I admit that I'm not really up on my Torah, but I thought that a major difference between the Jewish faith and the Christian one is that the Jews are still waiting for the messiah, and the Christians have picked one already. As such, "Jews for Jesus" would be Christians, and should no longer be called Jews..... ah, what do I know.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why is it that everything has to go bad at one time?  There's a lot of stuff breaking down in the house, but what's bothing me the most is the health of my cat. I have four cats, and for the most part I kind of grew up believing that cats were indestructable. I have one thats still going strong at 21 years old. But one of my babies is really sick. She'll be 2 on Sunday and she can't eat or drink without throwing up. Her sister is fine, so its not contagious... but still. I took her to the vet yesterday, and he proscribed pudding textured cat food and antibiotics. Its not doing anything. She's still really sick and is getting worse. GRR!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One class down, one more to go. I found out today that I tried to drop my classes ten days too late. Therefore, it has to go through the professors whether or not I fail their classes. I wrote everyone I could, the professors and the associate vp of academic affairs (she can bypass the whole ordeal and back date my withdrawl papers so that it doesn't have to go through the professors. But to cover my butt, I wrote the professors too. One of them, the one whose class I really didn't want to drop, wrote back immediately saying he always drops students passing. Yea. Now that leaves the blowhard. The one whose class I Really hated going to and don't mind dropping. Hopefully he won't be an ass about losing someone to listen to him drone about his kids. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is a better and  brighter day. Sort of. Matt and I are doing much better, after a really horrible weekend. Not because we were angry with each other, but because we're both frustrated in our career choices at the moment. Yesterday was the worst for him, not so bad for me except that I was with him while he was being depressed.  Yesterday was also my mom's birthday. I got her an icecream cake from Baskin Robbins, made dinner, and got her a gold necklace. Which all made her cry. Not because I was evil, but I think because dad and I always got her jewlrey for birthdays, valentine's day, mothers day, and christmas. I was just continuing the tradition. Besides, she had been drooling over the type of necklace I got her for a while now (herringbone).... She was actually happy about what I did for her, but didn't know how to deal with that.  Now for career stuff: I'm dropping out of school, temporarily. I had two classes this semester that I haven't been to in three weeks. I knew I was going to drop one of them but now I've realized that I can't catch up with all of the stuff that I've missed with the concentration problems I'm having right now.   Maybe I'll be in school forever, I don't know. But I guess it doesn't matter. I'll finish eventually... and if I don't I'll be a professional student.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I might just graduate. Weird. I decided to go in to get a schedual book today for next semester, wasn't really hoping for much, since the advisor told me that they weren't going to offer most of the classes I needed for another two years, but I thought I should give it a chance.  Oddly enough, they're offering 3 of the 5 classes I still need. Hopefully I won't have any problem getting in to those classes, but this semster I'm also going to be smart and get my advising done early enough to teleregister. I think I'll do my gym classes too, just to get them out of the way, since thats the only gen-ed classes I still need. Whooohooo!  No idea what I'm going to do after that, maybe stay in school for another seven hundred years and get my teaching certificate.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have an idea.  I don't think it would make anyone happy, but its still an idea. Cruise ships  are always looking for theatrical technicians. I happen to be a theatrical technician. I also happen to hate being in Kansas. However.  I don't want to abandon my mom, a  cruise line wouldn't let me bring along a cat or a boyfriend, and I don't know that I could deal with having to live in my room on a boat for months at a time.   If it was on Carnival however, I would probably only be on board for a week or two at most, then might get some time to fly home and see people. I just don't think that I have the courage to do it. I don't know. I just don't know.   I don't want to leave Matt, I hate being separated for a day or two, I don't think I could handle a month or two. And then there's the ever present fear that he would find someone else while I was gone.  Maybe I'll just write and see if I can get some information, that wouldn't hurt me.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not gainfully employed. Which is not to say that I'm not productive, it just means that I'm no use to the market economy. Well, not much use in any rate. I have some money, only god knows how I managed not to spend everything like I normally do, but I don't have any coming in. So I have to be especially careful.  I would like to eventually move out of my mom's house, because I will hate myself if I stay. But, as I have no idea what I actually want to do in life, I have no idea in which direction to point my education so that one day I can become useful to the capitalist society. I guess I'll have to pick up some crappy job that I'm way over qualified for so that I can pay for life until I become even more over qualified for it. ... eeep.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    more quizzes
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           urlLink Which John Cusack Are You?     Been taking fun quizzes tonight.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      End date on my sick kitty. She was put to sleep on Friday. The vet thinks she had some sort of luekemia, but not necessarily feline luekemia. If its FeLuk my other kitties may have caught it, but if its something else I may only have to worry about one of them. They're doing an autopsy to find out. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm pretty sure I lost a few IQ points tonight.  I watched the movie Zoolander. I thought that it was possibly like Josie and the Pussycats, completely aware that it was a silly subject and would be done making fun of itself. It wasn't. I used to like Ben Stiller so much, but now I'm not so sure. I still like Jerry Stiller, as Zoolander's agent, but the whole thing was just mind stoppingly idiotic. I don't recommend this one, at all.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I should probably pay more attention to whether or not I've disconnected from the internet. I've been connected for over 3 hours, and didn't realize it until I went to resign-on, thinking I had signed off more that 2 hours ago. Ooops. I hope my  grandmother didn't think that someone had come in and killed us and in the process had knocked the phone off the hook.  Its odd, but she does think like that.   I am also now a redhead, well, again. My blonde streaks were showing a little too well and my roots were growing in, so I chose an even brighter shade of red than I had tried before... or so I thought. I don't even think Matt's going to notice.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh YEA! My favorite Buggs Bunny cartoon. "Kill the Wabbit" I thought that they were never going to play it again. I've been watching almost every buggs show on cartoon network and haven't seen it in years. Until tonight. I flipped on cn and there it was. I didn't even really know that they played buggs and daffy at 2am. Whoohooo!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess my theory that if I don't talk, things won't get worse is a bad one. Its not that Matt and I broke up over it, but its been "bothering him" that we don't talk anymore. When I get upset, I stop talking for some reason. I guess that it seems like the more I talk, the worse the problem gets.  Now he thinks its because he's not well enough educated. I read a bit too much and actually can tell people, from a picture, what Hadrian's Wall is. Funny that. From all of the people I've hung out with, I normally feel like the least intelligent. Especially if you've ever talked to the person who maintains www.fidius.org . He and I hung out for a long time, and he's incrediably intelligent. Its almost impossible to keep up with some of his conversation strains, because it just comes out of nowhere. Matt on the other hand, has more practical knowledge. While he is a massage therapist (for a little while longer, at any rate) he's still more scientist than philosopher. Hopefully we can get through this and find things to talk about. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dislike my new job.  I am now very apreciative of higher learning, or more to the point, the capacity to learn higher activities. I actually never realized that there were people in the world that have problems following a chain instructions repetitively. I'm completely bored out of my mind at the absolute lack of thought needed to complete my job. While I don't believe trained monkeys could do it, and I wouldn't be able to do it for much longer than I'm going to, these people seem to be lacking most of the major mental processes needed to sustain a normal carreer.  There are obviously exceptions, as I'm in there (not really supposed to sound as condescending as it does) and there are others, but anyone over the age of 25 in there has no options but assembly line production. The rest of us were unlucky enough to think that we were going to be doing computer work . 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got to do something completely different tonight.  I used to go to Laughing Matters, and improv comedy troupe in Topeka about once every two months, or every other performance. I haven't been to see them since August or so, since one of the members of the troupe and I ceased dating. It really wasn't the breakup that made me stop going, it was the fact that if you watch them too much they get really old. I'm thinking I should go back for their show in May.  However, tonight, I was part of that company's sister company. Senior Class. Their normal technician was having some problems at work so she couldn't be there for the show tonight. They asked me to fill in. Its still improv, but all of the actors are over the age of 50.  Now keep in mind that they are not professionals, by any means.   And a few of them have Really short memories. But it still wasn't the worst thing I've ever been a part of. They were really nice, and while not always funny, they at least tried. And weren't afraid to push the envelope.  I looked at the audience, and most of it was made up of people over the age of 50, three exceptions being the artistic director of TCT and  his wife and a random little girl, who I think was there with her grandfather, and they came up with more interesting topics than the drunks that go to Laughing Matters.   The cast even asked me to go out to Applebees with them after the show. I declined, but not because they were all old, but because I'm shy and they are a pretty tight group.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't understand what is wrong with the people I work with. They seem to think that they're really supposed to get paid for sitting around and doing nothing, rather than what the supervisors tell them to. I do think that the job sucks, but rather than bitch the way they do, I would quit. They however, just bitch. Its not just about the job either. I've been told that I'll figure it out when I get older but..... insert really shitty depressive non-supported by evidence crap here. It just sucks the life out of me to have to listen to it.  Today it was that statistics are lies. Which can be true. But when talking about approximates  in populations, their about the onyl way to come up with a number. Yet she decided to explain to me how wrong I am for even remembering the number.  GAK!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I notice the most random things while driving home at  midnight when I have to be up at 530 the next morning and have been up since before  7 that morning. Like the fact that the fog just hangs right above the road in the perfect spot so that I can still use my headlights. Or that one of my neighbors is missing, something, as he has put up a neon orange  sign in his yard that says "reliv" or something really close to that. Too bad that when you're this tired, you do'nt remember things for very long.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I both love and hate the way my brain works. Its able to wrap itself around complex inter-personal problems and find possible solutions. That would be the part I love. The part I hate is the conditions it needs to work. Apparently, unlike a normal human brain, mine functions best on the delustions of sleep deprivation, going so far as to let me get enough sleep to make me REALLY tired (aka 3.5 hours) before waking me up to continue mental torture. So I didn't go back to sleep before I went to work.  But possibly I've figured out a solution that might save my relationship.yea.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've heard this before, but never really thought it was true, that a house will miss its owners when they leave. I honestly am starting to believe that the only reason the house I grew up in is still standing is that my dad loved it.  Now that he's gone its falling down around our ears. Its kind of spooky. We knew there were some problems with the house even before dad went into the hospital, but it was all completely managable. He was going to fix it. And we never guessed they were quite as extensive as they are now. It started with a couple of leaks. The upstairs toilette was leaking or something into the ceiling above the downstairs bathroom. Not too hard to fix, but it went on for a while because mom and I were at the hospital and didn't notice it. So now the upstairs bathroom's floor is sinking. Nothing too terrible, its not like its actually going to fall through, yet.  Then there is the weird spots in the middle of the house where the ceiling is just falling off. But there really isn't all that much of that.  Lastly, the piece de resistance,  half of the ceiling in the kitchen fell off this morning. Not like the floor fell through and there's a hole... well actually, since its on a part of the house that doesn't have a second level, you can see through to daylight. The biggest problem is that the roofers haven't had time to come fix the places where the shingles had blown away in a winter storm.  I'm starting to think it might be time to buldoze and run, but I Know mom won't agree.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its hard to say it, but I understand her timing. Its not hard to figure out that if you go after someone for child support who isn't making any money, then you're not going to get anything. So she waited until he got a real job. But trying to have a working relationship with him in regards to their daughter and going to a lawyer with out saying anything is just playing dirty. She could have waited for him to at least get one paycheck.  So Matt has to go to court. Her lawyer sent over paperwork today, I guess, because she wants child support. There is no issue with that. Its just that she should have said something. They could have possibly worked it out with out lawyers. Some people do do that. But I guess she feels like she's been scorned, as Matt wouldn't take her back last week, and hell hath no fury.....  I honestly don't think that its a terribly bad thing that they are going to court. She's not going to get everything she wants. Or at least I hope not. If I were Matt, and I"ll admit he doesn't really have the money for a good lawyer, but I would try to get my lawyer to request a psychiatric evaluation of Ginger. Since she's been psychotic for as long as I've heard of her. She needs help and that would help Matt not have to pay to never see his daughter.  Its also going to shoot her in the foot because if the court finds the way it normally does, she'll be stuck in Topeka. She won't be able to move away without appropriate court consent.  And last I heard, she was planning to move in less than a year.   And what is my part in this? None. Just that Matt called to tell me about it. He sounds so hurt and he won't let me come over and  give him a hug or anything. Why the hell did he call? Just to upset me? Probably not, and possibly he wouldn't have just told me to stay  home if I had answered the phone when he first called.  Silly me, taking a shower and all.   God I want to get that girl where it hurts, in the paycheck. In the fairest of all possible worlds, the court would find that she's not capable of giving Katlyn what she needs and causes an unhealthy environment, and then would award custody to Matt.... not that he really wants full custody, then she would have to pay child support.  Its not going to come out that way, and I really wouldn't ask that it did. He wouldn't be able to handle being a fulltime single dad, because he works nights as it is. He would have to put Katlyn in an allnight daycare, which doesn't exist. At least not here.   Alright, maybe I've gotten this off my chest now, but I think probably not. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm jealous. And I feel enormously guilty about feeling that way. Matt has very little freetime because of his two jobs, so most of what little free time he has goes to his daughter, which I understand. Doesn't mean that I have to be absolutely happy about it, but I'm not going to tell him that I'm jealous of that time. The time that gets me is that I do occasionally get to spend an evening with him its not just with him.  And yet when I say something to him about the fact that the only time I get to see him I'm with his best friend too, he tells me that I get to see him more than anyone else does. Yea, only because I showed up before his best friend did and left after. But the majority of the time was spent with the both of them.  Thats not to say that I don't like his best friend. Hell, he's dating one of my closest friends, who happens to be in another state and will soon be moving to France. Its just that occasionally I would like to see Matt without the entourage.   I actually feel like going and getting my own entourage so he can see what it feels like... but again, one of my closest friends is in another state and the other is married... no help there.   So, if I don't want to drop him, which I don't, I guess I have to live with the best friend time.... I just have to keep it separated in Matt's mind that I'm not just another friend thats always around. Thats happened in too many relationships in the past.   Pssst: Megs, don't say anything to Kirk, I haven't and don't really want Matt to get mad at me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't get it. Is it just a bad year? First I lost my horse, then my dad (which I'll admit is definately the biggest one) then one of my kittens. Now it looks like one of my other cats is about to go.  I woke up this morning and she was displaying some of the same symptoms that my kitten that died a month ago was displaying. Not only is it frightening, because it was incurable, but they're also rather gross. I got to wash everything in my bedroom this morning and clean up a lot of stuff.  Called the vet, but he was too busy to talk to me at the time, and couldn't get her in until tomarrow morning. The main problem is that when he did call back my mom talked to him. She tends to leave out major parts of the equation. Like she told him that the cat is peeing everywhere, but left out the fact that she's also throwing up. The first points to something minor, I don't know what the second point to. GACK!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I can get into my email again, YEA!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have just discovered my day of the year, and felt like this would be a good place to remind myself. May 26th is Grey Day. Whoohoo!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is quite annoying. I can't figure out what is wrong with my email account. All I know is that I can't get into it.  The server tells me that I've put in an incorrect password, please try again. I KNOW my damn password, but it doesn't work anymore. I wrote, using another email account, to the webmaster to tell them that I was having a problem on Friday... and I haven't heard back yet. I just want to get my email...probably so I can foreward it to another account and discontinue using the one that won't help me.  ?ACK!!! I'm disconnected from the world, and it hurts!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are some definate plusses to being unemployed. I got to spend almost everyday with my boy. Which was really nice because we didn't think that we were going to get anytime together once he started his new job.   And now for the downside: I have nothing to do when I'm not with him but play on the  computer. I found an apartment today, but I can't afford it. Which sucks because I didn't tell the landlord that. I took the application, because I want it, and could always hope that I get a job really fast.... who knows.   And lastly, I'm bored and have no money.... or very little. Grr 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sex in the City can make you think some crazy things.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Its odd what you notice in watching television at 3am. Right now I'm watching Gargoyles, the cartoon. I always knew that the person that was the voice actor for Xanatos was the same person as the voice of William Riker from Star Trek TNG. However, tonight I watched some of the  first episodes of Gargoyles and Goliath's "love" that he calls Angel (translates to Angela later in the series I think) is the same person who plays Deana Troi in Star Trek... I wonder how many other washed up actors from that series became cartoon voices for this series?  I know for sure that Will Wheaton didn't, because shortly after his last movie (after puberty hit him with a BIG ugly stick) he ended up answering phones at a technology company in Topeka Kansas. (I wasn't such a big fan that I followed him around or anything, I just live in Topeka)  Ok. time for me to stop this nonsense and get some sleep.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mosquitos are evil. I almost miss the fact that one of the harsh pollutants in the Bayou city was that they sprayed the entire city by air to rid the world of mosquitos. I am currently covered in bites... and it was because I wanted to enjoy the breeze and my new hammock. :( I  have to find a mosquito free zone to hang my hammock... and I think there's only one of those on my property..... inside the house.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why can't shopping for text books be as easy as it was when I First started college? Go to a website, enter your college and chose your classes... BANG! shopping done. Now you have to know all the isdn #s or just break down and buy them on campus. Ick.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am about to give up on computers as they are the most evil, frustrating inventions. They are actually more frustrating than people. I'm trying to install Warcraft 3 on the boy's computer. The problem being that it just doesnt bloody well feel like installing the damn thing. I can get it started, but when it gets to a point where I'm starting to feel hopefull about the whole process.... then, guess what happens......... no, not blue screen of death (that might be a welcome change) ... but it shuts the whole freaking thing down. Not restart, that would be ok I guess , but it just shuts off. GAAAAHHH!
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My rant for today: Girls who pretend to be stupid because "boys don't like smart girls" Well, this has been a rant for most of my life, but its getting worse by the day.  &nbsp; Today there were auditions for the improv comedy troupe that Willie is in. There is a girl that auditions, and who was cast, that is possibly the least talented actress I have ever seen. I have done several shows with her, and has very little talent.  &nbsp; Up until her last show, she has only had one character. Not that she's been type cast, but thats all she does. Someone that can't come up with more than one character in five plays can't be fast enough mentally to be successful in improv comedy. &nbsp; As for the pretending to be stupid part. The one character that she had used for all of the shows except that last have been the same character she plays for boys. The stupid useless blonde.&nbsp;  &nbsp; So, logically, if she's smart enough to be in improv and a boy that she likes goes to the show, she would have to pretend to suck at improv to impress him. Which would make her a bad casting choice. The director should have known better, since it took her until tech week to get a handle on her character... who is just an angry activist, and a role that I would have been perfect for... since its my type casting...... but you can't get a role if you don't audition for it, and I'm still not an actor. I digress. &nbsp; I'll admit to being friends with her ex-boyfriend. She did some psychotic things while they were dating, and because she was cute, he put up with it for a while. He is no longer willing to speak with her. He is also a talented actor. I wish that he would have auditioned, because he would have blown her out of the water, but he isn't staying in this horrible city anymore (more power to him) He guessed that she would be cast... but is in agreement with me that she'll be horrible. &nbsp; I've declared that I will not be going to anymore Laughing Matters shows, which is the improv troupe. I probably pissed Willie off by saying that, because he thought this girl did a wonderful audition.... and I had another friend get cast that I think is really funny.  &nbsp; I think what probably bothers me most about this is how attatched Will gets to the members of the troupe. I Really don't want her to be any more of a part of my life than she already is and he'll expect me to come out and hang out with all of them, and I just don't want to.  &nbsp; She's in the cast of the musical he's in now, and I HATE having to see her all the time now. With her being in LM, there will be no escape from her. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Its been a while since I last posted. Probably because I've been busy, but also because I didn't really need the outlet of a blog to get out my agressions.    Now I seem to need the outlet again.    &nbsp;  Willie and I moved in together in April. Which, one would think, would mean that we see each other occasionally. However, our scheduals&nbsp; are completely opposite. He works during the day and does shows at night. But he doesn't work a full forty hour workweek. He spends the rest of his waking time doing volunteer work at the local community theater.  Yea. &nbsp; Which means that he spends most of his time with little aspiring actresses.... most of whom I've worked with, but think have little to no talent.     &nbsp;  I really need to get out of this little town. I know almost everyone, and I'm starting to want to destroy most of them.     &nbsp;  Work's fine, but like all days you have your good and bad day. Dealing cards isn't what I thought I would be doing when I got out of college, but its better than doing what most other people I know are doing. The pay is better than anything else I could probably get. And it has pretty good benefits.     &nbsp;  Its also how I'm going to get the heck out of here. I can transfer between casinos, so when I feel like I've learned enough here, I'm going to transfer to Chicago, or somewhere else.    &nbsp; &nbsp;   &nbsp;   &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why is it that my freaking boyfriend is such an ass?    &nbsp;  He knows that I'm annoyed. He also knows that I pay the rent here and don't really have to let him live here. Yet, he still makes me feel like shit on a regular basis.    &nbsp;  I want him to choose me over his damn friends. Just once.&nbsp; He told me that we would go to this damn cast party for just a little while, knowing full well that I have to work in the morning. So when I started to fall asleep in a folding chair at 2am, he didn't really even want to leave to bother to take me home. So he found someone else to do it. Some one that I don't really know.     &nbsp;  I was gratefull to Kate for bringing me home, but its now 430 and the asshole is still not home.     &nbsp;  Why is it that he thinks I'm going to keep being the only one making a goddamn effort?    &nbsp;  I spend the majority of the time that I'm not at work alone. One would think that we were living in different states with the amount of actual time that we put in together. Yet we live in the same apartment. He does his shows, which would be different if maybe he was getting paid for them, then he goes to his castparties. Normally he drags me with him, in an attempt to show that he's not completely abandoning me to the theater. Which would be different if he didn't spend the entire party hiding from me. And then he wonders why I get annoyed.    &nbsp;  Its not fair to&nbsp; completely bring up all that I do for him to keep him alive, but its also not fair for him to completely take advantage of my good nature.    &nbsp;  I would like to occasionally feel taken care of and important.................. He tells me that he loves me right after he has told me that he's too tired to even stay up and watch a movie with me, which he has&nbsp; promised to do. "Tonight will be just for us"&nbsp; BULLSHIT!    &nbsp;  I can understand if he doesn't want to be in the relationship, but every time I try to talk to him about it he gets all upset that I don't just want to hear that he loves me, but I would like to be shown every once in a while.     &nbsp;  The thing that really sucks about this is that I can't sleep when he's not here. Every little sound startles me awake. I have to get up for work in less than six hours. I'm going to be a complete wreck.&nbsp; And I'm still awake. I came home more than 2 hours ago to get some sleep. I read until I couldn't keep my eyes open. Now I'm sitting in front of my keyboard trying to write out some of my frustration. However, it just seems to be getting worse.....    &nbsp;  And I still can't sleep.  
     

    
</post>


</Blog>