<Blog>


<date>22,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Tonite was yet another test of ones patience.I dont know how many times iIl have to sit through another steaming debate on the existance of entities. urlLink Nick  you know what im talking about.I dont care if your a ghost,if you know a ghost or if you've seen a ghost,and I really dont want to know the do's and dont's of comunication between yourself and the spirit.If I hear one more fraudulant " oh and this one time" story about ghosts Im going to kill.I know you've never seen one.So why lie ?Why not lie about something worth while? On the same note if I have to sit through one more uninspiring and down right depressing conversation on how much sex one person has.Not only will I kill this certain person,I will lobb the head off the next person who decides to rub it in.So you better watch out lovers of America,Im looking for heads.I belive I am doomed to lead a life half thought,pro me conversations.Its a curse but someone has to do it right?All I got out of this night is a nice couple minutes of harassment by john law.I was being accused of the infamous beer run.Which I did not commit.After about 10 minutes and a slew of the standard questions,where do you live?have you been drinking?whats your phone number?is this your car?have you been drinking?What gang are you from?Blah blah blah.Ok you have a nice night now.I sure will dick.Not only has this situation ruined my taste for the barley and hopps.I now have to here the person with me tell it to everyone in the vicinity of the happenings.So yet another test of ones patience.  peace............................ How did the show go  urlLink fellas 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      The trials and tribulations of everyday life are those of great books ,films,songs and people.What do these things create.Hope,hope for the future,hope for the past and hope for the now.Hope is an item easily lost and hardly found.What do you hope for? Some hope for themselves,some for others and some for all.Love lost ,love found,car keys,money and most of all hope.Should we hope for these things or should we hope that there is such a thing.Or is it just the carrot dangled foolishly in front of us?Are we using it selfishly or was it formatted for the individual?Mabey we should not hope for the now mabey we should hope for the later.Or should we hope to be hoped for?    peace 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Ok this is gonna be a short one i really dont feel like talkin too much.Tonite was a little shitty except for that 7 cans of the  BUD  I drank,and that lunchable i had at....lunch.Damn that little carton of crackers and cheese can satisfy even the savage beast.Andy tell the fellas I said yo,and its a damn shame about the EVIL SONG.It could have been a hit,TRL style.Tell nick I saw naked pictures of his mom on EBAY.Ok im out.   check out this  urlLink THIS BAD MUTHA FUCKA   Andy you got the site wrong................       urlLink this one 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today my brother said something to me that made me think.I dont know whether to take this as a really horrible put down ,or as a compliment.The bastard called me  FAT ELVIS .See here is the delema.Me personally i think fat elvis was alot cooler than skinny elvis.When he was fat he had the sideburns going.Speaking from the sideburn point of  view,ladies love"em.Oh yeah its true. He also had the whole karate thing going.We all know that fat dudes doing karate is cool.Thats also the time he was regulary called the KING.How cool is that?Cadilacs,jumpsuits,ladies,porkchops and gold chains what else do you need in life?The only thing skinny elvis had that fatty didnt,was the hips.I also think its really cool that people remember you in 2 stages.The skinny 1 and the fat 2.  If  my crew reads this .Good luck fellas,dont suck too bad. PLAY THE EVIL SONG DAMN IT! 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Ah yeah 36 hrs and im still going .(not fast but going). Whats up Andy thanx for the props playa.I think i will finish the  "Morning of sorrow " story now.  Well after my brief but life changing experience with the Bible kids, I decided to try and get some shut eye,but was that going to happen? I think not.It turns out to be an actuall service were people go around  asking to "trim"your trees,hedges or what have you.I have 4 trees  but if you put them all together you still dont get one.So i have to explain to this leather clad oaf ,manning a chainsaw that i do not  wish to render his services.             Who cuts trees in leather anyway? Is it for saftey precautions or what? So for about 10 min this guy is trying to sell me his shrub cutting idea, and i quote "  bro if you dont cut them now the damn birds will be shittin on yer car."   can you belive people actually pay this guy ?He also decides to tell me the complete work of art that  is his life.About how his old lady is expectin,he needs a new chain saw,did i see the guy win the million on    Who wants to be a millionaire  ,and blah blah blah.ten minutes may not seem long in the real world  but this guy had a time manipulator device.Ok i had nothin to put there sorry. So i finally get this guy to evacuate the domisile.When i get back to my 1974 waterbed,I check the tube, and whats on ........the mutha fuckin   LAST DRAGON  .There was no way i was going to miss this cinema event.So there gose the final hour and thirty of my sleepy time.   "Can you teach me some moves."              Bruce Leroy 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah im still up.im going on my 27hr,44min.right about now. Sounds fun huh?Well what the hell do you know?Its not like i haven't been trying to sleep.It seems that every time i try to get some well  deserved and badly needed R.E.M,something happens. I shall explain,about 10am when i first decided "hey its go time", for the first time in my life a jehovas witness gang decides to pay  my Bible fearin ass a visit.Ok untill this morning i thought this group of religious,  new age quakers were a myth.I thought they were just entities fabricated to teach  children the dangers of opening doors to strangers.Boy was i wrong .So now im faced  with a difficult decision.Do i a)kindly tell them that im not the religion type,or b)slam the  door in their faces like Craig in friday part 1.Man i wish i could have done that.But i fear my place in  hell isnt a lock just yet.  Ok part two of my morning of sorrow later  If you think hillbillies are funny ...well who dosent think their funny  urlLink check out this nasty site
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      well its about 9am and im still up ...surprising?......no i think not  Ive been up for almost 24 hrs. Yeah thats right! You got something smart to say?  Say it  to my face. Did I sound intimidating? No,ok. Now that ive figured this complicated piece of industrial technology lets see if i actually have anything to say. How many bet I dont ? 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Ok i finally figured it out . So congratulations cory you have a complete waste of time . If you want more blogs check out my Gs blog  urlLink right here
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      ok untill i get the hang of html this blog is going to suck! sorry bout that . like people are reading it anyway.........huh you bastards!..no just kidding i love you all!  like a good man once said.   "is it better to burn out or fade away?"  jack black 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      blah
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      blah
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Is it better to burn out or fade away   -Value  blah blah blah  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Hey there well this is the first time im using this so im still getting the hang of it. Bear with me . 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I really don't know what to say today. I have a loss for words, blogger block if you will. I think I may be trying to hard. Trying to hard to please. Trying to please the masses. Why? Who cares what you or you think? Truthfully I do. Its a sad fact but I have lived the better part of my life trying to please others. I could not start to tell you why it just is. I couldn't begin to tell you how to stop this bad habit. I hate it with every part of my soul. I spend every waking moment sometimes subconsciously trying to become a better person for the masses.Why ? Why do I care if my hair is combed or not. If my shoes are clean. All these things just so some person I've never met or will never meet wont think I'm a slob. Screw them and screw you if your one of those people I'm talking about. Ok I'm sorry I just freaked out for a moment or two. If you have been reading this you know about "THE DRAG OFF" well I know there is a part 4 but I haven't brought myself to write it. Anyway that particular night I took a few photos with my gender bending cousin, well the photos are back. I myself have not seen them but I can just imagine the look on my face. The shinerbock probably shows through my utter terror at the moment. I know when I get these I will immediately burn them. Last thing I need in my mediocre life is some photographs of me and a drag queen surfacing. So the will be torched. On a lighter note I heard my brothas played a good show. If you haven't seen or heard the guys do yourself a favor and don't. J/K . All you gotta do is look and the links on the side of this joint for "The Johnny Eulogy" and your golden. Well I have had enough of this endless game of who needs who the worst. I'm outty 5
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      My friends it is that time again. What time you might ask. Well I'll tell ya. Its time to let you inside. Inside the mind of yours truly. To those who know me, if you ask they may say.." well Cory really has nuthin up there but a few beans." At some moments these people are right. Are they? Tonight was your regular night of youth misfortune. As per usual not a single person has any idea of what or where to partake in our nights festivities. One again we are forced into the never changing ritual of getting in the car and just going. Truthfully I actually like this part I have a blast of a time each and every time we do it. Only problem is with 4 18 - 21 males in one car you get your run of the mill ideas for the evenings arrangements. You get your choice of hitting the local bar/ venue. Your local taco dispensary, which is always a favorite among the weak. Or the never fail, "Lets get some beer and drink in the desert!" If you are wondering about the whole desert thing, let me explain. You see the circle of friends that I have most are underage, not child molestation underage, just about 2 years away from being a legal upstanding citizen. You see? Ok so the desert is really the only place I can have a few with my friends. This situation really sux in its own beautiful way. The whole sitting in your good pair of pants (cause you know you only have one) in a huge pile of dirt, drink once cold but now luke warm KEYSTONE LITE. Desert flying creatures are trying at any chance they get to end their brief lives inside your beer. One of your bastard ass friends is reeking havoc on your freshly conditioned hair with huge clogs of dirt. Now that I think about this it sounds really shitty. For some strange reason some of the most fun I have had in recent months has come from the barren wasteland know as the desert. Tonight it was door number 2. The taco factory. I don't enjoy the place myself but what the hell. We spend about an hour or so in. I go on a straw attack spree, wounding anyone in arms length with a straw. We saw cactus jack, either it was him or a lost mountain man who has just found his way back to civilization after many a year living the grizzled life. So in conclusion I myself had an alright evening.   Go check this  urlLink playa hata's blogger 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I just got through reading my friend  urlLink ANDY"S  blog and it inspired me to come and do the same. My friend has hit upon a nerve in my conscience. You must read. Andy that's some deep shit my brotha. Not many people have felt inclined to share the secret drive time story. To some people this is a sacred and lonesome ritual. I have this very same train of activity. I go about driving my run-down 93  urlLink  Oldsmobile Achivea  to the depths of the gas gauge. When I'm driving my car around this fair city, I find myself at peace. A rare occasion because usually I am ridden with compulsive worrying in my tender age of 21. This is the only time I feel like me. It may sound weird to some, but to those who have been enraptured by the beauties of  usually occupied roads, but at this hour empty ,desolate, barren streets, the road is a safe haven for the broken hearted , the lonely, and yes the righteous. The fuselage of your automobile becomes everything to you. Your mother ,father , lover, and your mistress. All you have in the world is the two cd's you brought on your journey into the unknown. The street lights leave lasting impressions on your eyes, the stray dog you slow down to avoid, the way your usually shitty car stereo sounds in the empty night air. All of these senses and emotions make for one ride you could not explain in a million years. Its better than any roller coaster you have ever been on. Time has  lost all meaning in this ride into oblivion, a mere two, three hours have gone past you and you feel as if you just left home. The place where nothing makes since. The place you cringe to return to, you want to stay out , you want to stay were things make sense. Green means go and red means stop...................simple. The night air moving past your face with suave and grace. You think to your self if gas and money were had meaning at all, I would drive forever never to return. But as the saying goes..."all good things must come to an end", either the movie ended, the song is over , or your out of gas there is always a time to return home. Not just from your drive to know where, but in everything, love, books, driving, walking ................life. There's always time to go home.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today was your usual shitty,boring day. Nothing remotely interesting or informative happened. Only thing I could say that was worth while was that hour I spent at 4am watching ROCKO'S MODERN LIFE. Man I love that show its the best and its been a dog's age since I've seen it. Other than that nothing clever or up beat to report. Right about now it's raining GOD'S fury in my neighborhood, mabey it's all those jokes about the beast(SATAN) I made last night. If so I'm sorry man. I was just fool'n'. There is this huge river of brown rain water creeping toward my door step and its a little freaky. Now I have to go a reset all my damn clocks cause the bloomin light went out. I wouldn't be complaining about the clocks but when you have about 7 of them it becomes an endurance test of the mind. My mom is preparing the first-aid kit as if the world was ending, sure there is a shiet load of rain but if you lived here you wouldn't worry your little head. By tomorrow all the water will be gone and the sun will be roaring at a whopping 124 degrees. So I'm not even worried. I'm just going to sit back and drink my frost glass of.......................TEA. Ummmmmm that's what life is aboot(Canada). Last night I repeatedly got the athlete knocked out of me in my constant failure as an air hockey player. I will have my revenge  urlLink NICK . My day will come when I am the worlds greatest air hockey player, I will rejoice and then I will realize that becoming the international air hockey champ is nothing to be proud of. Them the sorrow and self- pity will arise. Then I will call upon my dark lord to smite my enemies. Yeah right I don't own enough black to have a dark lord. I will just resort to good old fashioned roughing up.    we've only just begun.................The Carpenters 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      This weekend has been a strange one.Nothing obscure or grief ridden,just strange. I have found myself  recently having the power of seeing through peoples happy, carefree, and other wise insightful facades. I can really see what people are feeling.They're not fooling me. The thoughts of giving up something so important for hopes for a great future show through on some. The feeling of being left behind and not knowing what the future holds for the both shows through. The thoughts of passed nights arguments and drunken words of betrayal and the true feelings of a trustworthy friend. I see them all, I know what these people are feeling and thinking. It's a clever trick to try and hide behind the face of grace and laughter. I have been the master of this skill for a many year. I know that at sometime someone was given the gift of insight, and they saw through my tricks and unloaded the same conclusion. Do I still have this wall of silence in front of me? In lesser terms I would say. Some days the wall is an impenetrable force only I can let down. Others its unlike a pain of glass easily broken and easily fixed. The only thing I have not been able to figure out is how to remedy these affections. Maybe that's the twist. Maybe its not for us to figure out.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Last nights events unfold like a child safety video.1)  urlLink Dont drink and drive . 2) Dont stare at a car full of young urban black men, you might have a gun waved at you as to say" dont mess or you might get shot." 3) Dont ever ,ever ever give rocks to a bunch of drunkin males in a pitch black desert. What will happen you might ask? I'll tell ya, you get 6 boys running around a desert all commando style throwing rocks at each other from a distance. All we needed that night was one head injury then the fun would have ceased. Luckily no one was seriously injured. We had groups of twos wandering out into the black desert night only to reimerge behind you with a pocket full of rocks bombarding their way toward you. Semi solid clumps of dirt hitting your bare limbs, spare dirt filling your eyes. You could only see the outlines of bodies against the moon. Silence, the bombs have stopped, ah relief, we can now drink in peace. Just as you were returning to enjoy your now lukewarm beverage. You hear a large rock land in the soft ground next to you. The war has begun. Souls shouting in the distance for you to stop throwing rocks. You ablige, till............................ you feel the dirt in your hair from an uncertain enemy. The battle rages........................................
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Part 3 of " THE DRAG OFF"   As James departed up the steps he took one more look at my half and half cousin and shook his head in the manner of, YEAH I WANNA PEICE OF THAT. Then he was gone. I can hear the water from the toilets flow through the pipes right above my head. My shiner was now all but gone,I was desperatly in need of another. By now its about 9:00 we have been in this basement for about 1 hour and 15 minutes. Now I can hear the crowd growing. I can hear their footsteps on the ceiling above me, and I knew it was getting packed. My cousin is now putting the finishing touches on his gear. All that was left was the shoes and the wig. On go the shoes,these black heeled shoes.The heel on these shoes had to be at least 4 inches, so now he was towering over me. The final peice of the puzzle is being combed in his right hand. "Dose it look ok?" Yeah it looks good.  He bends over to place this monument of  dark brown ,streaked with a little blonde, synthetic fiber, false head of hair over his short, nappy, bleach blond hair. He tugs and pulls for a few seconds, stands upright. The hair is in his face,fiddles,moves it out of his eyes. "There we go,how do I look?" Good god man, the wig really puts it over the top. Before the wig I was thinking, man you are no good as a woman. After that wig was on I was corrected. I sat back and watched my cousin go from a 5'11,blonde haired,skinny black man, to a 6'3,brown haired,skinny black woman. I was freaking. At first I was thinking that this was a sad day in my family history, but then it got really funny. About now the ceiling above us was rattleing with the sounds of drunken, gay dancers.I was loathing the next step in this night. It was now time to go up stairs and reveal this finished product. We slowly climb the steps. The music slowly gets louder I belive at this moment it was "What I like about you ." from the Romantics. I open the door first, I step through first nothing out of the ordinary, but when my cousin step through that door it was like that scene in "From dusk till Dawn." when all the vampires started going nuts. In my version all the fruits started going NUTTS. "Oh my God girl you look so good." slap. "Girl you look fabulous." kiss. "You go boy." slap. Over and over and over. I heard these types of comments all night long. So now he has to do his victory lap. There were kisses on the cheek and ass slaps for years to come. " Ok its time for us to get our pitcher of beer on." My cousin announces to me. About this time I am more than ready for alcohol. Isacc/Diamond is bartending, my cousin orders a pitcher of beer. I down my first glass. Pour me another. Im up to my fourth glass and he's still on one. So Im starting to feel the sting of the brew. My cousin yells in my ear to overpower the music "Im hungry." Im thinking to myself........so! He tells me that there is food by the other bar. We head over, it was like a buffet but gay. When I saw a few of the items they had I started to laugh, cucumbers and meatBALLS. See. Everyone walking by me just had hillacious amounts of meatBALLS on their plates. It was about this time I realized why everyone was  into the T.V. They had the gay networks going. Just imagine a big wide shot of a beach, hey theres a couple laying in the sand ,lets get a closer look. WHOA! There dudes. That was all they showed, and drag queen competitions. My cousin taps my shoulder," I want you to meet Steve." Hand shake, a nod of the head. "Hi Cory so nice to meet you." Steve spoke to me in a effeminate voice. Steve was cool and a tad funny. He was your stereotypical gay guy.A little chubby,recieding hairline, open shirt exposing chest hair, and he had really bright teeth. Usually that would'nt have bothered me , but Steve liked to smile ,,,,,,,,,alot. Steve and my cousin spoke for awhile and Steve explained how he was'nt going to stay long because he had to get up early the next day. "Im sad I havent seen you in awhile and now I have to leave early, I really miss you." "Yeah I miss you too ." My cousin replied to Steve. They embraced for a second. They part ways . "We have to go back down stairs my dick is loose." WHOA! At any other time or place I would have stayed up stairs and gotten drunk as hell. Not that night. I was clinging on to him like I was a small child. Everywhere he went I went. Now we are heading back to the pit. I hear a voice, ah good ol' Isacc, wait a minute your not Isacc. Now this suave mutha trucka's name was Mario/Verona. Just like the city in Romeo and Juliet. Mario was cool ,but what made this guy even cooler was that he had a loyal man servant. This guy did everything Mario asked. Get my shoes, find my wig, tie my shoes, comb my wig, get me a drink, everything in the book was asked of,"we'll call him Luigi". Its now about 10:00 and im feeling the effects now more than ever, but instead of loosening me up I just got even more tense. By this time Isacc has returned to get ready for the show. Imagine a basement, drag queens, and a scared boy. This is the beginning of a skin flick, and truthfully I was thinking this. So Im freaking. ENTER JOEY, Joey was kind of a dick, but he was no queen, I found this out later as he swung his dick over my head at the bar I was drinking at peacefully. Thats all we need to know about Joey. My cousin is now behind the infamous black plastic changing into the performance gear. I shudder as I hear the tape being ripped from the roll. I know what this is being used for. " Do you have a black bra I can use?" Diamond askes my cousin. " Im wearing it." he replies. "Oh SHIT." Diamond is not happy with this. My cousin emerges a new woman. He is now wearing a silver half shirt and a matching pair of hot pants.Yeah yeah I know. Now Verona is now fully dragged and Diamond is the same. Joey is now sporting is finest rip away pants, and the man bitch is retrieving a drink for me andhismaster."Ladies and gentlemen lets have a warm welcome for the beautiful VERONA." The DJ announces. Mario walks to the dance floor,a BJOrk song begins and so dose the fun. Watching Verona flail on that dance floor was worth everything I had to endure that night.   I really did'nt think that this story would go on this long but it has. So stay in touch for ...Part 4 of "THE DRAG OFF"   mabey the last part.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Part two of "THE DRAG OFF"  So there I am watching my cousin transform into woman.Thats when I decided that this story would make one hell of a blog entry.Im drinking my shinerbock, really Im chugging this frosty beverage like it was the last one in exsistance.I figure it was just my way of coping with this strange night."Diamond this is my cousins first drag show."My cousin is explaining to Diamond,mabey he said this because I had this look of shock on my face or just to start conversation. "Honey after tonight you'll never be the same." Diamond spoke to me out of character. Her deep voice rattled my rib cage.Like I was sitting directally on top of a speaker. I just smiled.Thats the way I communicated the whole night. A series of nods and handshakes. It was amazing to see this human transformation before my eyes. Diamond was really good at what he did. You see he was'nt a drag queen by night he was full -time. i sat and watched as he glued false eye lashes to my cousins eyelids.Next lipstick.So around this time in the metamorphis my cousin looks like a hip - hop guy with lipstick on. See my cousin by day is your typical male, baggy jeans,shirts two sizes to big,nikes the whole nine.At about the moment this story took place he was dressed in overalls and nikes, and make up."Girl you look good." Complementing my cousin and the make - up job she did."Thank you Isacc."My cousin replied. "Girl i need to get up stairs and work now." Diamond informs us as he fiddles through his things.See Diamond had multiple jobs at the MINORS club he was a bartender,DJ,and a Drag Queen .Grabbing a few items and his purse Isacc kisses my cousin on the cheek "I'll see you up stairs sweety." Diamond rushes up the rickety steps. "Nice meeting you Cory." Same here.My cousin and I are now alone in the basement. "Hey Cory Im going to need your help in a minute." Ok.I replyed wordering what strange task I was going to have to perform. So now comes the crucial part of the transformation. "I have to go put my ass on." WHOA.He grabbs a padded pair of ass enhancing panties out of the duffle bag. These things are insane. Purple prince style velvet. He slides into a room divided by this huge sheet a black plastic. I can hear him shuffling around in there. It stops. He comes out donning these purple panties. I know hes family and all but I did not want to see this. My skinny cousin is now sitting in a chair in front of me covered in make - up , stuffed in these panties, and only wearing a pair of socks. Whoa. Whats next Im thinking, terrified to find out.After shuffling in the bag for a sec or two arrive a pair of panty hose. He struggles to put them on. After a few seconds of heavy breathing they are intact. Out comes this tiger striped dress, is that the dress you wearing tonight? " No this is just untill the show." You see they wear one dress to perform and one dress to get free drinks. I'll explain. There are guys who claim to be straight but enjoy the company of men in drag. My cousin explained this to me over the free pitcher of beer we recieved on account of one of these men. So now hes shuffling in the bag again this time he produces a group of foamy things. They seem harmless. They turn out to be a pair of hip pads to make you look like you have a shape,and a pair of foam breasts. Whoa. Hes stuffing these hip pads down the panty hose, "they dont look right, do they?" Huh,Um yeah they look ok. He slaps his thighs, lets out this haunting giggle. "Now its time for my tits." HUH. Into the bage he gose returns with a roll of duct tape. Whats that for? I ask. "Its to tape my tits on and to tape my dick down." SWEET JESUS. Really? "yeah." Im losing my mind . So now hes applying the tape to his foam breasts and sticking them to his bare chest. Slips on the dress, now heres where my help is needed. "Can you tie this for me?" Uh sure. With his hands gripping his foam tits I start to tie his dress. In my mind this was the last thing  I thought I would ever be doing. Tying my manly 24 yr old cousins drag queen dress. So I finish tying it and he turns around and asks me,"do my tits look ok?" I dropped my gaurd for a second, no there crooked. "Hows that?" Um ones bigger than the other one. "Oh shit." "How bout now?" Yeah your good. What the hell was I doing helping my cousin fix his fake breasts. Ive gone insane, its the basement there are basement fumes and old beer, just about the time I was thinking this someone decends the steps. " Oh girl you look so hot." " Thanks." "Oh James this is my cousin Cory ." "Hey nice to meet you." I nod my head. This James was a character on his own. This guy was huge, dirty tatoos of skulls and naked chicks. I think he got them in his , Im not gay phase. James is talking to my cousin, slaps his ass " I wanna make you my bitch, but your to pretty for me." My cousin replies " and your to white for me." They share a school girl giggle. " Ok im going upstairs now I'll see you up there. " Hey nice meeting you buddy." Same here....................................... part 3 of the "DRAG OFF" next time.  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Boy "O" Boy do I have a story tonight.Shall I start at the top.Ok at about 6:oo pm my cousin calls me and asks me if I could give him a ride downtown at about 7pm.Of course i said yes.So around 6:45 he calls and says he's ready.I hop in my car and drive to his house,I get there about 7 min later I go inside and low and behold he's not ready.No problem I say to myself I have nothing else to do.Then I notice he's putting things into this huge duffle bag.See these aren't your run of the mill type things for a man to have.Wigs,dresses,hi-heeled shoes,and a gang load of make -up.Ok see there have been rumors that my cousin is drag queen,after tonight he'll be alot more.After about 10min of waiting we are finally on the road.Were chatting, blah blah blah,"are you going to stay for the show?"he askes me.Um yeah,I reply in an uncertain kind of way.So I change the subject.I forgot what that subject was but anyways,he asks me if he can smoke in my car I say sure buddy go for it."But I dont smoke cigarettes."He breaks out this pot pipe and starts tokin away.Ah dosent bother me."Man I wouldnt be able to handle life if I didnt have this stuff."Whoa! So after about a 15 min ride in the car we arrive at the destination."Hey you wanna come in for some drinks?"Aw im broke."Dont worry about it I got ya."Personally Im not one to turn down free drinks so  IM OFF .We get inside and everyone indside has there glossy eyes strapped to the tele.My cousin says hi to some dude.Thats when I noticed the change in the atmosphere.They did not shake hands or even hug .They kissed each other on the cheek.Whoa! I have no problem with this at all I was just caught off  guard. As soon as the rest of the crowd noticed him,a group off seemingly regular people ripped off there maskes and revealed their limp wrists and chest hair.Whoa! Ok the shock is over now I know where I am.Heres a hint:the name of this place was the San Antonio  MINERS  Co.Get it?Ok Im still cool Im introduced to everyone as this is my cousin which Im fine with.So at about this time Im carrying a huge red duffle bag filled with these odd items.In my denile I figured they were for some on else,a freind,lover,co-worker. We are no heading into the basement area of this bar /club,we have a seat.The room is dimmly lit with two light bulbs swinging from the low ceiling.Like in a cop show.There are 4 mirrors nailed into the wall.A pieace of large plywood sprawled across a few chairs as a makeshift table."Do you want a drink?"Sure I reply.Do you want something? "Um yeah get me a glass of water."I head back up the wobbling flight of stairs to find the bar crowd with there eyes to the tube again.I ask the bar tender,can I get a drink ?"Yeah sure what can i get you?"A shiner and a glass of water. Thanks alot.Whoa! A free beer.This might be good.Back down the shotty stair case.What do I see? My cousin sitting in a chair with some chick putting make up on him.Whoa! Ok I was caught off guard again.I desend the last remaining steps to realize that thats no woman putting make up on my cousin,ITS A MAN.FUCKIN  WHOA .Now how bout that shit?We are properly introduced.His/her name was Isacc/Diamond.Yeah I thought the same thing.Relax have a few and call it a night I said to myself,but little did I know there was to be no relaxing on this trip...............................................more to come .
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Sitting in the back of the cramped camaro,guzzling down luke warm shinerbock.I began to feel it comming back the feeling that I just cant escape these days(years).The feeling of being alone without being alone.Even  in a car chaulk full of freinds I still feel by myself.The car door opens I slip through the space between the car seat and door jam.It is the climax of the night.Urination in the great,wide,public,bush area.While outside in the now dust filled air,as the 4 cans of beer leave my system.I feel the lag on my mind and soul.The drunken souls chuckling behind the tinted glass.Exchanging stories of past female conquests.I stand and listen.                   Feeling sick to my stomach I inhale the dirt filled air as if to cure my churning stomach.A short walk across the street to my car to retreive a cigarette.The flame brightens my face for a moment,the thick menthol coats my tender throat.A gust of wind,dirt in my eyes.A time fearing man announces to the crowd,"what time is it".Its almost 3am."Oh shit I gotta go."The rest agree.I head toward my car,jiggle the key,get comfortable its a long ride.Now its just you and me. 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      So.......I guess I'll try to write some thing worth while.Mabey i can grip your minds for a sec or two.Doubt it but what kind of man would I be If I didnt try,HUH?I have been gone for awhile just under two months.Where was I? DEAD ?Almost.Was I on a spiritual journey into my soul?No.In my experience journeys of any kind are usually a waste of  time.Whether it be to the local corner store or a deep self-medicated trip into the mind.The results are the same ............nothing.I leave with nothing and return with nothing.Sure I return with that gallon of milk,but is that why I left?Mabey i was hoping to return with something else.Tangible or intagible.Did I forget the  TWIZZLERS ,could those tasty,twisted, red licorice strands really incite the journey-man in me?Doubt it.What was the trek for?Mabey I had found what I was looking for.Mabey it was in the crumpled wad of Washingtons I gave the cashire.So now she has it,or dose she?    
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Boy, has it been along time or what.Yes I have missed this litteral crutch know as "The BLOGGER".Well people its been a while, I have been out of the loop for a while.We have some catching up to do.Not now beacause I have lost my mind at the moment and mabey it will be back.So untill then....................
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2001</date>
<post>

     
      A few happening things have happened in my departure, not to many but a few. About a week ago I acompanied The Johnny U to a show in Albuquerque, NM. 4 hours to and fro. On the way we exchanged words of encouragement towards each others mothers. Played mind bending games of electronic scrabble, attacked mid country Arby's workers, and watched a mediocre, oscar winning film by the name of " Godd Will Hunting." After the first 4 hours mabey 5 we arrived in the great town mentioned above. Untill this time I had a great distaste for anything New Mexico.  This town on the other hand, small in comparison to our great city, had a great vibe I just couldn't get enough of. The little bar the fellas were scheduled to play, was in my opinion in the hippy part of town. This means that there were a lot of really nice people and a lot of bums. In this case the bums out weighed the nice people. But, in reverse the Middle Eastern population out weighed the whole community at a whole. Non the less everyone I came across was extremely nice and well mannered. The fellas played a good set, the band before was chalk full of middle aged anarchists, and the band after was your typical harcore band. All in all the night was great. The Dj / loafer of the bar gave us free beer, I con-ed some dude into buying a Johnny U record and I had the best "Subway" samach in history. ALBUQUERQUE I LOVE YOU !
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2001</date>
<post>

     
       I think in the year 2002 I'm going to pull a  urlLink bob Nanna  and watch 365 movies in a year. I'm pretty sure I could do it. Well is was struck by the curse of the 13th again. This time thankfully no blood. I was casually eating my lovely, piping hot cup'o' noodle when out of the blue the back door swings open. AT 11:30 pm ok. the day was almost over. when the door swung open I freaked like a little bitch and spilled that searing cup 'o' death on my unsuspecting crotch. Yeah yeah it hurt damn bad, I even fell out of my chair, furiously rubbing my junk on the shag rug. Luckily nothing was severely damaged, I only have mental anguish.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Friday The 13th, ohhhhhhhhweeeeeeeeeohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh, damn this cursed day. I dont care what anyone says this day is bad damn luck. Last 13th I had a little incident with a large piece of metal and my head.  I still have the Frankenstienesk scar on my forehead. I can vaguely remember other 13ths when I have had some other injury inflicted on me. Not this time my ass is staying in- side till 12 am tonight. I will not suffer the pain again. On a lighter note "The Johnny U" is on a small tour across this great state of Texas. Their probably bitching the whole time but at least their out there. So if they come to your town go check them out.   peace................................. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Salutations ............that's what that dork says 10 to the hour every hour on MTV2. You know who! that chubby, bald, white metal - head guy. Anyway, today I represented all the hardcore bums in the world. I did absolutely  nada . Maybe not. I did play the role of mechanic and fix my car. Of course this did not have its turmoil. By no means necessary am I mechanically inclined. It was a simple but mind bending task. You know that huge fan , that I'm pretty sure is used as some sort of torture device in third world countries, was rubbing against the radiator. Don't ask me how this came about ,but it did. So I had to figure out a way to rig this thing so there is no form of touching involved. While in getting down and dirty on this journey, I drop a very significant piece deep in the heart of the gosh darned engine. At first I was tricking myself to belive that I really did not need this piece. Of course later on in the rebuilding process I discover that this piece was the most important. I could have just taken off the bloody fan and driven the car as is. Eventually I would have exploded and that damn piece of metal would have become a flaming hot projectile aimed at my head. Wouldn't that be marvelous? Now I have to try and get this thing out of the engine. So I get down MAGIVER style. I concoct a crude lever of the sorts. Imagine this will you. Me , with this unraveled clothes hanger, with a huge magnet that I ripped from the fridge taped to the end of it. I'm sticking this damn thing in every open crevice I see. Hoping that the piece I lost had a different polarity that the magnet. I was actually thinking to myself," I wonder if this magnet has a southern polarity or a northern?" It was a low point in my life I admit. "CLICK" I hear something cling to the magnet. I pull it out and GEE WIZ its the darn piece I needed. Science prevails!  I resemble the junk and decide to give it a start. I crank the key and return to the front , to see if I could hear any scraping or what not. I hear nothing ,,,,,,,,, but I do catch a glimpse of a geyser of blood like liquid pumping out of my car.  At that second I remembered, OH YEAH ! I did disconnect that hose didn't I ? I rush to turn the car of , the poor thing had almost bled to death. It was like being in one of those operation shows on TLC. The car arrives bleeding from the head, I must hurry to reattach the hose/vein. Successful! Oh God Shes going under. /\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\/\---------------------------------------------------------- we need two pints of blood/ transmission fluid. I hop in the ROLLS/ TOYOTA and head for the local auto part facility. "I need two pints of tranny fluid STAT!  I'm on my way baby , do go , its not time your to young. ----------------------------------------------------------/\---/\------------------/\/\/\/\/\/\/\\/\/\/\/\\/\/\/\/\/\\/\. Excelsior! The after math was like an Evil Dead movie, red liquid everywhere, I looked like I just killed a man. The fluid was on me it stained my skin, my white under shirt was a bloody catastrophe. On the garage floor the huge puddle was slowly making its way down the driveway. The patient lived. A little rest and she'll be alright. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I had one of the best nights sleep I have had in farquin years! I vaguely remember some damn good dreams about the faceless queen that gives me such nocturnal bliss. Ok that little tid - bit kinda freaked me out. I now have a slight fear of the faceless freak I was once smitten by. Anyway besides all that stuff I slept like a....................damn sleepy person. My night, well really morning of undisturbed sleep, was ended by a phone call from the one I call MUM.  Of course this phone call had no importance at all, it was just a cruel trick by the gods of slumber to keep me in line. They knew if I had not answered the phone I may have slept forever. Then the world would be envious of my stature, as the king of nocturnus! Yeah I don't know either. When I decided to get my greasy ass outta bed I came to realize, that my ass was soaked to the bone, not only my ass, but half my got damn skin! At first a little embarrassed I thought maybe.........you know I had a little too much water before I hit the hay. That's when I heard the dripping noise on the wall to wall shag rug. GEE WIZZ! In my moment of pre pubescent memories, I had forgotten that I have this shitty ass, waterbed. I forgot that at least once a month this bastard of a bed decides he's had enough, he's gonna self- destruct. Boy did he ever, this little pin sized hole was pumping out water like there was no tomorrow. I wonder how long this was gong on? So by the time I awakened, the bed had lost half of its volume and it was in my shorts. I was damn waterlogged to the bone! My ankle is feeling a tad better , a little stiff but that's okay.  urlLink Andy  needs to drop some lines in the blogger form.   Peace....................................Oh Yeah my Dad got hit in the head by an air plane.....................HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2001</date>
<post>

     
      This is the run down of my 4th of July. Sure its 2 days late but ..........................SO! This was a night to remember in my book. It was a night I smoked way too much and drank way too much. A night that two lovers parted ways. A night filled with pyrotechnics and broken hearts. The evening started with a trip to good ol'  urlLink Andy's  house. There I met the crew for an eventful evening. This crowd of misfits included the following, The Don, Robert,David, urlLink Bubbs  myself, Hilla dilla, Andy, and  urlLink Nick . The majority of the group were engaging in a jam session of the sorts. Ripping out favoriets by the likes of Modest Mouse. Soon the session ceased and it was the infamous time of the night to figure out the nights plans. This is always a test of ones mind. Everyone always knows what they want to do but no one ever says anything. This type of heated discussion gose on for about 20 min, this dosent seem long but you see the two lovers were on a timetable and the BLACK hour was approching fast as hell. So finally we all agree on the same thing beer and the place to indulge it. We break up into two teams ...... Team 1.. you shall know us as Miller time....and Team 2 will be know as the lords of ice. yeah okay that one is lame but so what. So we disperse. Myself and the infamous Nick on beer detail and the rest on beverage coolage detail. We're OFF! Like a bat outta hell the golden bullet is catching ludacris speed. we are traveling a speeds unknown to man. the super market is still open, we rush inside to the living organism know as the beer isle. Nick says " GOD damn they clean out this joint." Bubba and I agree. The only cold beer they had in stock was Coors light and Natural Light. In my book I'd rather see death than those two beers. We parade around the corner of the isle to find our eyes blinded by the virginal pureness of the huge stack of unchilled Bud light. A sigh of relife immenates from our mouths. We have found gold boys, now to cash it in and be merry. We go through the preceding checkout lane we our bussiness and the usuall checkout with beer remark, " Wheres the party" the checkout lady proclaims aloud. Uh yeah. I reply. Once again we enter the time bending machine known as the urlLink Golden Bullet . We have to do a quik swing by Bubbs house, then to Hilla Dilla's. Now we are on our way to the PIT of DRINKING. Once again we have turned up the juice on the fluxcapacitor, we are making good time right about now....................untill we see the massive traffic carnage in our way to headquarters. The road was back up as far as the eye could see. Distant fireworks were exploding dangerously close to cars. I can remember think how I would love it if one of those fireworks had just blown up a row of cars keeping us from our destination but that would just be cruel. HA HAHAHAHAHAHAHAH. Well the 20 min in the hell fire of traffic we finally reach the  urlLink The Promise Ring . We arrive to find the rest of the crew already waiting in eager anticipation. We had in the hatch of the golden bullet a cooler of organs and the crew was the little girl waiting for her new kidney. We proceded to fill the ice chest with our luke warm beer and began to asened the hill of glory. The soft sand sinking benethe our weight, distant fireworks going off, some right above our heads. In the dark night our faces would light up with the colors of explosions. Then the dark would creep up to remain in the flow of things. We decided on a spot in the sand to partake in our festivities. We immediately began on our stash of alcohol. Our numbers were scattered at this point in time , no one was quite settled in. Someone spotted an oddly shape shrub and in great decor decided to set it a blaze. I had no problems witht this is was quite in favor . The plant gose up in a small but significant blaze. All cuddled around as it were the first time any of us had seen a fire before. The explosions were still going off all around us. you could here the occasional WHOA! from someone in the group. The evening was going on like usuall, a beer here , a toke there, after a few round of toke the beer I was on my way to farqued up town. By this time the evening was starting to turn. The BLACK hour was approching fast. The lovers time was almost up. Every now and then they would wander off into the night too have thier last moments together. I really dont know if anyone else noticed this but I did. While the rest of us were all huddled around the ice chest as if were a fire and were freezing in the arctic. the lovers were off to the side secluded from the group, if this were anyother night someone would have aknowleged this and would have asked them to join the crowd, but not tonight. Everyone understood. about this time everyone was feeling the efeects of whatever it was that they drank or smoked, Myself included. " I have to take her home." Nick anounced to the crowd. We all new it was time to say our good- byes. she slowly moved toward Bubba first, her longtime friend, and trustee. They embraced for what seems like eterinty, but not long enough. We all saw it the sadness, feeling of this person being already gone. Everyone saw this but everyone pretended not too. She moved from person to person we all told her to be carefull and good luck, but we all wanted to say more. The two lovers started their trek to the car. hand in hand they began one of their last walks together. It was downright heart breaking.Seeing the two walking off into the dark only hearing their voices trail off into nonexistance, and I swear as those two topped the hill, I swear a firecracker went off right above there heads and all I saw was their sillohetts in the distance and it was damn symbollic. The firecracker symbolized every relationship of all time. Think about it will ya. The rocket without a flame is a no useable object no use in the world. Add fire to it, sparks, flames, noise, the whole nine. the same as in relationships. You have the attraction to a person wich resembles a spark or what have you. The rocket shoots in to the sky, as the relationship becomes deeper, then there is the climax the point when the rocket explodes and colorful flames and noises light up the sky, the relationship has this also, the point when you are content with eveything at the moment, everything is beautiful and bright.Then there is a point in a rockets life when all the magic is gone and its nothing but a few shreds of paper hurdling toward earth. Its lost its glory and beauty. The relationship always has this par wether it happrn in a week, month. year or fifty years ther is always a point when it has to end all the beauty and flash just end. 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I know a boy named Artie. He's turning 18 and he's going to have a party.   Whats eating Gilbert Grape? 
     
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      As of right now "I'm reading On The Road" by Jack Kerouac. So far this little piece of literature is a page turner. I haven't been reading as often as I usually do, but hey what can you do? I haven't posted in a few days on account that I haven't really had anything to say.  urlLink Nicks  old lady came back on sunday so I'm pretty sure he's happy as can be. I'm happy for the man cause we all know that he was in his own personal hell while she was MIA, and frankly I got tired of all the Canadian references. I'm just playing, I've been on the job hunt for a few weeks now and nothing has turned up. Hopefully something will soon though. I registered for a higher education today and also returned to the old stomping grounds known as high school. It felt like old times driving to school with my G. While we were there we were even mistaken for high school kids and it felt good, so maybe I don't look as old as I feel. It's pretty sad when you feel old at 21 huh? Maybe I'm making it out to be worse than it is, I know I'm young as hell and there are people who would kill to be 21. Maybe because I expected more out of life when i was 16. I expected 21 to be a crazy party and just nonstop good times. Oh how I long for the days of 16 when a little was a lot and a lot was not enough. Maybe the party has started but I'm still 16 and I'm missing it. Maybe the party isn't a party at all, maybe it's a party of the soul, if that makes sense? When I went to that school today it was like I had never left. Not many people have such fond memories of high school, but I do. It smelled exactally the same, I shed a mere 3 years off my age as soon as we walked in the door. I had the urge to go to my locker and grab a book I wasn't going to use. Figure out a way to be late for class on purpose. If I had the power to do high school all over, and was able to keep the knowledge I have know, boy 'o' boy would it be the same. I would just get better grades, and I wouldn't have thrown that girls phone number away, and on a certain day in a certain sophmore year I would have taken a video camera to school. Screw that I would take a camera to school everyday that year. I would kick some arses I should have kicked and love some ladies I should have loved.  I want the blindingly cute to confide in me.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today the sleep god nocturnus irradicus was against me once again. As per usuall I was on a non-sleep binge and was going on my second day of sleep deprivation. Today around 9am when the urge to sleep finally caught me I layed down for what I though was going to be a few good hours of rest. About 30 minutes later I awoke with a strange song in my head. It was the empirial march, you know the song thats always playing in "Star Wars" when Darth Vadar is amidst the solar system. Well it turns out that a marching band decided to go on a crusade and bring music to the unfortunate people of my block. I look out my window and right in the middle of the street a miniture parade is going on. Chaulk full of everything that consists of what might be considered a good parade. Cheerleaders, band players, flag tossers, and the all to famous mascot suit, which in this case was a screaming eagle. I swear to god this was the slowest moving parade in all of history, they were in front of my house for three songs, we all know that the emperial march isn't a short peice of work. Finally they went by but the beauty of marching bands is that you can still hear them 10 miles away, I really don't know why I didn't hear them comming but I sure did hear them leaving and comming to every block after that. So as you might have guessed I didn't go back to sleep, I'm currently running on about 25-30 minutes of sleep. So right now I hate everything and everyone.   Theres just 5 words to say as you go down down down .................................... YOUR GONNA BURN IN HELL!                                                                                                                                                          Twisted Sister  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Do you know where you are? Your in the jungle baby, your gonna DIE!  Guns n Roses   So it goes.............................
     
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I have recently discovered that I have this imense feeling of hopelesness. I don't know where it came from or maybe I've had it all along. It's this feeling of not knowing anything or knowing where anything is(hypothetically of course). I can't see myself going on feeling like this very much longer, because it's so nerve racking and down right depressing. Maybe I've felt like this all my life and just didn't notice untill now. If I can recall I've always in my short life have felt like I didn't belong and or I just didn't know where I belonged. If I have felt like this all my life and now I'm barely noticing it, thats a lot of pent up crap to be finally getting out. I'm afraid I may blow up at any time on anyone for any reason. I'll lose my usually calm demeanor and freak. Hopefully I'll figure out a way to let go and resume the position I once held as a person who was Inpenetrable by such feelings of being lost and not found. I do believe that I have just read something that might help someone in my position, its a prayer of some sort and it goes as is;                                                         God grant me the serenity to accept the things I cannot change                                                                          Courage to change the things I can                                                                          and wisdom to know the difference  I saw this in my house just today and I asked my mom, "when did you get that?" It turns out she has had that little saying since I was a youngin. I saw it for the first time today, when I read it it sounded so familiar that I searched my brain to discover the origins of it. I just finished reading "The Slaughterhouse 5" by Kurt Vonnegut and I remembered that in the book he used that reference about a billion times. What are the odds of me being in the state of mind I'm in and then comming across a certain prayer that realates to my exact dilema. Maybe someone or something is trying to tell me to stop being a sissy and fight!........................So it goes.  Allison I'm waiting for my email.................Don't Make me yell!
     
    
</post>

<date>17,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Picture this; a perfectly wet thursday night, the rain and ugly clouds have been gracing my life for about a week and I'm enjoying every gray moment. Thursday night starts out with a trip to some ballroom, at this particular place every now and then they put on some amature wrestling show. I and a friend we'll call Joe arived at this establishment at about 10 pm, the whole wrestling thing was all but over and we just went to acompany his family in the post ring beer-a-thon. There is something special about this night if your a wrestling fan, which I'm not but there was a special guest this evening. You guessed it, Konan, from the crowd of autograph seekers and people wereing his shirts I guess he's a really known guy. I see this guy and he is utterly huge, raging tattos some of which I think he did himself or he just got shafted. His head was the biggest thing I've ever seen, and he looked really insulted that he was here and not in hollywood flaunting his ethnicity. At this point I'm forced to get in the autograph line and retrieve such. I say whats up to the guy shove the paper in his face, he scibbles some crap and I'm outside looking at girls.We sit there for about an hour and help the wrestling lackies deconstruct the ring and sit some more. Right about this time I was surronded by wrestling wannabes and there bandaged arms,knees or what have you. Another two hours fly by and the crowd deminishes except myself, Joe, his ma and pa and Waldo aka The General. This guy weighs about 350 lbs and is about 5'10. Yeah you guessed it he's pretty fat. So we're sitting outside of this place with a cooler of beer and 5 people. So we're pretty drunken, and I decide to put on some crazy wrestling mask and run around with my hands in the air and my pants around my ankles. This guy Waldo takes his wrestling really serious and decides that he's gonna give me a lesson in the art. I asked him how to do those crazy slaps that all the wrestlers do. He obliged and proceeded to use me as a dummy. Picture this me with a stupid mask on holding my pants up, while this fat guy is pummleing me with the back of his hand. Across my chest he is slaping the shit out of me constanly asking " dose it hurt ?"  Hell yes that shit hurt my nipples went numb and I started to lose my vision. This guy has a lot of weight on him but I think under it he has a plate of some indestructable metal. All in all i think the night was good except for the 5 minutes I was getting mauled by  "Earthquake" doyou remember that guy he was stupid huh?  
     
    
</post>

<date>14,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      When I posted earlier I ment to tell about this horrid dream I had. If anyone has been reading this crap then they know about my faceless woman dreams. Well I had another, usually when I have them my faceless queen brings me endless happiness and love. Oh no not this one, this particular dream was probably one of the most disturbing dreams I've ever had and probably will have. Imagine your in a church, lots of people, you really don't know them but hey its a dream who cares. So you realize your the guy who's getting married and you walk toward your blushing bride, only shes not wereing a white dress, its all dirty and mud ridden. So I think "hey maybe shes just protesting the norm of what a bride should look like. I like a woman with views. So I get to the altar or what not everything is fine, the preacher guy says whatever and .......you may now kiss the bride. I lift the vail and at this point I usually wake up,hence faceless girl, not this time I lift the vail and gosh darn it she actually has no face. She only has a pair of blue lips, and their all puckered ready for the lovin. At this point I freak and turn around to find that the wedding goers are now large bags of dirt. Everyone has turned into sacs'o' dirt, I turn and the faceless freak is still puckered up, the next thing I know I'm running balls out to the street then I wake up. I think this dream holds significance on any relationship I may have in the future, marital or casual. So basically I'm doomed to marry a sac of mud. Why does the dream god nocturnus irradicus torment me so?
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I haven't been awake this early in years. My day started at about 9 am, and in my world thats just plain old insane. So I'm basically running on about 3 hours of sleep. Strangely enough I'm not even tired, just seriously bored. Day-time television has to be the worst concoction known to man. I understand that housewives and grandmas are relaxing to the wide world of Matlock and Angela Lansberry, old episodes of family feud and Magnum P.I. Sure these shows were cool in 1984 but Matlock couldn't find his teeth right about now and sure as hell couldn't sovle a murder. I'm pretty sure Angela couldn't solve one in her prime and I'm pretty damn sure she can't now. As for Magnum, well he's just always sucked, the only good thing about that show was that kick ass black dude that flew the helicopter. Yeah you know who I'm talking about. Maybe I'll be a hipocrite and indulge in the crap I just ridiculed, oh yes you said it man one of the  urlLink worst  shows I have ever seen is comming on in awhile and if you must know, yes I plan to watch. Even though I admit that this show is crap, I can't stop watching it, even though its been months since I've seen it still I think about whats happening all the time and I wonder to myself, "will he ever find out that he's his father?" I don't know we'll have to watch to find out. Holy shiet ! 10,000 dollar pyramid is on, celebrity edition, well I think they were all celebrity editions. So long......................................................
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Man things are just not going right for me this week. First off one of my contacts gave me the shaft and ripped. Now my only form of vision is a pair of glasses that are broken and have enough of  urlLink this  on them to supply a 3rd world country with adhesive forever. As if I'm not ugly enough I have to lugg the copper wire known as my glasses around for a couple of days. Second, once again my lovely waterbed has decided to go on strike and blow its load all over me and my wall to wall shag. I swear to  urlLink GOD  if this bed had any more holes....(add something clever of your own making.) Then well yeah. And finally we have number three which is the least of my worries, I need a haircut. (In stand up comic voice) Well folks thats all my time you've been a great crowd, see ya and GOODNIGHT!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well it seems like the plans to become an adult are slowly falling together. My  urlLink compadre  and myself took a little trip to the land of enchantment to get some info on the situation we are getting ourselves into. So far we seem to have everything figured out, but the fate of the world will and I repeat will toss us a good one. We'll get there and everything will seem fine and then , wouldn't you know it the world shoots us a curve ball. Hopefully everything will work out though,(crosses fingers). At this point in juncture I'm pretty excited about the coming events. We all know I should have done this a long time ago. If you haven't guessed at what I'm telling you well then............................ I guess I'll have to say then. Yes I the guy that writes this crap has decieded to further his education and do something usefull with my waste of a life. So I have to start right now , planing the preceding events. As of  8'o clock this here morning I'am looking for employment. You say to yourself "why is he barely doing this?" I'll tell ya.....................its because I'm one of the greatest bums of all time. Only after  urlLink this  king of the lethargic, but I digress. I have forseen the result and I have liked it. So all those who oppose...............................so
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
               A little while ago I was sitting in my room reading and listening to the radio, something I rarely do(listen to the radio) and while I was doing all of this a song came on. The werid thing is that I remember the exact place and time when I first heard it. It was the summer between 8th and 9th grade. I was sitting in my room listening to the radio and talking on the phone to the only girlfriend I have ever had.Sad right? Yeah I know, so I got to thinking about all of my firsts. You know the first time you did something significant in your life.(Example) first time you drank a beer, smoked pot, kissed a girl, first job etc.......... I began to feel a little nostalgic for these certain things.         I started to remember things that I had once forgotten. I started to remember the way I felt at these moments and the way everything smelled and what not. I remember the first time I rode a bike, my dad taught me. It wasn't the; let me hold the bike while you peddle slowly next to me while you learn balance. I sat on the bike, he grabbed the back of the seat, gathered some strength and shoved me  full tilt into the street. Very effective; if you think about it in a moment like that you have no choice, fall or ride and I guess I rode. I remember the first time I kissed a girl, who dosen't? It was in her room, I can still smell her and the room. Her and I in a dark airconditioned room sitting on some little recliner thing that squeeked everytime you moved. She was sitting on my lap and in the cold darkness history happened. Boys 2 men was on the hi-fi and the room smelled of dead roses. The smell was a little relaxing as I remebered it. A small line of light creeped underneath the closed and locked door. The muffled voices of party goers just on the other side. That was the summer life changed. The summer of  94'. After that, new school, new friends, new everything. The time in life when you discovering yourself and everything else. Who knew it would last so long? I'm none the bit wiser than I was 7 years ago.         I remember the first day of kindergarten, the first time a lot of kids were away from their parents for the first time in life. I can remember the smell of crayons and finger paints. I recall the alphabet rug that was standard in every kinder class. I picked the P to pay tribute to the last name. A good portion of the kids crying as their parents left them behind in the company of a stranger. Some completetly losing their minds when their parents walked away, When my mom left I wanted to cry just as bad but i held that shit in. I had this huge afro with a chunk cut out of it right in the front. The night before I had an unpleasent experience involving a huge speaker and my head. So that chunk missing was replaced by a few stiches holding my 5 year old skull together. I had temporarily forgotten about that head wound untill lunch time when I was the freak of the school and everyone had to come marvel at the boy with string in his head. I think maybe thats were my fear of social eviroments comes in. After school when my mom came to pick me up I was never more glad to see her, then I unleashed the beast on her for making me go to school and exposing my giant freak head.        Ok last one, the first time I got drunk. This girls house, her name slips my mind right now. Nice trip into the archives huh? Anyway, she had this rad ass pool and her brother was old enough to by beer, her parents were out of town. Could this be more perfect? So, he buys beer and bottles of booze, when your 14 you have no knowledge of whats good and whats not. So eveyone is downing they could put their little hands on. So you have a backyard full of 14 year old drunken idiots. So you have that one kid who thinks cause he's drunk he can go and be an idiot, you have the kids who think their harcore and are sitting on the patio smoking cigaretts, saying to themselves"look at all these immature kids." In actuallity their the sissies that didn't drink anything and if they did they would go home reaking of booze and get grounded. So I myself was just getting trashed beyond all comprehension, someone has the bright idea of getting in the pool and doing whatever drunkards do in a pool. I see a shiet load of hot chicks get in the pool so I'm all for it. I get in having a blast, totally drunk and the next thing I know I'm bleeding a tad from the head. Yes once again I'm bleeding out of my giant freak head. It turns out that some jerk decided it was cool to fall down and in the process chuck his/her bottle 'o' wine cooler in my direction. So my head is bleeding just a little so that somebody notices and I have a crowd of people surronding me asking me if I'm alright. "YEAH I'M COOl!" the blood coming out of my head feels real good against my drunkin skin. Next thing I know I'm sleeping in some corner of some room in some house with a barrage of chicks surrounding me. YEAH! My head in some chicks lap, girls laying on my hungover legs, it was great. So I advise the getting hit in the head to get girls routine . Hey it worked for me at some point.   Hey that guy in the bandana is puking in your pool !  Some guy to some chick about some guy in a red bandana.  By the way the song that started all of this was an 'Ace of Base' song.....yeah yeah I know
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today myself and 3 g's dropped and insane hour or 2 of b-ball (basketball) you know for the unhip. This blistering 2 hour marathon was in all forms splendid. I myself had one of the shittiest games in history, the bubbanator was ripping the court up with an unheard of fury. I think he may have took my advice and called upon the beast. He asked me for a better game and in return all I desire is free pizza for life, which in my case is all eternity. AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHhahahahhahahahha. Ok that was just a little uncalled for. I do belive when it comes time for my departure from this earth, and I'm at the gates to be judged by that guy who dose all the judging..his name has temporarily slipped my mind. When it's my turn he'll see my name and automatically replay every instance when I in some shape or form had joked about or around either myself or an aquaintence of mine being satan. He will refresh every moment when I said something to either glorify or encourage the use of evil to get what you want. All of these things are all done in fun, and petty attempts at making myself seem comical. I can only hope that the   urlLink ALMIGHTY  will see fit to forgive and forget. (crossing my fingers at this point). Back to the story, these games took place at the only place in town that has nets on the rims, a little place known as.................................some middle school I forget the name. All I do know is that the mascot of this school is the mighty mighty MOOSE. The night air was dry and hot as any day in the gosh darned sahara. Any type of breeze or gust of wind was nonexistant. So as you might know the sweat and bodily funk was rampant. So as the story goes all good things must come to an end, off to the running bear for cold refreshments and hot chick lookout. The refreshments were easy to come by, but the girls were not. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today when I woke I realized that my fish were a little unmotivated. They were just laying at the bottom of the tank alive but other wise dead. Then I realized that the air pump(you know that thing that gives them air) was unplugged. So my guess is that from about 5am when I fed them, till about 2pm when I was rudely awoken by  urlLink pizza the hut , the  urlLink air supply  was a little short. So I see my babies flailing on the bottom of the tank gasping for dear life. I jump up and plug in the device just in time, slowly they come back to full health and salute me with a little water in the face. This blog was just a time killer and I went a little link crazy. Sorry  Peace.......
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      So I guess the  urlLink SLV  is still on the brink. We need to get a blog technician to come out and figure out whats going on. Luckily I have this trusty spot to rant and rave all I want. HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAH. Poor Andy hasn't any other realeses, his baby is on the down and out. Andy if you have the urge to blog drop me a line and I'll let get your fix in.  Peace..
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Right now I was trying to get a little posting in on the SLV, but it wont let me post. Either the good folks at blogger felt my post's were no good, and decided to end the insanity. Or, Andy decided that he was the sole perpriotor of the site. Either way I'm content, I will lose no sleep over it. I will in return  SMITE  Andy if he has decided to rid the format of my graces. Anyway I just finished 'Apt. Pupil' by Stephen King, and I must say that he is an utter(crazy hand gesture) nut. Good boy gone bad is the plot, and I'm not talking boy slips in his studies, and inpregnates the next door nieghbor's daughter bad. I'm talk'n boy goes on a shooting spree and falls in love with a 80 year old nazi bad. Decides he's going to start his own holocaust by ridding the world of hobos and transients. In a lighter note he's an all-star baseball player. YEAH ! Thats what we need more of; nazi lovin, hobo killin, all-star baseball playin, white kids. Hey that sounds like someone  urlLink I know   sans  the all-star baseball, the only thing this guy is an all-star at is making  urlLink pizza . 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Postmortum  recordings, in my opinion there a little creepy. You know when a band has a member die, but luckily before they kicked the bucket the layed down a few drum,vocal, guitar, cowbell or what have you tracks. Then later in life the remaining members decide to complete the unfinished work as a tribute to the lost member or members(SKYNRD). In actuality its because the remaining members haven't had a collective hit since 1984. By now the bill for the coke is starting to grow, your on your third wife and your 8th kid, the world just seems to be a dark and unforgiving place. Your cameo in the puff daddy video really didn't pay off as well as you thought it would." Hey I have an idea, lets get those tracks that our said drummer, singer etc......... laid down in 84' and lets realese them as a tribute album." Of course it has to be the song where the singer talks about dying, so the can give the line...."yeah this was the last track he/she wrote before they(give the slit your throat sign right here) passed on. Postmortum in my opinion is not really a good idea, unless you get me so lost (posthumous) "Tiny Tim" recordings. Them we'll talk.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      That last post was inspired bt a little situation I had last night. 5 people sitting in a driveway chatting it up, 2 of those people living it up on some ganja. The Don decides he has some stories to tell, he ventures back the year 1992 and warms the night with a story that took place hours after watching  urlLink this movie . His little brother and himself had a little spat and decided to take the match outside to the grassy knowle of his frontyard. We must remember that in 1992 The Don was about 10 years old and his brother was about 2 years younger. Some way or another they end up on opposite sides of the grass and they're yelling battle cries to each other. Since the thought of ' Van Damme' was running rampid in their minds The Don yells out " COME ON SLODIER!" this infuriates his brother and he starts to charge. Running at his 8 year old top speed he lunges at The Don, he moves to the left catching his speeding brother in the gut with a swift knee. He dangles lifeless across it gasping for air. The Don see's he has won the battle and decides that it's his obligation to provide a finishing move and delivers a lightning fast elbow to his brothers limp spine. All of this inspired by one stupid movie. Man I love them don't you?  COME ON SOLDIER!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      COME ON SOLDIER!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink This cinematic peice of heaven 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
                                   What now ?
     
    
</post>

<date>15,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      So today was another day of "what now ?" The whole day had sort of film over it if you can dig that. Most of my day was spent thinking "what now ?" After I did some sort of mindless task I would ask myself "what now ?" I went as far as dusting my room which is just insane in my world, I cleaned my fish tank my poor fish were swiming in a half empty tank (half full for the optimists) the water was the color of, I really don't think that there is a color for it but lets just say it wasn't clear or anywhere in the realm of clear. I escorted my brother to some sporting good heaven and let him roam free for about 45 minutes and I just walked around wondering what half of the gadjets were used for. I know what a football helmet looks like and the pads to boot but some of the items were just plain old unexplainable. Maybe I'm just an idiot and you're probably right. That trip cost me about 2hours out of my day and about a quarter tank of gas, as you may have thought yes this damn jock-topia is on the other farquin side of town. When I get back home I go to my room and ask myself "what now " ? I reach for the trusty book upon my entertainment thingy and I begin. I read for about an hour and ask myself, yeah you got it. "What now !" I receive a call and it's that time of night to figure out something to do. After about a 5 minute time span and a few unsuccessful phone calls we have it. I proceed in my almost daily trip to the other other side of town which in general turns out to be at least a 30 minute drive along a dark as Haties it's self and teeming with the smell of death (okay no death but it's pretty dark) highway. I arrive at my destination to find the usuals arriving at the same moment we enter and history is made. Don't ask what history it just is.  Monopoly is not only a game it's a mental endurance test. I think the military should use it in way's of torture or maybe training. If you can last a serious game of monoply and live to tell your hardcore in my book. " I want the iron"
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      In about 30 minutes I'm out the door and I'm on my way to some fun (hopefully), the plans for the evening consist of friends and booze, a personal favorite of mine. The plans have been etched in stone since yesterday and for the first time in my life the plans actually stuck. Usually if you or someone you know makes plans the day before the chances that they are going to fall through are pretty high, so tonight is a rare occasion. Right now in listening to some   urlLink  Deathcab for Cutie  and it's setting the mood for the evening, totally slow and relaxed. This of course is my favorite mood of all, and if the night persists to be in this nature then I can gaurantee the success of this mission. Yesterday was a test of my personal views at the moment when Nick was rubbing a bag 'o' pot under my nose for about 4 hours and roaming his house yelling pro-ganja slogans. If you really want to know I kept strong and clean. NO SMOKED THE POT FO ME! Till then....................................
     
    
</post>

<date>07,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      At this moment in time, I'm at  urlLink this guy's house . We acted like geeks and went to the comic store to purchase some reading material, I left empty handed but Nick left with a few "DareDevil comics. right now Nick is searching his house for certain materials to create a device know world wide. Yes folks I am talking about a "bong" a device used to get your smoke on. At this moment Nick is roaming the house yelling "WATER BONG" and it's utterly funny, he's trying to persuade me into taking a toke but I flat out refuse. It's true peer pressure is a bitch and a half but I must keep strong and deny the bliss. While I'm typing this he's he's asking me if I'm nervous, why, might I ask? Nick says "cause you feel like your going to give, you feel you wanna come to the darkside he yells. He constantly reminds me of goodtimes had under the influence, and the goodtimes we would have right now. I do believe that I'm not going to cave in and stick with my original decision. i'll keep you posted on the happs...................  Will he give in or will the good he really doesn't have shine through?    
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      It's that time kiddies for the conclusion of our night of misadventure.  We walk up to the front of this fine establishment, and there was this quiet little fellow with a flashlight carding people at the door. First let me establish why we decided to enter this certain bar. We were walking along the quaint little back roads of Mexico after I myself had been turned down by a couple 'o' bars and we needed to find somewhere that would let ugly people in. So we see this sign and it has the hats from   urlLink  this movie  and I do believe their called bolo's. So we thought that anywhere that would use anything from that movie had to be cool. We walk up tp the doorman and attempt to walk in, he stops us and motions for us to present the proper identification. We comply, first he askes  urlLink Andy  in spanish of course and he reaches for it. When Andy has his I.D in the guys face and remember he has this little flashlight, the guy starts to ask him what is your address and your date of birth? Andy had to tell me what he was saying cause if you know me I barely know english let alone spanish. After Andy passed this rigorous test it was my turn, and I'm thinking that he's going to kill me cause I don't inderstand a word he was saying. The thing that saved me was the fact that I remembered the order he asked Andy and I answered in the same order. After a few flashes of light in my eyes and some nods of the head we were on our way in. The problem I still have with this test is this; how can a person in another country ask you what street you live on? I can understand if your in another part of your city even in another state, but in another country? Come on, what was he going to say " oh yeah my mom lives on that street" or yeah I think your lying there isn't a street called blah blah blah in Texas. How can he interogate us about our state and our streets if he dosen't even speak the language of that said street? I don't know it was funny for awhile then I just got angry. So after our lie detector test was administored we headed inside, the first part of the bar looked like a high school shower room, then the main part was a very small club which housed an atomic drum set and guitars toboot. We ordered a beer from the bar in the shower room and we journied into the club. This place was a metal heads dream, the room embraced black as if it were the only color that existed. Long hair and bandanas were seen for miles, girls with their knee high death boots and fellas with their studded patent leather jackets. This place was hapening in a far out way, we grabbed a stool and shot the shit some more. The DJ was spinning out metal god favorites, Metalica, Slayer and alot of other bands I don't know. It definatly was rockin', if I must say so metal girls are hot hot hot. After about 20 minutes of sititng down and 3 beers a band asended the stage and prededed to tune up. The first song they played was a Black Sabbath tune that I can't remember the name of at the moment but the singer actually sounded like Ozzy. He had a lyric sheet to look off of so I figured "hey maybe he just dosen't know the words" it turns out he really didn't know the words cause they were in english. He pulled it off though I might say, the next song was unfortunatly the ripped off Limp Bizkit favorite "Faith" so as you can tell they were a Mexican cover band playing American songs. At this point I was feeling the beer and my head was rockin' from all the metal in the air, the whole time we were in the bar I could swear that it was a vampire bar. You know the bar that 2 regular humans accidentaly roam into and at the stroke of midnight they lock the doors and the party begins. I was waiting for the steel doors to slam and the blood to fly. Our friend that was checking I.D's was now roaming the bar with his flashlight now dim from all it's usage, searching for anything out if the ordinary. A couple of lovers behind us were actually loving it up in the damp metal heaven. After a few more we decided that we had had enough metal and Corona. So we headed for the entrance just in time before they slammed the steel behind us. We emerged drunken in the likes of booze and hardcore music.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Ok I just remembered that I have a little story to tell. On Saturday night Andy and myself constructed a night out on the town, the only problem was that we were the only 2 idiots in the whole world that had nothing to do. So we meet at his house and we directly decide to go to the infamous "La tuya". AAA was playing and "The Don" wanted Andy to purchase him a shirt because he had to work and couldn't attend the show. We arrive around 9 flat. Absolutley no one that I cared about was around for miles. We walked in Andy purchases the shirt and we return outside. Andy breaks out the trusty cell-phone and tries to get in contact with some hipcats downtown(Rob,David and Jon), no good their nowhere to be found either. We ran down the list of who's who in the state of Texas. As it turns out everyone was MIA. 20 minutes pass us by in a flash and someone brings up the idea of going to option of all options, "Mexico." After a few minutes of diliberation Jim and Trisha show up at the show, we conversate and we finally fully decide that Mexico it is. On the way there Andy and I discussed the rule about what we were getting ourselves into. The rule is that you can't go with less than 3 people and have fun, and obviously we were 2. So we're discussing and contemplating and degrading the fact that we were going to have a shitty time and the rule would stick. I decided before we got there that this was a science project and it was all in he faith of science. We arrive and we head directaly for familiar territory, sit down at the bar order few of  urlLink these  and start the conversation. We talked about music and movies and professions that would be cool to have. Basically we sat and shot the shit if you will. I  remember a specific converstion we had about painters and poets, the tortured artist and what not. Thats when I decided to be an underestimated artist, those guys/gals besides the fact of not being able to eat because they can't sell a painting have it pretty good. We were talking about the benifits and I brought up the fact about being able to tell girls that your an artist and that you have some paintings in galleries and what not and then the clencher, "I would really like to paint you nude" and your in like flynn. After we had a few more beers and a few more conversations of the sort we decided to venture out and visit a few other clubs/bars. We travel down to an "upscale" bar if thats what you wanna call it and I inparticular was turned away, " No baggies the doorman yelled in broken english" ok so we walk. The next bar is a sort of jock's wet dream, a place chaulk full of all the amenities that would consist of a jock's wet dream. Boxing ring, volleyball courts, with actual sand which is too far for me.etc etc etc. We walked to the front of the establishment and atempted to walk in, " No, baggies compa" I don't even know what a compa is, but it meant that I was a poorly dresses shmuck and I felt dirty. It's a damn shame when a place full of your antagonists dosen't let you in and you feel like crap. So anyway we decide to go back to the fisrt bar we were at because it seemed that it was the only bar that would let my ugly ass in. On the way there we saw a place we have never seen before and we decided to see whats inside...................................  Part 2 next time     
     
    
</post>

<date>03,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Gawd damn you half Japanese girls you do it to me everytime, oh the redhead said you shred the cello, and I'm jello baby!  Sorry about that I just had to get the song out of my head. Sooooooooooooooooo, today was a little slow as per usual. I had a really long night and morning if you will, a good freind and I returned to a certain place that I myself thought I would never return to. I wont say where this infamous place is but lets just say it's not a good establishment. I do believe that it's a parallel universe were normally beautiful things get ugly, really really really ugly. So I will just say that I drank a lot of beer and my beer goggles made the view tolerable. Only thing that I can really remember is that there was a girl there that wanted to give ol' Cory here a test run, but she got sick and we know the rest, lets just say I sobered up and my gogles disapeared and she wouldn't stop talking about her rabbit and I freaked and went home. Sorry about that crazy run-on............................... 
     
    
</post>

<date>31,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well it seems as if  urlLink Bubba  promised a post and he didn't come through. So his page has a whopping 3 posts on it..... enjoy. Surprised to see him online last night, first time in along time, as usual it was good  to see the guy and have a few laughs. This afternoon has been a good one, I saw my favorite episode of "Doug" you know the one where they go to funkytown, yeah the theme park is named funkytown. It was the Halloween episode so I took the hint and guessed that today is another excuse to get ' krunked up' as the dirty south would have it. I may venture to see " The Don" dressed in drag and hit a pseudo Halloween party after words, but I will definatley feel the hops. Whats with sonic and 25 cents, my theory is no matter what it is if it's 25 cents it's worth it. BUY IT!   I'd buy that for a dollar! 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Pumpkins are the worst.......... what the hell are pumpkins anywho? Are they fruits, veggies, WHAT! Well as I was saying pumpkins are the nastiest " organisims" ever, gross orange goo lives in the belly of these gigantic beasts, people feed on the seeds and run there slimy fingers over they're lips and ..... Oh God I grossed myself out. Well if you haven't guess I did a little pumpkin work today and got my carve-on. As the pumpkin smiting was going on of course the pump-gut fight had to start and as usual I was the first one with the eye injury and had to cut the fight short to retrieve the burning pump-flesh from my orbit. I had some laughs, threw some guts in some mouths, all was merry in the land of half-wits. Have you noticed in this post I've used a lot of " -" those, weird huh? Well it's nice to see that in her second day in the blogiverse she has been busy and the posts are commin and I expect more to come. So if your in the area give   urlLink her  a ring.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Today my pop's had a loss in the family, 2 of his best freinds died(his fish) a freak occurance went down as he did the ritual tank cleaning. A strange liquid was used to "according to the lable" build up the fishs' immune system and introdce key vitamins into the water. Well lets just say that they're immune system sure didn't go up and the vitamins were killers. The fish were just lifeless in the pseudo tank while the real one was being cleaned. A scream from hell as my mom saw the carnage that lay at the bottom, only a few were spared. Miraculously as we were cleaning the tank we discovered 2 little baby fish, strange? I think so, 2 die 2 are born, hummm. I hate to be the creepy life analysis guy but damn thats a strange coinceidence if I ever saw one. It's sad to see my dad keep up his charade of not being effected but I know he is, I know that they were just fish and what not but he loved them. So to the 2 that lost they're live in this crazy ride we call life, I'll think about you for a day or so when I flush the toilet. So long silvery fish and bumpy headed fish.  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I have just come to the convlusion that "  C ode Red" is my new favorite soft drink. You know Mountain Dew with a rush of cherry flavor(thats what it says on the can.) I have a question, why do they call them soft drink when their anything but soft? The drink sure isn't soft on your kidneys as your balled up in a corner somewhere after a kidney stone or 2, the carbonation hurts  l ike the dickens, and...and ...and, yeah I think thats all I can think of for the moment. Tonight was 2 different night in one, the first began with  a  trip to the good ol' coffee/pancake/sanitarium house, light relaxation took place, a few glasses of luke warm lightly d u sted with dirt glasses of water where ingested. The second was contrived of crappy cars and a crappy B horror film. Tonight I drove the worst car in history, it wasn't my automobilay of course. The car was called a "  D odge Shadow" if the name isn't shitty enough for you I have more, The window had 2 settings, rolled up and the only way your getting me down is by means of arcwelding or the ladder all the way down and you freeze, so I rolled it up and left the process of getting it down to the pro's. This car had a tendancy to turn off in mid- r i ght turn, if you wanted to change lanes which usually takes a slight movement of the wheel, you had to completely spin the wheel 180 degrees to get into the next lane. To make  a  complete turn I don't even want to think about how many revoloutions I had to make to turn that damn heap. My forearms are all defined and muscular thanks to the wheel of fortune and certain death.  T o top of the salability of this beaut when we arrive at out destination the radiator seemed to have sprung a leak and the car was  h issing and bleeding all over the place. Eventu a lly with my outstanding mecha n ical skills(the car just needed water) we got bac k  safely and without the aid of the police.  One more thing I received a lovely e-mail today, from a lovely lady. In this particular mail were a few  s hort lines expressing her love of my blog, I would mention her name but she might want to remain anonomous. I will take this opprotunity to express my thanks and gratituted for the comments made. Or maybe I'm making an ass out of myself and she ment to send it to someone with an actual, worth reading blog. 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      What shall I say about last night, pre- halloween halloween party, post pre - halloween party party. Confused ? Well don't be, it's harmless babble. Drunken, costumed people dancing to drunken costumed music, a singular fog machine pumping out ineffective fog.Someone dressed like an old woman refused to break character and hobbled around the party with a cane, I think I caught him/her dancing  sans  cane and limp. Peter Criss arrived a little later and gave all of us ' Kiss'  fans a real treat, hot girls with hot asses, sorry about that last one I had to tell about them. The scenery changed about 11 and we headed to  urlLink Andy's  house where we par-took in some festive drinks and festive laughs. I had the best teriyaki chicken of all time. All in all the night was worth the trip to hell and back.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Just returned from taking the 'act' and I'm pretty sure I flunked the funk out of it. I think im my history of taking tests this was the worst, I was completely knowledge-less and unprepared. Lacking sleep and food I stumbled and guessed my way through 4 hours of unadulterated stupidity on my part. So I'm eagerly awaiting my results so I can ball up on the floor and weep, weep like I've never weeped before. Tonight I'm making up for my failer and lack of dignity by drowning my sorrows in a tub 'o' beer. Who's comming with me! 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I think today was one of the worst days I've had in a long time. I wake up with a headache from the 7th ring of hell and it's not going away, the taste of beer and "Parliments" linger  in my mouth. The only thing on my mind during this trial was the jug 'o' milk gently chilling in my refridgidizer, I walk to the site of bliss and peer inside only to find a heartbreaking site, I really dont think I need to elaborate and it hurts too much anyway. So my vision of choco-love was shattered and left bloody on the floor of my heart. By this time I'm getting really irritated and I'm in a bad mood, I get a phone call requesting my appearence at my brothers school, (the bastard needs a ride) the fucking school is 10 minutes away, yet he needs a ride. I get in the car and arrive at the designated spot of pick up. I wait............and wait.......................and wait, a cop drives past me and makes a sharp u-turn. You guessed it he's comming for me, he parks behind me and proceeds to give me 2 tickets. The thing that made me the angry-er is the fact that my bastard ass brother had the nerve to call me for a ride and then decide he was going to walk while I'm in the process of picking him up. I get home and he's watching family matters or some shitty show of that nature. So I now have a hearty $200 dollars added to my devistating $300 odd dollars. Is there no end? I think my streak of bad air started last night while I was in progress of buying some gummy bears for a freind and began to get accosted by the customer service representetive. He accused me of being a theif, all on the grounds that I was looking at the candy and sticking my hands in my pockets. I stood in the store for about 10 minutes bitching at this creepy haired guy while he's walking away from the verbal assault I'm giving him. I wasn't cussing at him or threating his children, I was stating the fact that he was an idot and that if I wanted to steal something I would have. He throws my change at me and walks away, then he gives me a bag with a whole in it and my precious beer falls to the ground, like a gentleman I picked it up and threw it at him, ( Well thats what I should have done). I told him thanks for the bag and departed. I think I'm going to go again tonight just to torment him and taunt him with my pocket usage. See ya soon baldy.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I just had the worst 'Mountain Dew' I've ever had in my young life. When the dark draws closer than ever I'm still looking for slavation.    No sleep till.........................Brooklyn. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well it's about 6:30 am and I'm still awake pondering the meaning of life and all things that revolve around it, you know things like , love, money, comfort, warmth, lime green shag rugs, the massive amount of facial hair I have right now, the way the sky looks on a warm Texan night, the way my car shakes whenever I stop long enough to let it, how the sun hurts your eyes when you stare but if it were gone you would miss the little image it leaves in your eyes. The smell of a beautiful girl on a frosty winters eve, that shirt you have with a million holes and a million stains that reminds you of everything good in life, the sound of 20 pencils and pens writing frantically as a teacher spits out knowledge. The way you remember every note, lyric and beat of your favorite song, that first kiss or your last, a hand shake from your best freind, a good book or bad, the way your broken vcr only works for you, the sound of a lover breathing in your ear. the scar on your arm and the fresh gash right next to it, the way you feel when you just get a haircut, the first time you noticed hair under your arm, the first time you slow danced with a guy or gal, first day of high school, your first broken heart, the first time you broke a heart. The sound of your mom's voice when it was bad and the sound when it's was good, wanting to be like your dad, your favorite line in a movie, eating pancakes from "ihop", chico and his fucking tacos, chico and the man, 120 minutes, watching the sky turn from dark blue to pink, looking for patterns in the stars, sitting on the hood of your car, acoustic love songs, the way a certain smell can trigger memories good or bad, the sound of someones name bringing joy or pain, falling in and out of love, loose teeth, crooked teeth, fireworks and the dangers behind them, deep conversations with deep freinds, shallow conversations with a deep love, burned out light bulbs, unmarked Christmas presents, 7th birthdays, 17th birthday, strange rooms with strange girls, your first beer. first cigarette, first steps, first grade, first base, first record, first thing in the morning, the first time you realize your alive.   
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I just read  urlLink Andy's  news, and I must say that it's some damn cool news at that. After the slow demise of The Johnny U, I think the majority of the members thought the chances of being musical again were slim. To the course of a few months 2 of the founding fathers have found themselves in a position to rock and be rocked. Opening for  urlLink The Trail 'o' Dead  may change everything, have they been bitten by the bug once again? Has the joke worn off? Has the drive begun? Will we remember tomorrow? I don't know we'll have to wait and see.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Just returned from the bloomin court-casa, and I must say the the El paso judicial system works fast, well only if you admit your guilt and succomb to the fact that you owe 300 odd dollars and some amout of cents just for a damn stop sign violation. Yeah I sound bitter but SO WHAT! Okay now that I've gotten my anger out and the subtle thought of suicide out of the way we can get down to business. As  urlLink ass-ko  was aying earlier in the day about The Strokes, I say that they are a good band they rock and what not but I agree that the whole hype (aboot) them is just ridiculous, good band yes but jesus returned no. I'm wonderin how Andy did on his test I wish the man luck cause we all know he's losing his mind. So good luck to you my freind's and have a cherry day.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I keep procrastinating on the whole court appearance deal so pretty soon I'm going to have some uniformed officers repelling through my windows, grappling down my chimney and hiding in the suga bowl. All for 3 mutha farquin tickets, do I deserve jail time for not completely stopping at stop sign. Maybe I'm wrong and maybe  urlLink Nick's  going bald. I don't even know why I still give his link he dosen't even blog. So if you go you might get a post from 1995, don't be alarmed your in the right place.  urlLink Andy  has some new fellas ripping out literary bliss on his site now so go give them a read or 2. It promises to be some good shiet. So untill we can remember again................................................
     
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      last night was a damn waste of my time untill about 2 am when like clock work I found myself caught in the middle of another steamy debate about ghosts and what not. You see I wouldn't mind these particular conversations it's just that the people who usually bring it up say the exact same thing that they said 14 conversations in the past. So by now everytime it comes up I shut up and watch, calmly reapeting word for word in my head, but my post tonight really has nothing to do with that. While I was sitting there a person decided to get on the never ending conversation about GOD and religion, I never mind this conversation because I love to hear what people think on the subject and maybe they'll say something that would make me change my whole point of view. So blah blah blah we have the basics, then someone states, and right here is one of the best questions I've ever heard; "When does a child stop being innocent?" At first I thought I had the answer but after I would think about it for awhile I would retract it and start again. The rest of the night which was about 45 minutes after the question and the others were busy trying to convince me that ghosts can't hurt you if you don't let them and blah blah blah I was sitting and pondering that question. I have a vague idea of an answer but I dare not say.  
     
    
</post>

<date>09,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I went to the  urlLink Sparta  show tonight and I must say they put on one hell of a show. Watching those guys rip out crunchy melodic rock made me remember why I wish I were a musician. I think they might have done that for the rest of the crowd in hand. Even the musicians present wished they were as good as them. Watching the 3 guitar ambush created by this super group presented the fellings that make me love music in general, they had the crowd wrapped around Jim Wards's gashed thumb. The smell of smoke, the sound of breaking beer bottles and the decore of afro clad teens was the setting of tonights adventure in holy bliss. The sounds comming off the stage rivaled that of the majority of the members former band  urlLink At The Drive In . Im a definate fan of ATDI but Sparta made me question my loyalty. They ended they're set with Air and in my opinion is the best song they have out. Besides the occasional tall guy in my veiw the night was gee diddly great! 
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      The last 2 nights have been eventful to say the least. Last night   urlLink Nick  actually went to the sand with us and I think he had a pretty good time. So I was pretty happy about that because that guy doesn't hang out that much so it was a rare treat at that. Friday night was just plain old fashioned insane but in a good way, I would go into details but I'm sure a few people wouldn't like that so I'll keep my mouth shut. In the long run a pretty good weekend showed itslef to rival the shitty one's we've been having. Tomorrow is the  urlLink Sparta  show and hopefully it will be a good one. If your in the area you should go give them a listen they're worth it. I haven't been to a good show in awhile so i'm anticipating this one. I've gotten a few hits of some good albums comming out soon and a few of them are must haves. If you care to find out what the hell I'm talking (aboot)  urlLink right here  are your answers. A little follow up to the spider story, when I said that the hell spawn was going to be waiting for me, I was wrong it was waiting for my mum. She was cruising down the road when she spotted the dead beast on the dashboard of the car. How it died? I don't know. Do I wish I was there to see it die? Yes and no. I do hope that it was the most painful death in the history of all arachnitides. Okay I'm done with my rant, So a good day to all and all that matter.  Peace
     
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Tonight I missed a great show due to my employment status. That status lies within the realms of being unemployed and relying on my folks to spot me a bill or ten. Well this show just happened to take place the day before an eagerly awaited payday, my parents that is. The 12.50 I needed was nowhere to be found, so  urlLink MCD  were one fan short of a spectacular farewell tour. I bet  urlLink Andy's  employed ass went and just my luck he's gonna tell me that they played the best show of they're short but inspiring career. So I was forced to spend an evening of drawn out stories that really go nowhere and if I cared enough to actually listen to them they would probably still wouldn't go anywhere. Well that's another story all together, all in all the night was a total waste but it could have been a total waste at home which tonight wasn't on the agenda.  Peace.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I just had one of the worst experiences of my life. Anyone that knows me knows that my worst fear in life is having a momma spider lay it's 8 disgusting legs upon my skin. Well what do ya know this happened to me about 5 minutes ago. I'll set the scene, here I am at 3 am doing a little late night/early morning laundry. I have my garments in their respected carrying container and I'm headed for the garage where in hand the laundry facilites lie. This is usualy routine for me and hopefully anyone with hygine priciples, I walk in head for the washing contraption and place my clothes on the ground. The lid is closed and at this point and I proceed to open it. On the little gyration device that stands in the middle of the washer sits the biggest, hairest, brownest, thickest, ugliest, most horrifying creature known to man (in my case). My hand is resting on the rim of the opening and I didn't even have time to blink let alone move my hand. It felt as if my hand was glued to the machine and my feet plastered to the oil-stained concrete. In a slowmotion instant replay type of moment the hell spawn leaped on my hand and preceeded to crawl to my wrist. Then the tape sped up and I freaked, I jerked my hand back, slaped my face with the momentum, screamed something awful and tumbled backwards, knocked the family sized box of Gain with bleach off the washer, slamed full weight on my pops' 95' Toyota Tercel, set the damn alarm off and fell to the ground. With the alarm blaring and my face stinging from the selfinflicted slap I get on my feet fearing where the hairy beast might be lurking. I swear when it jumped on my hand he called my name out just to let me know that he was waiting for me. I run to find my dad's keys and silent the alarm, then the shock of what just happened sets in and I start to slap every part of my body and make wimpering noises. The slaps where to insure that the devil was off of me and wasn't hanging around in my clothing. I attacked the cabinets under the sink for some type of anti-bug spray and only came out with a bottle of windex. I cautiously entered the garage with full reflexes and a quick trigger finger. The bastard was nowhere to be found, it's probably made it's way into my room and is waiting in the blanket to finish the job. It's goal is not to bite me but to scare the piss out of me so I can slowly die of a heart attack. DAMN ARACHNIDS! Damn them all to hell.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Lets do the "How Much Money Cory Owes the El Paso Police Department" tally, so on this cold November day in 2001 I currently owe $700 and some odd bucks in tickets. I swear if I get one more ticket in my life I seriously think I will lose it and attack the offending officer or officers. Does the fact that both of my stickers are expired by an average of 4 months and the additional icing is that I have no insurance and I probably never will, do any of the afformentioned keep me from driving my car? NOPE, I'll drive that bitch untill the FBI comes looking for me. I thought I would drop a pre-work post and do a little rambling because everyone knows thats all I'm good for is some unadulterated babble. I'm patiently waiting for my mom because she's on her way home with a rockin samich from 'subway' and I'm getting giddy waiting for my turkeywich. I think  urlLink someone  else would agree that I haven't had a great subway samach since our little trip to Alberquerque. I've had some good ones but none to rival that of New Mexico. I'm looking forward to work, I know that today is my day to make money as is every friday for that matter, the crew is probably partaking in Mexican festivities tonight and hopefully if the gods see fit in letting me leave work early I'll be partaking as well. I bought "The Day Linclon Was Shot" today for 35 cents so thats a deal if I ever saw one, I'm going back before work to purchase a Kurt Vonnegut book for 2.00 bucks which is also a steal at twice the price. The Paperback Exchange will keep me knee deep in books till I die, I finally finished " On the Road" and I think that I've never been happier to finish anything in my life, graduating high school had nothing on finishing that book, nothing will ever take the place of that moment ever. Last night we all indulged in the leaf and I must say that we were all lit to the max, some more than others but we were all in the same frame of mind. For some reason I can't get The White Stripes out of my speakers they have been ruling my world for a few days and the last few days have been good. Yesterday I talked to someone I haven't talked to in awhile and I must say it was fun, and I'm glad  urlLink she  returned from her trip in one peice and  sans  salmonilla. I'm sure thats not how you spell it but so. After spending a few hours in the freezing weather last night my knees, I think have permenatly frozen in the sitting down position cause they aren't working to well right now or today for that matter. Holy crap my wich du sand has arrived so thats my que to shut up and get fatter.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Drinkin some hot cocoa and evaluating the certain things in my mind, example why is cocoa spelled with an 'a'? why not 'coco'? Okay I'm losing it, the spelling of cocoa has no effect on my life and probably never will. Just returned from a slow ass day at work and I must say that days/nights like these make me wonder why I'm wearing my sweater in my 90 degree house? As you can tell this post is turning out to be a piece of shiet and I'll be the first to admitt it. I discovered today that kareoke has to be the dumbest idea of all time, all day long I listen to idiots butcher songs, dance like the nsyncboys, mumble or giggle their way through a normally good song. You have the regular people who can actually sing but constantly sing the same songs over and over again, you can only hear "dust in the wind" so many times before you want to rip out your own eyes and offer them to the masses. You have your horrid "Kareoke host" who has to call everyone "the party capi-tan" of the evening while he sings "just a giggalo". I've had it, I swear the next time I hear a kareoke rendion of "riders on the storm" I'm going to swing from the rafters and decapitate the unlucky soul. Beside kareoke mishapps life is good I can't complain but I garauntee I will.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      So it seems that to fix my record player I need about 50 bucks and it's not like it has an electrical problem, the needle just broke! Well thats just another twist in the endless tale of my life, wow that sounded a little self-loathing. As I were in the past I must say no to that direction of self-abuse and self-defeation. I opened a bank account for the first time in my life and I am now in the proccess of saving, for what might you ask? I really don't know either there is talk of plans for the near future but we all know the way plans and I work out. I'll just wait and see for now, but it's always nice to have a little something for a rainy day or 2. I have to make another court appearance soon and I'm dreading it, I feel as if I'm going to walk in and the cops are gonna run my name through the doo-hicky and pummle me on the spot, I would only be cool with the beating if the fuzz actually used the word pummle or bludgent. listening to  urlLink The White Stripes  and I must say that they are setting the mood for this cold, empty night. On nights like this I have the urge to smoke cigaretts and sit in my backyard gawking at the sky in wonder and wishing I could see the stars up close. Right now the sky is a smokey kind of gray and the air smells like snow, I love it when you can see your breath in the air it gives me a kind of fresh and free feeling, sounds queer I know but I can't help it im a romantic.   This cigarette it could seduce a nation with  it's smoke, crawling down my tired throat,  scratches a part of me that's purring.  jets to Brazil.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh, the day off I love em' I get to sleep and slump my lazy ass down for as long as I want. I wish I would have done something today though instead of sitting around watching TBS all day. This weekend has been a blast for some and a damn nightmare for others, groups of people visiting for the weekend and groups of people causing drama in the circle. I did a lot of working during the weekend and I made some good money which is always a good thing. I dropped by a raging party lastnight, well at least it was raging before I got there and thats good enough for me, I really didn't know anyone but the hot girl ratio was outstanding and I saw a girl that looked like a girl I don't wanna look at right now. That little sighting was strangly reasuring and very night ruining, I guess I could say that the night for a lot of people was like that fun yet disturbing. The last couple of days have been strange in turn all of my friends including myself have been on the defensive and we've all been super pissy. I really don't know why but I hold no grudges against it. I'm sure everyone has had or still has something on or around their minds that make the shit toleration at a minimum, personally I think I'm too young to feel pissy what do I have to be pissy about, but I guess your never too young to feel like hell and want everyone else to fee like it too. Last night I was accused of being rude, and truthfully I was offended, personally I try my best to be a nice person and be as kind as I can but, what can you do? I barely realized that I have VH1 classic and if I must say so it's rockin, I've seen some good ass videos in the hour and a half that I realized that I had it. I barely realzed that this post sucks and it was a complete waste of my time.  Hasta
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      HOLY GEE WIZ! It seems as if  urlLink Nick  has decided to blog for the first time in lets say along time, it's good to see that stuff going down. Well let's talk shall we? Good things have been going on and as usual I'm here to rub it in, while your reading this I'm out having a good time and laughing it up. I swear to hey-zuse my dad has the farquin heater on 120 degrees, it's hotter than  urlLink Andy's   breath on a hot Texan day. Mexico last night was one of the greatest nights I've had there to date, no-stop laughter, non-stop corona de little and non-stop ladies. The group that went this night was the biggest to date about 10 people were involved in the debauchery and it was greeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeat. Jon decided that he had had enough booze and came up with the plan the he was going to puke on the bar, and so he did. A late night breakfast at Denny's proved fatal as Andy lost his mind and acosted the waitress with his long distance bickering and neverending want of the check. After my lumber jack slam was half devoured and my sprite was all but gone we headed for home gently yelling  bloody hell the whole way home. As usual the night was a total blast and I wish you could have been there with me, or maybe I don't cause I would have probably had to spot you some beer and I'm not a rich man just comfortable.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Aren't meteor showers the greatest? They bring out the poet, scholar, romantic and idiots all in one sitting. Sitting in the backyard of La Tuya, drinkin a cold one and loungin with friends the sky amused us all and amused some too much. Listening to some  urlLink Album Leaf  feeling the deep grooves and feeling tired and relaxed. Question, why are Chuck's the only shoes that look better dirty and used? I couldn't begin to tell ya why, some people strive to keep they're shoes clean and orderly but if you get some Chuck's they better be ragged. Lastnight I ventured into the coolest house of all time, it was abandoned warming for renovation but it was grand, gothic in a way yet cozy and modern, Sitting on Nick's roof lastnight partaking in the sky-works brought back some long forgotten memories and it was nice to remember, I think I like remembering better than actually doing the memory, if you follow. When you do something sure it's fun but it has it's down points and all that jazz but, the memory is always good and it is even better than the actual experience. You make the happenings better in your mind, more likeable so to speak. That night your girlfriend broke up with you, now you think of it as nostalgia and it has a new feeling. Remebering the many nights on Nick's roof talking and laughing and endangering our lives, see it sounds really crappy and sort of cheesy but, the memories makes it lovable and you wish that you could feel like that again. One day all the things I do now and the people I do them with will unfortunatley be a memory and I'll bet you a milion buck's they'll be good ones.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      have you ever noticed that when your having a conversation and suddenly the voices stop and it's dead silent, everyone looks at each other trying to see who the conversation starter will be. I wanna be the conversation starter but I don't think I have what it takes, I'm just the guy who points out the silence by saying something smart ass-y or just pointing out the problem by making an akward face or something of that nature. Everyone hates that crap yet when you get in a spot with a person that will not shut up everyone hates that too. I feel bad for the converstion people in the world, they are hated all over no matter where you go someone somewhere is making people irritated by talking to much. Is the talking the real problem or is it a deeper issue? Maybe we are all jealous that we don't have the converstaion skills to keep up and we have horrid conversations that only last a few moments and we move on. Maybe we are the irritating ones and they are the real conversationalists, or maybe we all hate them because usually when they talk and talk and talk it's usually about themselves. I'm really sorry I had to get that off my chest so to speak. Well it seems as if the crew has made plans to attend a Thanksgiving parade it should be fun, I've never attended a parade before and I have a bad image of them due to the high school marching band attacking my street and ruining my slumber. We'll see how that goes I'm always down for something out of the ordinary, and hopefully the parade will be ready too.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Mini Corona, watered down ta-kill-ya and lots 'o' laughs, as you can see last night was a good one due to the 300 drunkin college kids dawning red limp bizkit yankee caps, chubby girls in backless shirts, hot girls in backless shirts, hot girls in hot backless shirts danicing to " U Can't Touch This", yeah it was great! I thought the night was going to be a total waste but I had a good time and I do hope everyone else did as well. For the first time in along time the al-key-hall had an effect on me and I was feeling like a million bucks plus 2. There was some crazy drama at the bridge and we were stuck in a drunk hold up for about 20 minutes, getting to know your fellow drunkards sometimes can be a little mental test and sometimes you just wanna slap bleach out of the eminem look-a-like standing next to you and believe me you would have had your choice of which person to do so. I was actually let in to a club/bar that for some reason or another in the past has shuned me away and lowered my esteem du self, last night was different they actually let me in with no reservations and it was go time! 50 cent coronas, can't beat that no matter what time zone or planet your on, plans to indulge in the leaf were in the making and a late night laugh-off was eagerly anticipated. The weather put a hold on that little plan and the night was over around 3:30 am, I say that anytime after 2:30 is a good time to call it a night anything before that your just a sissy.  Work is calling my name in about 3 hours so I better get my lazy ass crackin, have somethings to do and people to hate.  hasta.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Listening to some  urlLink AM/FM  and I'm feeling good. Last night I popped some crazy allergy pills and I started to trip out and I thought I was on my way out of this life, but all I needed was some long deserved R&R. Today was my first day off since I started working and I wish I was at work right now, I've been bitten by the money bug and I need/want more, is wanting as much money as possible wrong? I personally don't think it is, money is the root of all evil but it's also the root of all things heavenly. As of right now I'm feeling heavenly, I have a pocket full 'o' cash, the crew has made plans to partake in Mexican festivities and the weather is chilly and the sky is gray. My room smells of death due to the ritual waterbed explosion and my wall to wall lime green shag rug is soaked to the core with moldy, dank water. According to the  urlLink Violence  Bubba has made a triumphant return to the world of blogging and if I must say so myself I'm glad to have the guy back, hopefully we'll get more from him before he returns in to his self-inflicted exile. Just the other night I was going over my life as if it were a small movie of the sort and I decided that my life wasn't that bad, rockin even. I have good freinds, money , family that only mildly pisses me off and I'm alive so what could be better than that? Well of course it's missing a few important objects but that will come in time right? As the masses say everyone gets their one chance at everything, and hopefully I haven't missed mine.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well it seems as if I haven't posted in awhile, maybe because I haven't. So lets get reaquainted shall we? HI my name is(read bottom of post). How goes it loyal reader, it's been about a week or so since my last post and I've missed you dearly. My blog lover where have you been this past lonely week, ah I've found you right where I left you. So for those who don't know the reason for my post vacation, it's that after months and months of half assed job hunting one just fell in my lap for free so to speak. I've been a full time waiter and a part time rock 'n' rolla for about a week, the money keeps me in music while my dancing career gets off the ground. That was funny me a dancer, anywho the food industry has been good to me and hopefully it will continue to bend at my dynamic serving skills. Nothing really interesting has happened in the week of my disapearance but as I fear and impatiently wait for the food industry has some pretty creepy characters walking through it and hopefully I'll get to see one or 2 of them flip out over the cheese they ordered on they're burger. As the say in the bussiness " Food's up"
     
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      What can I say about last night, not only did I witness the greatest show ever but I was also having a damn dandy day. I was feeling extra cheer and feeling that life was good, the show just put a period at the end of the night and a damn good ending it was.  urlLink Trail Of Dead  showed everyone how to do it and why. The night was just chaulk full of great bands, Orson Wells, Siva, Universal Recovered, and you will know us by the trail of dead. Orson Wells just happened to rock my socks but the band thought different, the pressure of playing for such special show got to their minds and the freaked but all in all they were rockin'. Siva and Universal ripped it up as per usual and I was in indie heaven, a night full of black rimmed glasses was no match for my mood. As for Trail of Dead I really don't think I have to elaborate but I must! Myself and the entire crowd knew what was in store for us and we still got more, so much more. It seemed as the show went on the Trail just started rockin' harder and faster every song, more shaking and more hunched over guitar playing. My ears were seconds away from bleeding with furious passion and the room was bending at the raw power emitting from the amps. Aside from the tall guy standing in front and in back of me with his damn digital camer, letting the damn strap " grace" my hair and me freaking out everytime because it felt like a bug or some critter lounging on my domepeice. If blowing the shirts of our backs with their crunchy rock wasn't enough, the band decided it was a good idea to destroy about 75 guitars and a window toboot. The drum kit took a beating as well, watching the guitar tech run outside to throw the snare back in the window was worth my 6 bucks alone. After all the mayhem stopped the stage was left in a musical graveyard state, and the crowd snapped out of the music induced trance and parted ways with the Trail and will tell tall tales of that night for years. I myself left the scene with pockets full of Trail 'o' Dead merch and I was a happy boy. After the show I took that long journey home and partook in some leaf with Nick, partook in some late night comedy that we were generating on our own. For the record my left ear still isn't 100% and I'm starting to freakout, but if I do go deaf it would have been worth it.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I seemed to have forgoten how good it feels to have a job and then I remember how much it sucks. I've been working for 3 days now and it's an easy job and what not but......but.................... it puts a cramp on the life I love-d and worship. The life of sleeping till 2 and then doing absolutely nothing till 10, everyone has been there once or twice, I really miss it already and it's only been 3 days. Well today was a short test in embarrasment, here is the scene, it's 9:45 am and an evil little man that dosen't know english is mopping the floors,  I slowly walk to the top of a 2 step high platform do some odd jobs and proceed to walk down. I place my foot on the first step and I took  noticed that the step was soaked an I should be carefull, I step on the floor and my right leg starts to slide and I begin to do the splits. I try and keep my legs from parting in opposite ways and start to flail my legs and arms furiously, The thought in my head was that if I do the splits the odd's of my tight ass kahki's ripping and exposing my droors where pretty good so thats why I began to flail. I fall back on my hip and my knee slams into the floor, my head hits the floor as well. I lay there yelling "OH GOD OH GOD" for a good 20 seconds and then I realize that a few people were looking at me and gawking at my pain, at that moment I wanted to die and kill at the same time. As if slamming key bones on to the floor wasn't enough pain for me The fall decided to leave my freshly pressed and washed kahki's scuffed with some sort of black grime or something of that nature. I had to walk around the whole day with black streaks on my ass due to some watery steps. I should fake an injury and claim some workmans comp, free money cause we all know employment is for the birds.  ( In a cool  urlLink Bob Nanna  voice) Run for your life The ride is on fire All in tune All of this abandon I can barely stand it All in tune. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Drinking some Dr. Pepper, really don't like it but I have a crazy urge for sugar and the pep is providing. Last few days have been the usual, fun; but the usual, lots of beer and lots of illegal psycotropics. Mexico last night was fun and some crazy debauchery went down once a-gain, std's were spread oraly, corona was ingested oraly, cigaretts were smoked respitoraly( if thats a word), and chico's was eatin verticaly. Tonights Jon's B-day and the poor lad is inside pondering his life over a gigantic dub, and I'm sitting here pulling computer geek duty while the rest of the world is doing something that would probably make me mad. This post is going nowhere and I don't care one little bite' yeah i said bite.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well as I predicted Halloween was a total bust. I could see it from the empty streets in my nieghborhood, and many others also. No candy seekers what kind of Halloween is that? Has this years Halloween come in a year where threre aren't any kids left, just angry, acne ridden teenagers, party seeking post teens like myself, or is it a deeper conflict? All I know is that I had a good thing going last night and gave it up for a test in bordome. I left free drinks and drunkin kareoke ballads, hot waitresses, hot friends and hot french fries. I left all that for a cold beer, hard cookies, silent hill, really loud surfer guys, peanut M&M's(well those are cool) and a scooby doo movie. Yeah you guessed it, a complete waste of time, I guess it could have been worse I was with good friends and around 2 am I started to have fun.  urlLink Nick  stopped by with some leaf and we had our own little party.   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2001</date>
<post>

     
      8:45 am............... My dad shakes my foot and tells me someone is on the phone talking about a trip to Pheonix, the man with the master plan is  urlLink Andy , greetings were taken and the question was " are you ready?"..........................NOPE. I needed about 20 minutes to get ready and 20 minutes it was, a race against the clock ensued, a quick shower and a stroke of deorderant and we were on our way. A slight detour was in progress when we decided we needed to ingest in some donuts from the infamous Dunkin donuts, hot cocoa or coco as I would put it burned my sensitive tongue and the journey was on. 5 minutes into the drive I had already spilled some damn hot coco on my gear and burned my hand with the searing liquid, Andy, the man with the plan and the mouth of steel gulped his piping hot goodness in easy strides. The road was calling our names and we were speeding toward it, eagerly anticipating the events ahead. First stop.... food and an inerstate 'subway' was grabbing our thoughts and we participated in good humor, a few trucker jokes and a hot 'subway' employee later we were back on the road as JK would say. Later a game of " who can make the most truckers honk by pumping their fists in the air" began and at last count Andy was up by one truck, I was down for the count untill a truck weighing station showed her face to me and the trucks honked in my favor. One last stop before our final destination, a restroom break in the mother of all truck stops, they sold everything from candy to cd players, they even had an arcade room where I had to stop off and try my luck, after a few games of video hunting and a handfull of  urlLink hillbilly  jokes, the road had us. The last stop was of course the great town of Pheonix, Arizona, I loved it as soon as I caught a good glimpse, traffic was insane but tolerable since I wasn't driving, we met the lovely ladies that were letting us sleep on they're floor shortly after at one of the coolest apartments I've ever seen. After a warm greeting and a couple of dogs we were on our way to see the town and head for the reason we traveled so far. A slow trip to a rockin record store and a quick trip to a convienence store and we were on our way to glory and some just plain old rockin and rollin. The Nile Theater 7:30 pm, the presence of "EMO" and all of her stupidity was present as we looked for parking, the walk to the club was like none I've ever taken, I was just about to see  urlLink Hey Mer  and I was giddy with anticipation. The place was packed with black rimmed glasses, beatle hair cuts, tight pants and the worst part, I saw a few geeks wearing the're very own, home -made Saves the Day shirts, frankly I wanted to punch every last one of them.........but I digress. The first band showed their faces and I expected the worst noise ever to come out of the pa but boy was I wrong,  urlLink Thursday  showed me a thing or 2. Slow ballads laced with cruchy guitars and some serious drum work was the making of this band, besides the sometimes cheesy mic spin and the Cedric-esk dance moves, they ripped! The moment I and probably 3 other people were waiting for, yep you guessed it Hey Mercedes took the stage, the opening chords to 'Frowning of a Lifetime' reared it's head and I began to sway, the band hunched over with the force of music and I hunched along, singing every word and slapping the drum beats on my thighs I was in semi-heaven. The following songs would consist of 85% new record and the rest old, every song put me into a dreamy state while Bob shook his head to the beat of the song, watching them play made me see that they are insanely great musicians and they made it look effortless, Damon has to be by far the greatest drummer I've had the privalage of seeing, not only did he rip it up for Hey Mer but he pulled double duty and rocked it with Saves the Day. With my fist occasionally in the air and the words constantly in my mouth I shuffled my feet and slapped my thighs for one of the greatest sets in history, they blurred the line between humans and God. After the set I parted ways with Hey Mer, hopefully not for the last time. 9:30... Saves the Day takes the stage and the crowd loses it, I'm not to enthused to see them on the basis that they have idiots for fans and the whole time before they came on I could here them talking shit about they other bands, thats just not kosher where I'm from. As usual STD as the idiots called them by their handcrafted crap shirts rocked it, played some of my favorites and a lot of songs off the new record but all in all they ripped as well, not as rockin as some other band that played called Hey Mercedes but it was good. Vicky and Valerie knew the happs on a little after show hangout and we stopped by for a little look at what too much pot and too much beer can do to a person, "The Flying V's"(Vicky and Valerie) had a few things to do in the morning so the stay in the crack house was abruptly ended and the coronas were tapped, the buzz came to me in a cigarett and hunger induced shock. An air mattress, a dog bitting my hair, and a few hours of sleep. Day 2 involved a late breakfast early lunch, brunch if you will at a place called " The Cheba Hut" which was a Marijuana themed samach place that had the names of pot for the names of their samacha's. The food was rockin and I want to go back right now, a stroll in the shopping section of town was induced and my love of the town grew, I was a little sad to leave but I will return one day, so Pheonix I hope your ready for me and my crew.   We have a new record out called "Everynight Fireworks" and this songs not on it............  Bob Nanna
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Drinking some caffeine free coke and I must say due to my love of all things bad for you this shiet is pretty bomb. Another day at work and another day wasted with the trappings of fame, who's fame? Well my fame of course, not a day goes by that I don't wish I were normal and could walk through a mall without getting spotted by flocks of young girls, having my picture taken and being able to buy whatever the hell I want. See you dumb ass rock stars you see how dumb that sounds. I would give my right eye to have all that and some. If you don't want people to know who you are then don't become famous and don't put your face on the cover of cosmo girl. Frankly I'm sick and tired of all this bullshit e-mail I get everyday. I don't check my mail for 2 days and I have 100 messages by some chick named Julie and all she dose is talk about how much fun she had with me last night and how wet her nasty cunt is. Sorry for the explicit words but I must show the whole picture. If I get one more message from Julie or her cunt.... it's go time! Today I received 3 warrants for my arrest due to the horrindus amount of money I owe the EPPD, if they catch me it seems like a few days in the cage for good ol' Cory. I really don't think I can handle that, I know I know noone thinks they can handle jail but I swear if I get pulled over before I have a chance to pay those bastaches off, you'll see me and my red Oldsmobile Achieva running for dear life on the interstate 10. I promise I'll get away and start fresh in some other cun-tree where I'll change my name to Filliberto, attorney at law.  My name is Jonas......................................  
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      This cough I have is starting to wear thin on my patience. Okay enough about my lung fluid let's get to the babble. I was reading the  urlLink Violence  earlier and I remember those late night B-ball sessions as well and damn were they the best. I wonder if you fellas remember the night we played in the pouring rain in Portland, Maine? That was a crazy right? We all freaked out on that last bolt of lightning that came dangerously close to our persons. Andy gettting smacked in the head with a soggy ass B-ball while tieing his shoes and what-not. Damn those were the times even though they were a few short months ago it feels like ages ago. So it turns out that Bubba's pride and waste of money was hit and now I think he's on the verg of a serious meltdown, so every chico's damn tacos be on alert Bubba's out to drown his sorrows with a mega helping of 'raton de caldo'. I really don't know what that means it just sounds gross. I was drinkin drinkin drinkin coca coca cola, I can feel it running right on down, right on down my throat-a.  I'm out like clear Pepsi........................ 
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      We are Wyld Stalyns! Damn that movie still makes me laugh after all those years of growing up and girls, I'm still a big ass geek that laughs at stupid stoner kids. I'm talking to Andy's arse right now and I must say it's good to talk to him, the poor fella has been sleeping on a couch for a month and he thought he was receiving a nice comfortable bed......... all he got was a cheap ass mattress. It seems Bubba likes to chime in every now and then to insult people, don't get me wrong I'm all about hurting peoples feelings but sometimes you just have to refrain from calling people clowns, especialy when your nickname is 'Bubba'. I saw Vanilla Sky last night, and I loved the hell out of it but I don't think I watched it under the right circumstances. My opinion of the movie........ I say it was the craziest thing I've ever seen and I was glued to the screen just so I could get some sort of grasp on what was going on. If you haven't seen it I say it's a must and if you never see it then your no freind of mine. I was just thinking right now about something that I haven't done in awhile, and that is attend a show of some sort. I haven't been to a really good show since Pheonix, you know Hey Mercedes, Saves the Day ..............day. Yeah well thats how long it's been and I'm starting to feel  the musical itch in my beat keeping foot. While were on the subject of Hey Mer and STD(as the queers in some places like to call them), why is it that everyband on that tour no has some bullshit video and Hey Mer dosen't? I'm pretty happy that they don't though cause I would hate for some poser as emo kid to ask me if i saw the video for 'Quit' and how melencholy he felt while Bob Nanna belted out the chorus. On the same subject, I was told by someone that they have lost a little love for Hey Mer due to the infactuation of another fan that this said person hates. If your confused go read a book........ I'm out.   Quit if your through with it you are gonna make me sick, sitting there with your hands in your hair.  Hey Mercedes
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I had this crazy dream lastnight, and in this certain dream everyone that was in it had huge heads, imitating that crazy 'Ludacris' video. I started to freak-out a little in the dream but then I realized it ws really funny and I became envious of their copulant, cranial capacity and I started to wish them all harm. So in short I had another freaky ass dream in which I started getting slow evil revenge on all that attended. This mega pouch of 'Capri Sun' is tearing my taste buds apart with it's neverending quantity of life giving solitude and it's rambunctious attitiute of drink me fast and hard wait till I'm empty to taste. Did anyone see the damn Raiders lose there shit in goddam New England of all places, what the shit is that? I think they should make a rule that teams only play each other if they have the same climate,  what the hell gives having a team from sunny ol' Oakland play a team from blizzard ass New England. Maybe I'm just bitching because I've been a fan of the Raiders for 16 yeras of my life and I can't remember the last time they were that close to " The Bowl".  Coach, do you remeber me? It's me George Costanza, JFK high...........  Can't Stand YA!  
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Will the violins be playing? Noone is going to play the harp for you when you die. Kill me in my favorite clothes. I drug your ghost around the country as we plotted out me death and every city visited whispered " here is where you rest." I just thought I 'd share a few of my top creep lines from certain songs with you. Listening to back and to the left by a little band know as " Texas is the Reason" and I must say that this record just never loses it's flare and I must say that flare is sort of a drab and isn't a great word to describe anything let alone this record so I'll change it from flare to unpenatrable beam of Godly light that blinds only the weak and sterilizes the evil. Right now my self-esteem is just above the ground because a very beautiful girl walked by me, smiled and said hi to me in Mexico tonight, I know I know pathetic you say well I say your jealous and you wish you were as handsome as I was. I also think that the boys over in Austin are becoming heavy drinkers and are beginning to lose touch with reality and they think that it's cool to have a good time and drink with hot chicks in hot pants with hot freinds that have hot asses, you Bastards! I hope one or all of you have a severe eye injury due to careless drunkin dart olympics and you need eye prosthetics, patches, glass eyes, you know the works.    Well this town was built on miles of hope and I dare you give me one reason to stay.  Texas is the Reason
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Damn it seems as if the boys over at  urlLink the violence  have been busy, I didn't expect to hear from them in awhile seeing how school has started, and they are in a great town living it up. Well it's good to see them keeping to the posting policy, maybe I'll take que and resume the position I once denied (what movie is that from?). Well these past few weeks have been a little strange and alot of good things have been happening; my pops finally got his job back and he's getting paid a hefty amount more than before so that means, oh wait he never gave me money anyway. My cousin has finally decided to stop being a thug and she has decided to join the army, that wouldn't have been my choice for a career but I'm glad she has decided to do something with her life. For awhile I was getting a little worried about her she's had some rough times and she's seen alot for only being 22 years old. At work alot of things are going on, people are going to get fired, hired and fired again. People at work are some serious bad influences, in the last month or so I've been living the life way to much and it's starting to take it's toll. I talked to the playa Andy a few days ago and I must say it was good to hear from him since his departure, on another weird note David and Jon just up and left one day and the last I heard they are living it up in Georgia, hotlanta if you will. I think today I'll follow Andy's lead and end this post with a little Alk Trio Tribute................ I never had a drink that I didn't like, one taste of you and I puked all night. Christ thats harsh!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I hate the U.S mail. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The freeway going 65 mph, my fuel indicator going on 'E', my Marlboro Ultra Light going on filter, and  urlLink Sparta  making love to my ears. That was the scene I was in earlier this afternoon as I was returning from a pointless day at the office and in a bout 2 hours thats where I'll be returning to for a little thing we call a split. Today has and is going to be a weird one, I was harrased and then charmed by a young urban fellow selling pixie sticks on the off ramp, I was accused of stealing food from young childrens mouths, and to top it all off I just received some more good tidings from the El Paso Police Department. Hopefully this damn day will get a little more interesting, last night was odd as well, a whole day aimlesly wandering this fair city in search of happyness and relife of the endless torment known as boredome. I watched a little movie called "13 Ghosts" last night and I must say it was one of the worst movies I've ever seen in my short and uneventful life. last night ended with a few glasses of Amberbock and a few drags of leaf, a few Z's, a few waffles, and a few dollars.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I called into work today and told them I had a severe case of the vomits and now I'm relaxing in front of the comp debating on the coming events of tonight. I feel a little bad about the whole work situation because some poor sap that thought they had the day off is now pushing plates, and answering rude customer requests till 5. So it seems that Andy didn't leave yesterday, yesterday I smoked alot and ate alot of mashed potats, yesterday I made 56 dollars and spent 11, yesterday I realized that the live "Fleetwood Mac" record I have is the best live recording I've ever heard, yesterday Nick had a pretty horrible day and he's super bummed and I wish I could tell him something to make him feel better but I can't, because I don't know what to say, yesterday I fell in love with " Maybe I'll Catch Fire" by  urlLink  Alkaline Trio  again, yesterday was today yesterday.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I think that Monpoly has run it's course in my life and I vow to never lay my hands on that damn iron (not a hot one but the piece in the game) again. Tonight Andy beat me by a few small dollars and won the farquin game, or maybe I let him win on account of him leaving in a few short hours and me wanting him to feel good on his last night here. Well how ever the story goes it can't compare to this Texas sized headache I have at the moment, I've taken some aleve and I must say that they are doing the trick, all I need now is some well deserved R&R  Your telephone's the one that helped me wrap the cord around your neck... At the Drive In  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Have you ever wondered why? I have a-many time, and the answer is always ' because'............................................... Right now I'm wondering why my left eye is puffy and sore while the rest of the dual eyed population is resting easy on they're soft pillows and warm blankets while I sleep on flat pillows and a semi-warm blanket, with a swollen eye. It's been awhile since blogger and myself have crossed paths and I think it's time to rekindle some old flames. I wonder if the  urlLink one  person that read this little peice of solitude, still reads? These past few weeks have been some to remember and some to forget, the holidays were like any other holiday in my whole 21 years of celebrating........... tolerable. I see that  urlLink Bob Nanna  has finished the " Top 365 songs of 2001" and I was a little surprised to see who was number 1, but I do agree it is a great song. Speaking of great songs I'm listening to a little diddy by the name of "Halo of the Strange" by a little band known as " Karate", I haven't dove into Karate in so long and it feels good to come back. On that note of comming back, I think I'll end this little testament of lattitude and retire myself to the depths of slumber.  Hasta
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2002</date>
<post>

     
      While I'm busy posting on everyones blog under the sun my own creation sits and waits for the return of it's master. It seems as if the blogger community has exploded and the walls are now comming down. It also seems as if Andy has a serious over-crowding problem at his little  urlLink vision . All is well in my area of the globe in fact I feel that things are better than they have ever been. I have this strange feeling that everything makes sense, even though there are millions of questions and millions of answers for those questions, I have the feeling that I have them all and there is no need to disect and evaluate any and everything. There is this guy that comes to work almost everyday and he sits in the window, drinks tea and water and he lightly talks to himself. Everyone thinks he's a crazy ass and he should be shot and I will admitt at first glance he is severly insane but, if you sit down and have a conversation with this fellow, as I did and as I discovered he happens to be one of the smartest people I have ever spoken too. He's like my own personal buddah and he guides me through life with his vast knowledge of what he thinks life is about. He once told me that all life is is one big mental trick, if you think that your winning then your winning, unfortunatly some people are so far in the hole that there is no possible way to trick the mind. If you think your winning then your winning.  Kelly we can't go on pretending.................  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2002</date>
<post>

     
                                              Cold apendages seek warmth on the apparatus of God.                                              The pages smell of bark freshly cut to entertain.                                                               4 wheels of gratitude prespire on the forehead of fear,                                          indefinate change dangles my lust for all things descrete.                                    Indentations of emotion lay dying on the shag, and loosend lips tell of the loss                                                                                                                                                               ????                                              
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Okay it's official some bastard thug has stolen my soul. About a week ago while I was at bloodyknuckles' lab someone broke into my car and stole all of my music, that's right they took the one thing that meant something to me. These poor excuses of humans have stolen my kids and I can't do anything about it. Now I drive my car listening to the local clasic rock station and long for the memory of blurry rides home lost in the "music" that was once everything to me. So untill I referbish my collection and the perpetrators are punished by the melting of they're organs, I will be in mourning. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      So it seems as if having a job actually did take up alot of my time, I see now that in the wake of not having a job I have ample time to sit on my ass and ponder life and all things that make it at this point in my young life stagnant and lackluster. After waiting about 2 months for the U.S. mail to work in my favor I finally received my drums, and after having them for a combined 14hrs I've already had the fuzz called on me due to a " noise" complaint due to Nick and myself rocking the fucking roof of the joint. So now I have to rock my kit guerilla style and pull some incognito damage. As of now Double Decka Donny Darko has informed me of a little And you will know us by.......... appearance on Mr. Conan so I must be off.  Catch ya later hater. 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is the first time in almost 2 years this bad mutha has seen the likes of me. I'm like a proud father seeing his only child after a hiatus of sorts. I'm sure that noone will even see this so I'm bound to ramble. I'll do my best and try to get this sucka jumping again like the good ol' days huh boy? I'm sitting here watching "Teen Wolf" and I must commend Hollywood on their ability to make a racially concious movie work no matter what the premise is. A "teen wolf" goes through the the trial of being a "teen" along with being a "wolf" now if you ask me thats just classic stuff. I think back to movies like "Mississippi Burning" racial tension in the heart of the south/ racial tensions amidst a small suburban town with a guy named Styles, I say classic. Why can't they just see him for who he is, a young kid trying to score with the popular girl and also be the star of the basketball team. I mean who dosen't want that? I did but I wasn't lucky enough to have wolf in my blood. I didn't even go to the prom, oh but "Teen Wolf" goes and he's looking like a damn monster, fucking freak he should have been shot and killed as soon as he "wolfed out" at the basketball game. He lands Boof and I'm sitting here typing this travesty, life is so harsh. I wannna be a "teen wolf".  Alright ramblers lets get ramblin' 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>