<Blog>


<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Burn asshole....burn  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I feel your pain  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      you have no clue do you?  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Poor Roger...I'm sure we all know penguines just like him  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Believe me...I use this every day  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Get 'em started early  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yes...you are....  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Just vote Republican  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      In case I forgot to tell you....Happy New Year!  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Piss us off....we're on the way...  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thanks for making it abundantly clear!  urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thanks to the advent of photoblogging, I now have an outlet for all the humor I have welled up inside.  Before the problem was one of server space and bandwidth. Now that I don't have to worry about either of those I shall have free comedic reign!  Let the Bull-Shit flow forth, and let us be jolly!
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A man is dining in a fancy restaurant and there is a gorgeous redhead sitting at the next table. He has been checking her out since he sat down, but lacks the nerve to start a conversation. Suddenly she sneezes and her glass eye comes flying out of its socket toward the man. He reflexively reaches out, grabs it out of the air and hands it back.  "Oh my, I am so sorry," the woman says as she pops her eye back in place. "Let me buy your dinner to make it up to you."  They enjoy a wonderful dinner together, and afterward they go to the theatre followed by drinks. They talk, they laugh, she shares her deepest dreams and he shares his. She listens. After paying for everything, she asks him if he would like to come to her place for a nightcap ... and stay for breakfast. They have a wonderful, wonderful time.  Next morning she cooks a gourmet meal with all the trimmings. The guy is amazed. Everything has been so incredible.   "You know," he said, "You are the perfect woman. Are you this nice to every guy you meet?"   "No," she replies, "you just happened to catch my eye."      In a small town the bell ringer in the church quits. The sexton advertises for a replacement. The first guy who shows up has no arms.  "But ... but ..." the sexton says, "How can you ...? I mean, with your handicap?"   "Just watch," says the no-armed man. They go up to the bell tower and he runs at the bell and BANG! he slams it with his face and the bell lets out a dull bong. Then he starts to do it again, and the sexton stops him.  "Not again," he says. "I can't watch. Tell me, do you really need the job this badly?" The man assures him that he does. So the sexton hires him.  Sunday comes and it's time to ring the bell to summon the faithful to church. A breeze is blowing. Just as the bell-ringer runs at the bell, the breeze blows it sideways, and he misses it and plunges to the ground, to his death. The sexton runs outside, where a crowd is gathering. A policeman arrives.  "Do you know this man?" he asks the sexton.   "No," he says, "but his face rings a bell."    
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      If you don't know what the shocker is check out the following links:    urlLink Big Shocker    urlLink Hanover High Shocker    urlLink Shocker Band?    urlLink Urban Dictionary Definition  (Must See!)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Einstein dies and goes to heaven only to be informed that his room is not ready yet. He is greeted by the doorman, who explains, "I hope you will not mind staying in the dormitory, but it's the best we can do and you will have to share the room with others We are very sorry!"  Einstein says that this is no problem at all and that there is no need to make such a great fuss. So the doorman leads him to the dormitory. They enter and Albert is introduced to his four new roommates.  The doorman states, "Here is your first room mate and he has an IQ of 180!" "That's wonderful!" says Albert. "We can discuss mathematics!"  Next the doorman introduces his second roommate, saying, “His IQ is 150!" "That's wonderful!" says Albert. "We can discuss physics!"  Further along, the doorman says "And here is your third room mate. His IQ is 100!" "That's wonderful! We can discuss the latest plays at the theater!"  Just then another man moves out to capture Albert's hand and shake it. "I'm your last room mate and I'm sorry, but my IQ is only 80." Albert smiles back at him and says, "So, where do you think interest rates are headed?"
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This year's Arkansas Alpha Sigma Phi Epsilon "Sigep Sweethearts".  If you're interested in signing up for Rush, feel free to contact me!   urlLink   
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How many men does it take to open a beer? None. It should be opened when she brings it.  Why is a Laundromat a really bad place to pick up a woman? Because a woman who can't even afford a washing machine will probably never be able to support you.  Why do women have smaller feet than men? It's one of those "evolutionary things" that allows them to stand closer to the kitchen sink.  How do you know when a woman is about to say something smart? When she starts a sentence with "A man once told me.."  How do you fix a woman's watch? You don't. There is a clock on the oven.  Why do men fart more than women? Because women can't shut up long enough tobuild up the required pressure.  If your dog is barking at the back door and your wife is yelling at the front door, who do you let in first? The dog, of course. He'll shut up once you let him in.  What's worse than a Male Chauvinist Pig? A woman who won't do what she's told.  I married a Miss Right. I just didn't know her first name was Always.  Scientists have discovered a food that diminishes a woman's sex drive by 90%. It's called a Wedding Cake.  Why do men die before their wives? They want to.  Women will never be equal to men until they can walk down the street with a bald head and a beer gut, and still think they are sexy.  In the beginning, God created the earth and rested. Then God created Man and rested. Then God created Woman. Since then, neither God nor Man has rested. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Quite often we ask ourselves hard to answer questions, like, "What is a sonofabitch?"  And we wax philosophic with metaphysical postulations, incomplete aphorisms and inconsistent sophism that make one more and more sure that the only true thing is that a picture is worth a thousand words.  In this photo, the guy on the right is a member of a bomb squad in midst of a deactivation.  The guy behind him, well, he's a sonofabitch.      
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Kerry + Edwards   Let's get it on!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink DONKEY!   If you don't do anything the rest of the day, click the donkey link.  It's well worth it!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The Associated Press reports that New York Junior Senator Hillary Clinton narrowly escaped injury when the aircraft that she was piloting was forced to make an emergency landing in Southern Texas because of bad weather. National Transportation Safety Board officials, have issued a preliminary determination that pilot error contributed to the accident, and that the senator was flying in IFR conditions while only having obtained a VFR single engine land rating. The absence of a post-crash fire was likely due to insufficient fuel onboard. No one on the ground was injured. Pictures taken at the scene show the extent of damage to Senator Clinton's aircraft.   
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Check out  urlLink this link for some very interesting Microsoft Help topics.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Memorable Quotes from Sleep with Me (1994) : "  Sid: You want subversion on a massive level. You know what one of the greatest fucking scripts ever written in the history of Hollywood is? Top Gun.  Duane: Oh, come on.  Sid: Top Gun is fucking great. What is Top Gun? You think it's a story about a bunch of fighter pilots.  Duane: It's about a bunch of guys waving their dicks around.  Sid: It is a story about a man's struggle with his own homosexuality. It is! That is what Top Gun is about, man. You've got Maverick, all right? He's on the edge, man. He's right on the fucking line, all right? And you've got Iceman, and all his crew. They're gay, they represent the gay man, all right? And they're saying, go, go the gay way, go the gay way. He could go both ways.  Duane: What about Kelly McGillis?  Sid: Kelly McGillis, she's heterosexuality. She's saying: no, no, no, no, no, no, go the normal way, play by the rules, go the normal way. They're saying no, go the gay way, be the gay way, go for the gay way, all right? That is what's going on throughout that whole movie... He goes to her house, all right? It looks like they're going to have sex, you know, they're just kind of sitting back, he's takin' a shower and everything. They don't have sex. He gets on the motorcycle, drives away. She's like, 'What the fuck, what the fuck is going on here?' Next scene, next scene you see her, she's in the elevator, she is dressed like a guy. She's got the cap on, she's got the aviator glasses, she's wearing the same jacket that the Iceman wears. She is, okay, this is how I gotta get this guy, this guy's going towards the gay way, I gotta bring him back, I gotta bring hi"
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      On the first day God created the dog. God said, "Sit all day by the  Door of your house and bark at anyone who comes in or walks past. I will give you a life span of twenty years." The dog said, "That's too long to be barking. Give me ten years and I'll give you back the other ten." So God agreed.  On the second day God created the monkey. God said, "Entertain people, do monkey tricks, make them laugh. I'll give you a twenty-year lifespan." The monkey said, "How boring, monkey tricks for twenty years? I don't think so. Dog gave you back ten, so that's what I'll do too, okay?" And God agreed.  On the third day God created the cow God said, "You must go to the field with the farmer all day long and suffer under the sun, have calves and give milk to support the farmer I will give you a life span of sixty years."  The cow said, "That's kind of a tough life you want me to live for sixty years. Let me have twenty and I'll give back the other forty."  And God agreed again.  On the forth day God created man. God said, "Eat, sleep, play, marry and enjoy your life. I'll give you twenty years."  Man said, "What? Only twenty years! Tell you what, I'll take my twenty, and the forty the cow gave back and the ten the monkey gave back and the ten the dog gave back, that makes eighty, okay?"  "Okay," said God, "You've got a deal."  So that is why the first twenty years we eat, sleep, play, and enjoy ourselves; for the next forty years we slave in the sun to support our family; for the next ten years we do monkey tricks to entertain the grandchildren; and for the last ten years we sit on the front porch and bark at everyone.  Life has now been explained to you. 
     
    
</post>


<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Not a minute too soon, I have completed the work I set out to accomplish.  Last night I completed work on the presentation, and tonight I wrapped up the paper.  It was a little long for a 5 page paper (about 15 pages).  Overall I enjoyed working on this project and I look forward to what the future holds for UML and XMI together.  If you would like more detailed information on the project feel free to mail me at  urlLink webmaster@kennethpwoodruff.com . 

						
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The project is progressing and though I am behind schedule I'm confident it will be complete by Friday.  So far I have completed the presentation and have begun working on the report.  If I have time I will go back and edit the notes on the presentation to give myself a little bit of guidance.   Two Main Goals:  The report and presentation have two main objectives for the modification of the UML ToDoList.mdl:  Add functionality at the business layer to facilitate the later addition of a “Modify” capability.  Add functionality at the business layer to facilitate the later addition of a “Mark Completed” capability.  Diagrams and illustrations are used to detail the modifications that take place.  I would perfer to do a full demonstration of the capability in Rose, but I don't have my own laptop which I could have the software installed on ahead of time.  I would rather not bother the professor with having to get a specific configuration ready before class, plus I would be hesitant to do a presentation with out a dry run.  Even  urlLink Miscrosoft  has shown that if you're not careful you can mess up a demo.  Check out the  urlLink Video Clip  of Bill Gates getting the Blue Screen of Death! 

						
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I didn't find what I was looking for, but I did find myself...sort of.  While trying to track down some information on XMI and UML I stumbled upon....this page!  It was ironically number 25 on  urlLink yahoo 's list of the search "XMI to UML".  Not exactly what I was looking for, but hopefully there is some good information out there.  I'm having to do a lot of searching.  Here's where I stand.  I have selected the project, and a good example, I will be using the Rational Rose example ToDoList.mdl.  The exporting is fairly straight forward, and the importing equally so.  The difficulty is showing how to modify the file and return it to Rose.  It's not that hard, but showing it in a quick presentation will be a little challenging.  My goal thus far is to add a method and an operation and return it to the model.  Possibly I will be so bold as to add another class...not so sure yet. 

						
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Nothing like a little elbow grease to help a good solution come to light. Ok, so it's the easy part that I have out of the way so far, and the real project is on the way. I have decided to go with Option 2!   Since I have a copy of Rational Rose at my disposal I have decided to put it to use for the forces of good. After a little  urlLink searching  of the internet I happened upon a  urlLink page  on a  urlLink Stanford  site that describes using an add in to Rose that will allow you to import and export XMI documents.&nbsp; A little more searching turned up the actual addin.  The process is a little rough around the edges, but what I hope to do this weekend (if I'm not spending the entire time in the office) is refine it to the point that it is workable.&nbsp; I would like to show a solution that involves a simple class diagram which we then add a new attribute,&nbsp; & operation to a class.&nbsp; If possible, I would also like to add a new interaction between classes, and what ever else I can come up with.  As I see it here are my tasks that remain:    Determine best way to display/edit XMI   Figure out what all of the information store means   Develop a simple class model   Come up with a good demo   Write Report   Prepare Presentation   I want to be able to show that if a standard representation exists then interoperability between tools can easily be accomplished. Thus in a multinational corporation where not every uses the same modeling software, data can still be shared.   

						
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I'm hoping by Tuesday of this week to have finalized my decision on project options.  Here is a little information about the driving factors.   Option 1 :  Missile Model  This option involves elaborating futher on the Missile Project created in iUMLite.  The advantage is that I am already somewhat familiar with the tool.  Also, I have a good deal of information already compiled in report format.  This data would need to be scrubbed throughly, and the model completed and documented.  Also, I'm not positive that I can get the simulation to work.  I will have to continue reading up on the iUML specific implementation of Action Semantics.   Option 2 :  UML -> XMI -> Modifications -> UML  This option involves the creation of a UML model and exporting it to XMI, adding or modifying the model in XML and returning it to UML.  I'm leaning towards this approach now because it seems more interesting, plus I already have some XML experience.  There is also plenty of information readily available about the subject:  urlLink XML and XMI Resource Page .  I'm currently looking for tools to help accomplish this.  If you have a suggestions, hit the comments link. 

						
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My quest into executable UML begins.  The purpose of this page is to document my progress on my class project to explore iUML.  Currently I have a delima.  With only two weeks before the project is due I must choose between 2 options.  The first is to further explore a project I've already begun which involves using the  urlLink Kennedy Carter   urlLink iUMLite  tool.  The project is a missile system where a battle management entity sends target data to aircraft in battle and when it deems appropriate delivers a fire command.  Seems easy enough, but iUMLite has a pretty steep learning curve and is not very user friendly.  The second option sounds a little more interesting.  It will involve using XMI.  Basically the idea is to create a UML model, generate XMI, add something to the XML code itself, and round-trip it back into UML.    Hopefully I will have an option chosen within the next few days and will be able to start working.   

						
</post>



</Blog>