<Blog>

<date>30,May,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      ok. you have no idea how stupid of an idea i think this is. i have this overwhelming desire to create websites at work. listening to hot snakes  automatic midnight  right now. it's pretty good, but kinda obscure. fuk it. goddamn html isn't coding right. i'll get it. hot snakes are now on their second rotation.  misanthropy and irony are in heavy discussion today, and i still can't get this shit to code right. fuk fuk. hot water music is on now. work dammit work. well i supposse this ia an ok comprise, re: stupid html.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      i am wearing faded black 505's, a navy blue "hapiness is" bar t-shirt, a brown belt with my name "timothy" etched into the leather, and white tennis shows. i have a moustache. i play softball.  i am old and feeble. liver spots scatter across my face. i don't notice that my mouth is gaping open. nor do i register  the string of drool stretching from my my tongue, which resting on top of my teeth, to my top set of teeth. i am hunched forward gripping the steering wheel tightly. i wait patiently at the intersection. i am sure it is not my turn. nothing is happening. what am i doing here.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      after seven months in europe, my brother is back in the uk-town. he brought back a hearty pile of postcards, including one from the capuchin cemetary in rome. since about the 1600's the  urlLink capuchin monks  took the bones of their dead and decorated their monastery with them. the  urlLink remains of over 4000 monks  adorn the monastery. death wielding a scithe, an hour glass with wings, all made of human bones. some seriously creepy shit. am totally into it. now i really want to go to europe. i could do a spooky/gothic tour of europe. instead of wasting my time in school, maybe i should head over after the pear season.  cody max applied here. mos def will put a word for him. pretty much demanded a raise today. will get crakked if it doesn't go through.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      ha ha. my dad was mentioned in dave barry's  urlLink column  last sunday. too bad dave barry suks.   ....Our next incident is described in a Dec. 15, 1998, article from the Santa Rosa, Cal.,  Press Democrat , written by Mike Geniella and sent in by many alert readers. It states that Sergio Gutierrez, a truck driver for Sea Products Inc., was driving a tractor-trailer on Highway 101 at 3:15 a.m. when he slammed into a bear crossing the road. Gutierrez was thrown from the truck, which then overturned, the result being that he was, according to the story, ``buried under an avalanche of frozen mackerel.''   i should mention, my dad is the writer, and not the truck driver.  
     
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      the other night, the ukiah police were trying to scare transients out of the abandoned palace hotel by having the police dog bark into the patrol car's megaphone.  also, the bad place, aka the sunset, aka the spunset, aka the skumbset, aka perkin's street grill, is hiring for security.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      posted up at home last night. at about 11:30, i said fuk it, cleaned myself up a bit and went into town. happened upon  urlLink travii , and went up to his place. girls, brews, and  urlLink levi . drank a sobe zen blend to my dome, and got props from the girlies for being sober.  proper ukiah night prompted us to go for a little walk to the stoner park, aka 40 park, aka mcgarvey park, located across the street from the cop shop. we hung for a while...then i noticed the west-side constellation,  urlLink cassiopea . a giant "w" in the eastern sky, whenever i look at it i hear dre's "let me ride" or eazy-e's "real mutha-fukin' g's." the west-side constellation is one of the best things about june.  my brother returns from europe on tuesday...am looking forward to that, may even take the day off.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      just saw joe's pictures from  urlLink bfd . they totally rule. fritch and smith with fred durst. fritch and smith with pauli shore. that wacky joe. dumb girls. they'll be up on  urlLink upupdowndown  by the end of the coming week. unnnhhhh!  only had four discs at work today, so i listened to each like three times. now i have shades apart  seeing things , hot water music  fuel for the hate game , face to face  big choice  and rocket from the crypt  scream, dracula, scream!  stuck in my damn stupid head. also i am dumb, and bragging about my stupid music selection.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      fuk. spent 8 whole hours at work today, no breaks, no lunch. i am finally done with this project; this stupid, immense project that has sukked away four months of my life.  successfully missed my ride to the city. no fuking show for me. ukiah is going to be fun tonight.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      yes. it is now about 4:15. am still at work. my ride to the city and the show leaves any minute now. this rules.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmmmm. been breaking my back at work the past few days, trying to get the  urlLink ammonia risk management plan  i've been working on for the past four months done. on thursday i pulled a 16 hour day, friday a 12 hour day, and here i am in on a saturday. it's about 11:45 right now, should be done by about 13:30 if all goes well. the absurdity of this project....you can't imagine the kind of figurative  urlLink red tape  our governement puts businesses through...  as mentioned before, am going to the nerve agents show tonight at the  urlLink cocodrie  with co-worker and brother of  urlLink garrett , kristian alto.   joe and phil won't go, as they are feverishly working to get  urlLink upupdowndown  online.  the other day kristian & i were talking about  urlLink  girl, interrupted   . i realized i was generally pretty happy (delusional) up until the hours i saw that movie. i remember walking out of the ukiah 6 thinking, "i used to be depressed. i need to be more depressed. i was pretty sweet back then" and i woke up depressed the next day, and have been that way since. kinda weird how i turned this round on like a switch that i can't seem to turn off.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
       the following is an icq transcript between ryan and i. all the events described herein occurred last weekend.    pabst_     6/20/00  1:07 pm    tell me more stories about ukiah, you always have the best ones.   peteg      6/20/00  1:11 pm    at nod's party at capri's smith donned the germs leather that has at various times belonged to jade, merchie and smith, and he became "puke anarchy." he was sober, but staggering around flipping off chicks and bumping into dudes like he was bodhi or something.   pabst_     6/20/00  1:12 pm    hahahhaha anarchers!!!!!!   i've never seen puke anarchy, but he sounds all real. more stories!  peteg's stories are the bestest!   peteg      6/20/00  1:12 pm    later, wearing the same gear, he took kevin graham's aviator amber shooting glasses and became a rock star. by my prompting, after every three sententces he would  tilt his head back to show his nostrils and ask "am i cool?" and then brush his nostrils with his hand. it was pretty funny, because 3/4 of the people there took that shit for real   pabst_     6/20/00  1:13 pm    hahahahhahahahha niiiiice.   am i cool? excellent. encore! more!   peteg      6/20/00  1:13 pm    in the middle of the night that dave guy that always wears red and drives a blue caddy pissed on smith's feet, thinking the bed in capri's loft was a toilet. smith's pants, pager, feet got soaked   pabst_     6/20/00  1:14 pm    bwahahaha did smiff kill him?   peteg      6/20/00  1:14 pm    smith got hella defeated. dave was too fuked up to know what was going on   pabst_     6/20/00  1:15 pm    teehee.  more stories!  dont stop!! uhn   peteg      6/20/00  1:17 pm    on friday night i went to the 7-11 to meet up with the crew after listening to the new lc at travii's. i walk up and see cougar asking nod to beat him up. then a 14 yr old girl stuck her head out the 2nd floor window and per cougar's request, spit in his mouth.   pabst_     6/20/00  1:17 pm    ;lkasjdf;lkajsdf;j why was cougar asking to be beat up by nod?   peteg      6/20/00  1:18 pm    i round the corner to see a helluv drunk scarb leaning up against a pick up, dry heaving and staggering. i ask him what he's doing and he slurs "practicing random acts of kindness and senseless acts of beauty"   pabst_     6/20/00  1:18 pm        you have the greatest anecdotes in the history of man   peteg      6/20/00  1:19 pm   cougar can be a nine ball. later cougar rolled solo to the sunset. he saw beverage pissing in the bathroom and reached between bev's legs and gave his nuts a little squeeze. beverage lost it, elbowed him in the face, and proceeded to beat the shit out of him. cougar has two shiners and a bruise on his forehead   pabst_     6/20/00  1:20 pm    lmao "gave his nuts a little squeeze"   peteg      6/20/00  1:21 pm    early friday night i rolled up to low gap for nod's birthday bbq and the first thing i saw was n*** cutting a line of coke with an atm card on top of a milwaukee's best ice 12 pack box   pabst_     6/20/00  1:21 pm    my....god.......im truly amazed by all of this   peteg      6/20/00  1:22 pm    i  talked to n8 about klebold & harris and kip kinkel. it ruled. he loves human racists. when patricia commented that she couldn't imagine anyone even thinking of that shit, n8 got crakked and told her could.   pabst_     6/20/00  1:24 pm    ahahahha.  tell me more about people.   peteg      6/20/00  1:25 pm    i am starting to run dry...   pabst_     6/20/00  1:25 pm    get to it big boy   peteg      6/20/00  1:33 pm    ....nod, jerry & i were rocking out to "fade to black" as the girls got ready to go to the bar. patricia came up and turned off the stereo & announced it was time to go. baffled, we were like whatever. as we walk down the st. i say "patricia, you'll never be able to understand me because you don't understand rocking out" she got craked....   pabst_     6/20/00  1:34 pm    sweet.   peteg      6/20/00  1:35 pm    soon after i started saying "you can really get to know a person, have a good idea who they are, really like each other, but sooner or later you get to a point where you just can't know a person any better, and you'll never know me because you don't know rokking out." she flipped out, told me to fuck off, told me i always make fun of her and i need to stop. it was fresh, everybody else told her she was crazy...   pabst_     6/20/00  1:36 pm    hahah pete is making people crazy, sweet   peteg      6/20/00  1:37 pm    ....they told her that i am a stand up guy, she's trippin'. she got punked. then she threw up in the 7-11. karma!   peteg      6/20/00  1:40 pm    cougar kept asking me if i thought he was gay the other night... "yeah, sometimes i do." "well i am not." "i hope that works out for you. keep up the good work." "do you really think i am gay..." etc, etc, ad nauseum   pabst_     6/20/00  1:40 pm    hahahhaah.  cougar is just a sexual outlaw   peteg      6/20/00  1:44 pm    yeah, out of society's bounds. brown interviewed here yesterday. he is making min. wage at the brewery and is looking to the sheds for skrill. i told him the spanky story and in an ironic twist, he asked "when is that guy going to do something with himself?"   pabst_     6/20/00  2:02 pm    hahahaha, that is a fantastic quote from brown.   peteg      6/20/00  2:03 pm    yeah, it was pretty nice. i wish i was you and only got to hear this stuff second hand instead of having to live it. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      fuk
     
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      am posting this for posterity. it was in the  urlLink ukiah daily journal  on 11 june, 2000.    ARREST  -- Nathan Daugherty, 23, of Ukiah, and Jeremiah Williams, 23, of Hopland, were arrested on suspicion of disorderly conduct at 2:40 am Friday in the 300 block of Spring Street. They were reportedly walking up the street screaming and kicking fences.   apparently jj was swinging from porches like a monkey. they were thrown in the drunk tank for the night. n8 kept playing with the intercom switch, and in some way roughed up jj. jj was passed out when johnny law brought them breakfast, so n8 ate both their meals. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      unnnhhh! joy division  permanent  going off in my cd player at work. went to walmart on my lunch break and saw "yokayo pomo fucker" painted on a van's spare tire case. when i returned from lunch, kristian "k-rock" alto was in the office, just starting. we have tentative plans to scope the  urlLink nerve agents  at the cocodrie in ess eff on saturday. rumoured to open is the explosion...they are on jade tree records, but apparently are a '77 style punk mosh. heavily into it.  joe, fritch and phil did a bunch of work on  urlLink upupdowndown  yesterday. i think we can have that up by the end of the week. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      spanky bailed this weekend, prolly from being high on beer, and opened up the wound on his thigh. instead of going to the hospital, spanky had scarb remove the staples in his leg with a fork. the leg, of course, got crazy infected. susan described scarb's medical "procedure" to smith as the "stupidest idea anyone's ever had since walking on bridge   last night, bob virgin took one look at spanky's leg and without hesitation, drove him to the emergency room. the doctors were shocked, immediately plugged an anti-biotic iv into his arm, and told him that if his leg got any more infected he could lose it. when they released your homey, they told him to keep the iv in for the night and return for another in the morning. of course, spanky took the iv out because he "wouldn't be able to sleep with it in" and grabbed a molson ice from the fridge. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      smith and i broke our no-drinking binge in ukiah last night at brandon's birthday party. had a pretty good time last night, but am pretty fought today. helluv washed up, almost slipped into skandal with several of the wrong chicks and realized that soon i will be 24.  been rockin'  urlLink  ...and out come the wolves   all weekend. that album is the key, i have prolly scoped it like 8 times in the past three days. also on hit....face to face,  urlLink  don't turn away  . both these albums have heavy nostalgia value for me, and prolly, i am going off so hard to them because i have a certain amount of dissatifaction with the present. whatever. eff it.  heard the new  urlLink loose change  disc at chon's on friday night. it's helluv good. the first four traks are hard-melodic, in the vein of this  urlLink good riddance  or  urlLink kid dynamite . # five is traditional loose change, and trak six starts off with an early 80's new wave, kinda inxs feel to it and merges into classic loose change form. chon does a duet-style on the vocals on this track and it sounds really cool. didn't scope a lyric sheet, but they sounded pretty good. have had the songs stuk in my head all weekend, so they must be doing something right. i can't wait for it to drop so i can scope the reaction to it. it's nice to see that band back in the swing of things.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink upupdowndown  is limping along but should be out within the week, i hope, i pray.   smith and fritch hit the road with the  urlLink afi's  sometime early next week and will be gone for about a month. garrett goes to alaska for two weeks on sunday. so i am pretty much posting up in ukiah, pretty much. excellent.   kcin says there is a  urlLink tiger army  show with the nerve agents on july 7 in orange county. sounds all word, not sure if i can make it.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      so fuking hot in the uk town. nights have been nice. at night, smith and i have been walking from his house to mill street to get ice creams and then over to garrett's on grove. walks through the west side are always the key, especially when one is avoiding the skumbs that hang out in susan's pool. i always forget how key ukiah can be in june.  first concert in the park with pretty packed. nice change in that there wasn't a single person i went to high school with asking me what i am up to. the usual assortment of skumbs and f-w's going off; it wasn't exactly hopping off, but it didn't entirely suk for once.  went to the new downtown brew pub. smith and i drank ice teas as we are currently on a bar ban/no drinking binge in the uk town, so i can't comment on the beer. they took the black bart bar from the palace, which is cool, and it seems to be a fairly sucker free zone, for the time being. drying out seems to be paying off for us pretty well. both of us agree that our game (the little to be had) is in top form.  wishing i could go to bfd....but the afi's play at like 4, and the shoreline is skandalously far away from here, and i have missed a lot of work lately to go off with various lifestyles...including peeping the punk-o-rama tour in chico.  the distillers cut out of their tour, so the point subbed for them in chico. the show went off. chico started singing bar room heroes at the murphys set their gear up, and the point crew led some seriously intense oi! chants. during the encore of "skinhead on the mbta" & "dirty deeds done dirt cheap" (ac/dc) the crowd rushed the stage. i thought the place was going to fall apart.  in other chico news, the  urlLink union of the dead  guys just self released an ep recorded at chico state. it's helluv good, i am backing it 110%. chico is a lot more punk than it was a year ago which is cool, although i think i would rather visit than live there.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      went out for a night on the "town" last night. soren was in town, so everybody was in a pretty festive mood. started the night at the new brewery. that was fine. went to the forest. hung out with props.   heard this exchange on state street between garrett (smoking a jay) and an indian chick. it is for real:    indian  "i am sober these days. i don't do that shit."  props "oh yeah? how long?"   indian  "i've been off crank for two days."  props "i've been up for two days"  props "do you want a hit?"   indian  "i only smoke weed laced with crank....speed weed."   then i went to the bathroom...as i worked my way across the bar, i heard scarb yell out "hey! hot chicks! let's get drunk and naked!" i enter the bathroom, and observe two mexicans snorting crank off the toilet.   later, a welcome relief to my intensly shitty night, i ran into k-rock alto, monica and julie. we went back to julie's house with these mexicans we work with. they are pretty fresh. they showed me their ticket stubs from nofx/ramones at the hard rock cafe in culican and we may take them to see aging orange/teen idols/loose change show at the 'drie in sf .    [as an aside: kristian and i took jaycon to see the show, which ended up being the last show at the crocodrie ever. r.i.p. we saw exactly two songs of loose change's set, but jaycon was pretty baffled by the city]    it was pretty interesting talking to those guys. although by american standards their taste in punk is pretty fucking generic, those guys are pretty out there for mexicans. all them have their own bands back an mexico, and claim to play in front of 300+ crowds regularly.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      last weekend was horribly weak. drifting in and out of fever (101 at it's worst), dizzy and nauseous at times, but not so fought that i couldn't work on my bedroom for a while. taking occasional breaks to deal with my "symptoms," i managed to drywall about half the room. i don't know what the fuk i have; i've been sick like this about every four weeks for the past three months.  after two weeks of dealing with my dumb mistake of ordering lp's instead of cd's, i finally got my discs from  urlLink jade tree . promise ring  nothing feels good  is helluv good, more rockin' than  very emergency .  shorter, louder, faster  is a proper second release from kid dynamite, but i still think they sound like good riddance or something, and don't really understand what the fuss is all about. joan of arc  how memory works  is also pretty good, but all the electronic stuff seems more like a gimmic than anything else. what do i know about any of it, though?  fritch called yesterday from thunder bay, ontario. the  urlLink afi's  tour is going really well, and they are about to join up with the east coast leg of the  urlLink warped tour . we didn't talk long, but am looking forward to hearing his stories. merchie is selling his car. smiff and i should buy it and sell it on ebay. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      today, smith and i went to baskin-robbins to get sorbets. there were these trad 11 year old skate kids doing tricks out front. as we passed them smith told one of them, "you have to be able to ollie before you can do a heel flip." the kid was like "i know how to ollie!" and demonstrated how high he could ollie. the other kid told smith "you do it then." smith attempted to do a heel flip, but couldn't pull it off, even after 5 attempts. as we walked away one of the kids called smith a "faggot." we just laughed at the tradness of it as we hopped in the tradillac and drove off.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      god. this weekend was pretty fucking intense. partied at cougar's both nights.   jevon was in town on friday night. watched nod get his ass kicked three times by jevon and scarb. heard pathetic "scarb, stop hitting me, come on, stop hitting me" come from nod. saw jevon drag brandon across the street, scraping up his back and the side of his face. nod destroyed the tree in front of cougar's house. shoddy unloaded gun play, talk of playing russian roullete with jevon's .44 mag revolver.  nod got in some sort of fight at the forest with some guy that claimed nod stole his ounce of weed from leverage's house. the guy said “not on state street,” so nod threw him into state street.   saturday night trevor hosted a libra party that was suppossed to be at brahma bull but got moved there. uk freaks (as in wierdos, not as in what i pop off with at the sunset) in the house, sober smith and pete, high on 3 red bulls each. wierd. sorry my sentences lack description, prefer not to relive any of it.  
     
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      so, you know, i am posting up at carla's yesterday, kicking it with her, when a frantic cody barges in. he's covered in dirt, like he just got off work and has a 1000 yard stare in his eyes.   "you guys seen eli? where is he?"  "the other day he called my girlfriend a bitch, then he went to the cops and told them 'cody is going to kill me'. this was before i even knew about what he said to kim. then that little piece of shit went to kim's work and told her manager she was harrassing him and asked what he was going to do about it, trying to get her fired. where's brandon?"   to which he aburptly left. also, grimm, his best dog, died the other day. he was on a chain, and tried to jump over a fence, hanging himself.   about a half hour later eli showed up at freedom. brandon challenged him and told him to get the fuck out of the store, that he is only going to cause problems by being in there. i told eli he should get the fuck out of town, because it's not like cody is going to just bump into him on the streets, and maybe talk things out. he's across the street of your house at three a.m. with a a skinhead army. he is under your bedroom window. he has his black nike gloves on.   on sunday night, smith and garrett were walking down school street. they saw eli's truck and heard a scuffle in the bushes. thinking it was eli and his girl brandy messing around, smith yelled something like, "hey you two, settle down." the response was an emphatic "eli, get the fuck off me." smith went over and grabbed eli by shirt collar and put him in a headlock. brandy dropped a fucking dog to eli's face.   this is an understatement. i am glad i am not eli.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      an email i sent to my friends:   just seeing what you all are up to for thanksgiving. my mom said i could prolly invite a few friends over for dinner, perhaps joe or phil might be interested in this? are any of you coming up?   after we do our family things, and after fritch gets back from his grandparents, we should all party at the black hole. we should smoke a lot of "stotches" and get wasted on beer with spanky. nodnarb will supply the whiskey. every few minutes, creeper will stick his head out of the bedroom door and call in the next person to do a line.   we can drop by the forest club, and hang out with all the college swords in town for the holidays. tank-ass will sing in drill sargeant voice, i will spit that ill game to ill sword chicks, and "mr. prison ink" can almost get into fights with washed up jocks. then we can pass out at the black hole and sleep in blue cigarrette smoke all night long. when we wake up in the morning, our lungs will be splitting, our gullets tripping, and our heads aching. then we will walk all the way across town, a walk of shame if you will, to our cars. let's make this a thanksgiving to remember.  
     
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      time for an update, dog
     
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      chico was pretty washed up for halloween this year.  also, every time i go there i feel like i am running a script. i hang out with the same people at the same houses, got to the same bars, have the same conversations, go home with the same girl, make the same walk of shame in the morning, get the same breakfast at the same restruant with the same lousy service and same good food. i am not so interested in going to chico anymore. are any of you up for a trip to chico on the 18th to loose change and union of the dead?   nod asked "carla, did you get hella jealous when you found out your boyfriend pete spent the night with another girl?" carla blushed and told him to shut up.   the best part of the trip was the words that came out of laura's mouth. laura is the 16 yr old sister of laura and belinda's roommate emily.  to carla, about the cd that was just put on her car stereo:  "a gangster that listens to afi?"    to carla about her car:  "i've never been in a gangster car before."    when carla and marcy (carla's mexican homie) explained that they are are not gangsters:  "oh, i thought you were gangsters because you hang out with mexicans."    on the subject of oral sex:  "that is so gross. i would never do that with a guy. i wouldn't even do that to mark wahlberg. he's pretty fine. i'd make out with him."    on penises:  "they are so gross. gross looking, gross feeling, they don't feel good, i hate penises."    on san diego, where carla, and marcy  are thinking about moving:  "san diego is cool. it has everything. there's the beach, music, movies...there's even a ghetto for you guys."   unsolicited, after a long stretch of silence, on her lifestyle:  "i guess i am what you would call a 'preppie.' being a preppie is cool. you wear nice clothes, get good grades. maybe you drink a little bit, but you don't really have a problem. some preppies are closet alcoholics, but preppies don't get all crazy."   unsolicited, on her music:  "i really like limp bizkit."    as we roll into chico:   "can we drive by all the frat houses? i bet there's some cute boys there."  
     
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      after discussing my desire to own a lomo camera with joe, and after he mentioned the lubitel, i  came across this site that sells urlLink  kommie kameras . futhermore, in webmonkey, if found an article on producing  urlLink "cheap and cool photos."  unnh. i am a stupid.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>

	 
      fritch and smith showed up to ukiah, so i kicked it with them. kinda silly. smith had his leather binder thing with a strap that i call the "action purse" while the afi's call it the "doormat". he carries it around with him all the time in case he gets a call on his celly and has to handle business.   we go to walmart, and schatts and smith is getting all these calls and handling all this business on the street and in the walmart cosmetics section, because we are all looking for black eye makeup (which there was none).   and fritch just joined the cell phone posse. all black posse, all dudes, cell phones, action purse/doormat, comsmetic section of ukiah walmart. yeah, we weren't conspicuous or anything.   oh yeah, and smith's mom and little brother happened to be at walmart. his brother came running up with this toy called (no lie) "exploding head psycho"  later we went and saw "vertical limit' which i am backing. the best part of the movies was seeing the preview for the new sean connery movie, in which he says "who's the man now, dog"  to sum:   --action purse   --fritch has a cell phone, and his comedy is to claim the number is "g0t axe w0gy"   --exploding head psycho   --"who's the man now, dog?"  
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      chico for the third weekend in a row.  this time joe came up from the sc-town and we kicked it deep. in addition, about 8 other people came up for chico party time. friday night was marked by some rug cutting at mr.lucky's, which has become a regular stop for my weekend lifestyle in chico. we cut up their floor so hard, we are getting a bill for damaging thier shit. rachael sprained her ankle, and i aggravated the ankle i twisted sno-boarding a few weeks back.  saturday night, lars frederiksen and the bastards played their first show ever. lars, you should know by now, is the lead singer of rancid, and the bastards were the key. they play some fucking punk, oi/'77 style, but it's mos def its own kind of thing. lars is kind of a punk rock bruce springsteen; most the song topics related back to growing up in campbell, ca. the lyrics were really good, the songs well written and set was going off.   joe defeated me by telling me to look at the sticker under the lars' pick hand. crappy sparkly silver media stereotype alien head. i got him back by pointing out the lars' tight SP, with his modification to the marshal logo to read "lars" on his gear.  the nerve agents went on next and delivered their usual brand of barely contained chaos, reminding me that i love seeing them live way more than listening to thier albums. the show was wrapped up by about 8:45, which left a whole night ahead of us. joe and i did a pretty extensive amount of shooting around downtown, as well as some posting up at the towne lounge.  the next day, everybody went their own ways...luckily i saw enough of the super bowl to see one matrix-style instant replay, and the new budweiser alien waazzzzaaa commercial, so i can now die a happy man.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      ended up in chico last weekend.   jesse and jon from flipwreck started a new band, belladonna, which debuted at mr. lucky's on saturday night. belladonna was cool; an amalgam of techno with live instruments. the synthesis claimed belladonna was a "lo-fi nine inch nails." i wish. it was the kind of thing you could dance to, and it wasn't particularly spooky. i helluv backed flipwreck, and it's good to see jon and jesse continue on.   abe, the former guitar player/singer of flipwreck was also there. it was good to see him. after a stint with HPA in the south bay, he's moving back to chico, and is planning on doing some solo work, along the lines of elliot smith. abe has some gosh darn talent, so i am looking forward to hearing what he comes up with.  before belladonna's set there was a drag-queen contest. the key was the posse, about 10 deep, of gay hicks that showed up in full hick regalia, including moustaches, goatees, wranglers, hankerchiefs around necks, and shirts. the gay cowboys were slipping their fingers into the back pockets of each others tight gay cowboy wranglers, and rubbing each others gay cowboy backs. the contest concluded with a lip sync by all the queens to shania twain's "man, i feel like a woman." never in my life have i wished more that i brought a camera or tankass. i think he would never sport wranglers again if he saw that shit. 
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink afi  made into the most recent issue of rolling stone magazine as the first "random note." which is pretty baffling to me. the brief paragraph long article starts of with "All the way from the hayfuck town of Ukiah, California, come AFI...."  ukiah is exactly where i am leaving.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      i spent sunday atop hull mountain learning how to snowboard, which means i fell alot and twisted my ankle real bad. when i got home sunday night, there was a message from my mother:   "call phil ASAP. needs a roommate in the city. $432/month."   i called. i was wishy washy. phil wanted me to move in two weeks, which seemed kind of intense. about an hour after hanging up with phil, ryan calls me from phil's house on his celly.   "move in with phil. i will lend you money."  call waiting.  "pete, this is fritch, move in with phil."  you see, fritch too, was on his cell phone, and i was getting the press from my homies. ambivelent about making such a lavish change, i told them i had to think about it.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i want to work at home. i am not sure i can can really do that, but i think that's the answer for this guy. my current job is pretty cool, but clawing my way up in somebdoy else's system is losing it's appeal.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today got off to a rough start. no reverse, so i circle the block about 8 times, looking for a suitable parking spot. at some point i say fuck it, and start heading for the bridge. i get as far as 5th and folsom, when 4th gear goes out. i decide to fight downtown traffic and double back to  urlLink tari's  neighborhood.   another 8 or so laps around the park, up and down the hills and i find a friday spot on Buena Vista East going up the hill, so i am able to roll back into the spot, and also be able to come out going forward. hopped on the N and then onto bart. 15 minute walk to work, and i was only 15 minutes late.   it doesn't make sense for me to sell the car, because i still owe like $8k on it, and the best i can sell it for is prolly $4-5k with the shot transmission. that means i'd still be making payments on $4k for a car i don't have. i would rather take a $2k hit than a $4k hit and still have a car i really like. the engine is strong and will go forever.   i'll start getting estimates from various shops and figure out how to pay for the shit.   i am dissapointed, but had been secretly expecting this for a while. it tough to plan for this kind of thing, but at least my car didn't fail on the bay bridge or in some parking garage. i welcome the chance to read for an hour everyday, and the 15 minute walk from my work to bart is pleasant 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my parents moved out of my childhood home today.  i don't have a wholly formed idea of what this actually means to me. thoughts like "i will never go there again" or "where will i sleep when i visit" or "the flowers and birds and trees and the pasture were really beautiful the last time i was there" or "remember when it snowed" puntacted the day's otherwise normal proceedings. knowing this event is happening without me made today feel like when terrosists fly planes into buildings. more on this later...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      at this moment i sitting in a financial district coffee shop, sipping tea, passing time. a little black bird wandered in from the street and is pecking at the crumbs that litter the floor. it's near closing time, and the baristas are busy with their side work, but they haven't swept yet so there's no shortage of treats for the little guy.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      for a ride back to the city, i decide take an AC Transit bus across the bay bridge. i heard this is a good way to get to the city because the busses are rarely crowded, and the view riding high on the bus is worth it. i have seen the  urlLink dark green buses  lined up at the transbay terminal, shiny and new like some rock and roll tour buses. the windows are sealed, suggesting air conditioned luxury and i've seen rows of plush high backed forward facing seats.   i spent my day imagining the luxury, the view, the relaxtion while cruising across the bay in mass transit opulence.   you saw this coming, i know. if i had read the website above a little closer i could have avoided this. right now, i am sitting on a bench, facing perpendicular to the roadway. it's hot and smelly on this bus. it's the kind of general route bus i am used to seeing growling up the hills of SF, except this one has a blue trim instead of an orange trim. every time the bus gets moving, the engine roars and the wind whistles through the slat windows like a tea kettle boiling over. my fellow commuters, in this case a busload of teenagers, raise their voices to combat the racket.  i am uncomfortable. i am couched in hard plastic, vinyl, and stainless steel. This bus was built to be hosed out at the end of the day, not for glorious day trips through the bay area. the ride is rough, and i slide forward every time the driver gooses the brake pedal with his discount brand white high tops. it is nice though, and the view from up above is something new, even though i've been across the bridge hundreds of times.   
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      it's june. and there's a shocking chill to the morning, a fact i discover as i rush down the hill to catch a train to work. a fog has nestled into the valleys of the city, and the mist hanging in the air stings my face. now would be the perfect time for me to cite a mark twain quip (which  urlLink he never said , by the way) about san francisco weather.   naturally, the train departs the station as i round the corner, so i decide to walk a few more blocks to a coffee shop. i pass a few moments with a cup of tea, and then i run to the muni train that just rolled past my present location. the hot tea slops out of the plastic lid, burning my numbed hands. in case you didn't know, these muni trains bound for the financial district are usually so improperly packed with people, there's no way an honest feller can drop a dime on the ride. i don't feel like much of a citizen when i do this, and would pay if i could. last car for BART too, because those cars are usually empty.   these days i work in oakland, just across the bay bridge from san francisco. to be precise, my work is situated exactly on the border of emeryville and oakland.  urlLink cinder block  is in the business of making merchandise for the entertainment industry. that's a fancy way of saying we make tshirts for bands. although cinder block has some pretty big clients like REM, Radiohead and Phil Collins, we have a stronghold on the smaller/punk band market. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      in the little spare time that i have these days, (which is usually on a BART train between SF and Oakland), i've been working on a recap of the past three years. my idea is to start where i left off. it's kind of an interesting exercise; putting together a highlights reel of my recent history. so keep an eye for that.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      today i had the very first performance review of my working life.     this means i've been at my current job for 3 months. i feel like it's been far longer. this a good thing; an indication that i fit in very nicely. the review went well. my boss could have nailed me on a few things, but he was very generous, and rated me far higher than i rate myself. and i thought i was pushing my luck.     i am now an official employee, with access to all the privileges therein. i didn't get a raise, which i was secretly hoping for even though i don't think people always get those so soon in their tenure. we can only get raises when we get reviewed, so it's disheartening to think it'll be another nine months before i can obsessively, secretly calculate my new pay rate.     a good lesson to learn, and i've been schooled a few times now, is that things in life that are worth having are worth having because you had to work for it. you can only appreciate something if you have to earn it; usually your appreciation is proportional to the amount of work you had to put in.     as i mentioned before, i've never worked at a company were there were reviews and procedure for giving out raises. although i've steadily worked my way up the income ladder, i don't think i've ever been given a raise for simply doing a good job.  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have a gmail account. my car has a five speed now. work is for jerks. summer is not hot in san francisco, which is ideal. i have one last payment to make on a credit card i've been maxed out on for 7 years. i've been hanging out with my friends a lot more. i started a savings account. my vegetable intake has increased. i talk to my brothere frequently. i read a book every single day. i haven't been sleeping enough. i drink tea several times a day. i've eaten at good restaurants recently. people are still rude idiots. 
     
    
</post>


</Blog>