<Blog>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now It Has Begun...
 
Well, I'd rather not brag to Liz "I told you so," so I decided to tell the whole web that I told it so. One Neon Tetra down, twelve more to go. When we got back tonight from dinner, Liz made this discovery. One of her little guys had sunk to the bottom. "Now it has begun" was all I could say. (I got hit for that remark.) Oh well. The matrix of life has readjusted itself. Now we are dealing with a smaller organism number in the same size matrix. I am not sure which of my hypotheses is correct, however. Liz noted that the Pleco was looking sort of aggressive afterwards, but that doesn't prove anything. As for the other hypothesis, none of the other Neons look suspicious, so I am not sure of the validity of that hypothesis. I did think of a new alternative hypothesis, the suicide hypothesis: A Neon Tetra, after being exposed to the pressure of 13 other roommates, reaches a critical stress level and kills himself. Since he cannot drown himself (or jump out of the tank) this is done by a refusal to swim. The swim bladders now deflate, and once at the bottom, the sunken fish starves to death (or suffocates - I will have to check my high school bio book on that one). I will get back to you on this as my experiment continues. I expect at least one more to die before this weekend. (Liz thinks I am mean.) The fact is, no one considers the scientist who proved that dolphins were being killed in tuna nets mean. They implicated the fishermen who subjected them to those conditions as the perpetrators of the crime. Just a thought. You decide.
 
 I am thinking that a way to prove my hypothesis is to have my father perform an autopsy on these little guys as they die off. We can rule out foul play or maybe stress induced death by this method. The latter can be done via a blood test - if the cholestorol levels are too high, we can assume stress. We shall see. 
 
In other news, I went out to dinner with my father and Liz tonight. He is in Gainesville learning some flow-cytometry methods from some doctor at the med school. I assume he intends to put this knowledge to use somehow. Dinner was really good, and the conversation was even better. It was pretty nice, because Liz took away some of the tension that had been existing between my father and I, and my father alleviated some of the tension that has been plaguing Liz and I. (I live a stressful life.) Either way, stress was lower tonight, and I learned a lot about my dad. I guess I don't give him enough credit all the time. He deserves more. When I listen to him, I actually learn a lot. I should probably have done this more often growing up. Maybe now I will. Maybe not. Who knows.... We all have to learn on are own at some point. Either way, tonight was productive. 
 
Had lunch with Amier today also. We talked about  urlLink RhinoHazard  at lunch today. He gave me some thoughts about database programming. If anyone knows where I can find professionals capable of doing some massive database programming, drop me an email at  Marcelino.Alvarez@duke.edu  Progress continues, however. We are shooting for an August release. I really don't know how feasible that is given the current lack of a database. I will keep you posted on this. 
 
I think this is all for tonight. I need to study some organic chemistry now. Test next Wednesday. Yay.
 
Goodnight, everyone. 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Social Experimentation
 
 
Yesterday afternoon was bad. The fish I picked out at PetSmart died on the way home. He really didn't have much of a chance. Liz wasn't happy. It was supposed to clean her fish tank. She even suggested that the fish wasn't moving too much, but I told her that's how Pleco's are. Oh well. You win some, you lose some.
 
Liz went back today and returned the frozen Pleco. They gave her another one to clean her socially saturated 2-gallon fish tank. She had 6 Neon Tetras in there (Actually, there were only five. She left one in the net when she cleaned it out last week and it died.) For some reason, the PetSmart sales clerk in the aquarium department (who must have been on crack) told her she could get seven more Neon Tetras for the tank because they are social "schooling" fish. I told her that her fish tank is a social experiment, like one of those intro computer programming assignments where you randomly genereate several "organisms" in a 2x2 matrix, and watch the effects on the adjacent cells through subsequent "generations."
 
Liz didn't take too kindly to that remark, but it is true. If she was having ammonia problems with five fish, (which is why I suggested she buy a Pleco, a bottom dwelling cleaner-fish) I can only imagine the fun now with thirteen. It will become my research experiment for the summer. How long will it take for these things to kill each other? The normally pacifist Tetra transforms into a violent mass of blue and red when subjected to twelve neigbors in a small environment... That is my hypothesis. My alternate hypothesis is that the algae-eating Pleco, in an effort to promote social darwinism, will become a carnivore and devour the Tetras one by one, until the remaining fish fulfill the maximum value of the Predator-Prey equation, and the Pleco will return to eating algae. (I am really glad I took Diff-Eq's, I understand it now). We shall see. I will keep you posted on the status of the social experiment.
 
In other news, I need to write my MUN position papers. I also need to study more orgo. Wow, what a summer - I live on the edge....
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      
06.03.00
 
Damn. I just realized that my theme for the summer cannot be discussed on the Internet because it implicates certain people in places or situations that they are not supposed to be. That sucks, because I had some pretty funny stories. Oh well.
 
I work for ZoomCulture.com. I videotape things that artistically inspire me. I also interview people (drunk or sober) who have informative things to say. It's a fun job, and Fred, Liz and Chris have helped me out with it extensively.
 
Still no name for this log. How about Mog? Short for Marce's Log? I know that Mog also refers to a character from the Final Fantasy series, (Mog the Moogle) but I think I will stick with it.
 
Welcome to Mog!
 
Note to self: Bring computer to college. It is a must.
 
Every experience in life builds character. No matter how much it hurts.
 
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      06.02.00
 
"Why do all these people have weblogs? And who sits there and reads them all anyways?" I wondered aloud, thinking how stupid I am in ripping an idea from my friend  urlLink Fred , who ripped it from some other  urlLink guy . "But then again," I thought, "I'm a funny guy. I deserve a weblog."
 
But what do I call it? Everyone has these stupid things. They all find some catchy name that somehow describes their personality and voila, they have a cool concept. I can't use RhinoLog, because RhinoHazard is the name of our business "concept" (note concept, not company)- what a great way to lead into  urlLink RhinoHazard .
 
So what shall I name it? Hmmm. The Marce Chronicles? Sounds too much like the Indiana Jones spinoff series. Damn. I am sure I'll find something. 
 
 


     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Experiment Continues....

I know it has been a while since I have posted, I had an orgo test that occupied most of my time over the course of the last week. Some interesting new developments have occured. 
 
So Liz's fish have developed a disease. It is called ich. I suggested she go get some medicine at the pet store. When she went, the pet store guy told her that ich was caused by stress. He then asked her how many fish she had in the tank. When she told him that she had twelve fish in a two-gallon tank, the guy nearly flipped out. He asked her who the hell told her she could put so many fish in one tank; she told him it was another PetSmart guy. Oh well. An undiscovered hypothesis - a plague will fall upon the fish for living in such horrid conditions.
 
So I visited Liz today. It has been a while because I have been locked up in my apartment studying orgo. I went to her fish tank to see that the ich had spread from the two or three fish that had it on monday to almost all the fish. In the corner of the tank, a tetra lay there breathing his last. I asked her when the last time she gave them their medication. She said she hadn't started it because she was waiting for me. I am starting to feel really sorry for the fish. I immediately doused them with the ich removal formula. I am going to use the "extremely hard to get rid of" dosage of twice a day instead of just once every 24 hours. I figure that the disease has progressed enough and that it needs immediate attention. I might even consider doing it 3 or 4 times a day. At this rate, the fish are going to die anyways, so why not make it more pleasant? I am considering getting a larger aquarium and setting it up for her fish. This is getting ridiculous.
 
I have some other amusing things that happened over the course of the last week, but I am still figuring out how to post them with regard to their most recent occurence. One thing that is definitely going up is a section about my dreams. I take long naps when I get back from my 8AM orgo class, and during those periods of rest, I experience some of the most vivid dreams I have ever experienced. I am even having recurring dreams for the first time, either they involve different orgo themes or me killing Liz's fish. Either way, they are freaking me out, so I think it is time I visited a shrink or started a Dream Log. Hmmmmm... "Dog?" Already been taken, I suppose... Until next time.....

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Improving their condition...

The fish are getting better. One more died this morning, and only one tail-less fish remains. Photos of the tank are available at this link: 
 
 urlLink Liz's Fish Tank 
 
See you after Friday....


     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Last Straw...
 
 
I finally had to do something about those dying fish. So after I finished my last Mog update, I headed over to PetSmart with Liz where we purchased a 25-gallon tank with an Eclipse filtration system. I set it up when we got home, put some dechlorinator in it, and I was going to wait a day before putting the fish in. Then I took another look at those decrepid fish and decided that since they were going to die one way or the other, I might as well put them in their new home and risk some minimal shock to them. At this point, two Tetras had no tails whatsoever, so I decided to move them. 
 
I really don't think it was the shock that killed two of the fish, but rather the fact that they could not swim without a tail had strained them enough. One died first, and I nursed the other one for several hours inside a pet-store fish baggie inside the tank. Unfortunately, that one kinked out too. Now we were down to nine neons.
 
On the second day of the new tank, Liz and I went to a specialty fish store where we bought 35 lbs of rock and some plants to decorate her tank. I must say, I did a pretty snazzy job. I will put pictures up soon. This morning, two more tetras had no tails; they must have ripped them off during the night. By the end of the day, one more tetra had died, and the other was in really bad shape. Of the remaining seven, only three had really bad cases of ich. The pleico was doing fine. 
 
I got my orgo test back yesterday. I missed an A by two points. That friggin sucks. Then again, I haven't been even close to an A in a science class in a while, so I should be happy, right? Of course not, I am pissed! Oh well. I have a final this friday, which means sporadic Mog posts. Oh well...
 
I am home now in Orlando for Father's Day weekend. I went kayaking with my dad today in the lake, and took some wildlife photos with my camera. Mosty egrets, mostly blurry, I am determined to master the use of my manual telephoto lens. Being on a kayak doesn't make it any easier. I will post the good photos soon.
 
My sister is coming up with me to Gainesville tomorrow. That should be fun, although the orgo studying will probably take up most of my time. Kathryn is also visiting from San Francisco on Wednesday. I need to learn time management.  I do get the followin week off for summer break. I'm looking forward to laziness. Yay!
 
I have nothing more to say, really. I hope the seven neons are doing well. I miss my babies.
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My turn to be a father...

Over the last few weeks, I have grown attached to Liz's tetras, most of which died because of overcrowding and disease. It was a learning experience, and although I am still mourning their loss, I have found joy in my own little project. 
 
My cousin and his wife were visiting from Puerto Rico. Like most of my family from my mom's side, they are intrigued by my terrarium, which houses Puerto Rican Coquis. Unfortunately, in my absence (up at UF) I have not been able to pay close attention to my tank. When my cousin's wife pointed to a small speck in the terrarium and asked me if that was one of the frogs, I laughed at her and told her that they were much bigger than that. It wasn't until I really looked closely that I realized she was pointing to a miniature replica of my coquis: They had finally bred in captivity.
 
I am not sure if anyone else has ever done this before, which is why I feel kinda special. Anyways, I have taken photos, and I promise they will be up soon. No lie! Take care, and I hope you are all out there....




My coquis finally bred
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I am going to try to do this daily post thing. Some days might have more than one post. There is a lot of catching up to do. I am not even sure where to begin. So, perhaps these first few posts will sound like I am rambling. I am not; I just need to update the world.
 
I guess the theme for the month of December was "Blast to the Past." So many of those things which I considered to be part of my own "history" resurfaced. Although I suppose that these incidents had precursors going back to this summer, most of the reminiscing really came in December. I had about six days in Ft. Lauderdale. In that time, I was fortunate enough to see those friends dearest to me. I guess that the Blast to the Past wouldn't be a theme if it was unique to me. There were others who were experiencing the same. I wish them the best of luck. As for me, the blast wasn't as far as you would think, but it was enough to make me realize some of the mistakes that I have made over the last four years.
 
I finally got to hang out with the girl I have affectionately called "Game Seven" for the past four years. (That's a long story, think baseball 1997.)  She unfortunately thought that I was still seeing my most recent ex, which I suppose was part of the reason things didn't work out so well. Seems like some things from the past are harder to shake than others. Oh well. That reminds me - I have to mail out a package when I get back to Duke. Anyways, I guess the realization that I did come to was that things seemed so much simpler then, which is perhaps why we have a tendency to long for the past, or things similar to it. In 1997, my biggest problems were finding ways to extend my curfew past 1am and what colleges I should be considering. Now, I wonder where I will be one year from now, and how that is going to affect the rest of my life. 
 
I suppose that part of the reason why I have developed this interest in the past is that those things which I considered faults then now shine like virtues. Add that to the list of already existing virtues and now the good significantly outweighs the bad. Perhaps I am rambling, but that is why I have this Mog. There is a point there, albeit somewhat ambiguous. You just have to look for it. I needed a chance to explain myself to many who couldn't understand. I hope that I did so here. Good night, all.
  
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It has been a while; this I know. Time to post once again....
 
Here are some updates..... 
 
The website needs to be redesigned. This will be done in the next couple of weeks before school gets too hectic to do anything useful. I intend to overhaul some parts and entirely scrap others. I might even throw in some new sections. This will be done once I return to Duke. 
 
Zoom Culture is awesome. I may have failed to stress that in the past, but I will certainly do so more often in the future. These guys really have an awesome idea, and they are working hard to meet their goals. They're actually flying me out to the Sundance Film Festival in 2 weeks. Robert Redford, here I come....
 
That reminds me, Chris and I have a new secret project we are working on. I am not allowed to divulge the specific information here, but if it takes off, you can bet that I will let the world know through this site. This current idea is one of the best we have had. Things are actually going in our favor, for once. Stay tuned for this one.
 
As I spend my last few days in Florida, I must once again make the remark that I have so often made. There is absolutely no place in the world like home (I am treating the entire state of Florida as my home.) Orlando is nice, Miami is amazing, and Ft. Lauderdale is the best. If our project takes off, expect Marce to purchase a multi-million dollar mansion out by the beach. Wishful thinking? Yes. Impossible? No.
 
Stay tuned! The Mog is back.
 

 

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Cool. I was on television today. 1 week till Sundance. Zoom Culture is awesome. 'Nuff said.

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This will be a quick post... I am kinda tired.... Big day ahead tomorrow....
 
Coffee went well today.  We had a great conversation as we reminisced of things past and future possibilities. I think it's funny how something can be sitting before you for so long and you fail to realize that it even exists. Even when you do realize that something exists, it takes some catastrophic event for you to realize the significance or the importance of an often overlooked characteristic, one that some might even call a flaw. Funny what three years in Durham, NC will make you do or think. Florida was fun. I am glad that I saw all those that I saw. Thanks for the talks, the special moments, and for making me realize the importance of friends who understand who you are and where you come from. Most especially, thank you to the new found friend, my blast from the past, for helping me realize what is important in life. Your perspectives and advice have changed the way I see things. Thank you.
 
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just keeping true to my daily post promise...
 
Not much going on today, my last day here in Florida. Tomorrow I am off to the land of no social scene, Duke University. Oh well. Such is life. It was fun while I was here. Avoided trouble and I had a great time. Who could ask for anything more? I am off to UCF tomorrow to meet someone for coffee. If that goes well, then the break will have been a total success. Good friends are hard to come by, and I know that I have been blessed with several. 
 
Life is good. Ten days till Sundance. Yay!
 
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today's thoughts come from an IM conversation with a good friend of mine. 
 
  

Marce: I like it when people I don't even know have heard of my sexual exploits
 
Marce: some of which I hadn't even heard before
 
Marce: you'd think it would be a guy talking the sexual stuff
 
Marce: I guess that's women's lib for you
 
Marce: same story - one little incident gets exaggerated a million degrees
 
W: well, its a different world... there is a level of openness about EVERYTHING where all matters are now "chat" material, and nothing is regarded as personal anymore
 
Marce: yeah, but not with everyone, though  
Marce: there are still girls out there who hold a certain degree of decency when it comes to those things  
Marce: but as you said, hindsight is 20/20 
Marce: how could I have predicted that the end would have brought me more trouble than staying in a relationship 
W: yea, i know... but oh well, sooner or later, that mask has to come off 
Marce: yeah I know 
Marce: call me old fashioned, but some things should still retain their intimate value 
Marce: otherwise we'd all be porn stars
 
W: yes, absolutely 
Marce: oh well 
Marce: that's actually a big thing for me 

W: but of course, in today's world, everyone is a porn star... that's why everyone has that sticker on their car... if you're incapable of sex without love, something's wrong with you... and if you're incapable of conjoining your private life with public life, you're a prude with something to hide 
Marce: this is true 
Marce: I am not saying deny your sexual existence 
Marce: I don't care if people know about my life 
Marce: not because it affords me some machista bragging rights but because I agree with you - it's stupid to hide that  
W: i know...  
Marce: but at the same time no one other than the person you share that experience with should know the details 
W: not everyone is a group sex therapist that you need to outline with schematics every aspect of your love life? 
Marce: that's what makes it intimate 
W: yup. 
Marce: I guess that is what hurts the most 
Marce: is that she took away the intimacy 
W: College is a fucked up place... you like few others search for something that we're conditioned not to want... right now, women are supposed to be as sexually outgoing as men, and therefore women are to have "locker room talk" that, while there were many guys in the locker rooms who didn;t want to hear about others lives, most still decided to brag... women therefore can do the same... and if you're not fucking out in the open for all to see, there's something unhealthy with you... 
Marce: society sucks 
Marce: I got a threat from someone today 
Marce: asking me to remove my "slanderous" thoughts from my website 
Marce: I didn't think anyone read it 
Marce: but I took it down anyways 
W: society is not a third party with an iron fist, rattling the shackles of your life begging for conformity... you're in society, and while you may not agree with the norm, the other people are still around... 
Marce: I guess there's a limit as to how open you can be, even for open people :-) 
W: everyone really needs to learn their lingo... LIBEL is written untrue insults... Slander is spoken 
Marce: this is true 
Marce: all I said was that it sucks to get cheated on 
W: For everyone who wants to believe there isn't a line in the sand about where "openness" starts and stops, there is a line... its just blurred by "tact" 
Marce: I am not sure if I meant that literally, though 
Marce:  I heard rumors 
Marce: but even still 
Marce: I was cheated on in a way 
W: i know in your log for today, you said something about missing all the women of SoFlo (excluding your ex) 
Marce: but people don't look at things that way 
Marce: yeah I changed it 
Marce: it now reads something more pleasant 
Marce: you wonder to yourself if everything was a lie 

Marce: part of the motions that people are trained to believe are necessary 
Marce: not worth exposing yourself 
Marce: it gets boring after a while 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Edit.
  
I said it originally: Once I read what I wrote at 4:30am, I would probably wish I hadn't written it. 
 
I apologize for the post. To those who read it, I hope you enjoyed it. To those who laugh at my expense, continue to enjoy it.
 
Zoom Culture is awesome. Sundance, here I come.
 
Fabiana, the girl from Italy, has a shoestore in Las Olas.
 
Hot showers help relieve stress.
 
Sleep also helps relieve stress and helps avoid doing stupid things.
 
Have a pleasant day.
 

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sorry I haven't posted in a while.... Matt, Dan and I took a road trip out east to East Carolina University. It was a fun trip - we visited some lovely ladies from Clement Hall. Thanks to Helen for letting me sleep in her room. The clubs were fun, but alas, they were not Miami. Neither were the girls, either. Oh well. Three more days till the Sundance Film Festival. Uma Thurman, here I come.....
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a while since I have posted. I got back from the Sundance Film Festival last Sunday, and I have spent most of the week trying to catch up with school work and stuff. I was originally supposed to spend only four days in Park City, Utah, but then ZC asked me to represent them for the whole week. Kinda difficult to let that pass, so I took a chance. It was well worth it, believe me. I will put pictures up soon (I know I always say that, but I will) and as soon as some of the ZC videos get edited, I will put links up here.
 
 
I will talk about Sundance at a later point, I'm really not in the mood for it tonight. I guess my theme for this week has been to clean up the clutter in my life. I haven't been able to fulfill that goal completely, but I think I am doing pretty well. Tomorrow, I clean my car. And maybe the fridge. At some point, I need to start a 35 page paper I have due in 19 days. But that can wait. 
 
 
I want to reflect on something, but I really don't know what. Sometimes I just wish I could erase all the mistakes I have made in my life. But I suppose that if you do that, you wouldn't have anything to learn from. Maybe mistakes are a way of improving yourself, just as long as you realize when you're making them. I hate when I ramble. I know I have a point somewhere, but I can't always find it. Things are going to improve from here on out. That is my goal. Using the past as my marker, I will work to make things right where I have wronged and to build new bridges where I have torn down others. Here I go.
 
 
I am also going to work on some video editing for some snowboarding footage that I captured up in Utah. That will be on the web soon.
 
Until next time.......

 
 

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some thoughts from late Saturday night.....
 
Heroin addicts suffer from a condition known as chasing the dragon. After their first taste of the drug, they experience an amazing high that can never again be attained.
I am chasing my own dragon, not a substance based one, but one based on love. Four years ago, I felt a love that I have since been unable to attain. In my youthful ignorance, I let that love go. I let it go because I fell prey to the belief that something better existed. I failed to realize many things, among them the very simple tenet that nobody's perfect. (Aside: Have I yet learned this lesson?)
 
I am still chasing the dragon. I saw her tonight. In her aura of brilliance she stood; her visage absorbed my every emotion. The way she came into my sight was poetic. The fog from the club cleared as the people dancing before me symmetrically separated in opposite directions. As this was occurring, the spinning overhead lights landed on her and held their place: It was the sun breaking through the clouds after a long storm and bestowing its radiance on an on a solitary flower.
 
Why do I chase this dragon? Maybe because I, like the heroin addict, believe that continued exposure to the object of my desire will yield a pleasure like the one I felt so long ago. Who knows? 
 
Anyways, although these thoughts might indicate otherwise, the Bahamas were a blast. I’m wondering what segments will make the final show. The erotic dice were a nice touch – hope they don’t get anyone in trouble. 
 
Bahamas show will air on E! in late April. Should be pretty cool. 

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Vivid dreams suck.
 
 
Saw High-Fidelity yesterday. Good movie. Made me think. Way too much, actually.
 
 
Reminds me of the Communist theory of self-criticism. Practiced by Mao, Leninists, and even by Sendero Luminoso in Peru. The basic concept is that in order to make yourself a better citizen of the state, you purge your "crimes" by criticizing your shortcomings. Everyone does it to make themselves look like a better citizen. Now, you have to be asking yourself how this movie is like self-criticism. I think the effect might have been unique to me, but the movie made me look at my actions, both past and present, and evaluate their validity. If I were to follow my interpretation of the movie directly, then my current actions are blatantly wrong and I should be going back along a different path that I have ruled out entirely. Sucks when you're wrong. (Or at least perceive yourself to possibly be wrong.)
 
 
Still have questions? Watch the movie.
  

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I get this email from a service called Crush Link. It's an online secret admirer service network thingie.com. Apparently, someone has a crush on me, and could think of no better way to tell me than to use this service. So I, the gullible idiot, decide to play along. 
 
Apparently, in order to guess who my secret admirer is, I have to input their name and their email address. Now I am not a big fan of the spam game, but I figured that the search engine assigns priority to email, so I put in the names and emails of several girls that I know, thinking that I would get a match. Not so.
 
 
Then, it offers me a hint, if I add 3 more emails. So I add three of my own emails, thinking that if I got a hint, I could venture better guesses. Well, within, 30 seconds, I get three emails from the Crush Link service telling me that I have a secret admirer. The stupid thing sent out emails without my consent! Then, my hint - oh what a spectacular hint - My secret admirer's first name has five letters. That's friggin useful.
 
 
The best part is that the girls on my first round of guesses all got these emails. Should they be as naive as I and play past the first and second rounds to get a hint, they will find out that their "secret admirer" has nine letters in his first name. That narrows it down. This sucks. This stupid post is the closest thing to damage control I can think of.
 
This is probably a prank, but I want to get to the bottom of it. So onward I play. It's not Dan or Matt with a prank, because Rosie O'Donnell didn't register. Then again, if my email priority theory is right, then I'd have to figure out what those two would speculate as Rosie's email address. This is annoying.
 
 
Argh.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am in the mood to write.
  
Caffeine will do this to you.
  
It makes you smart.
  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      MONOLOGUE:
   
I'm doing a story of my life this summer.    
Marce gets dragged on one last family vacation to Alaska. You see, Marce's adventures with a video camera began on these family vacations. Whenever I got a hold of the family video camera, you saw the Alvarez family like no one ever did before. It was reality tv before reality tv even existed. Imagine Marce at the age of 14 - I am making my expository piece on my family, criticizing every family member, making really sarcastic jokes and managing to get my camera priveleges revoked at every possible instance.
In order to get the camera back, I had to make a promise that I wouldn't speak when I took hold of the video camera: "You'll ruin the footage" they said.
 
 
Now fast forward 7 years later. I now have a job that pays me to use a video camera. My skills are infinitely refined. I just got back from a trip whose sole purpose was to document my perception of my spring break experience. Now I can enact my revenge on the world!
   
 Day 1: Intro to the Alvarez Family 
Oh yeah... 
they're scared... 
They can't take the camera away from me anymore...  
hahaha (evil laugh)  
It's all over....  
I now have editing possibilities.  
 I can now do voice overs....  
 I can now digitally crop images...  
Oh - the possibilities are endless...  
 Muhahahahha.  
 I have to also include lots of opportunities for flashbacks. For instance....  
Flashbacks to when I was 14...   
when I was 16...   
Like the time I was filming my dad and his friend, Mr. G (The G family always accompanied us on these trips). They were taking photos of the bison in yellowstone national park. They were all into it - with their huge telephoto lenses, and their big camera bags, too preoccupied to realize that the bison was charging at them. So there I was with the camera, making fun of these two fools with their cameras. Hahaha. And adding my color commentary to the charging buffalo. The thing actually ran past them across from where I was standing and into a hot spring where it suddenly dropped to the ground, kicked its feet into the air and started moaning while it tried to rub its back against the hot rocks. Very amusing. I wish they would have had steady cam back then, because my hand was shaking so much from my laughing that the video came out wobbly.
That is just one of the many stories I can retell now in digital format.
 
  
Soon, my moment of triumph will arrive. Soon.
    
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I finally got Mog up and running on RhinoHazard. It took a while, but it is now up.
 
 
Cool.
 
 
So anyways, as you can see I am in the process of updating my website. RhinoHazard will become my all purpose website. I am in the process of designing graphics and layout, and slowly but surely, I will finish the site in the next few weeks. Please feel free to send me comments. 
 
 
Later.
 
 

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Mog is now on RhinoHazard. Welcome to your new home.
 
Updated posts will come soon. The website is currently being redesigned.
 
Beware the Rhino!
 
Please work.......
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know what's bullshit?
 
 

That the last time US News & World Report ranked fine arts graduate schools was in 1997. If that had been the case with med schools or law schools, the premeds and the prelaws would have thrown a fit and called mommy and daddy to fire the evil people at US News.  

Do you know how useless this is? Their excuse is awesome:   

"However, we decided not to publish them in the 2002 edition of Best Graduate Schools because, in the opinion of our research team, the programs in these areas have changed enough—schools may have added, dropped, or changed content—that we are not comfortable publishing these rankings as describing the present situation in these fields."
  

 Do you know what that means? Let me translate; here is what they are really saying:   

 "Unlike everything else we rank, which has had static curricula over the last 30 years, ranking visual arts, which actually change over the course of 12 months, would require us to do actual research, and not rehash or shuffle the previous year's rankings".   

"Thus, since the possibility of our giant gag on the world of academia might be exploited through this loophole, we have decided not to risk it. Thus we will never publish rankings in the visual arts."
  

"Students seeking to study visual arts might have to base their decision on the following unconventional standards: 
1. Academic interests  
2. Academic and social environment  
3. Style of teaching  
4. Career goals  
5. Pursuit of intellectual stimulation  
 
While our rankings in other fields of study prove contradictory to this, we feel that this might make you a better person, though it won't help our sales of our magazine to people interested in the arts. 
Have a nice life!    
--Your friends at US News."
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a very long time, but I am happy to say that my weblog is back in service. So much to say, so little space. I'll update the world in a little bit.

-M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I enjoyed my trip to North Carolina. Brad and Anna's wedding ceremony was
really beautiful, and everybody looked happy to see them get married.
They're the first couple with whom I am close friends that I have seen get
married, and I'm honored that I was a part of the bridal party. Both Brad
and Anna had some cool friends that I met, some from as far as New Zealand
and others as close as NC. Overall, it was a fun (and sometimes scandalous)
four days, and I'm actually going to miss NC (I'd never thought I'd say
that.)

 
 
It was also a bit of a mental refreshing. I'm glad that I was able to see
some of my college pals, and it's always good to catch up on new happenings
in everyone's lives. I had the opportunity to walk around Duke campus, and
to take some of the photos I always wanted to take but never got around to
doing. They'll be up soon; I promise. Walking around campus made me a bit
nostalgic for the good ol' days (they weren't ever that good, but two years
time will help you forget some of the not-so-good memories; it's the Eternal
Sunshine of the Spotless Mind effect on collegiate days.) In that vein, I
guess that being back on campus made me reflect on my future academic goals.
I think I'll probably start looking at grad school this week for potential
admission in Fall 2005. I'm definitely thinking of business school, but I'd
like to supplement that with a bit of Political Science, perhaps a Masters
in IR with an MBA. Who knows.
 
 
In other news, stil working on getting everything together for my Egypt trip
next month. I still need to secure my vacation time, and I still need to
finalize my trip details. All in all, it should be an incredible trip and
I'm looking forward to working on a social documentary again.
 
 
Well, I guess that's all for now.
 
 
-M 

  

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the countdown has begun to departure. Just 15 days before I leave on my trip. Still have plenty of things to get ready -  waiting on some camera gear to arrive, waiting for my new passport to arrive, as well as some other things. This trip has definitely become my newest preoccupation, which is a nice departure from my most recent real estate preoccupation. (My lease is up in September, my rent is supposed to skyrocket, and I have no idea where I'm going to live.) I guess I'll figure that out when I return.
 
 
T minus 15 days...
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, it's official... I'm going to Egypt next month to film a documentary. I'll be leaving on July 1st and returning on the 18th. I also have a nice 2 day layover in Madrid, which will serve for some fun sight-seeing. Stay tuned, because this website will serve as a travel log and photolog as well. 

 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just a little over one week left till I head out... Just finished placing my second (and thankfully my last) order for some equipment from B&H. Goodies should arrive on Monday. Still need to get some clothes, some medicines, and some luggage, but other than that, I'm good to go.  :)
 
 
In other news, getting ready to head up to the ATL this weekend with my art director, Ty. Should be a fun trip. I haven't partied in Atlanta yet. I'm stopping by Orlando to drop off Sobe and say goodbye to the fam before I head abroad. Other than that, it's just a matter of getting things finalized. Gotta go...
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Me encantan las mujeres de España...
 
 
I could totally see myself living in an apartment in Madrid. This is a city designed for my lifestyle (and my sleeping habits.) The people are friendly, the food is great, and everyone is up till the wee hours of the morning. Took some city photos at dusk - can´t wait to see how they came out.
 
 
http://www.ofoto.com/I.jsp?c=503vnnup.a6zqvjrl&x=1&y=jwhzqn
 
 
Tonight: Out and about...

 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First off, I´d like to thank all my family, friends, and colleagues for their support with this project. (I guess this is how my speech to the Academy would begin.)
 
 
In all seriousness, I really appreciate all the care and concern expressed by my loved ones regarding this trip. I´ll be safe - promise.
 
 
I look forward to exploring the different aspects of Egyptian social life - from the Bedouin fisherman to college kids partying it up in Cairo. Overall, I my goal is to portray a positive image of life in the Middle East, one that I believe is requisite to improve East - West relations, especially now in this time of conflict.

 
 
- M (7-01-04)
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Some pre-travel thoughts will go here... need to transcribe them from the journal. Not in the mood to do it right now.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well today has been a rather busy day. Early this morning John and I headed over to Gold's gym, which is located in a former papyrus museum on the Nile River. There, we met with a kick boxer named Konga who is interested in being in our film. Konga seems like an outgoing guy, and I think he will work well for the film. In addition to being a kick boxer, Konga is also quite the party animal. Though he doesn't drink, he's a known frequenter of all of Cairo's clubs, so he'll certainly be able to shed some light in the realm of things.
 
 
Afterwards, we headed over to an Italian restaurant near American University of Cairo called Al Dente. For 21 Egyptian pounds (about $3.50 US) we had a bruschetta appetizer, two bowls of pasta, and several rehydrating bottles of water. The food was great - the chef apparently spent 10 years in culinary school in Italy.
 
 
After lunch, we headed over to AUC to meet with several people, the first of which was a New Zealand woman named Jan, who teaches in the broadcast journalism/video department. She had some really useful information regarding shooting the doc around Egypt, and even went as far as offering one of her daughters for the documentary. (Her husband is Egyptian, and she's been living here for quite some time.) In addition, she suggested several other upper class girls who might participate in the doc.
 
 
The AUC campus has the feel of any other college campus. It's kinda empty because it's the summer, but some students and some younger children enrolled in camp are mulling about. One interesting thing to note - instead of squirrels or birds floating about the campus, there are cats - lots of them. Some huge, others small, of every color variety, just pacing about. Some are really cute, and I'm tempted to bring one home (there's one kitten in particular that I'm eyeing.
 
 
After we spoke with Jan, we were met by Ahmed, one of the potential subjects for the documentary. The best way to physically discribe him is to say that he's the Arab version of the redhead from Mad Comics, minus the mischievousness. He's got a very large head adorned by oversized square glasses and his ears exaggeratedly protrude from his head. His academic focus is physics, though he's an Arabic teacher/tutor in the AUC language institute. He's also quite a fan of philosophy, and is particularly obsessed with the writings of Einstein. And on top of that, he has a remarkable tendency to go off on tangents about the roots of words, whether they're in English, Arabic or any other language. I think he contrasts quite nicely (both physically and socially) to Konga - and I think he'll make a great addition to the film.
 
 
We met one last person at AUC, a professor named Abdullah Schlifer, a Muslim convert who formerly served as a Mid-East correspondent for NBC for over twenty years. He’s pretty much covered every war out here (minus the two most recent Gulf Wars) of the last half century. He now teaches broadcast journalism. When we entered his office, he was giving an interview to a student about the Arab-Israeli War of 67. He was explaining how he avoided having his door kicked in and having flash grenades thrown inside his house by just unlocking his doors. When the Israeli army came in, they didn’t use force, just asked him some questions, and moved right along. 
 
 
When he finally finished her interview, he entertained some questions about our social life documentary, although he wasn’t too interested. John then mentioned another academic documentary project he wanted to pursue while out here, to which he responded more favorably, providing us with some contact information for some people, among them the local foreign press correspondent. 
 
 
We left AUC and headed over to the Cairo Jazz Club. We met with two of its owners. Ammar and Akhmar, to discuss shooting insider their club. They were both very enthusiastic about us shooting there and in our project in general. We made arrangements to shoot there tonight, as well as Thursday.
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I finally made it to Cairo. Safely and without a hitch. I met John and his friend Samy, both for the first time. I have a really good feeling about this project. I think John has some great ideas, and I think he's lined up some cool choices for subjects. Samy reminds me of the guy from Indiana Jones - whose name currently escapes me. He's full of anecdotal Egyptian knowledge as well as historical aspects of Egypt's social and political development. He's full of zest and proud of his country's history.
 
 
We got to John's apartment around 11:15 pm Cairo time and I met one of his roommates and a friend of his. I showered, got dressed and headed to a club/bar called After Eight. They had an Egyptian band, Wist El Balad, playing different Arabic and non-Arabic songs, including a really cool Spanish flamenco song. John tells me that he's spoken to someone that represents the band, and they're interested in providing music for the documentary.
 
 
I also met John's friend Yasmin, who introduced me to an 8% by volume Egyptian Beer, Meister Max. Despite the high alcohol by volume content, the beer tasted really sweet. I also found out that Heineken sold here is brewed here - I'll report on that as soon as I have a taste. Afterwards, we went to a hotel/restaurant called Versailles Palace, where I drank some mint tea (Lipton with mint leaves in it - not what I was expecting) and where Samy and I each smoked a shisha. I went for the cherry flavor - much fresher than the stuff back home. John and I talked loosely about the doc - some subject related stuff as well as some editing stuff.
 
 
On another note, John mentioned scuba diving in Sharm el-Sheik. I asked him about doing some open water dives to get my certification (he's an instructor, and I've already taken the course twice but managed to get seasick on my open waters both times.) He thinks he can swing it in a day or two, which would be great. Too bad I didn't bring the Nikonos.
 
 
Overall, I'm really excited to be here. We've got meetings set up all day tomorrow. Some with potential subjects and others with potential advisers/investors (more the former than the latter.) Hopefully, it'll all go well. Until next time.
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      International travel can be a pain in the ass. After arguing with the woman at the check in counter for 30 minutes as to why I shouldn't have to pay a penalty for a schedule change made without my consent by Air France, she then told me that I could only carry one bag. So then I kindly tried to explain that my AIr France flight from MIA to Paris and my connecting Air France flight from Paris to Madrid were cool with it and therefore it was a little too late to make any changes.Thankfully, she gave up eventually. I then had to battle through a mob to get to the security checkpoing - a mob caused by two things. 1. The lack of ropes to form a line and 2. Parents walking thei high school-aged kids all the way to the front of the mob to say goodbye. People, leave your kids BEFORE the mob. Thanks, management.
 
 
On a side not, I'd like to mention that my travel experience has been greatly enhanced by a cool new selection of music given to be by Mia. Good stuff. Thanks, Mia.


 
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Happy 4th of July! Celebrated by partying it up in a club in Madrid. Met some cool girls from W. Kentucky U. Had some drinks, and an overall good time. Great techno (80's remixes, house) at the club, Cibeles. Fun fun fun. I head for Egypt tomorrow in the AM. It's 5:30 AM  here, but it still feels like 11:30 to me....

 
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I did the museum thing today....
 
 
Went to El Museo Nacional del Prado. I had the opportunity to see some amazing works of art...
I especially enjoyed the extensive selection of works of art by Velázquez, including "Las Meninas," which is one of my favorite pieces of art. In addition to Diego V's stuff, I saw some pieces representative of diverse European eras of art. Among them, pieces by Van Weyden, Tiziano, El Greco, and Goya. I'll post some JPEGs of my favorite pieces eventually - I decided to forego that whole "take pictures of the art at the museum" thing, so I'll find them somewhere and post them eventually.
 
  
Afterward, I headed over to el Jardín Botanico de Madrid. Took some photos there, but mostly of landscapes - there wasn't too much in bloom. I had initially hoped to use the garden as a shortcut to another museum, but when I got to the other end of the garden, I realized there was no exit save for the entrance. So I walked back....
 
 
I later headed over to el Museo Nacional Centro de Arte de la Reina Sofia (mind you, I have walked everywhere that I've gone to) after el Jardín. They had a special exhibit on Dalí, which was my main reason for heading over there...
 
 
Oh, how Mr. Aloma would be proud. Saw some great works from Dalí, one of my favorite artists, including some cells from a movie he was supposed to do with Walt Disney. (These have never before been seen by the public, apparently.) It never made it to the silver screen - Dalí's work freaked Walt out - but some of the non-erotic shots looked strangely reminiscent of scenes from Fantasia.... I wonder....

 
 
- M

 
 
P.S. Photo link:



     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Chillin' in the back of a bar somehwere in Madrid... Bumped into the group of Auburn kids that were on my plcae from France to Madrid. I didn't see any of the kids I had talked to, so I didn't say anything.
 
 
It got me thinking, though, about bumping into someone I know out here. What are the possibilities? Who knows. I wonder - who would I want to see, and who would I now? What would I say to them?
 
 
The other day, as I was looking through my Europe books in preparation for this leg of the trip, I remembered that I had bought those books anticipating a trip to Europe with Liz after my college graduation. That trip never materialized, but I'm sure it would have been fun.
 
 
Anyways, bar hopping solo isn't as fun as bar hopping with your normal group of peoples. Ty & Kristyn, you guys should totally be here - we'd rip this town apart. :)
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got up, somehow. Met our driver to drop off our equipment. Went to go look for a dive t-shirt. Went back to anemone dive club to say good bye to the guys. Went to lunch at the Marriott Hotel. Very Italian presence there. They were doing some daytime aerobics class. (Mind you, it’s like 120 degrees outside.)
 
 
Left Sharm, stopped by a giant sand dune to take a photo. Walked precariously to the sand dune from the side of the road – about 100 m walk. You have to watch out for Israeli landmines that were left there after the war. The Egyptians have done a good job in clearing most of them out from Sharm, but you still have to be careful.
 
 
Sand dune was really cool. Took some photos of it, then John took one of me chillin on a giant sand dune. Good stuff.
 
 
Drive back was fairly uneventful. Slept most of the way, though I kept waking up to find ourselves on a collision course with a giant semi. The road to sharm is just a two lane highway. I use the word lane very loosely. At any point in time you have two cars side by side going one way and one large truck going the opposite direction. Just a  tad bit stressful. 
 
 
I’m really going to miss Sharm. I could totally see myself spending a week there and doing dives every day. Maybe I’ll come back in December…..
 
 
Drove to the City of the Dead to film a sunset over Cairo from a Mosque. This place is known as the City of the Dead because it’s a poor neighborhood that is literally built on top of a cemetery. People have built homes inside of tombs. It’s kinda creepy. The first mosque we went to had its access to the minaret closed off. So the keeper of the mosque (a doorman, if you will) walked us over to another mosque, where we climbed some rickety stairs in the back to get a shot of the sunset over Cairo. Took some photos while I was up there too.
 
 
Left the city of the dead and came back to the apartment in Mohandeseen. Nahla text messaged us about getting together. We made plans to go to Khan el Khalili at 9:30. She came and picked us up and we headed over the Khan to pick up some goodies. 
 
 
She dropped us off at Pizza Hut in Zamalek (John and I were starving) and we ordered a cheese lovers pizza.
 
 
Got back to the apartment around 12:30 and packed for about an hour. I barely fit it all in. Went over to the airport – got there around 2:15 for my 4:15 am flight. I’m really sad to leave Cairo. I really had one of the best times of my life, and I met some incredible people. Editing the footage is what keeps me on the happy side of things. I really can’t wait to have a finished product to show all the people that took part in the doc. Thanks everyone, for making me feel right at home in Egypt. I’ll miss you all!
 
 
- M

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A ton of notes from today also. I'll post soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have a ton of notes from today, I need to formulate them into something coherent. I will post soon. Promise.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      John and I gave a lecture this morning to an undergraduate broadcast journalism class at AUC. We spoke about the foundations of our project, and how are shooting has been going. The students and the professor asked us different questions, but they were mostly interested in the why of our project. We explained to them how media perception in the Middle East in relegated to coverage of the war and coverage of poverty in the Middle East. To me, this seems to perpetuate the misconception that “We” are better than “them.” This film is a way to make a link between youth in America and the youth in Egypt. Why the upper class? There are the most similarities to their lives and ours back in the states. This increases the ability for audiences to relate. Is there a political element to our decision to limit our studies to one particular social class? Yes, there is, but we never claimed this project to be an all-inclusive study about life in Egypt. There’s absolutely no way to do that effectively in a one-hour film. In focusing on the social life, we make one link between east and west. We’ll leave the other links to be made by the audience. There are economic and political links embedded in some of the things our subjects have mentioned. Particularly, I think you’ll be able to see differences in the different groups of people that we interviewed even though they are mostly of the same age and social stature.
 
 
We went back to AUC to interview Selma and Norhan one last time. They both gave excellent interviews, particularly with regard to social stigmas in Cairo. It was the first time these two really spoke at length about these issues, and I think it really completes the footage we have of them so far. I’m really feeling confident that we’ve captured their identities and personalities really well. 
 
 
So John and I went back to the car rental place to go rent our car. Turns out they had run out of the 170 pound a day Daewoo Leganzas, leaving only the 700 pound a day Jeep Cherokees, to which we said no. There was also a 100km limit per day with a 5 pound per km excess charge. So on the 1000km roundtrip to Sharm, we’d be paying another 3,500 pounds in excess charges. So we left the agency. On our way out, I see a small telephone number on the back of a car driving by that says “Rent-a-car.” So we call the number and find out that we can rent a car with a driver for 250 pounds a day with a 1 pound per km overage charge beyond 300km. So we made our reservations for the next morning. 
 
 
Later on, I interviewed Nahla again, this time on the rooftop of our apartment. I just wanted to follow up on some more social issues in Egypt, particularly with regard to her identity as an Egyptian and how she sees things. Our other interview at Campus was more about her speaking generally about life in Egypt, not necessarily with regard to her own personal experiences. After hanging out with her for the better half of the last week, I figured that we had established enough repoire to ask her more personal questions. Again, another solid interview. I think she really conveyed a lot of great thoughts about social life in Egypt, contextualized by her own experiences living abroad and back here in Cairo.
 
 
After I interviewed her, Nahla insisted on interviewing me on camera. I obliged. She asked me several questions regarding my perceptions of Egypt thus far. I think one of my best articulations of social life in Egypt came during this interview. In Egypt, people complain about being judged socially by their peers, the root of this being in an interpretation of Islam that prohibits women from behaving in certain ways (be it smoking, drinking or hanging out with different guys, even if on a platonic level.) This seems to be the biggest complaint among all the girls we’ve interviewed. According to them, this social stigma doesn’t appear in Europe, nor in Sharm el Sheikh, which for the most part is a European tourist spot (except three times a year, when tons of Egyptian youth head over there to party.) This is why many upper class youth head over to Europe and Sharm (when it’s not full of Egyptians) to go party. In Miami, you don’t find a social stigma with a religious foundation, but you definitely find one with a secular foundation. You can only get into certain clubs if you dress a certain way, you have to dress a certain way otherwise your continuously judged, and even your close friends judge you based on who you associate with, especially on the dating scene. And in Miami, it applies to guys and girls. Sure, you can escape to non-ritzy places such as Ft. Lauderdale or certain parts of Coconut Grove. But then it seems like the floodgates open to a certain social class of party people (especially in Ft. Lauderdale) that are kinda trashy. While it’s fun here and there, it gets old quickly. The Grove is fun also, but definitely more of a college scene (albeit a UM college scene that is a social step above most college towns.) But it still gets old after a while.
 
 
So on the social end, life in Egypt and life in South Florida have more similarities than I thought, both on the good end (which I expected) but also on the bad end, which was not something I anticipated. 
 
 
- M

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We went to AUC to go listen to an Egyptian documentary film speak about his experiences. He was also working on an experimental narrative film project. He found several actors, including one that represents him. He is filming them using locations that he encounters in his daily life. So if he goes to a party, he brings his characters to the party and films them there. Since he was lecturing in the class, he brought the actors to the class, including his actor-self, who gave a lecture before he did about a film on female genital mutilation in Kenya that he had shot in 1994. Needless to say, it was very graphic. I thought it was a particularly interesting choice of a film to show to a classroom full mostly of girls, most of which I would say are conservative.
 
 
After he shot his scene, he then explained his project, and showed another film he had shot in 1997 about life in Taliban-controlled Afghanistan. His cinematography is absolutely incredible. Jan said it best – the camera becomes a natural extension of his body. He almost never uses a tripod, but you could never tell. I filmed his whole presentation to the class – I think it might fit into the documentary somehow as a possible self-reflection on making documentary films and partly as a closer look into the lives of the girls we’ve been following. 
 
 
Later on, we interviewed Ahmed in the library. We finally got in. Finally got approval to shoot there. It seems kinda trite, but that was a big accomplishment for John and I. The library has been the one and only location that has been proven difficult to shoot in, despite our AUC-wide approval to shoot everywhere, including the library. We had to get the library administration to approve. Even then, our interview with Ahmed was supervised by one of the library managers. Whatever. We didn’t ask anything political nor did we say anything obnoxious. After the interview, which by the way was Ahmed’s best thus far, we filmed him reading some books. I went to go take some photos from the rooftop and was stopped by security. Had to show him my pass while John explained it to him. Took my photos, wrapped things up, and headed back to the apartment.
 
 
Later in the evening, John, Nahla and I headed over to the Cairo Opera House to go see a jazz festival in an open amphitheatre. The same drummer from last night was playing with a different band. He still had a drum solo every song, and he still deserved it. He is seriously one of the best drummers I have ever seen. 


     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So John and I made our way over to the AUC campus at 8:45 am. That’s way early, For the record, my “vacation” has been filled with days where I’m getting up really early, which after a night of shooting/partying, is really fun, I must say.
 
 
So we get over to AUC to meet with the students. We jump in three separate cars and head over to the outskirts of Heliopolis. The plan is really simple: we head to a meeting point where we will meet with Norhan’s dad, who will then lead the way over to the construction site. If only simple things could remain simple in Egypt.
 
 
So we get to our meeting point to wait for Norhan’s dad. He gets there, and we begin to follow him. Four cars. Norhan’s dad is leading the way. Well, our driver (an AUC provided driver) decides to pass Norhan’s dad. Why? I have no idea. Another AUC driver does the same. Now, John and I are riding in the back seat, talking with Jan, who is riding up front. We’re not really paying attention to what’s going on – we’re assuming that our driver can do is prescribed job of following the car in front of him. 
 
 
So about 25 minutes later, the other AUC driver zips up next to us and flags us down, letting us know that we’ve passed the exit.  (Mighty considerate of him, to do so – otherwise we might end up all the way in Sharm.) So we need to make a U-turn, which is not as simple as it seems because the highways in Egypt aren’t designed like they are back in the states. The next exit/U-turn is like 10 miles down the road. So we make the U-turn and come back to another exit about another 5 miles beyond the exit that we missed so we can make another U-turn. We do so, get off on the exit, and then stop. We don’t see anybody. So we ask the other driver if he saw where everyone went. He didn’t. He just saw the exit that he “knew” we were supposed to get off on, so he flagged us down. This led to about an hour’s worth of confusion. We call Norhan, who is with her dad, to see if she can give us directions. She can’t, because she has no idea where we are. (Oh yeah, did I mention that streets in certain parts of Egypt don’t have names? That makes it way easy to figure out where you are.) So we jumped back on the highway, looking for another exit. We literally drove back and forth (in 10 and 5 mile increments) making u-turn after u-turn, trying to get off on the right exit. So it turns out that after we passed everybody, they passed us again and kept going. So we never passed an exit where they had gotten off. We finally made it to the construction site about and hour later (after one of the girls jumped back on the highway, found us and led us back to the site.) Needless to say, Jan was less than pleased with this whole incident, but John and I (partially because of sleep deprivation) thought it was hysterical. 
 
 
Filming on the construction site was fun. Let’s just say that construction standards in Egypt are just a little different than in the US. The girls had a fun time climbing up an inclined plank (not attached to anything) that led from the ground level to the second floor, where the workers were building part of the second floor foundation. Fortunately, a nice breeze kept us relatively cool – it was probably only 100 degrees, but the wind made it feel a little cooler. The lack of humidity helps. I think by this point, I have grown so completely comfortable with sweating profusely that I don’t even notice it. We got some really good shots at the site that I think will help show the girls’ personality. They really have fun in almost any situation. They don’t really complain about anything – they just joke about it. 
 
 
Afterwards, we went over to a café/restaurant to get some lunch. I ordered a virgin pina colada in the hopes that it would cool me off. It wasn’t too good, but it did cool me off. John and I picked up the lunch tab for the class – we figured it was the least we could do for them for letting us follow them around nonstop for two weeks. 
 
 
John and I came back to the apartment, where we crashed for a bit. Even though it wasn’t sweltering at the job site, the sun does have a way of just draining all your energy. Slept just enough to barely refresh ourselves and then headed back to AUC to film a dance performance by Selma. AUC is hosting a Model Arab League and their opening ceremony features some introductory speeches as well as some performances. Selma danced with two other girls to a traditional Egyptian dance track. Out of the three, she was definitely the best dancer – mainly because her on-stage presence was really strong. She really enjoyed the dance. Afterwards I asked her about it, and she explained that she had been dancing for years, but had to quit because AUC stopped offering dance classes and because she couldn’t pursue it professionally.
 
 
I had wanted to go to the pyramids by night w/ Nahla, but she cancelled. So I stayed in for a bit, then headed out to Cairo Jazz (where at this point I am definitely a regular) to meet up with Yasmin and her mother for some drinks. We bumped into Shirine from Campus over there – she was hangin’ out with Ammar, one of the owners. There was a live jazz band playing tonight at Cairo Jazz (obvious, you might think, but it is only the second time I’ve heard a jazz act here.) The drummer was absolutely incredible. He had a solo pretty much every song, and he totally deserved it. Really solid performance. John and Yasmin know both the lead guitarist/singer and the bassist, and we chat with them a little bit during one of their breaks. It’s really true what everyone’s told me about Cairo – in the upper class circle, everyone knows each other. This has its benefits and its disadvantages. In a society where external pressure and judgment are ever present, I can see how it can be totally annoying to see the same group of people when you go out. At the same time, I think it’s pretty cool that you can go anywhere, see someone you know on some level and pick up a conversation from where you left it off last week, last month or even last year. 
 
 
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ah, finally a day to rest. I slept in this morning while John went to his 10 am class with his Arabic tutor. It was nice to sleep in and catch up on some missing z’s. We have been trying to squeeze in the occasional afternoon nap throughout the week, but it’s been very difficult with the shooting schedule that starts early on and ends rather late.
 
 
Some reflections on Cairo. First off, I never realized how not having hot water could be such a luxury. Freezing cold water showers are the best thing since sliced bread. After being out in the heat all day long it feels absolutely great to take an ice cold shower. It really does. Although our apartment has AC, sometimes it’s not enough to escape the heat. The shower definitely hits the spot.
 
 
Driving is a cultural phenomenon here in Egypt. There are usually two lanes in the roads here, although there are no lines painted on the streets. Consequently, what was intended to be two lanes and a median becomes a five-lane street. Since there are no lines to respect, people just flow in their cars from one side of the street to the other. Traffic lights are just recommendations (even if there is a cop standing on the corner.) Sometimes, the cop decides to enforce the light, but if he does so for too long, people will go ahead and move. Horns are used like turning signals (every few seconds.) You kinda have to, otherwise you’ll get hit by an oncoming car. It took me a couple days to get used to the traffic rules (or lack thereof) but now I feel pretty comfortable with the traffic situation.
 
 
 Today we went over to Maadi to interview Alya and company over at their house. We interviewed her and one of her guy friends, a doctor who is also an aspiring musician, while the others looked on. We also played back some of the footage from Tabasco Café from earlier in the week. 
 
 
Later we came back to the apartment to get ready to shoot at a lounge called Mint with the girls from AUC. We interviewed them out there (it was a tad bit noisy) and drank some really strong espresso. The lounge set-up was incredible. Cool graphic designs graced NY loft style walls. Crazy lights hung from the ceilings and minimalist couches graced the floors. There were walls, but with cut out alcoves in them. There were also some LCD monitors on the wall where you could access the internet for free. Music was really good too, mostly house with a couple of dance techno songs mixed in for good taste. The girls we interviewed all had some really excellent points about life in Egypt and on maximizing their enjoyment of life with regards to social and cultural restrictions. Yes, they might have curfews, but they can go out, have some coffee, relax, talk, joke around and live a busy and exciting life. 
 
 
John and I left Mint, came back home, dropped off our equipment and waited for Nahla to pick us up to go meet a friend of hers. Her guy friend was pretty cool – he could have been a skater somewhere in Santa Monica in a previous life - short, skinny, baggy jeans and a shaved head with long sideburns. He was really chill. We decided to get a faluka and go on the Nile at night, which was really nice because it was breezy. Nahla dropped us off at home later on. We had plenty of time to get a good night’s rest for our shoot tomorrow at a construction site in a satellite city 25 km from Heliopolis, which is 15 km from Cairo.
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Morning begins w/ Samy driving us across town so we can video tape Cairo during the day. It’s easier to shoot the video w/ a driver that we know than a cab because cab drivers might report us. Shooting goes fairly well – I sit in the back of Samy’s SUV so I can film from both sides of the road. Got a good shot of the pyramids in the background with a billboard of a woman w/ blue eyes in the foreground.
 
 
I have to hide the camera every time we pass a police checkpoint. Even though we’re technically tourists, the police might not be too pleased if they see us shooting. I also got some good shots of the Nile, including one where some kids had abandoned their small fishing boat so they could go swim in the reeds. Samy then drove us into town, where we shot the exteriors of some of the places we have been to. This was a little bit tricky because we were unable to avoid the police seeing us shoot in broad daylight. We definitely got their attention, and although they watched our every move, none of them said anything.
 
 
While we were wrapping up this portion of our shoot, Nahla once again text messaged us to let us know that she had made reservations at Abul Sid, a famous Egyptian restaurant for lunch. She also offered to pick us up, which was great because that meant that we wouldn’t sweat in a cab all the way over to the restaurant. (Today was pretty hot – it was about 110 degrees Fahrenheit.) 
 
 
Lunch at Abul Sid was good. The restaurant is decorated in a traditional Egyptian fashion. Antique tin signs and old photos and paintings adorn the walls.
 
 
Nahla ordered the entire appetizer menu for us as well as a shisha before the appetizers. By the time the main course of   … (a type of glazed chicken served over a bed of rice) came out, I was quite full. 
 
 
John left lunch a little early to meet up with Kristin. My runny nose was still persisting, which now at day 2 in full effect, was truly beginning to annoy me. 
 
 
After lunch, which Nahla graciously (and insistently) paid for, we walked over to the Diwan bookstore to pick out some music. She wanted to recommend some local Egyptian flavor to take back home and possibly use in the film. We ended up going with three albums by a famous Egyptian composer. I plan on getting more music to bring home, though much of it will be through the connections from the awesome guys at Cairo Jazz. 
 
 
Speaking of which, later that evening John and I met Nahla and Shireen over at Cairo Jazz, which is celebrating their third birthday. (They’re actually making a whole weekend of it.) The DJ was spinning some awesome throwback tunes from the 80s remixed with some crazy down-tempo beats. I’m becoming a regular at the Jazz club – Akram (one of the owners) came over to do some shots with us (two for John and I because the girls don’t drink) and hung out for a bit. Everything continues to be cool in Cairo (I’m finally over my sinus headaches….)
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Woke up with the most splitting headache I have ever had. It definitely wasn’t the alcohol – I only had a few drinks. The pollution has finally hit me hard. That and perhaps jet lag. Oh well. Four days isn’t too bad.
 
 
First on our agenda today was a visit to AUC to film the girls in their classroom environment. We had to pick up our official paperwork from the head of PR on the way over there. We stopped by her office and picked up the paperwork, which we then had to take to the head of security in some other building two blocks down before our permit would become official. 
 
 
We entered the head of security’s office, and from his waiting room, we could see and hear two American girls (presumably AUC students) visibly upset at some situation. They were hysterical and yelling and demanding assistance from campus security. Apparently, one of the American girls had given an Egyptian girl (whose last name they apparently didn’t know) 2,000 Egyptian pounds (like $350 US) and the girl was now holding that money back. This argument proceeded for quite some time, so I had to leave the office and head over to AUC to tell Jan and the girls that we’d be running a bit late. Although I’m not completely sure of the particulars of this event to me, it seems that if you’re new to a country and don’t speak the language too well, perhaps you shouldn’t give 2,000 pounds to someone whose last name you don’t even know. But hey, maybe that’s just my way of seeing things. By the time I got back to the office the argument was still raging, with another member of the security team (apparently a former Egyptian General) in the office with the girls. Fortunately, in the time that he entered the office, the head of security had taken the time to sign John’s paperwork. So off to campus we were.

  
 
We shot the girls interacting in their video class for about 40 minutes. They were doing critiques of video clips they had shot on site somewhere in Cairo. The class seems like it would be really fun to take. Everyone jokes around and has a good time, all while maintaining their journalism focus. We made an appointment to shoot the girls on location on Sunday morning at a construction site (Sunday here is the first day of the work week) where Norhan’s dad is building a house. That should be fun (and very very hot.)
 
 
We had a 1 pm appointment at Heliopolis to meet with the editor of Campus Magazine, Nahla. It took us forever to get to the office. Our first cab driver dropped us off in front of the wrong building. The second cab drove in circles for 30 minutes, stopping periodically to ask other cabs for directions. No one knew where the building was. Part of the problem is that the building was located on a street with no name, so one had to know the nameless streets in order to know where the building was.
 
 
We eventually found the building and the office of Campus Magazine. Campus’ editor, Nahla, received us with open arms. The office set up is very similar to what one would expect from an indie magazine. Cool art design graces the walls, vibrant red walls and the logos of Campus and its sister magazine, G Mag (a Cairo nightlife magazine) are also prominently displayed.
 
 
First off, I must say that everyone at Campus and G Mag were incredibly accommodating of us. They allowed us to interview in their lobby, shoot all around their office, and invited us to hang out. They are without a doubt some of the nicest, sincerest people I have met anywhere. I only hope they come to Miami sometime so that I can show them as good of a time.
 
 
We interviewed Nahla and Shireen about life in Egypt and about how their magazine addresses certain social issues that we too are exploring in our film. They spoke to us at great length about both the positive and negative aspects of social life here in Egypt. Afterwards, they interviewed John and I for a while about our film project and life in the US.  I’m all about a little publicity for the film. :) 
 
 
The girls from Campus invited us to go to a Lounge called Thirty-Five. It’s a brand new lounge that recently opened inside the Four Seasons Hotel in Giza. John and I showed up around midnight and met up with the ladies. The décor of the lounge is very reminiscent of something one would find in South Beach. Light colored floors, white walls with plasma televisions showing underwater footage, and dark mahogany furniture. Glass columns are lit with fiber-optic lights that change colors to match the melodic sounds of some house music playing in the background. Other indirect lighting highlights the ceiling and other alcoves in the lounge. The menu featured a variety of specialty drinks, both of alcoholic and non-alcoholic fares. I personally went for the mojito, which was served in a martini glass full of crushed ice. (Ok, so it’s not Miami, but ice in Cairo is refreshing, especially after riding in a non-air-conditioned cab.) Overall, it seemed like a very chill place, one that I would totally frequent occasionally if I lived in Cairo, or pretty much anywhere else in the world. Nahla pointed out some of the famous attendees in the lounge, including some well known socialites and some actors. 
 
 
Nahla and her friends are great conversationalists. I spoke in Spanish with one of her friends, Dina, who is fluent and always looking for someone to speak with. (I was more than happy to help her with that endeavor.) We had a great time just relaxing and chatting it up for a few hours. When we were done, we parted ways and cabbed it back home. Overall, a pretty busy but incredibly worthwhile day.


     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Met w/ Salma after missing appointment yesterday and her friend Norhan. They both seemed very receptive to our project, and we made plans to get together later in the week.
 
 
Met with PR woman to procure pass to shoot. We had to write a letter explaining our project in order to receive approval. Turns out this woman's husband, who also studied at Harvard, is world-renown Time photographer Barry Iverson. His photos of Egypt adorn the walls of the PR woman’s office. 
 
 
Afterwards, we headed over to a cafe in Maadi to meet with two girls who are interested in our project. While there, we stumbled across a magazine called Campus that features Egyptian youth social life and writes about it in a very NY indie style. I suggest to John that we call them and see if we can interview them. They’re cool with it and set up an appointment for 1 PM tomorrow in Heliopolis, which is like a thirty minute cab ride.
 
 
The two girls meet with us and they seem really cool. They’re not too conservative, but moderate. They talk to us at length about the social stigmas of going out in Cairo, and how going out in Sharm (touristy coastal town up north) is much more acceptable.
 
 
Came back to apartment to get ready to shoot Konga. After trying to call him several times unsuccessfully, it’s evident he’s sold us out. With our night open, we decide to head over to Khan el Khalili, a market in Old Cairo, to shoot some photos.
 
 
We take a cab over there. We get out, and John pays the cab. Now the cab driver apparently thinks John underpaid him. So in what has become typical here, we argue to the contrary. We paid him five Egyptian pounds, which less than a dollar, and he wanted ten pounds. John says no, throws down the five, and we leave. The cabbie decides to ditch his car in the middle of the road and get out to argue. Now, here we are, in the middle of an Egyptian market in a really huge argument with this cab driver. I’ve got my camera out because I’ve been taking photos along the way, and my hope was to remain as inconspicuous as possible. That’s no longer an option. The fight continues, with the cab driver grabbing John’s arm, which is a huge no-no. So we go to a cop to arbitrate in the hopes that he’d rule in favor of the foreigners (they usually do.) But in this case, he agreed with the cab driver. So the situation got worse. We had a crowd of people now trying to negotiate our paying an extra two pounds. After about another ten minutes or so, we finally gave in and paid the two pounds. By this time, we had quite a crowd of people yelling at us. Not fun.
 
 
Khan el Khalili (the letter k’s are silent) is a bustling part of town where one sees the old Egypt often portrayed in movies. Merchants selling all sorts of goods - alabaster bowls, silverware, shisas, musical instruments and a variety of handcrafted items form a labyrinth of stores. In some parts, the streets are so narrow that only two people can walk comfortably side by side. There are small cafes where people sip tea and smoke shisha. The merchants cater to locals as well as to tourists, the former receiving better deals on all their products. Having John as my guide pretty much makes us more local than foreign; his negotiating skills with the merchants are incredible. They even go as far as sometimes asking him if they want to show the good products or the bad products when trying to sell me something. They totally see him as one of their own (which is really cool for getting good deals on things.) John also knows his way around the market like the back of his hand. He navigates in and out of small alleys to find a store in particular that sells handcrafted products made from camel bone or water buffalo bones. He knows the best places to get alabaster and other stone products. It’s really incredible. I took some pictures here – when I get high speed internet again, I’ll upload them.
 
 
We came back home, showered (again), got dressed, and headed over to Latex to shoot. John's roommate Erin, and art history grad student at Harvard, joined us.
 
 
Party at Latex was cool. The club is composed of various lounge rooms with mirrors in the background. The mirrors have green Christmas lights hanging down in front of them, which kinda makes it look like the matrix. The show didn't start till late. One of Ammar's  (from Cairo Jazz) groups that he promotes (called Sundial) opened up at midnight. They were much better than the DJ. 
 
 
Heineken sponsored the event, so I tasted my first Cairo brewed Heineken - much better than the stuff in the states I must say. 
 
 
My nose began to run - I think the pollution is finally getting to me.
 
 
Kristin and her friends joined us later – around 2 am. Hung out till 3 over there – cabbed in back with Erin. John stayed out a little longer.
 
 


     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So after waking up on Kristin's couch this morning, John and I cabbed it back home. We called Jan to apologize for missing our appointment with one of her students. She wasn't too pleased, but set another appointment for 9:30 AM tomorrow.
 
 
We showered and headed out to a book store called Diwan to meet with Ahmed. We figured surrounding him with books would make him feel right at home. We weren't granted permission to shoot, so we chilled out at the bookstore cafe for a bit and talked. Ahmed got into a discussion with John about the root for the word giraffe, which comes from some Arabic root. Ahmed couldn't remember that root's meaning so he went to go look it up. In his bringing back to the table a large dictionary, he broke the rule prominently displayed on a sign above our table - "Cafe is for coffee and food only - NO BOOKS ALLOWED." This prompted a non-Egyptian girl to ask the guy working there if she too could bring a dictionary to translate some Arabic herself. The guy said no, then gave Ahmed a dirty look. I found the whole incident hysterical (and John did too, probably because we were both exhausted) so I started teasing Ahmed about how he was causing problems for all the patrons at the cafe. He proceeded to explain to the cafe guy that his breaking of the rules was for an academic purpose - to find the definition of the Arabic root of the English word giraffe. His delivery of this explanation was so ornately elaborate (yet awkward) that at this point the whole cafe was laughing too, including cafe guy. Ahmed finally  put the book away, and then upon some encouragement from John and I, went over to help the girl with her Arabic.
 
 
Without permission to shoot at the book store, its use to us decreased considerably. So we headed over to the Nile and rented a faluka, which is a small wooden sailboat guided by a captain. After haggling the hourly rated to 40 Egyptian pounds (under seven US dollars) we headed out. Our purpose was to interview Ahmed in the middle of the Nile, surrounded by water, or as he put it, so that he could become a social island, island in Arabic is jazeera (like the news channel,) jazeera which is a passive Arabic root, means something which is ebbed by water, it is an object upon which water acts. So too is he an island, which in its isolation observes as it is acted upon by an outside force - in his case society. Ahmed also indicated to us that he is the curator of the lexicographical museum. (He alleges that a google search of the preceding only has one unique result - him.) 
 
 
After our boat ride on the Nile, we crossed the street and walked a few blocks to the Cairo Hilton, where we met the assistant to an owner of a club located there called Latex. The owners from Cairo Jazz had mentioned her to us, and had helped us set up an appointment with regard to shooting there on Wednesday night, when a prominent Italian DJ is supposed to spin.  We met with her and her assistant, and explained the scope of our project. They were both cool with us shooting there, and granted us permission to shoot. They gave us four passes (for John and I, as well as Konga and a guest) to get into the club. We left the meeting feeling pretty positive about our progress thus far in procuring locations to shoot.
 
 
We went back to the apartment and ordered Italian food from a place called Cafe Mo's. Pretty good, pretty cheap. I'm really enjoying this whole 6:1 exchange rate over here. 
 
 
- M
     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight’s artist was a producer named Fathy Salama. He’s an Egyptian based out of France, where he’s very well known. We shot about an hour’s worth of footage. Fathy asked for a dub of the footage, and we exchanged contact info. 
 
 
Towards the end of the shot, I met some of John’s friends from Cairo, including his ex-girlfriend, who’s also a grad student of Middle Eastern Studies at Harvard, and is half Mexican, half American. She introduced me to some of her friends – a guy who’s in a local dental program and is originally from Palestine, an Egyptian teacher who currently lives in Saudi Arabia (and is remarkably similar to my friend Carolyn) and some other friends as well. The most interesting person out of that group was this girl Memba, who along with her friend Isabella, were visiting Cairo for one month while they are on summer break before their final year of medical school in Brazil. Let’s just say this – Memba is Penelope Cruz in Woman On Top. She’s a little shorter than what I imagine Penelope to be, but she looks almost identical to her, and has all the Brazilian energy of Penelope’s character in that film. And boy can she dance. Fathy’s performance, which consisted of two percussionists, a male vocalist/rapper, a Algerian female vocalist, and himself on the turntables, provided just the right electronic Arabic-Latin fusion of music that made this girl feel right at home. Anyways, we had a great time at the jazz club.
 
 
We followed that up with another visit to After Eight, where we danced to Mediterranean music for another hour or so. That was followed up with an after-party at Kristin’s (John’s ex) that pretty much lasted till the sun rose. This after party consisted of more Arabic music, some salsa, and a little reggae. My lack of jet lag and my feeling that it’s still seven hours earlier has greatly helped my social endeavors. Overall had a pretty solid time – John’s got a fun group of people that can mix a good conversation with some great dancing. Busy day, long entry. Until next time.
 
 
- M

     

    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Sitting in a café in Madrid, reflecting on my trip. 
 
 
My trip to Egypt has solidified my belief that first and foremost, I am a filmmaker. I don’t think there is anything that I enjoy as much as the filmmaking process. 
 
 
Although the Egypt production was pretty low budget, I could totally see myself doing a combination of ethnographic/social documentaries as well as fictional narrative films. I think that one part could finance the other. Now I just need to find a way to finance film projects on a continuous basis. Going the academic route is certainly one possibility. There is something to be said about being in school for 9 months and then applying for a grant to shoot for another three months. I would just need to find an academic program that would allow me to combine the two. I’m not much of a cultural anthropology guy, but if that’s what it takes, I may go that route. The other route would be to concentrate on one comparative area (say the Middle East or Latin America) and enroll in an academic program that focuses on a variety of socio-political and economic issues from the said area, and then apply for grants to shoot films in that area. I suppose that another academic route would be to go for the MBA, specialize in entrepreneurship, and use that academic foundation to open up a production company that combines the academic documentaries along with narrative fictional projects. That’s the strongest possibility right now. I need to start writing to admissions officers to see how I could structure such a program.
 
 
Another thing about going back to school is that it would certainly allow me to take off to Europe for a summer and take some courses. I really really love Madrid; I think it’s absolutely great. I could totally do Barcelona or Salamanca for a summer semester and then head out to other European cities on weekends and breaks. On that note, perhaps I should consider London School of Economics. That’d be a quick way to get to Europe and do the academic thing at the same time. Hmmmmmm. 
 
 
Need to see how this is all going to work. So many thoughts running through my head, but for the first time in a long while, I am beginning to see a semblance of the path that I need to take in order to make it all happen. Weird – as I’m writing this, my iPod is playing a song by JET called Move On. First few lines – Well I been thinkin’ ‘bout the future / too young to pretend / it’s such a waste to always look behind you / you should be lookin’ straight ahead. Yeah, I’m going to have to move on / before we meet again.  -  Mia, your music taste rocks. 
 
 
MBA – production company – documentaries – film projects – creative projects – photography – graphic design. I think my resources (in terms of networking, personnel and personal skills) are at a point where I can make it happen. Just need some venture capital. Make your checks out to Rhinohazard Productions, please. : ) 
 
 
I love the fact that it’s 9:30 PM over here and still daylight. Been here at this caf? for about an hour, and (partially because of the two espressos that I’ve had) I am really enjoying life right now. It’s going to be really difficult to get back into the swing of things back home mainly because shooting this film has really made me aware of everything that I’m missing out on in life. So many people, so many places, so many projects designed to discover. I know I’ve said this before, but this has really been a life-changing project. I think I need to take more time to discover peoples and their societies, starting back home in Miami. I need to do more photography projects, I need to shoot more fun creative projects, and I need to write more. This is just a start, but I can say (and it’s not the caffeine speaking, I swear) that I’m on an incredible natural high right now. I just feel like smiling. Life is really good right now, and I just want to make this feeling last. I think editing this doc will help me sustain it for a few months. But I need to travel again, and soon - possibly a December return to Egypt with my dad and my brother to do some more scuba diving in Sharm and perhaps a return to Cairo and the pyramids. I might also do some more touristy stuff like the museums and such.  I think I might also take an Arabic class. I got to a point in my time in Cairo where I felt comfortable listening to the language – I could recognize words (not necessarily their meanings) spoken in conversation. Reading and writing Arabic are a whole other world – but maybe I could learn. Might come in handy some day. I was able to pick up enough conversational Arabic to take a cab back home. Another fun project. I think if I infuse enough caffeine into my system when I get back home I’ll be able to sustain my energy for all these projects. But it’s so difficult when naps are soooo tempting. Must fight off the urge – at lease for the next three months. Life’s challenges are so hard.
 
 
Another thought. I guess one of the unforeseen personal benefits from this trip has been this: In conducting several interviews with each of our subjects over the course of two weeks to arrive at an articulation of their perceptions of their identity and their society, I’ve been able to reflect on my own identity and articulate my own thoughts on some of the issues they’ve addressed. In addition, I’ve been able to branch off from their ideas and construct an interpretation of how I view myself and the society I live in. This to me is the greatest aspect of documentary filmmaking – that in the process of telling the stories of individuals and their societies, I absorb their stories (and the process of recording them) into my own personal history. So vís a vís the documentary process, I continuously reflect on my own identity and further define who I am as an individual. I can’t think of any other way to learn about other people and their cultural nuances and still retain part of their stories as part of your own. 
 
 

     

    
</post>


</Blog>