<Blog>

<date>31,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Happy Birthday Vitriol..  Another year older hey..well enjoy it. Don't do anything I wouldn't do. Pretty much leaves your options open there. *smiles*
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Why do hot dogs come in packs of 8, but hot dog buns only in packs of 6? *sigh* 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      ah HA! I knew it.. your a closet Dawsons Creek fan... come to the dark side vitriol.. *mwahahhahaaa*  Before you know it, i'll have you reading  urlLink marvel  comics, and watching  urlLink Pauly Shore  movies and the next  urlLink Big Brother  series.. *rubs hands together with much evil intention*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
       Perhaps so. But I hardly inferred that every last member of the human race was culpable as far as the said degeneration is concerned. I simply worry for the trend. And of course there are exceptions... as there are with all things. The Shawshank Redemption is, as you say, a thinking-viewer's film, and a surprising choice for the all-time favourite movie. Speaking of candy-flicks, I would have though Star Wars would have rated up there.  And don't tell anyone, but I quite enjoy Dawson's Creek, for that very reason. Their vocabulary is, for the first time on television, interesting. Like yourself, Pacey appealed to me in respectable quantities. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      ok ok point taken.. but give people some credit.. lets look at it like this. Named as the most popular movie of all time is  urlLink Titanic  as it is currently the biggest grossing movie at the box office to date. So many people look down on this movie as it was over commercilised, and its just a no thinker chick  leonardo "baby face" dicaprio  flick. This movie may have been the biggest grossing movie of all time, but when it comes to popularity ppl name the best movie of all time as  urlLink Shawshank Redemption . A classic 'intellectual' film that has everything, a movie that is in every which way worthy of this position. So give ppl some credit please.. we arn't all cows and sheep.  Oh and not all todays entertainment products are 'dumbed-down'.. i mean geez.. look at  urlLink Dawsons Creek .. mighty intellectual i say, hurrah!  *cracks up*. mmm pacey.. *giggle*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
       I must say, you make a fine point. I capitulate in part to your theory in regard to such lame productions being partially for the purpose of appeasing one's partner, whether she be blonde or he a thug. And I also acknowledge the fact that many people watch movies and television to forget about their hard day's work. The only problem is, I am of the opinion that many people don't even think while they are  at  work. In which case, they should certainly be making up for it when they finally get home.  However, there are many of us (though growing less, it seems) who watch films for the artistry of such things as direction, cinematography, acting and set design. There is nothing I love more than a grim, morbid-looking film, a pure hit for the aesthetic-dependent. Directors like David Fincher, actors like John Malkovich, and films like Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon are worthy of such praise. One does not float into such films for a no-brainer, but are often woken up by the sheer talent of those involved in its production.  One of the detrimental facts of our present culture is its dependence on icons of happiness and frovility. Feeling sad? Get a hit of happy-go-lucky Coke. Feeling stupid? Go and see Legally Blonde, with the ever-so-blonde Reese Witherspoon, idolatress of the pre-pubescent generation. That should sort things out.  Because if pretty little Reese can be smart and blonde  (yet still stupid),  so can I ! The prevalence of popstars and celebreties rather than bands or musicians has infested our airwaves. I doubt Britney Spears even knows how to read music. She is an iconic vehicle for the money-making machine that is the contemporary music industry.  Therefore, in defense of my first statement, I must acknowledge, but not agree with your statement. There is nothing wrong with dumbing-down entertainment products for mass consumption after a hard day's work. But when the entire culture becomes dumbed-down, when everything you see and hear is made simple for easy digestion, it becomes crass, oversimplified and degenerative. Anxst has been buried under a snowball of pretty things and distractions. Independent thought has been smothered in bombardment from logos, images, advertisements of all kinds. We are told how to think. How to feel. How to react. And I bet pretty little Reese reacts exactly the way you expect her to. The usual tossing of the hair, poor-me syndrome followed by the notoriously easy-and-fun rise to popularity.  Yay. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well.. I knew that would get you going.. perhaps i should inform you that a bulk of the audience was couples over approximatly 25.  Three rows back a couple brought themselves and there three  ( crying sniviling *grumble grumble* ) kids. Most of the couples where all lovey dovey.. which adds to a little theory i have that movies like this are made so guys can take there girlfriends too in order to get some brownie points. Its the same reason  Arnold "heck i'm so popular i could pull of being a kindergarten teacher" Schwarzenegger  movies are made, but for the reverse reason.   Also when it comes down to it, a bulk of the population after working all day doesn't want to think. I don't mean that in a bad way, ppl like to turn on the idot box and watch something that doesn't make there brain hurt.. and if it has a cute guy/girl in it.. all the better. I'm one of these ppl, I do love 'intellectual' film, ones that make you think.. but sometimes I just like to watch a movie that doesn't take any concentration whats so ever.. and thats why these movies make it big.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
       *shakes head* Christ. Legally blonde. Is this movie screaming to be canned, or what? I cannot believe that movies like that can get made, and will sell like hotcakes to popstars and little girls (and some older girls, too, by the sound of it), and a great many decent movies can't get off the ground because they are too 'intellectual', and won't sell.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Your right we really need something to get conversation going, well heres somthing that will make your blood curdle.. I saw a classy film last night which couldn't get any more tacky if it tried.  urlLink Legally Blonde  *laugh*. I laughed my butt off in this movie, it may be tack, its not going to win any awards, but i bet it will be one of this years biggest rentals when it goes to video.  Heres a highlight:   'Exercise makes endorphins. Endorphins make you happy. Happy people just don't kill their husbands. They just don't.'   *snicker*
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
       I anticipate the eventual necessity for a 'best-of' page. With the most intriguing discourse from our various tete-a-tete adventures. But there is no dire need. However, it would be pleasant to herald the birth of our little project with some distinguished banter. Perhaps we require a good subject to get the chins wagging, so that there might actually be a history for our two-and-a-half fans out there to actually read. For the sake of clarity, I have also decided to darken my own speech, which should remove all confusion as to whom is speaking. Although I doubt, though, few would confuse one of my hideous diatribes for a Zenism. *chuckle* 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
       *smirk* I found this little snippet amusing, regarding Russ & Meg:  It was reported in January this year that the couple had separated when Crowe chose to spend time with his cows at his Coffs Harbour farm rather than live in Los Angeles with Ryan.  
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
       Smashing.  Well, it seems I may have worked out how to manipulate this darned contraption after all. Excellent. Now, if only I could manage to affix my name to the underbelly of this post, I would  truly  be happy. 
     
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Welcome to  Vitriol and Jubilation , to best describe what we are about I'll use the words  Vitriol  wrote:   'a culmination of dark and light, glamour and morbidity.  A fascinating mix of pessimism and optimism, goth and pop, hard and soft.  Listen, and you shall hear the sound of two voices, speaking as one, defining the world through opposite eyes; male and female, yin and yang. '   To describe it in my words, its a place for myself and my friend to bitch at each other and have disscussions.. publically to full fill our egos *laugh* Which should be not only fun for us, but fun for others to read. The differences between us always makes our discussion interesting. We respect each others differences, but at the same time enjoy giving each other crap as well. Its all in good fun, and to keep our minds busy. Anyway enjoy!
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
       I see it is almost a month since I (or anyone else) last spoke. I shall use that discrepancy as an excuse for my excessive expression now. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
       It is, however, all too true, from a certain point of view. I would certainly suggest that nothing prevents oneself from forming very strong friendships both at work and with lovers, but these two particular conditions make such friends of a different kind. Allow me to clarify. Although mutual affection and intimacy exists between both friends and lovers, I would expect a far more intense bond connects the latter, whereas a quite flexible arrangement befits the former. Friends can feel free to act and speak as they please around one another, and amongst a circle of such companions, whereas lovers have formed a much deeper, and therefore riskier, cohesion.  Most lovers share a part of themselves that they do not share with their more common 'friends'. Indeed, lovers can be 'friends', but once their liaison begins, it becomes increasingly more difficult to sustain a 'normal' friendship, as one or both look for a deepening, or a relaxation, of the relationship depending on the circumstances. Putting one's true self to the test in such a fashion exposes one to a hurt which can also be exploited by 'normal' friends, but in a different way. Which is why becoming involved romantically with someone requires trust. Certainly, Shakespeare (and myself) makes a number of assumptions here, but I believe the presumption correct. If trusting lovers can find that special place between frienship and romance, then they have found the balance required for a lasting relationship.  In business, the opposite is true. Never, ever trust anyone in business. If one thing is true of human nature, it is that money changes people. Perhaps only marginally in some cases, but for most, money is more important than friendship, or has an influence that transcends that of a mere association. In business, money is everything. Which is why employee-employer friendships are rare, and most usually treated with great care, with extra effort required to overcome the financial barrier. Friends who engage in business are similar: many a friendship would suffer due to the resentment caused by debt, or a perceived deficit in financial capacity.  Friendship, therefore, is not compatible with the office, nor with affairs of love. Shakespeare is careful to say 'affairs of love', rather than simply 'love', because they are two different things. Affairs of love would encompass short-term lovers, flings, romances and those little duels of lust that the young find so appealing. In such things, friendship is more a burden than ally. It is an unloved complication. In love (I refuse to capitulate to cliche and add 'true'), however, friendship is an absolute requisite. How one can be completely devoted to another without being able to call them friend is inconceivable. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
        Quoth the Raven:    Friendship is constant in all other things Save in the office and affairs of love    Much Ado About Nothing  Act 2, Scene 1 William Shakespeare  Another feature to look forward to. I must confess my great love of the usually abused quotation. What a fantastic opportunity to remove a statement, often quite beautiful or poignant, from its context and thrust it forward afresh, for all to observe. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
       Thankyou, my dear.  Someone asked me the other day, "when did you last cry?" Contrary to popular belief, I was far from teary-eyed after the Grand Final this year. I believe the last time I cried was when I visited my grandmother in hospital last September and realised she was going to die. It seems a worthy enough condition, if you ask me, which you did not, but others have. *smirk* I would thus pose the very same question to you.  In fact, look forward to more  Someone asked me the other day  segments from now on. 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       I find myself distracted by thoughts of the world around me, and if not distracted then often frustrated. I see many, many things every day that I disagree with, many others that annoy me simply with their presence. Yet, I revel in the fact that I will never find an easy way through the world, because I am so resistant and opposed to much of it. But that is what makes  me  who I am, and it provides me with the motivation and strength to create prose worthy of interest by a wide variety of readers. Therefore, I would not give up that conflict, as strange as it often seems to many people.  Now, to preying once again on your beloved pop culture... *smirk* ...I submit to your notion of resisting the temptation to label everything 'pop' as popular culture. I agree. I suspect much of the larger population do not like Ms. Spears, nor the Spice Girls, nor Haiku. However, what they  do  like is what their culture forces upon them. The anti-Spears campaigner in your last post; he refused to admit any hint of admiration for the girl. And not for any source of his own distaste, perhaps, but because the reinforcement and expectation of his friend has placed upon him. This, in turn, is provided by the stereotypes and rigid structure that very lad has absorbed from the cultural influences around him.  Now, I'm not saying that this is wrong. I just disagree with it on general principle. The world needs its little sheep to buy and consume and toil for the benefit of the rich and powerful. But what I  do  encourage is for these same people to  think  about what it is they worship, and why. Much of the time, such introspection might invariably inspire that individual to look at alternative forms of influence. Otherwise, they  are  the simple sheep bred (or allowed to be bred) to labour in the service of those who direct them, by force or culture or rules.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Now to the rest of it..  how do you sleep at night?  your mind must be twirling with all that going on, but i suppose this is why you write.  I like what you have said. You look at these two worlds side by side and I am amazed out how you manage to keep them both in control. Well done.  And now, onto defending my beloved pop culture. I don't think pop culture and conformism and sheep like nature should be put in to the same shoe. Yes it is a large occurance to with it, but its not the only thing.  ok maybe it is, but not in the way your thinking..  Here is a tacky example, but lets say Britney Spears ok. If you walked up to the average person on the street and asked them if they like little britney they are going to say  "Shit no, have you seen her, she is so fake, virgin my butt!" ..  and why are they saying this? cos they are sheep too. If they say they like britney they are going to be cut down by there mate..  there are just as many ppl out there saying they hate pop culture for the same reason ppl are saying they like pop culture.. becuase they want to fit into what ever little mold they have made for them selves..  I mean dear Vitriol.. what would ppl say if you came out of the spice girls closest? would ppl look at your words differently? many ppl think they would  The key is to be yourself and not care what other think, like what ever you like regardless of wether its harry potter and the rest of the world is on the same pop culture band wangon..   Sorry, if this doesn't make to much sense, my mind was racing and who knows where my thoughts jumped.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       I must say that there are few things more splendid in this world than the smell of freshly baked bread, wouldn't you agree? I find it quite divine. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       Punishment, you see... for your little slip-up. *smile*  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      So in response to the haiku, in even simpler  terms..  you don't know either *snicker*  now see this is one the the  little things  that one should enjoy in the world that i spoke of before teehee
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       I suppose you intend to scathe me for my lack of specifics in my rather vague answer to your first question? Perhaps infer that it I should look at it as something to enjoy about the world? *raises eyebrow* 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       In response to your second point, I will say this: The world to me is a confusing place, and I am perpetually torn between the two parts of me that vie for control of my conscious perception. On the one hand, I see the world as that stinking, polluted, business-infested realm of greed, selfishness, crudity and worthlessness. A dark, grey place of morbidity and cruelty. Yet, I am also just as equally a believer in challenging and enlivening that world, that nothing is beyond any person's influence as long as they are committed to having a go. The world is full of such beauty, such wonder and fantastic things that defy description. Nature and all its unique creations, culture, friendships, football, poetry, music, clouds and thunderstorms; how can a world suffer that has these things?  The answer is that both sides are true. I focus on the negative side of the world, and criticise the things that I dislike because I believe the world  should  be better. That if people bothered to look deeper into themselves and the fantastic gift they have been born with, that they will be better off for it. That too many people -  most  people - waste their lives and so many opportunities to improve not only themselves, but the world around them, because they are too weak or lazy.  And that, my dear, is why I insist on challenging people. Because I believe they are  better  than what I think they are, or are capable of being better, improving themselves. Pop culture bothers me because it is simply  easy  to conform, to believe what others tell you and to aim to be what everyone else wants to be. It is the shepherd who is doing all the work. I'm not content to watch people rest on their laurels, to watch them cop out and follow the easy path simply because they can't be stuffed  bothering . If more people bothered, there would be a more rewarding world out there to enjoy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
        I admire you optimism, Jubilation. To begin with, I shall respond to your query regarding the 'fridge magnet poetry'. Indeed, I would have thought you'd have nailed the new Haiku by now, and would be a fount of knowledge as to its purpose, meaning and place in modern society and culture. However, it is refreshing to be reminded that not everything is accepted by everyone.  To be honest, I don't  get  Haiku either (and I make the assumption here that the plural and singular Haiku are one and the same), but being a form of limited poetry akin to pentameter, I can accept its structure and apply my own perverted psyche to it adequately enough. In 'Jube' terms, I would be saying that it's not really anything at all, just a set of rules. And all one needs to do to create Haiku is to conform to the words, even if they're jibberish. They still obey the rules, which  are  the Haiku.  Therefore, a bunch of simple, crude words such as:  Stupid little flies Bother me all the time now I hate f*cking flies  are just as much Haiku as the more 'poetic' or culturally applicable version below.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       *blink blink* ok i'm awake..   now, am i the only person out there who doesn't really get haiku's.. i'm mean ok i've never really gone out of my way to understand them, but still. When you look at me, being the weird girl who likes tackyness, pop culture, zen, and snowglobes you'd think I'd be a big fan of the little ole haiku..  *shakes head* they just remind me of  fridge magnet poetry  (if you get what i mean).. you grabs some words,and you slap them together cos they sound nice. Now see..  I like fridge magnet poetry .. but haikus.. now theres ment to be all this meaning and non-randomness behind it right?  I'm not saying haikus are bad, i just want you to explain it to me.. oh and  vitirol  explain it in an amusing way so I don't look like an idiot ok *grins*  An before you fill me in, i want to say a few things about your haiku while i'm in the dark as it were.  The world really is a bad place to you isn't it. I mean you like to relish in the worlds delights, you are passionate about so many things in it, but you seem to generally look at the world as a whole.. and all you see is death and evil and all that surrounds it.  I think looking at the world as a whole straight up is wrong... you gotta start with the little things then look out.. then get bigger.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       Having discovered one of the Little People's latest crazes is actually a form of poetry, I thought I might indulge myself. My first Haiku (or whatever it's called) was thus born:   Money, little death The corporate devourer Death, little money   I think it sums up much of the world quite nicely.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
       *sings*   And the mouths of babes sing revolution The mouths of babes scream dissolution You can't break what's already broken From the mouths of babes comes nothing.   
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
       *grumbles*  Damn Collingwood supporters... don't hear a peep from them for the best part of a decade, and suddenly after one wet afternoon in which the sun shined upon them exclusively, they all weed their way out of the wood like the lice they are. *raises eyebrow* I'm not losing any sleep over this one. In fifteen rounds' time, we'll just see who's laughing. I'd also like to see a replay in the dry; where talent matters.  I wouldn't get too cocky if I were you. By the way, the only reason Collingwood supporters cheer louder for the Anzac Day clash than for the Big One is because they never make it to the damn Grannie.  *smirk* 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
      *zenny proceeds to sing the collingwood football club song..*  ahem.. actually its ironic, i don't really care about football at all (but i respect that other people do).. but as soon as ANZAC day comes round, i just have to know who won the  urlLink Collingwood vs. Essonden  match.. its been burnt into me as a child that this is the only game that matters (even more so than the grand final).. and since i was a child, its "COME ON THE PIES!".. just to get up my dads nose, and ironically enough, i can also rub it up your nose too vitriol *smiles*
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      .. with lots of flowers... yeah flowers *smiles*
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
       Ha ha ha!! That is it exactly, only in Jube terminology. *grin* The sentiment is exactly correct. People don't  want  to have to move, they don't  want  to get off their fat arses to see if there's somewhere better to go, something better to do. They just want what they've got to be the best. And they're so scared that it isn't that they are prepared to go to great lengths to ensure that they feel nice and secure about their apparently thrilling, perfect lives. That is why television tells us we're doing the right thing... to keep the flock of sheep in line, to keep the masses perpetually believing their patch is just as good as the next, when really it stinks. Of course, there are always a few brave souls who bother getting off their patch and finding a new one. Sight unseen, it could be a big clod of dirt, but at least it's something new. In time, they might grow their own grass, some really, really green stuff. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      now thats just sad isn't it.. *sigh* its the grass is always greener thing isnt it.. but in an mtv world like ours, no one wnats to leave the grass they have to check out the other good grass, so they just make themselves believe that the grass they have is the best, why would they want to go try that other grass.. 
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
       Knowing you are who you are and how they expect you to react, a lot of people probably want to hear from you how miserable life in the city is, how you're  not  glad you moved, so that they can feel better about their own petty existence. If you aren't enjoying Melbourne, then where they live  must  be better, mustn't it? So, they pester you about what's wrong with Melbourne. A lot of people my fiancee knows pull the same stunt; they  want  to hear that the city is a filthy, trashy, miserable place to justify their prejudices against it. Just as a lot of people I know from the city want to know why I visit the country. Because they too have a prejudice, this time against the no-frills, grotty, uncivilised rural banality.  
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Since my move to Melbourne, I've had alot of ppl ask me the question  "So, are you glad you moved?"  And this question always seems to come right after they have asked  "Are you working yet?" , which I am by the way.  I find it interesting, and heres my theory on it.  I don't think ppl thought i would actually go through with the move. I don't think they thought i would actually go, and now that I'm here.. they are waiting for me to run back to Shepparton with my tail between my legs.. I could be wrong, but there you have it.  Oh and I have no intention of going back any time soon. I like it here, I've succeeded it getting away from the small town crap that was pissing me off, and am actually out of the rut i was in and enjoying myself. Don't get me wrong, I loved shepparton, and still do. But if you have to much of something you like, you'll learn to hate it, so i got out for a while.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I do believe Vitriol and myself have neglected this site, when it has a potential of greatness. I realised this when I had a conversation with Vitriol the other evening about "Mind vs. Heart" conversation. Which would have been something great to discuss on here. I think thats the trouble, so many of conversations are spontanious and there for never make it to this site.  I am going to have to think about a solution to this dilema..   perhaps just posting transcripts of our conversations here might be the  solution.. so to start the ball rolling.. here is the above (edited only to protect others) "Mind vs. Heart" conversation, enjoy:  J: i think its funny how the brain and the rest argue.. its a funny interesting thing.. J: we are very interesting creatures.. V:  Yes, yes it is. I'm not so sure it's often all that funny... perhaps in hindsight. But certainly interesting, i have not doubt.  J: well not funny 'ha ha' but funny 'weird' J: i think its amazing the things ppl will tolerate, and ignore, .. and how we become blind in particular situations J: the human brain V:  That is true. Although, I must admit, I never really found many of my feelings strange. I always knew what they meant, and why they were occurring. Perhaps that was why I could control them more easily. And you're right; the logic in us will often revile the very person our 'heart' adores because of how they behave or act. It seems a constant battle.  J: yeah never find them strange.. but its just something i was thinking about just now..  i think its what makes ppl do things they always thought them selves never capable of..  J: i dunno.. its mind vs. heart V:  A friend of mine has a theory; that there are 'head' people and there are 'heart' people. Some are somewhat in-between. Or, to be a little clearer, there are degrees and extremes of both. I, for example, would be a 'head' person, because my logical mind is dominant over my desire and passion. Passionate people, however, lose much of their ability to be logical, especially when their passion is particularly ignited.  V:  Hehe... I'm glad I got that in first. *smirk*  J: yes i'd definatly say that i'm probably a heart person.... well swaying more on that side anyway.. but your right, it tends to be only in the moment.. i'll push away the head part and ignore it..  gets me into trouble *laugh* J: though i think i've grown from that somewhat  V:  To me, 'head' people often seem a little colder, harsher, and selfish than 'heart' people. Although far less self-effacing in their tendencies, and a little more honest about their true intentions, because they intrinsically (logically) -know- what they are. Heart people, I think, find themselves in trouble and in pain because they lack control over the situation, but ironically that's because they've invested far more in it.  J: see i agree and dissagree.. or more to the point correct somthing on that commeny.. heart ppl (well myself anyway) know what they are too..  and in the moment we choose to either ignore the logic or go for the "oh fuck it, i'll think about it later, and just enjoy the moment" heart choise.. J: hense why heart ppl tend to be racked with guilt and worry about the effects our choices have on ourselves and other ppl V:  Well that's something I've always suspected, actually. That perhaps 'head' and 'heart' people both know darn well what's going to happen, but 'head' people see themselves as being able to cooly assert themselves and make the 'right' decision, whereas 'heart' people tend to take a punt, or risk pain in order to experience the pleasure of the moment.  J: yeah.. heart ppl risk more for the chance that regardless of all the logical and most probbable reason that it won't turn out for the best.. that it just might turn out just wonderful V:  Yeah, but how often does that happen? That's my rationale. I reckon everyone begins as a 'heart' person, but only those who learn from their mistakes become 'head' people. *smirk*  J: i think thats somtimes the case.. J: but thats makes it sound like heart ppl regret there decisions.. J: i may look back on somthing and say.. "ok maybe thay wasn't the best idea as it didn't go anywhere".. but i don't regret it.. whats done is done.. hehe... and atleast i had fun in that moment.. a head person wouldn't have had the moment at all J: head ppl need a little heart or they won't ever take chances.. J: every relationship is a risk.. "should i or shouldn't i ask for her phone number?"... shes is brilliant and beautful and amazing, and chances are wiill shoot me down.. logically she's tell me to rack off.. but what if.? V:  Sometimes 'heart' people do regret their decisions. Sometimes 'head' people regret them, too. Mainly because they've been a right-old prick * .  J: yeah.. *ahem* J: :) V:  That's also true... 'heart' people do tend to take the bull by the horns, so to speak, more often than 'head' people, because they're willing to accept the risk to get the reward.  V:  Hehe... yeah, I thought you'd like that one ** .  J: sorry, couldn't help it.. ***  J: but that also goes back to the whole blind thing.. heart ppl tend to be the ones that become blind..  J: though in that case it wasn't blindness it was nieveity ****  J: how ever you spell it J: ah well..  V:  It's like anything; there are advantages and disadvantages to both. Sometimes it's better to be a 'head' person, sometimes it's better to be a 'heart' person.  J: yeah and i think we do swing both ways..  V:  Yep. Like I said, there's degrees. And 'heart' people will, in some circumstances act like 'head' people, and vice versa. There's no overriding rule, but I think most people 'tend' toward one or the other.  J: i find that when i'm attracted to a more  "head" person... i tend to go all heart.. but when its another heart person.. i'm probably more "head".. as if i go heart too it could turn out really nasty V:  Well, that's right. Two 'head' people are going to be picky, methodical and cold toward one another. They'll be trying to second-guess and work out the other person's objective from day one. Two 'heart' people will abandon everything they own and desire for the chance to be together as often as possible, even if the whole thing breaks down in a few weeks.  J: well i found that i think its cos with the heart ppl who fall for me.. my head goes.. what if i don't fall for you as much as you fall for me.. thats not fair on you.. i cna't hurt you.. its strange V:  I know what you mean. It's as if you can see 'em coming a mile away, and think "shit, I'll have to be nice and open with this person because if I'm not, they're liable to get hurt, because they're all heart". Which might also infer that they have no trouble abandoning everything to make your life hell for a while, also.  J: yeah.. J: like when partically drops there whole life to please me.. freaks me out.. that much heart is scray.. i mean geez.. be your own person please.. V:  Hehe... indeed.  J: *smiles*  * Vitriol and I once had issues, we actually stopped talking to each other due to these issues for like two years ** but where over it now, and better friends than we ever were *** and now joke about the situation **** and use it as a reference in our dicussions hehe.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Well, let's get this ball rolling, shall we? Now that I know that my posts here will be duly responded to, I find it far more encouraging to write something in the first place. All these blogs, so much pressure! I really find it hard to think of enough interesting things to say. Without, of course, referring to the work or inspiration of others.  For the moment, I have little more to say than bravo to Jubilation for having brought this thing back to life, resurrecting it from its slow and unkind death over the last few months. But now that its spark has been rekindled, the onus is now on both of us to maintain it. Eh, Jube? 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Just to start the ball rolling, I decided to sift through some old logs and see what I could find, the below was the result.  Sun Oct 20 00:26:17 2002 V:   So... bitter, eh? What brought that on? You've been some other mood for months and months now.  J: bitter? J: did i sound bitter in that comment.. i didn't mean too..  V:   No, on your page... your mood is 'bitter'. It was something far more neutral last time.  J: oh ok.. yeah i'm not bitter any more actually.. apparently it as a bit of a missunderstanding in the end that brought that mood on.. V:   Okay. *raises eyebrow*  J: and about it being another mood for ages and ages.. its not really acuarate you see.. i don't change it very often, because its one of the the things my mother takes note off.. so i tend to pick a happy mood for her to read hehe J: i shall change my mood now actually, thanks for pointing that out to me J: my mother will start to worry if i leave it like that for too long V:  Haha... of course she will. And some of your friends. You're not, after all, a very bitter person, all in all. I'm sure if I had bitter as my mood few would be surprised, but I, for example, would expect something a little more... chipper, from your good self.  J: oh for someone as chipper as myself, i'm pretty miserable alot.. heh V:  Haha... I suppose that's true.  J: i'm still rather bitter about alot of things, and lack faith in humanity.. all this chipperness and nice out look on life takes a shit load of effort on my part J: i have to consiously  make my self happy alot of the time, which probably sounds strange.. but yeah i really work hard to fnid tghe good in things, and try to enjoy everything the best i can J: its hard work heh V:  That's good. And I do know what you mean. I'm pessimistic about the world for the same reason you're optimistic about it. We both want the world to be good: you expect it to be. I don't. I'm not sure either of us is really right, and I don't think it's particularly easy for either of us to be made happy by the world, either.  J: yeah.. its not that i expect it to be.. its more of a "well i'm gunna damn well make the best of it" V:  Well, good call, I say.  J: plus i do't think its up to anybody else or the world around me to make me happy..  J: only i can make me happy.. hense my motto "choose to be happy".. otherwise i'd jsut be miserable all the damn time J: plus i try not to expect great things.. its in the little things.. like good deeds, and snow globes, and a saxaphone playing under the concert hall down in south bank ecoing in the night  throught the beautiful lights of melbourne.. J: :) V:  Fair enough. I think my motto would be "choose unpredictability". That way nobody expects me to be happy, nor do they always think I'm morbid. I can just deal with things as they come, and people who don't like me can get fucked.  J: good call J: i have a simialr thing with in my philosophy as well.. V:  Ahh, yes. The little things. I think I expect more from the little things than the big. Big, blustery events don't get my attention. It's the subtle, slight things that attract my attention.  J: its not about other ppl, its about our selves.. V:  Uhuh. Besides, I don't give a stuff about many other people anyway, *grin* so it fits well with my self-absorbed existence.  J: yeah iits all in the little things i think.. you gotta stop and notice things once in a while.. be like a child and remember to look up.. adults do'nt look up.. we forget too.. J: children are the first ones in a theatre show to notice the dome ops way above them.. they point and point till fnially the adults look to see what they are pointing at J: i always try and remember to look up when ever i'm in a new place now.. V:  *laughs* That's cute. It must also be satisfying knowing that somebody appreciates what you do, too. Without, that is, just looking at the program and going "oh, yeah. The techs. Good work."  J: well i dunno.. i also like the idea that well we are doing a good job if they don't know we are there at all, as its all part of the magic.. J: your not ment to think about us or know we are there.. as thats all part of the point..  J: but every time a kid notices, i always smile.. its just nice V:  I suppose that's true. It's one of those 'only a good job -if- nobody notices' sort of things, yeah?  J: yeah thats the one
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well lookie here, look what is working again. Finally a working vitriol and jubilation, shock horror. Hopefully interesting a witty conversations to follow.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       My dear Zenny.tech, I have acquired the following possibilities for our catching up to watch  The Chronicles of Riddick : on the 29th of August, the mighty Bombers will play the not-so-mighty Bulldogs during the day. That means that I can hang around until you finish work and we can catch whatever session, wherever, and go from there.  However, it did also occur to me that you may have meant  Saturday  night. If this is the case, then our options expand, significantly. For example, tomorrow night Essendon play the very-mighty Port Adelaide, and though the game won't finish until about 11pm, I presume you won't finish work until then anyway. If this happens to be convenient, let me know ASAP so that I can change my schedule.  Otherwise, on the 7th, Essendon play Carlton during the day, which makes a night flick a pretty good option. I might have to kill some time in the city but hey, that's really not so bad. On the 21st, the Bombers play Sydney, in Sydney, which makes the weekend entirely mine. Unfortunately, it will also mean I will need to commute both ways, which stings the pocket somewhat. It can be arranged, but I'd need to know in advance to save my pennies.  Feel free to let me know which one suits you best, and we'll go from there.  V. 
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       With the aformentioned title affronting the latest Herald-Sun movie review, I was inclined to think it might receive a bad score. Although not entirely flattering, the reviewer, Leigh Paatsch, admits that although it's not indie, arthouse or anything remotely tasteful, there is a lot to like about  The Chronicles of Riddick .  I must admit, my favourite line of his review was "His Armie-esque line delivery might well make him sound like someone who enjoys telling young children that their favourite pet has just died - but it fits the bill here." What's  not  to like! The main difference between a film like this and, say,  Troy  is that the latter is based on a brilliant literary masterpiece, and so when it degrades itself by presenting barely B-grade schlock, it comes off as a disappointment. I never thought a sequel to  Pitch Black  would be anything but, so I can go in knowing what to expect.  Perhaps the best news: "Some five years down the track, Riddick still has a knack for getting stranded on far-flung and forbidding (sic) planets, but no longer has to carry around that deadweight entourage of intergalactic castaways." All right! Now we don't have to satisfy every demographic; just the Vin Diesel demographic. I'm lookin' forward to it. 
     
    
</post>



<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From   The Chronicles of Vitriol and Jubilation   at vitrioljubilation.blogspot.com  With the aformentioned title affronting the latest Herald-Sun movie review, I was inclined to think it might receive a bad score. Although not entirely flattering, the reviewer, Leigh Paatsch, admits that although it's not indie, arthouse or anything remotely tasteful, there is a lot to like about  The Chronicles of Riddick .  I must admit, my favourite line of his review was "His Armie-esque line delivery might well make him sound like someone who enjoys telling young children that their favourite pet has just died - but it fits the bill here." What's  not  to like! The main difference between a film like this and, say,  Troy  is that the latter is based on a brilliant literary masterpiece, and so when it degrades itself by presenting barely B-grade schlock, it comes off as a disappointment. I never thought a sequel to  Pitch Black  would be anything but, so I can go in knowing what to expect.  Perhaps the best news: "Some five years down the track, Riddick still has a knack for getting stranded on far-flung and forbidding (sic) planets, but no longer has to carry around that deadweight entourage of intergalactic castaways." All right! Now we don't have to satisfy every demographic; just the Vin Diesel demographic. I'm lookin' forward to it.
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If John Howard is still Prime Minister after the next election, I'm boycotting this country until he isn't. As soon as I have enough money to live somewhere else, I will. The guy is just fucking everything up. In fact, ditto for a Cabinet that includes  Downer and Ruddock as well.  I don't have the time or the energy to go into it - and I can't find a tie-in with Britney Spears, so Zenny won't read it anyway - but there is something very, very wrong about the Federal Government at the moment. Very wrong indeed. Not that Labour's a great deal better, but they have to be better than a Howard Government. It might be a Green vote this year.
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Show 130 this afternoon. When all this is over, I'm going to become a florist. Perhaps a busker with my unicycle. I'll learn to fire twirl at the same time, and travel europe. Go to Paris and just curise around. Perhaps I'll stay here and and get a day job. Have real weekends. Go the pub, drink and go bowling. Beer and skittles. Yeah.
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I killed one of my favourite characters today. Dead. And unlike others I won't mention, he won't be resurrected by any greater power, or by his own hand. So it's a bit of a shame, really. But, he does take his dignity with him, and spills a lot of blood on the way. In fact, the whole chapter's about blood; it's everywhere, and there's more to come.  It is a strange feeling finally saying goodbye to a quality character. Especially one with such uncompromising principles, one who has few contradictions and has lived his life as an exemplar for all he stands for. Other characters won't be so hard to say goodbye to, because they're flawed. And though he has his flaws, he does what he says, and says what he means. So having really done nothing wrong, he still suffers. And that's the tragedy.  But, tragedy is great, and so die he shall.
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My good man,  Once again you have, with the most direct appraisal, managed to lift my own spirits with your words of admiration and insight. Indeed, having had Shakespeare high on my own Mantle of Idolatry, I understand completely your admiration of the man. I must admit, even I was not aware that he had completed many of his 'great' works at such a tender age. It leaves one wondering what tremendous fortitude and perception of mind possessed young Shakespeare in his early days.  Indeed, your own assessment of his virtues seems all the more remarkable as you indicate not having done a great deal of reading on the matter. Most come to admire Shakespeare through his  works  rather than his life. I suspect you have a great deal of admiring yet to do, my friend, if your respect for his talent is akin to my own. He, ultimately, is the soul whose talent inspires me the most, and I must acknowledge my granting him more esteem than even the great J.R.R. Tolkien, for though the latter was surely a great creator, there are no parallels to Shakespeare anywhere in the world.  Consider that he has managed with the English language something that no speaker of either our, or any other language has mastered before; the use of almost all its forms. Prose, poetry, beat and time, syllable rhythm, allusion, allegory, abstraction... he is a master of them all. It is all the more bewildering to understand how he could have, even within an entire lifetime, come to understand and utilise such a vast array of wonderous linguistic tools with such skill.  I found myself once again feeling the utmost empathy for your plight of ambition versus realistic appraisal. It has been a subject of almost limitless study in the spare moments I find myself meditating on the complexities of life, and though I have devoted hours upon hours to the thought, I am really no closer to finding an answer. I can only suggest that there needs to be an appropriate measure of two things to succeed: ambition and temperance. I think that there is no harm in having vast aspirations, and this is a healthy state, provided it is measured with a temperate perspective.  In choosing the term 'temperance', I am alluding to several things. Some modesty of potential and talent, obviously, but also a keen and self-assessing forethought that contemplates carefully what are the realistic boundaries in the world, not of what individuals or even insitutions set as limits, but what  are  the  real  limits. Within these, somewhere, is the answer. I often find myself swept up with wild ideas of challenging many notions in my chosen field; literature. I pursue that goal with fervour, and believe myself possessed of great knowledge in that field, for someone of my age.  Yet, for every flight of fancy, for every thought that the world is simple, that with the right 'stuff' anything can be achieved, I must steady myself with the reality that it might not. That any endeavour, even if my thoughts of boundaries are realistic and my belief in my own potential is true, I must still work very hard for what I look to achieve, and I must temper my own ambition and talent with some view of the realistic world around me. At some time - and this will break my heart - I will have to compromise with an editor, a publisher or an agent.  I might sacrifice a character, a chapter, a perfect phrase, because it is too complex, unnecessary, or simply not intriguing enough to the average reader to justify its place in the die-hard, cut-throat market that is publishing. Just as most artistic markets, including music, film and the tactile arts are just as severe and daunting. As much as  I  know literature, and as masterful as my work might be, at the end of the day, if it does not sell... what is the use of its quality? Of course, no matter the consequence I will still be content with my work, and this is the sole fact that keeps me positive during my questioning self-absorbtion, but there is an audience out there I must satisfy. And unfortunately, those with the cash aren't necessarily those with the stamina to work through a masterpiece.  Let's face it, most people in the modern world don't understand Shakespeare. They know who he is, that he is a master and most will have 'studied' him at school at some stage. But few understand his work. This is primarily because of the language barriers a few hundred years will provide, but nevertheless the complexity of his work seems to strain the mental facilities of many modern readers. Why pick up a book and slog through an archaic dialect when you can flick a button and watch half an hour of Big Brother Uncut instead?  And that is what motivates me; to create something that is challenging, but accessible. I don't pretend to want to be the next Shakespeare or Tolkien, mainly because I would hope my own work would stand alone, in its own unique way. But I think the essence of achievement is to  be  inspired, to look at the Shakespeares and Tolkiens and Satrianis and Hendrixs and Hirds and Corgans and Nietzsches of the world and say "that person motivates me", or "I am putting my hand up to be admired as they are admired by me", because that is the ultimate reward for such endeavours.  But temperance and ambition must go hand in hand, I think. Always look to the heavens, but be careful not to trip for a lack of looking where you're going. They stumble, who haste too fast [Romeo and Juliet]. I am constantly amazed at how simple some 'complex' things in the world actually are, and how complex some 'simple' things turn out to be. But to compare one's self to a Shakespeare or an Einstein is to compare one's self with the greatest that humanity has had to provide. This is where some temperance is required, to realise that not all achievers are prodigies, and not all prodigies are achievers. Pace yourself, my friend, think carefully and with wisdom in what you do, and the rewards you seek shall be yours.  I have seen you develop your musical talent with what I would consider amazing speed and dedication. Nor did it occur in a vacuum; it took shape around a healthy social life and University studies. But be careful not to assume too much knowledge, or neglect ideas that might conflict with those you already have. Nobody can see all ends, or the shape of all things, no matter their study or intelligence. This is a lesson I have myself spent an inordinately long time learning.  There are many lessons yet to be learned, by each and every one of us. There are some that require more learning than others [refer previous posts on 'disciplinary solutions'], in matters that may not be artistic or academic. But I would suggest that with a good seventy-odd years to go, you don't need to start cramming yet. Temperance, my friend, temperance. Extremity is a short-term ally indeed; it  never, ever  lasts the distance.  With respect in kind,  Vitriol
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I awoke this day, as every other day, listening to the classical station on my FM radio. It is, without a doubt currently the only way I am exposed to any culture in our world. Where I used to fill my mind with the views, images and ideas of the television, I now have replaced that medium&nbsp;with insightful commentaries and discussions from prestigious individuals from around the world. The topics range from mainly music - since it is a classical and operatic radio station - through to&nbsp; extrapolating about the thoughts, feelings and motivations behind the pieces creation. This is the side that I am mostly interested in. Since I find it remarkably dull (partly due to my own laziness) to head to the library and dig up a book on the legendary figures that have, and are, shaping our world, this serves me as an adequate portion of culture that I may digest at my leisure.  &nbsp;  This morning I was awoken to a discussion about William Shakespeare. Having aspirations of my own to someday become a great writer the discussion immediately piqued my interest. From my bed where I silenced my mongrel of&nbsp;a dog with a sharp rebuke and pricked up my ears to hear what was being said in the conversation.  &nbsp;  The discussion began with the shows host, an aged woman whose name I can never remember -&nbsp;even though she states it quite consistently at particular parts of the day - and a director currently working with the Bill Shakespeare theatre and operatic company.  &nbsp;  The Host began by questioning whether and if so, how much, influence did Shakespeares personal experiences with life have in his writing?&nbsp;Just to note,&nbsp;this is not an essay about this exact topic as it is mostly concerned with Shakespeare. I only included it to be informative and set the scene. Firstly, here is some info on the prodigious man himself:  &nbsp;  Shakespeare was married at an early age to a woman eight years his elder: Anne Hathaway. By the time he was 21 he had already completely some of the greatest stories/poetry of his day, that continued to last until the very contemporary era we now reside in. He was remarked to have unimaginable vision into the motivations and behaviours of humans - perhaps the makings of a great psychologist - and so exploited his awareness in his stories. Now the discussion wasn't about the ins and outs of his life, but these particular points were brought up and I wished to highlight them here.&nbsp; &nbsp;  What I was fascinated with was that at such an early age, he possessed such amazing skill. He was an artist with words and so painted a picture in your mind with his vivid vocabulary, articulate artistry, and the rudimentary romantic exploitations of his experience with, and understanding of, human behaviour.  &nbsp;  Until this very morning, I did not realise that this man was to be a new idol for me. Placed upon the pedistool that already contains the world-renowned Joe Satriani and Jimi Hendrix, J.R.R Tolkien shall now sit William Shakespeare. That mantle is not easily given in my books, but there are several good reasons and they shall be extrapolate below.  &nbsp;  Firstly, the man understood people. Being someone who is interested - and sometimes even obsessed - with the reasons and workings of humans myself, I find that perhaps I have someone here I can learn from and be influenced by. Of course I will not take his words in the medical context but more as a useful guide to facilitate my imagination when it comes to writing and manipulating humans in my stories. This leads me to my second reason.  &nbsp;  We are both writers. Well, I shall humble myself and say that Shakespeare was a legendary writer and I his boot-shine. The mans very spittle would turn to gold before it struck the cobblestone roads of 15th century England. I embellish about his fortunes here in the contemporary era but I don't think life was as peachy in Shakespeares time. No matter. This man experienced and understood two aspects of my life that give me great joy, exuberance and purpose; writing and psychology. Had Shakespeare played the lute he would probably be numero uno on my life of worthy people to admire.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp; Thinking about&nbsp;Shakespeare led me into another&nbsp;stream of pondering.&nbsp;I am amazed at the early age upon which the legendary in our world seem to be unleashed. Einstein at 28 conceived the theory of relativity; Shakespeare at 21 had the hearts of people in their throats with his intricate writing style, combining poetry timing and format with a plethora of humanistic behaviours and motivations to perpetuate his imaginative tales.  &nbsp;  This led to think about myself and my aims at being recognised in the world, at making my own renown, something that I have spoken about for some time now...  &nbsp;  I suppose I have always been ambitious. I don't aim to compete through conscious reasoning, but my heart tends to adrenalise a drive in me when it comes to such competition. It is not just in proving my superiority, but also in wishing for and achieving success&nbsp;does this drive become highly noticeable. I bring this up because I feel my heart has more ambition than my mind does skill. When I look to these legendary figures my ambition begins to soar; seeing a peak that it instantly wishes to climb; accepting the&nbsp;challenge of the gauntlet thrown at my feet. But I am dreaming. I&nbsp;have realised that to go out every day and seek to become legendary is absurd.  &nbsp;  A legend is like an anomaly in that it is rare and product of many different systems interacting and coexisting together at that very moment. A minute shift in the balance and it is no more. It is a whisper on a mountain peak, that if a wind blows too strong it is gone and its chance at being heard is lost forever. The world is my mountain peak, and I feel I am the whisper in the wind. These, I guess youd could call them insights, do not give me much comfort. Though my mind realises they are probably very true and indeed likely, my heart cannot give up the glory of such legendary ambitions. To place it in perspective, it is the Atlas of ambitions, so strong it could support the world upon its shoulders, as the great god himself was believed to. How can I sequester such power? My mind must be a shadow in its strength if I am driven by such very basic instincts. I am so very young. I think here is where wisdom teaches you that being aware of a problem and understanding it are very different to living with its understandings and the knowledge that accompanies it.  &nbsp;  So quickly did this letter change from being about reverence to one of self-contemplation. Perhaps it is important to question the very difficulties and disagreements in our lives at the moment whence they arose, lest they be forgotten and ignored so to with the lesson they accompany. I feel there are many lessons to go and I am behind in my class. Time to do some cramming.  &nbsp;  Respectfully yours,  &nbsp;  DisSenter  
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Without attempting to make this a bigger issue than it already seems to have become, I shall respond to what I see as a couple of particularly obvious contradictions in the previous post. Once again, these are not an effort to make this a bone of contention, I must merely raise these points for the sake of posterity. I will no longer be advocating an abandonment of said statement, for if it has its place, then it has its place. As previously stated, I can only comment on what I see or hear.  In regard to  intent , I would repeat that my previous point was about purpose, not intent. I took no offense from the 'cheers moment' nor from its particular use, for as you rightly say, it is part of your 'repertoire'. I was, however, looking at the reason for its use in the first place, and its actual purpose, not the particular intent of any given example.  I will not demean myself by engaging in the 'parallel' between said statement and anything said during sex. The two are as unlike as spitting and taking a piss, so I cannot see where the point is served.  As for excitement, I will concur that at times stupid things are said. I will not pretend that I haven't said stupid things, and certainly wouldn't even dream of considering that Soz, for example, hasn't said his fair share either. The difference, I might point out, is that said stupidities are not repeated after the fact. At least, not by the originator of the comment. That would be acting as a glutton for punishment. So again, I'm not sure how this draws into the discussion.  As for the ever-intriguing Leo Mu Bai, I would heartily concur that he makes a mockery of speech in all its forms, and is as crude as... well, anything else you could think of. The difference, however, is that his statements are, more often than not, amusing. Leo says 'spanktacular', and a carload bursts out laughing. At least that satisfies criteria #1. The point about crudity is not the issue, either. I am regularly crude and uncouth in my speech; and not because I don't have to be. I have an admirable repertoire of my own, of perfectly sound linguistic and grammatical statements that are appropriate for any occasion. But do I see the sense in returning to 'the pretentious speaking habits o f15th-Century aristocracy'? Fuck no. There is a difference.  Now, of all the guff that came before, I believe the last point has the most merit. I think you could have justified its use simply by saying 'my brother inspired me with its use, and I found it a good conversation starter'. That's about all it is, but it would have satisfied me. I'm not sure there's really a point to the arguments laid out prior to that.  Now, as a conclusion, I'll say that in regard to this pet statement, I don't really care whether you use it or not. I don't like it; fine. As long as you do, continue to use it. However, the slightly more disturbing aspect of your response was its touch of bitterness. I would suggest that there is a distinct difference between positive criticism and 'criticism'. My intention was to outline something I thought you could improve. That should not be an indictment on me, and I would suggest that you could use some like suggestions from time to time.  I outlined in a rational fashion the reasons for my having brought the issue up, and I'm not sure that there was much in the way of positive response, except for the one paragraph that mattered; the origin of your statement. For someone who prides themselves in structured and logical responses to argument, I think you may have allowed yourself a little too much digression from the subject.  Again, and this  is  important; I say these things not because I want to irritate or condemn you, but only because I look forward to positive discussion, and analysis of complementary ideas. I would ask you to think carefully about the intent of statements before assuming they are detrimental. My last two posts have had one primary goal: to bring to light something I felt might help you improve your respectability.  Yes, the statement might be an icebreaker. Yes, some people might find it amusing. But from where I sit, it might also alienate or distance some people from your otherwise jovial and good-natured banter. From my perspective, it jarrs with your persona, and as I said before, your usual wit and intellect. That is the point; I wouldn't want to see that tarnished. But, that said, it is your right to say what the hell you like, and I certainly won't stop you. All I wanted to do was to show it from another perspective. That done, I shall withdraw.  P.S. Having taken some of your own good advice, I have changed 'djinn' to 'ujinn' [ujinni; ujinaen]. I was tempted to go with Gjinn, but the 'g' really wants to be a back-of-the-mouth consonant, which grates with its intended flow. The 'u' adds another syllable, but I can deal with that.
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its not that I even give a toss what anyone thinks about my use of the term, Cheers big-ears, pap smears and engineers, but something has to be said about the rebuke concerning the terms intent. Simply put: there&nbsp;was no intent, apart from it being something said during a cheers moment. An expression, see also: to express, in the English Dictionary.  &nbsp;  This is but one of many examples of situations where a term has been heard or conceived and found some personality of its own amidst the speaker. There are many examples where this takes place and is usually found to be charming or part of the persons character. In other cases, the term can occur because of an explosive outburst for reason of hilarity, excitement or for the sake of being ridiculous. The difference between the casual hybrid word and the term that is used constantly in recurring situations is subjective and dependent upon the speaker. I think the use of my term metamorphosed from one, into another form, of term intent. Before I begin the explanation of how the term arose and its personal significance I shall provide some examples about how and why these strange term amalgams come about.  &nbsp;  Sometimes in life we are so excited we cannot help but blurt out something stupid. For example, when that sexy girl we have been eyeing off for ages confronts us, always hoping to talk to her but never getting the chance. One day, strutting up to you she grabs you balls and says, Lets fuck! and all you can do, apart from drool on her tits is say, DuuhhoohOkaybefore she drags your sorry carcass to the bedding room.  &nbsp;  Okay, thats a little rich and probably an unrealistic example. Lets just say she comes up to simply talk to you. The first thing that happens is you go numb, forget yours and her name, get sweaty palms and can think of nothing to say. Even the simplest reply of Hello eludes your mind. Instead you probably say something completely fucking stupid, making yourself look like a bigger dick than you already are. Youre drowning without a life jacket, my pedigree chum. Excitement can sometimes cloud your better judgement for word choice. This is not a reason to use the said term, just an explanation as to how it came about: from sheer spontaneity.  &nbsp;  Yet another example of saying something stupid at a usually serious situation is during sex. What did the term Im coming! get coined from? Does it imply the man/woman is actually arriving or departing a said location or rejoin elsewhere? Of course not! The guy/girl is blowing their load, so to speak  hows that for style and grace, B? The statement is completely stupid and explains nothing that needs explaining. If youre excreting vaginal fluid or semen your partner will see, no need to shout about it. In fact, some of the most stupid statements have been spoken during or about sex. Do they need a reason? Of course not, its an expression.  &nbsp;  If we are looking for some more examples of ridiculous sayings we need look no further than to our own Chewwy. Leo Mu Bi, master of the green desktop, has many strange sayings without much clear point or meaning. Some examples include, spanktacular, fucktacular, cockspank, fuckeyed, etc, etc and their derivatives. These sayings can be seen as offensive or ridiculous, but we tolerate them because Leo is cool, and these outbursts generally offer amusement for those present. They dont mean anything half they time; they are just something that comes out when Leo is excited. If they occur frequently they becomes catch phrases for the said individual. At this point they move into the realm of being a characteristic or particular feature by which we recognise an individual.  &nbsp;  As can be seen, ridiculous sayings occur in normal, everyday life. They can occur because of exciting or nerve racking, humorous and even ridiculous situations presenting themselves, at which the lack of sensible thought generally overrides the logically sound, articulate and appropriate response. In this light we can imply that strange sayings do not always require a reason to occur or recur. They are just some individuals way of expressing themselves. They werent intended (in some cases) to be humorous or to offend or even rhyme, but if they do we take them as doubly rewarding when we hear them. They make us tear up and howl with laughter over their strange, yet appealing nature. Why should we silence such unabashed expressions? Should we all return to the pretentious speaking habits of the 15th century aristocracy? I think not. We have reached a level in the English language where slang and hybrid words are becoming increasingly tolerated. Personally, I am aware of the undertones of allowing such activity, but the individual(s) in question here are not out to challenge the English language.  &nbsp;  Now, it is time to explain my use of the term in question. I acquired it many years ago  about 5 or more now  from my brother, Zoran. Initially it was used as an icebreaker between people. Every time it was uttered it would provide an enquiry such as, What?! Doing so gave me free entry to openly discuss with those who may have, until such time, remained isolated and quietly free of conversation during the course of the gathering. There isnt a time I can remember when I used the term and didnt get a smile or recognition for it. In this light, it seems my ridiculous and mildly offensive term was gaining me esteemed social renown and recognisable and well-needed attention among potential new-friends. Why then would I cease its application? I wouldnt.  &nbsp;  In time, the word just became the norm. I grew comfortable with its use and I was highly aware of its people pulling powers. It is more likely that the strange and the weird that gathers our attention in this world, not the straight, narrow and direct. Also, I believe when you use something for so long it begins to form a part of your personality. The term as I mentioned earlier, has been in my repertoire for so long that it wouldnt be a night out  to me  if I didnt use it. In the end, it makes me happy, draws a smile from people rather than a greaser and thats good enough of a reason to me for continuing its use. Those that have further problems with the term can refer to my toll free complaints line: 1800-How-Does-Fuck-Off-Sound.  &nbsp;  Cheers,  &nbsp;  *G*  
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The time has come, I'm afraid, to bring to light an issue of style. I can no longer allow this travesty of tawdryness to continue. The issue has existed for some time, and my subtle and underhanded attempts to bring it to light have failed. Therefore, I now deem it time for more significant action, after which the user(s) of such phrases will be well-aware of my feelings on the matter, and can act as they deem appropriate. The point at issue is as follows:  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Cheers Big-ears, Papsmears and Engineers...   Now, to the  casual  observer, this might seem like some simple, blokey pub-inspired colloquialism with very little or no particular meaning. However, I must bring to light a certain few questions I have regarding it, and the first of these is purpose. What the  hell  is it's purpose? As I shake my head, I have to presume it has none, in which case it seems to me a gross waste of time to bother memorising, much less to repeat every time the glasses go a-tinkling.   Or , it could have one of three possible purposes: 1. To be funny 2. To be offensive, or 3. To be clever.  In response to the first, I doubt most people who hear this statement made would immediately laugh, unless they were so inebriated that pretty much any nonsensical schlock or verbal defecation would send them into peals of laughter anyway, which is more an indictment on the statement than a benefit. I have to conclude that it is, quite simply, not even remotely amusing. So let's move on to the second point.  If the statement is meant to be offensive, then I'm not sure on what basis it makes its effort. It contains a pretty lame put-down, a medical term and a common profession, which don't really add up to me as the sort of thing to put anyone out. Though, I will say that if any of the three points above are to apply, this is the one. For  fuck's  sake, a vaginal examination testing for cancer is not the sort of thing I want to be thinking about as I'm downing some amber fluid, or any kind of ingestion, to be precise. It's tacky, lame and lacks any class whatsoever. I can only shrug and wonder if that - against any logical reason I might be able to summon - is actually its point after all.  The third point is cleverness. Now, its content is outlined in the previous point, and there's nothing clever about that. The  only  single merit to its name is that it rhymes. It rhymes. Wow. My three-year-old niece can rhyme, and she can't even talk properly. Rhyme is not clever. It is  boring , simplistic crap for children (with a very few particularly clever examples, but this is  not  one of them). After all, why not invent something just as moronic as 'Damn! Ten grams, mammograms and Amsterdam'. Exactly the same sequence, rhyme and pointless content, but just as meaningless, just as schlock, just as retarded.  Now, don't get me wrong; I'm not sure where this one was picked up, and my purpose here was to slam the  saying , not the user(s) of the saying, who may not be aware of how stupid it sounds from a third-party-perspective. I would say the individuals involved are being henceforth alerted of this crime against their style because I would have thought such a crudity well below their otherwise impressive intelligence and wit. But, now that my rather excessive diatribe is finished, the ball is now out there to be abandoned or played as appropriate. Perhaps I've missed the point; but I can only comment on what I see.  And it wouldn't be Vitriolic if it wasn't harsh.  P.S.  Whopping  heft, eh? Damn! Ten gr... wait... Wamma Jamma! Sounds like it the night could have been alternatively entitled "Preview to Heaven, as Burke envisions the place". Now, on the subject of Wamma Jamma, that term is actually warming on me. I propose a  new  toast; sight some heft, raise a glass and state 'Wamma Jamma!' Preferably without drawing the attention of said heft, hehe.
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night a group of us went to Pugg Mahones in Carlton. The crowd consisted of various social groups intermingling, including Soz and I, Leo Mu Bi, Big Leo (named accordingly), Shawn, John, Zenny and Co., and an internet friend of mine, Jen.  &nbsp;  The scene started off with some whopping heft being flung before my eyes.&nbsp;Girl after girl&nbsp;seemed to&nbsp;wear less clothing, revealing tantalizingly more&nbsp;cleavage than the last. Notably and probably most memorable was "red-shirt girl", who had a massive rack on her. Burke, you would have been proud to perve this set of wamma-jamma knockers. Hell, they were so good I invented a new word: Wamma-Jamma.  &nbsp;  Also, worth mentioning was the girl sitting behind my stool. Brown top, dark hair and eyes and a nice rack also. All in all, apart from the whiplash from looking every which way but loose at the gargantuan tits about the place, much drinking, humour and rejoicing was&nbsp;shared.  &nbsp;  Now that the important facts have been stated, lets get on to what took place, shall we?  &nbsp;  As we arrived (Soz. Leo B&nbsp;and I) we found Shawn, Leo F and John looking a little shaky upstairs at the bar. Finding a little nook under the stairs, we began the rounds of drinking. Slowly but surely the boys pumped drink after drink into Soz. Surely, after an hour the corner-booth's table was covered with empty tumblers. One of the druken lads summed the situation up well : "Soz, you have gone one-for-one everyone on this table, man", and that was the truth of it. He had probably had about 6 drinks to everyone else's one. And he looked fucked-up for it. Go Soz.  &nbsp;  An hour after we started drinking, Angela and Kayla, along with Bec and her retarded friend arrived. Soz greeted them all warmly, since he was tipsy at this stage and began to paw all over the girls since he had practically NO control over his body anymore. His dick was now in control. It was an amusing sight to behold. Once again, go Soz!  &nbsp;  Stupidly, I forgot that I was driving and so went to the bar and purchased 3 scotch and cokes, setting me back only $10.50. Score. But, I could only down one since they would have put me easily over the legal limit for driving, forcing me to -reluctantly- give the other two away.  &nbsp;  The night drew on and about and hour and a half into the night, Zenny and Co., arrive.&nbsp;&nbsp;We&nbsp;didn't really share much conversation with the three that tagged along -&nbsp;the couple left so early you could almost pre-ordain that the guy was getting laid that night. Zenny on the other hand, attracted copious amounts of attention with her burgundy corset. Fwahhh! Nice work, girl!  &nbsp;  So, the night eventually drew to a close with the two Leo's and John departing with Shawn since they were&nbsp;considered officially soft. In the end, I had to take Soz out of the bar before he caused any more insane havoc. Those that know the boy realise he is UNCONTROLLABLE when he is drunk. Only woman have the power to subdue the wild lad, so having the masculine equipped merchandise, I failed to secure the authority from Soz I required. This was not surprising&nbsp;because he had drunk over 11&nbsp;glasses of&nbsp;scotch and coke and 2 setruse shots. Oh to behold the woe found&nbsp;in those red, red eyes of his. &nbsp;  Kissing everyone good bye and deciding we were hungry, Soz and I headed to the car to meet the girls at Maccas. As soon as we pull out of the street, the&nbsp;fuzz pull us over. No doubt they heard Soz's loud taunts at the crapness of Coles over Safeway (Che`?) and decided to check upon (us) drunken louts. Blowing in their suspicious contraption (breathaliser), we were waved on our way and so met up with the girl was Maccas without a hitch.  &nbsp;  Eventually we made it home all in one piece and so I would regard that as a good night. I hope we are well on our way to turning it into something like this time last year.&nbsp; The liquor flowed steadily from chilled taps. Smiling faces and hefty busts were all about to greet us. Life was good. May those days continue.  &nbsp;  Cheers Big-ears, Papsmears and Engineers...  &nbsp;  *G*   
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided not to include a title to this one, because the language I would have used may well have put off any potential readers. Whilst enjoying a little Austar with my meal (something I should have thought twice about before actually undertaking), I caught the end of  Astroboy  on Nickelodeon (a show I adored as a kid), which was followed by some guff called  Totally Spies .  Now, there were two significant differences between these two shows; the former included fairly obsolete (though still acceptable) animation, and adequate as it was, they still decided to jazz it up with a completely new ending to the show, complete with new music.  Totally Spies , however, was a flashy, new piece of garbage with cutting-edge animation and flawless appeal. Yet somehow it lacked the more subtle appeal of  Astroboy ; namely, plot.  Well, there was a plot, and here it is: three 'new-age' girls must save the world from disillusioned supermodel who wants to 'modelise' an army to take over the fashion industry that spurned her. The world is in danger why? Because! It's... ummm... well, you know... she speaks with an English accent, dammit! Oh, and the uber-cutelings will lose their delicate features and become... *gasp* ...normal.  That's right, folks. What are we teaching kids today? That you have to save the world if someone threatens to take away your good looks and curvaceous figure. Mmmmm. And of course, the girls are aghast at each other when they discover the results of their 'modelisation' (which seems strange since the victims are ugly, but I found that quite hilariously ironic); they are stuck with freckly skin, red hair, braces and 'stocky' legs. That's right; not  fat , just stocky. But boy, you should see the fucking fuss these chicks put on.  Now, I found this interesting, because their 'robust' legs are not useless, nor flabby; they are in fact, super-strong. But that is of no interest to these uber-cuties, who want their slim, trim, stick-like legs back, because despite their tone and strength, the new ones don't fit into the tiny-tight clothes they enjoy wearing. And then there's the faces; we get heaps of jokes about carrots and the sun glaring off those horrible braces.  *frumple*  I would have thought that any self-respecting individual would resist this kind of obscene crap. But, it's for kids; and what sort of choice do  they  ever get? So sit down kiddies, and enjoy your powder-puff-wielding, lipstick-laser-shooting and x-ray-contact-lens-wearing heroines reinforce the stereotypes of body and physicality that thinking women have been trying to eradicate for decades. Here's to cartoons and uber-cuties!  It is worth noting that  Astroboy 's plot was once again about protecting the little natural wildlife left in his futuristic, robot-inhabited world, and his sister gets a decent piece of the play, using her  wit and intellect  to make suggestions, rather than whipping out a make-up-fucking-holder-thing and using it to vanquish her foes without thought whilst bitching about her 'overly-powerful' legs.  This shit gets me way too worked up. No wonder I don't watch television any more.
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bonjour,  I like the Islam point; I have a cunning idea that I can work  that  definition, ironically, into the Fellis, who can then call their slaves djinni... as a nice touch. After all, I'm trying to make people think, not just hand them some funky tie-ins on a nice silver platter [mbrbrbrrFeistmrbrr].  As for the D&D kids? They can go fuck themselves. I'm not too worried about what a few obsessive wankers are going to think about their favourite critter from Monster Manual XVIII or the Sixteenth-Ed. Fiend Folio. Just like they can't complain if I used the word 'kobold' or 'goblin'. These kinds of words are well-established and were likely pillaged from another source in any case. Usually, as you have discovered, from cultures other than Anglo-Saxon.  And I'm actually modifying the word slightly in any case; djinni is the proper noun in all the other cases; in mine, 'djinn' is the noun, and 'djinni' is a specific plural. Thus, the two words are different, even if slightly. As you can see, I'm not too concerned with 'copyright' or stepping on anyone's toes here.  One word I  did  out-and-out flog, which is acknowledged specifically at the end of my story, is the word  ghola , from Frank Herbert's Dune series (notably the latter two or three). I don't use it in exactly the same fashion, since it is a technological term, but I keep its basic essence, which is along the lines of a construct of resurrected genetic material. My version is magical, and isn't a big part in the story; I just love the word.  My first three chapters are fully edited now, and they kick arse. I'm about four or five chapters from the actual finish, and it's freaking me out. I'm not sure how I'm going to think when it's done, but who the fuck cares? It will be one step closer to masterpiece: complete.  G, it is great to hear you talk about your experiences the way you did. I think it's fantastic that you can share that kind of intimacy with someone; it's one of this shitty world's greatest experiences. Izz sounds pretty funky, my friend, and I'm looking forward to meeting  her  even more than I am the Queen of Heft (who, after all, is just hefty). Don't be too concerned about missing someone; that's just another way of realising it's worth the trouble. And besides, missing someone is half the fun of being together; you'll only enjoy the reunion that much more.  So thanks very much, motherfucker: you have me all warm and fuzzy inside, you bastard.  Adieu and au revoir.   Postscript:  James Hird trained today. Hardcore. He was only released from hospital last night.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings Droogies,  Let's get some of the bureaucratic things in order first, before things begin.   In response to Vitriols last post concerning my initial post on the philosophy of road laws, I am currently forming a counter argument. I found the reply interesting and courteous and so I shall reply consequently similarly. Realising that the point was enormously extreme, I did find it interesting which aspects were supportable compared to those less so. These shall be discussed at my convenience, as I cannot be stuffed spending the time doing the mental gymnastics to modify my views on the subject. I merely wished to provoke argument and rattle a response from those interested enough, more to assess where strong views like those presented would sit in the large picture in comparison to others; if you never question you will never learn. This does not imply I shall be lenient in my counter appraisal. I shall be merciless. Let the slaughterous assessment begin!   B: The LAN is going to be in August. I believe the exact date is the 7th, which is a Saturday. Have no fear about missing it. Just make sure that your hard disk is pretty organised, saving as much space as possible, since there will be lots of things to peruse through and leach  not to mention the glorious gaming that will be had.   Secondly, my old chum, on the topic of Djinn, I think perhaps you might have some angry AD&D players knocking on your door once they notice the use of their word for Genie as your use of the word for the elves. I would argue that it is perhaps in the same realm as using the term Istari  The Wizards from Tolkiens world. I know the word sounds cool but you might have conflicts because of it. I figure if perhaps the AD&D people hadnt already used the word Genie in the phonetic spelling of Djinni, you might have got away with it. I reckon, scrap the word and make a new word of your own for it.  Personally, I think the connection is interesting, but the term use may cause you trouble. Genies are in a sense slaves, bound to their flask until some unweary adventurer sets them free. I suppose this is very much like your elves since they were bound in the beginning and are now set free. I dont know how others will interpret the connection since the term Genie (spelled: Djinni) is so well known.  Something you might find interesting about a secondary use of the term Djinni is its use in the Koran, the muslim bible. It reads:   djinni - (Islam) an invisible spirit mentioned in the Koran and believed by Muslims to inhabit the earth and influence mankind by appearing in the form of humans or animals  Perhaps you might be able to use that instead. It is a different meaning of the word and well, if you just liked the word this allows you use of it, without ripping off anything that many people would know of. Except muslims, but they are a minority [note the irony].  My agendas: Well, I had a great night with Isobel (Izzy) last night. Even though she had to leave early to go away with friends the following morning, she still made the effort to come past and spend some time with me. The night was filled with constant laughter and witty humour. We watched a few movies she had hired and one from my own (petite) collection. They included: Till Human Voices Wake Us, The Long Kiss Goodnight and finally A Waking Life. All in all, I felt an amorous connection begin to grow between us. Where once light brushes of body contact were the norm, we have reached a stage where we can comfortably share the warm of one anothers body. The union of unquavering eyes, laden with hidden messages rocked the very foundation of my senses. I cannot comprehend the novelty of such closeness nor the splendour that accompanies it. May the seeds of passion in my heart bear ripe sweet fruits, rather than adding to the already decaying pods of expended blossoms. She will be away for the weekend until the next Monday, and I am glad I got to see her one last time before she departed. She shall be missed.   I dont have much else to comment on as of late. There isnt much to jog my mind or cause it to focus now that holidays have begun. Perhaps I shall finally sink into my short story and complete some long forgotten personal writing. As long as I can wake afore the cockcrows.   Adew  *G*
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the footy was spectacular. 24.11 to 11.11 is extraordinary in anyone's book. The General, as always, was taken down by the enemy halfway through the piece, and in his 200th, missed half through injury. A fitting hallmark of his career, really. Luckily, the lacklustre team rallied hence, and pummelled the pathetic Tigers within an inch of their lives. The Velvet Sledgehammer managed the lazy nine, with only one behind. Coleman number three, here we come. Just finished watching the replay on the teev, and it was a lot better knowing the result. Adam McPhee is a tank. The Johnsons are harder than granite. Rama is back in a big way.  In classic Hird style, if he's going to be bothered doing an injury, he does it properly. He breaks a rib, is blessed with a nice bout of bleeding through the lungs, and decides to play on for another six or seven minutes before he's finally dragged by the team doctor and wanders around the boundary (in what is obviously great pain) into the rooms, where he is ferried to hospital. Hospital. The hardness of that man is astonishing. It's a shame his body can't keep up.  Unfortunately, the writing hit a wall today, which is a solid bitch. Hence the late-night enthuse in the hope of regaining some semblance of quality upon the morn, though the likelihood of that seems slim to none at the moment. But, what can one do? Edit. Rework. Think. Play really fucking loud music. And that's about it.  But, the badminton was a blast; it's lucky for those poor bastards I don't play the competition night on Thursdays, or I'd have to take it seriously and they'd never win a fucking point. Sometimes, I amaze even myself. It's been five years, and I reckon I've regained about 70% of my best form in about ten weeks. I just can't play doubles. It pains me. My perfect partner would just stand in the fucking corner and do nothing while I won the fucking game for them. But... you have to let the fuckers have a hit. So... you lose. Take one for the 'team'. Even though the 'team' consists of one person scoring and the other just... fucking things up. Sport. Love it.   G:  One point of interest; my 'elves' are now called 'djinn'. The plural is 'djinni', and the accusative 'djinaen'. They call themselves the Djinaen Aelfraaye. Except the 'Ae' is one of those merged-AE symbols. 'Djin' means 'slave' in the old language, which I thought was a nice touch. It's deliberately synonymous with the 'Djinni' that are like genies (may even have been where our word 'genie' comes from), considering that they too, are slaves. Read it over a few times and let me know if it seems right. I was thinking of making the djinni some kind of race other than elves, but I couldn't think of anything similar or convenient enough.   Soz:  If that LAN is on this weekend, it might be a negatori from this end. Essendon play in the West and I won't be getting a freeload, so it would be expensive. But for the life of me I can't remember when the hell it was anyway. Besides, there's an opportunity just arisen to hit a pub with a cute chick that might even outrank the footy. Keep you posted.  That's my life, at 3:13am.
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having just engaged in the ever-worthwhile effort of reading DisSenter's opinion, I will direct any readers of  this  post to the aformentioned article. Most of the discussion in this text will be referrent to the one previous, and though I will attempt to bring relevant exerpts to light, it would be useful to read DisSenter's own words first.  On the whole, I would agree with the utmost emphasis, with the general suggestion raised by DisSenter, in that an alternate solution to the current road rules, their punishments and regulations, is necessary. I would also concur that the most extreme, the most consistent and the most reckless offenders are those to whom the law should indeed strive to punish. However, and this is the point at which I will begin, I do not agree that an immediate, all-pervasive and likely draconian punishment is the answer.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Why put faith in the value of conditioning when it has been &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;shown to be so falsely and weakly supportable? Better to  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;remove those directly off the road quickly before potentially &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;more harm takes place. The ruling should be the first time &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;you speed or break the road rules; you should suffer an &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;immediate loss of licence. No second chances implies that &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;those that have their licence will be more reluctant to give &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;it away so easily, and those that are careless enough to be &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;apathetic towards this wont have it for very long  and &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;rightly so.   I would in all honesty ask whether conditioning in regards to the punishment of fines has actually been shown to fail in the majority of cases. It may be that in many cases conditioning does not work immediately, if at all, and that it is not a complete answer to the problem of reckless or careless driving. However, as a general deterrent, I would think it works quite well. I would point out that it may in fact fail the  majority  of times in extreme cases such as that outlined by DisSenter, but it is not these extreme cases it sets out to deter in the first place.  But, presuming this is an article against particularly deficient and negligent drivers, I will assume that the point is moot, and look at the next case in hand; the immediate refusal of licenses for first offenders. This, I must say, would be completely inappropriate. Both the severity and swiftness of punishment might well deter most drivers from speeding and/or infringing, but it will not stop those, who as DisSenter most adequately stated himself, have a contempt or disregard for the law, just as conditioning will not.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; If it is done this way, it will restrict repeat offenders since &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;they cannot continue speeding, not even just a little, since &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;any minor infraction will cause termination of licence.   Perhaps, but it also restricts  all  offenders, and anyone who is caught is punished just as harshly, since 'any minor infraction will cause termination of license'. To subject an entire society to particularly harsh or strict rules because of the idiocy of a few is ludicrous.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Whether they have learnt their lesson or not is unimportant &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;here since they are not given another opportunity to prove &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;their erudition.    What about those who  have  learned their lesson? Neither are they given another opportunity. I would suggest, at a minimum, that three offences occur before the suspension of a license. The law is about precedent, and three offenses is a clear precedent in any case. The time period between each should be less than a year; after all, it is a bit hard to ask every driver on the road not to err more than once in an entire year or face the loss of a license. Unfortunately, we are all human and make mistakes. We must give some breadth of opportunity for error and instead focus the higher penalties upon those who earn them.  In this regard I would also disagree on the abandonment of varying penalties for varying offenses. To say that an offender who exceeds the limit by 5km/h in a 110 zone is just as reckless as one who exceeds the limit by 60km/h in an 80 zone is ridiculous. Because they are not. To exceed the limit by less than 5% could in fact be written off to a momentary distraction or neglect; an infringement perhaps, but not one that deserves a penalty of removing their license for 3 years! On the other hand, to infring by such a gross margin as the latter example, which amounts to a 75% excess, might well earn that penalty. I would thus argue that the current system supports this method of punishment, in an ascending scale.  What, I think, needs to occur in regard to the punishment is to ban repeat, significant offenders for longer periods of time. Anyone who exceeds the limit by over 50% should have their license suspended immediately. To repeat the offense at  any  time in the future should incur the same penalty, for double the duration. A third repeat of such a significant offense might even render the driver ineligible to drive again. Not many people could argue that such a punishment is unreasonable; such excess is no accident.   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The road to getting the licence should remain the same, for &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;reasons not argued here, but the road to keeping it should &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;be much, much harder. Roughly this is because mental &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;maturity is too difficult to assess at the time licence testing. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;It cannot be determined prior to the accident whether this &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;individual will or will not be a road hazard.   In this case, I must completely disagree. The current methods for acquiring a road license in Victoria are an absolute joke. Answer a few multiple-choice questions, press a few buttons and bumble your way through a sterile driving course and you have yourself a  ten-year  license. Many drivers struggle to identify simple rules such as whose right it is to turn into a street first from various points in an intersection; when it is appropriate to indicate; which lane of a road to drive in, and when. What importance is actually given to retaining any knowledge of road rules after the test? What respect or caution is given by young drivers when they pass the test and possess the 'right' to drive a vehicle? The limitations on beginning drivers are very thin and only barely adequate.  Mental maturity is indeed difficult to gauge, not only during a fifteen-minute driving test, but at any stage by anyone with a brief amount of time in which to do so. Nor is it the place of testers to identify whether or not a given driver  might  be a road hazard in the future. What is required are stricter guidelines, and a more in-depth procedure for acquiring licenses in the first place; perhaps even mandatory refresher courses or tests in the future, especially for offenders.  Just as important as the punishments in place, and indeed even the rules, is the culture of those that offend by the most excessive amounts, and the most regularly. Statistics by various government and private companies show the most serious offenders are males aged between 18 and 25. The next bracket includes males between 25 and 35 and females between 18 and 25. It is not surprising, in light of the accident outlined in DisSenter's article, upon further detail to find that the vehicle driven was modified. I would ask: what proportion of serious, frequent offenders are not only in the first of these brackets, but also driving modified or particularly powerful vehicles?  I would therefore suggest that the culture of vehicle modification is a significant contributor to the cause of serious road injuries and fatalities. I would also suggest that the demands made on truck drivers over long periods of time due to inappropriately short demand times is another significant contributor to road injury and/or fatality. In the case of the latter, it might be as simple as gearing unions to achieve workplace standards or instituting regulations for minimum travel times for long-distance truck drivers embedded in legislation. In the case of the former, it seems that the very culture of the individuals involved will be much harder to erase or positively modify.  Unfortunately, not all those who modify cars are 'hoons'. Many are, but not all. To crack down on the entire culture would be particularly unfair on those who enjoy modified vehicles but who also obey and respect the law. I would suggest greater limits on age and experience for allowing certain vehicles to be driven, or even owned, by particular individuals in certain age brackets. No doubt these regulations already exist, but provision might need to be made to more effectively reduce the capacity of repeat offenders to own or drive such vehicles. I would suggest that far more significant fines and, more appropriately, restrictions be placed on young males with modified vehicles, repeat offenders, and serious offenders.  Although it is in the best interests of everyone to keep 'road-maniacs' off the road, where they belong, it is also a matter of balancing more severe penalties with those of lesser offenders, who may have made simple mistakes or are quite capable of changing their ways. In any case:  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; If you cannot handle your car and are a hazard on the road,  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;then you should not be allowed to continue driving.   This is the point beyond dispute here, and no matter what may or may not be the best or most reasonable way to go about it, there are distinct holes in the net that is currently used to both catch and punish those responsible for avoidable road deaths. Accidents happen, and they will never be avoided. But crushing the spine of a so-called 'friend' because you were driving at 160km/h is a disgraceful, disgusting abuse of any privilege, or right, and deserves a strict and unbending application of severe retribution. The driver of that vehicle does  not  deserve to drive again, but  does  deserve the pain and guilt he may well feel for the rest of his life because of the idiotic and reckless actions he took, again as DisSenter has adquately put it, as a child.
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Morning All,  This is one of the longest posts you shall receive on this site and so I ask you to only read it if you are interested in improving our road safety. This is primarily a political philosophical argument and as yet incomplete, yet should provide you with something to think about. Bear in mind that it is as yet only proof read once and still in the process of being edited.   Regards,   *G*  Not wanting to work on one of the many stories floating about in the asylum of my mind, I chose to question the government with some political philosophy.  Recently to my great dismay, I received word that the brother of a friend was almost turned into a quadriplegic. Sitting in the passenger seat of his friends hotted-up vehicle, they collided head on with another car while driving over 160 km/h on a dark, rainy road. The driver of the car almost had his bowels eviscerated by the seat belt, while the two back seat passengers were practically unharmed. But the brother of the friend had so much trauma damage to his spinal cord that it was hanging by a thread. So devastating was the damage that moving him ever so slightly could completely sever the neurons holding his spine together.   Rushed to the hospital, friends, relatives and immediate family were in tears. The individual came so close to passing into the next life that Death herself could be heard whispering in his ear. Strapped to a table to debilitate moving, the unfortunate boy now remains in intensive care fighting to keep his ability to walk again if not his life.  What are we to do to prevent such disasters from taking place? Who is to blame for the catastrophe? Many possible solutions and counter arguments present themselves. Let us begin this first by assessing blame by the parents. Showing that firm parenting is not a suitable solution to the problem, I shall assess possible changes to the road laws that govern whom may be afforded the luxury of driving automobiles. Using two primary and common cases of road law infringement, I shall show that it is illogical to continue to allow unsafe drivers upon the road. This being the case the problems that arise with the argument are shown not to be flawed when considered independently of other factors but could turn out to be potentially disastrous for the general smooth operation of the population.   Returning to the case at hand, this child  for that is exactly what he is  threw caution to the wind and willingly jeopardised his life. Now, is this the fault of the child? Abso-bloody-lutely. Everyone is responsible for his or her own actions and this case shall not be argued against here. What about the parents? I would say, being lenient and aware of what it is like having disciplinary parents of various styles that not all the blame should fall on them. Certainly if they are being terrible role-models for their children  exposing them to all sorts of bad habits and routines  the child will pick up some of these from their day-to-day exposure to it. But this may not necessarily be the so in the majority of household operations. Certainly what could mostly be argued is that parents with difficult children or young adults are either too apathetic to care about their childs behaviours or too lacking in control to discipline them will be more prevalent in such road infringements.   What seems evident with both these groups is that if the apathetic parent became the caring parent and those that lack discipline suddenly found an appropriate method of controlling their children, it would not guarantee that their child would be sensible behind the wheel. As children grow they gain many different influences  such as friends and other relatives  and so the parent can only set the stage and rehearse with child then allow them to dance their own way to the allotted script. With such limiting control, a parent can only hope that their child has the sense to behave in a way that is safe and appropriate, but this as a fact is never the way the case presents itself. Children experiment and that is a fact of life, but when experimentation becomes dangerous  to themselves and others  then external intervention is required. Being educated and told right from wrong isnt enough anymore. The law was designed to serve in the interest of humankind, to maintain prosperity and sanctity of life, and this is a case that most strongly requires a sensible and suitable intervention.   My argument will seem incomplete if I ignored the minority groups of parents that are quite poor with their children, so to address them I make the following comment: They will most likely never change, and their behaviours are so ingrained that their children will probably suffer by default. This is tragic, I understand, but we are dealing with logic and the majority of reasonable, caring parents. To be sensible we should call a spade a spade and realise that the law can go above the idiocy or irresponsibility of poor parents and this is a situation where it is direly required.  Seeing as it is unreasonable to rely on the assumption that, given their parents can control their children, it would cease their juvenile and dangerous behaviour. Relying on a higher order to organise and maintain sanity and protection of the denizens of the city from such acts, we are forced to resort to the law.   Teenagers these days are given the right to learn to drive a car from the age of 16 until they reach 18 where they begin their probationary period for three further years, finally reaching their full licence at 21 (without prior offences). The law as it stands, and heretofore I shall refer to it loosely, that those breaking it suffer fines according to how much they erred. Let us deal with two types of penalty incurring acts: Speeding and road related accidents such as collisions.   Firstly, I wish to go into speeding and how such acts promote or can act as a signifier of potentially hazardous drivers. The law asserts that generally those that speed will desist in their efforts to overtake the speed limit if they are fined heavily and suffer demerit points lost off their licence. This will eventually result in licence revocation. The law asserts that this will remove dangerous and hazardous drivers off the road and allow for safer driving. This is unjustifiable. It is as irrational as the parent that believes if they scold their child for the thousandth time they wont play with matches again, or tread through the house with mud on their feet, or speed. Punishment and regulation does not imply that someone will learn their lesson and decide to behave appropriately and sensibly according to the law. Most likely it will make repeat offenders more volatile and encourage contempt for the law or anything that restricts them. Their sense of wronging or punishment will further push them away from the law rather than steer them in and encourage them to behave appropriately. Even if this is not the case there is nothing to suggest that they have improved in their mental maturity and will from then onwards aim to behave within the limits set by the law. Why put faith in the value of conditioning when it has been shown to be so falsely and weakly supportable? Better to remove those directly off the road quickly before potentially more harm takes place. The ruling should be the first time you speed or break the road rules; you should suffer an immediate loss of licence. No second chances implies that those that have their licence will be more reluctant to give it away so easily, and those that are careless enough to be apathetic towards this wont have it for very long  and rightly so.   The road to getting the licence should remain the same, for reasons not argued here, but the road to keeping it should be much, much harder. Roughly this is because mental maturity is too difficult to assess at the time licence testing. It cannot be determined prior to the accident whether this individual will or will not be a road hazard. The only fair option, without causing an infringement on their rights, is to allow someone to have a fair go before they are condemned. After that time all strikes count as fatal. If it is done this way, it will restrict repeat offenders since they cannot continue speeding, not even just a little, since any minor infraction will cause termination of licence. This factors in that the mindset of the individual need not change across time while they are driving since as long as they break the law they will be off the road permanently. Whether they have learnt their lesson or not is unimportant here since they are not given another opportunity to prove their erudition. As long as they offend, the law should stipulate immediate termination. In such a way, the reliance on conditioning to improvement via fining or suspension is forgone.   To become realistic, it would be impossible to terminate licences permanently, as this would be seen as condemnation without revocation. What should be implemented is sever penalties that, irrespective of the size of the speeding infringement, invoke immediate loss of licence and at least 2 or 3 years. Driving is a privilege by those that are worthy enough to use the roads sensibly, and not a privilege by default as it is regarded today. When it comes down to it, ask yourself whether giving a road-maniac the ability to drive again so that he or she can potentially offend again is important because its their right to do so or whether the safety of your children, family and friends is more important. Surely, you will remove the offender of the road and keep your loved ones safe. Speed limits will be adhered for fear of the penalties and so some order shall be restored, not by relying on the good will and learning of others, but by removing those that are resistant to such learning from the equation.  What needs to be recognised here is that the right to apply for a drivers licence should be available to everyone without discrimination, but the privilege to keep it should be for those that are able to maintain and prove their worth as a driver. This would imply little or no accidents and certainly no speeding fines or reckless behaviour. Such acts only serve to show the lackadaisical attitude of the driver and the lack of discipline that is essentially required to sit behind the wheel safely.  Reasonably it would not be sane to put an inexperienced suburban parent into space after a week of training, as although it is his right to see space and beyond, he is not up to the challenge to attempt deep space voyage. Doing so is an endangerment to those working with him in the cooperative system. Rights and privileges are mutually exclusive. You can have the right to go into space, but without proper skill, testing and training, you may not receive the privilege to go up there.  The other sort of dangerous driver is the frequent accidental or careless driver. They are the individuals that constantly, through fault or not fault of their own engage in accidents involving cars or others objects along the roadside. These individuals are a bane to society, obviously lacking in their ability to handle their automobile safely enough to keep themselves and others clear of danger. This is a similar case to speeding since it can be caused due to carelessness; lack of attention to the task at hand, poor training and coordination and various other reasons. The argument to remove these drivers off the road also stems from the aforementioned case of if they arent on the road, they cant cause a problem. This seems logical enough. Why keep someone who is unsafe on the road at all? They should be removed leaving the law-abiding citizens to drive in peace and safety. Until such time as they can be shown to be safe on the road again when they are shown to be safe and wise in their vehicles method of operations  through a driving clinic for example  they should be reprimanded from further driving activity. Driving is a privilege not a right  something that has been forgotten in the interest of government income and revenue. The same applies with driving dangerously. If you cannot handle your car and are a hazard on the road, then you should not be allowed to continue driving.   My aim from both of these two cases is to point out that taking the factor out of the situation would serve as the best means of a solution. A driver who speeds does not respect the privilege of driving and so it is denied it. Similarly, a driver who is dangerous on the road and a cause of continuous accidents should also be removed since they are not apt enough to handle themselves on the road in a safe manor. These simple things can save lives but there is always something that causes the situation to become more complicated.   Likely, the government would stop making money if people that were speeding were to be taken off the road and so would resist such a drastic termination process. Also, the sheer volume of drivers to be suspended would be so high that it would possibly destroy, if not severely damage enterprise since people would not be able to arrive to work any more. It might also increase a sporadic crime wave of car thefts, unlicensed driving, and joy-riding by those that have had their licence revoked, possibly required more policing in that particular area.   These possible situations seem evident and even highly likely, but at what cost are we to keep the lives of your children and family safe? Removing idiots off the road serves to keep those on the road safe, but the effects on the community need to be weighed also. But this can remain for another discussion.   Adew All.  DisSenter 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't need dictionary.com. I  am  dictionary.com.  Hey, whatever you want to write, it's kewl. Don't feel pressured into maintaining some standard, like the G-Meister and I, who are founding members of Pedants-R-Us. It's all good, little matey. I tend to write things like mini-essays on Medea when I get bored. It's a by-product of my anti-social life here in I-know-nobody-land, a.k.a Bendigo.  It's just there to read, not to emulate. Besides, if you write a Spotlight on The Illiad, I'll probably pick it to pieces anyway. So just do what you do best... whatever that is. Heh. This is not meant to be some kind of hyper-intellectual forum for dissecting the nuances of the human dichotomy, but if that rocks your boat, then it certainly can be.   I watched the 'Shane Crawford Show' last night, or Under the Covers or whatever the stupid thing was called. Crock. Of. Shit. Funny at times, and quite watchable, but as far as an expose goes, this fell flat on its boof-head face. It wasn't anything out of the ordinary, nor anything pertinent. In fact, it reeked of "Feel Sorry For Me Because One Of The Hot Chicks I Won't Sleep With Is Stalking Me". Well boo-fucking-hoo. Just sit at home in front of your two-hundred-inch Plasma and enjoy the replay of your last belting by Collingwood, is my response to that.  So that's my pop segment for this week.
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HI. this is a blog entry from angela. Everything on this site seems intellectual and you all write with big words but i dont. so ner. im breaking the rhythem. i dont even know how to spell rythem and im too lazy to dictionary.com it. My mum just got harry potter 3 and spiderman two on dvd from some guy at her work. im so bored. kayla is about to come over. i said that to myself 3 hours ago. im sorry if i ruined the notion of your GLOB blog. i'll write more another time when i expand my vocabulary. Mrs Marsh said that i need to expand it byebye!
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Consider: If someone  is  intimidated, they are made to suffer intimidation against their will. If someone is  intimated , would they not be suffering intimacy, also against their will? I find it interesting, in that context, to take a look at some of the effects of such activity, as explained in common American by the Thesaurus of most Scumsoft products.  Write 'intimated' into any Word document, use the Thesaurus (shift-F7), and be amazed at the effects of being made intimate...  One no longer has to question why the logic of men often goes to greath lengths to avoid such conditions, as oulined within the very nature of our language.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's my Birthday and I'll Blog if I want to!
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love this story. It has all the essential components of a good read: intrigue, betrayal, murder and failed romance. Real romance is for amateurs; only a master can capture the grotesqueries of the most twisted romances. It has a great hero, Jason, of the Argonauts and Golden Fleece fame, now reduced considerably in the esteem of she once his concubine.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; You filthy coward! - if I knew any worse name &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For such unmanliness I'd use it - so, you've come! &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;You, my worst enemy, come to me! Oh, it's not courage, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;This looking friends in the face after betraying them. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;It's not even audacity; it's a disease.   To save her love, Medea sacrificed everything; her home, her father, her sisters, and travelled back to Corinth with Jason. Two children and a bitter relationship later, he has forsaken her to marry the daughter of Creon, King of Corinth. Now, let there be no doubt in anyone's mind that Medea is  hard . She's a twisted, bitter bitch, but I  love  that about her.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; What makes me cry with pain &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Is the next thing I have to do. I will kill my sons. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;No one shall take my children from me. When I have made &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Jason's whole house a shambles, I will leave Corinth &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;A murderess, flying from my darling children's blood. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Yes, I can endure guilt, however horrible; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;The laughter of my enemies I will not endure.   She ends up having her vengeance upon Jason, who in this tale seems fairly chauvanistic and simple. Medea, on the other hand, is very complex; she loves and hates the man, and struggles with the moral dilemma before her, finally giving in to the urge to do what I was dying for her to do for the entire length of the plot: Unleash the fury.  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Arm yourself, my heart: the thing &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;That you must do is fearful, yet inevitable. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Why wait then? My accursed hand, come, take the sword; &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Take it, and forward to your frontier of despair. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;No cowardice, to tender memories; forget &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;That you once loved them, that of your body they were born. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For one short day forget your children; afterwards &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Weep: though you kill them, they were your beloved sons. &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Life has been cruel to me.    Now that is willpower. Euripides sure had a fair old imagination, because he dreams up some pretty savage stuff. People often say that violence on television is ruining young minds, but by that rationale, young ancient Greeks should have been homicidal maniacs, the lot of them. Tragedy and murder were laid before them constantly in their amphitheatres, which were the television, radio, cinema and MCG of their day. But no mention of Medea can go without my favourite quote, one of my all-time most precious;  &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Let no one think of me &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;As humble or weak or passive; let them understand &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;I am of a different kind: dangerous to my enemies, &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;Loyal to my friends. To such a life glory belongs.   And that is the beauty of Medea.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Three points:  I : Good call, my young Padawan. A timelier piece could not have been constructed, unless of course, it had anything to do with current affairs, such as Israel-Palestine, the US-Australia Free Trade Agreement, or Mark Latham's plethora of prior assault charges, to name a few. But, all things being considered, this ranks right up there.  II : Due to his being called 'The Muscles from Brussels', I have a fair idea where this 'Kraut' is from.  III : I think, to put it plainly, we should establish some ground-rules here. Namely, that some sense of decency and etiquette should be maintained. Therefore, I have to ask what the  fuck  you were thinking when you answered your random question. Have some fucking class, man.  Other than that, spiffy, my friend. Spiffy indeed.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to the first of many 'Stating the Obvious'.   This week we shall look at Van Damme, the muscle-bound moron from wherever. Equiped with a bad accent and even worse acting skills, Van Damme has once again attempted to take his skills seriously with the action flick "Derailed".   The words "What the-" and "That makes no sense" may constantly flood into your mind as you spend your valuable time attempting to understand the plot - which in fact doesn't exist. Okay, okay, I am being a little too harsh. Lets just *assume* there is a viable plot, what now? We are not at a complete loss. The director however is way up shit creek. This movie could have been made to be somewhat credible. Hefty chicks parade throughout the movie. In fact, they were the only things that facilitated my vigilence; a busty brunette theif, a sandy-haired slim doctor and a glasses wearing tall, petite violinist. With such tits-n-ass, it was remarkable that the director created such a flop. But what does this have to do with Van Damme sucking? Well, it doesn't have anything to do with it. He just sucks. That's why this is called "Stating the Obvious", because it doesn't require explanation or definition. It is undisputed.   But, before I leave I would like to put my polished boot into Van Damme's stomach. He sucked for the following reasons: - His pathetic accent - He is incapable of showing any convincing facial expressions appart from anger.  - The fact that his characters are so one dimensional yet are given enormous amounts of authority. - He is always the ONLY man for the job. He is an idiot, if that's the only man for the job, consider the mission a failure and move on.  - There is something to be said about the technological advancement in his movies. For exameple the Russians have been using AK's in movies for about 35 years. America, meanwhile, is technologically superior in every way to that back water swamp of an ice world. If this is the case, why do the Russians always put up such a hard fight with the most primitive of weapons when battling american forces? If so, why do the yanks always send one muscle-bound Krout (Van Damme) to get the job done rather than nuking their enemies base of operations or sending in a tactical SEAL or Ranger team to get the job done? It's all about believability, and his movies are highly unbelievable.  - He plays the same character every movie.  - He takes himself seriously. This is the worst of his flaws. The fool thinks he is good. Oh my! He was holding the door when Satan was giving out brains.  In conclusion, I would recommend this for our aging Mr. Van Damme: Look in your study. See how many different academy awards you have - this should take you about 2 seconds since the number would be zero. Now go to the movie cabinet. Count all the good movies you have made - this should also take only a few seconds since the number could be counted on one hand. Divide the score by the number of years as an actor to get your final score.  The higher the score the better. Let's do a quick tally for Mr. Van Damme:  (0 + 0)/18 = Undefined. Wow, you have it there folks. The truth eventually shines through.   Quit while you're ahead, or in your case, just quit.  *G*
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A moron, a dole bludger and a Collingwood supporter walk into a bar...  ...and that was just the first guy.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is not very important, but neither is this message, which is just a test.
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right. This is an idea the G-Meister and I  have devised from years of swimming through a boatload of shit on the internet, as well as intense discussions on the topic. It struck he and I as a convenient way to keep in contact with people, whilst circumventing the need for chat programs or e-mail.  How it works is that you all get permissions to make posts here, to which any or all of you can comment with further blog posts. That way, no matter the time of day or night, you can jump on and find out what the rest of us are talking about or thinking about and reply in a semi-public forum. 'Public' in that it's inclusive and not just a private message between two people, and 'semi-' in that nobody without the address will bother reading it, nor will they have access to post their retarded opinions, unlike posting boards.  So, providing you all like the idea, post a blog to show that you at least know how to use the darn thing. That requires you to visit blogger.com and start up a profile, which you may already have done if you got the permission e-mail from blogger.  Oh, and I must warn you: Blogger requires an inordinate amount of patience, dial-up or no.
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so unbelievably pissed off at some of the things said in this current topic, but I'm not sure how I'll go expressing my feelings, but I'll give it a go. You guys have had bad timing when it comes to this topic, I've just had an ex of mine for the last few days completely mess with my head. So I'm in no mood.  Not suprising affairs happen because chicks let down there guard on taken men!.. Fucking bullshit. I am a fucking magnet for unavailable men. I couldn't even count how many times a man has cracked on to me, only to discover they have a girlfriend or are FUCKING MARRIED. And when is it that they tell you? Well never if they can help it, and its only a friend that saves you. Or perhaps they bullshit you, telling you its over or some crap like that. I'm not saying females arn't capable of such things at all. But all this MALE "I LET MY PENIS DO THE THINKING" BULLSHIT is the REASON femaled have that guard up that you speak of. And frankly, when it comes to me, I'm the opposite. My guards down UNTILL they tell me they have a girlfriend. Cos thats when said girlfriends starts to hate me because i'm too good a friends with their boyfriends, or said guy starts looking at me like a piece of smeggin meat, and thinking "all right she could be a bit of fun, I can have my cake and eat it too blah blahblah"..  If men are _supposedly_ more logical than women, then men should bloddy well no better shouldn't they. Actually, to hell with it. My guards gunna be up all the smeggin time now after listening to you guys and after my weekend.**  Whats the quickest way to a mans heart? Through his cheast with a sharp knife.  **Apologies for not referencing your posts specifically, for spelling mistakes, and bad gramMA. But frankly I just don't give a hoot.
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, two things:  1. Isn't it IRONIC that women, that gender so often inappropriately sought after, so aloof and unapproachable, are suddenly turned into 'normal' people upon the acquisition of a female partner. I agree completely, that this so-called MYSTIQUE that they possess is rendered completely and utterly useless under any circumstance that, of course, inhibits any interest being shown in them.  Now, I would add to this comment that not only do they engage easily in all forms of conversation, but are INEXPLICABLY more likely to show interest in said partnered male. And one WONDERS why affairs occur. Single man = no interest. Partnered man = fountain of yap. It is equally interesting to realise the BANALITY of many said chicks in this regard. Certainly, the concern of the male cracking on to her may well have been alleviated, but it remains nonetheless a fascination JUXTAPOSITION in the male-female relationship matrix. Namely, that part that takes logic, breaks it into a million different pieces, and spreads it across a layer of ice so thin that any wrong step with send the hapless interloper into the CHASM OF FUCK-YOU-CREEP.  2. The G-Man has acquired the status of 'Boyfriend'. Sen-fucking-sational. In a Hyper-Thalamus salute to G in his acquisition of aformentioned and strikingly intelligent heft, I have but one final comment to make:  RRRRRRRRRRRRRAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHH!!!!!!!!  P.S. Isobel; she even has a sexy name, man! Kudos to Kodos! I have also discovered the recent interest of lesser-age nubile sirens; I can only figure it has to do with my current LACK of all facial hair. Therefore, I postulate the notion that beards are fucking bad, man. Heft + Beard = No Noogie. Heft + No Beard = Significant Interaction. This is my latest theorem, based on practical experience and fieldwork analysis.
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings again,  Today I learnt something fascinating. Having recently been promoted to the rank of boyfriend to my lovely lady, Isobel, I have had some rather interesting interactions with women. Women have smiled to me a lot more, appeared more friendly and less threatened by my brusque and manly countenance. But why has this sudden turn of feminine fortune been thrown my way?  This seemingly peculiar question along with some "psychological testing" that I have undertaken has shown to me - without a doubt - that when you utter the phrase "I have a girlfriend" to a woman they are automatically disarmed. By disarmed I mean that heavy, thick plate-mail they wear to protect themselves suddenly vanishes as you move from alpha-male predator to attentive and non-threatening friend.  Today I witnessed a seeming miracle as I spoke to some random chick in the corridor as she sat outside my tutorial class. At first, I could tell she was just busting to talk to someone. She did common female things like moving her foot erratically while she sat cross-legged, looking from side-to-side and not at her lecture notes. So I sat beside her. Betting on the assumption she would strike up a conversation. I was pleasantly surprised when my gambit paid off.  We chatted about common things; the class we were about to enter and that we both shared some overlapping subjects. But this wasn't of great interest to me. The moment I said "Oh and I have my first real girlfriend now, I am new to all this" it was as if she stood up, threw the thick armour and gauntlets to the ground and proceeded become transparent before me. She took off her veil and it was as if I was Sauron of Lord of the Rings, able to see into her very mind "as she lay naked before the lidless eye." From that moment on in the conversation, she was a new woman. Bold. Adventurous. Disinhibited from her defensive ways. She had been miraculously and most astonishingly disarmed.  I cannot begin to understand, nor comprehend such overwhelming power. Being charismatic by nature, I had to gain my influences over women by playing to many various techniques and styles, ranging from being empathetic to charming and most painfully, attentive (note: that last part is quite fictitious). But now I have a new weapon. A weapon of epic proportions that could turn the tide in the battle of Men Vs Women for all time. I have found the chink in the armour.  Ironically, this insight has struck only me after I have, for all intents and purposes, been quite satisfied with a gorgeous partner. But that is hardly something to be remorseful about. I now understand what my fellow comrades (e.g. Soz) was experiencing when all his female friends were begging and groping for the attention of his ear; women want nothing more than to gasbag about anything to someone who isn't like to make a move on them. The logic seems so profoundly simple it borders on ridiculous. But, alas, true it is.  I am sorry if this was boring for some people to read over but I found it very profound and eye opening.  Finally, Soz offered his opinion on the subject appropriately titled Dis-Arming Women 101: Step 1: Sever Left Arm, Step 2: Sever Right Arm, and finally Step 3: Gloat!  Thank you, Soz for that marvelously unique perspective on Dis-Arming Women    Adew
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dearest Comrades,  Realising the plight of our dear friend Burke is one that has plagued our esteemed comrade for some time, I thought I would provide some Heft Resistance techniques that have served me well.  CAUTIONARY DISCLAIMER: The following information is to be used with extreme jest and ridiculousness in mind. The facts, figures and information presented herein is at best speculative and at most completely fallacious.   On Eye contact: 10% Resistance  This is completely forbidden. 10% of all "picking-up" is done with the eyes. That look from afar from a delicious siren, the immaterial connection between two individuals, serves as the first position where defences need to be erected. Avoid it at all cost my friends. This is easy to do: Don't fuckin' look at her!!   On "That look on your face": 10% Resistance  Look surly. Enough said. No one wants to come and talk to someone who looks like they just took a crap in their pants and don't know how to rectify the problem; or as if you have found out that your wife/girlfriend has just fucked your best friend; or that just as you lost your job and had your favourite Chia-pet break while you were at the footy, watching your favourite team lose to Port Adelaide, after you have just driven for 8 hours to cheer them on!! Note: Don't confuse this with looking like a hard-arse, as it might get the contrary effect. Just look depressed and lame. If they appear to make eye contact a reaction like Edward Norton from  Fight Club  - the scene in the board meeting with the new client - would be sufficient to elicit the appropriate reaction.   On Flirting: 15-20% Resistance  Flirting occurs once eye-contact resistance has been breached. You rolled your D20, failed your saving throw and now youre up the creek without a paddle. Flirting adds a vast increase to your "Gonna get laid and go to jail" score. If you have that intense eye-contact thing going on and you begin your flirting you are well on your way to the next stage of things; Body contact. Ways to avoid flirting or turn off your said victim depend on how far you are willing to compromise your image. They could be as subtle as pretending to look at her tits all the time or perve at other chicks as they walk past. Alternatively they may be as overt as farting and burping in her presence. Flirting can easily be shut down with a few of these effective methods.   On Body Contact: 25% Resistance  Body contact in anybody's book is extremely tantalising, especially with someone whom you have shared eye contact and excessive flirting with. A light brush of a hand or their hair on your face or clothes could get a salute of attention from all parties present. To gain maximum resistance, avoid contact and appear still and unresponsive when your defences are breached. Pick your nose from time to time to make hand contact less appealing. Rub some beer or water under your armpits to make it look like you're sweating so that cuddling is likely to be nullified.These techniques will make you "less desirable" to the opposite sex and so facilitate great levels of resistance.   On Rejecting the Target: 10% Resistance  You can simply just use your willpower. This gives the final 10% and is only possessed by the most strong-minded and unshakeable individuals in our world: me. If she comes up and wants some "sweet thang" just tell her where to go. Don't think about it, just do it often enough so that it becomes and automatic response, in which case you will rely on your brain to make the said judgement not your dick/heart/other appendages. This is the hardest 10% to gain, but the most rewarding since it can be the final barrier between jail and prolonging your promiscuity a few months longer.  Finally, if you observe above, I have not set the resistance any greater than 75%. This is because there are those circumstances where it is simply NOT POSSIBLE to resist a woman. For males this sits at about 25% of the time we make contact with one. If the said siren falls within this category you will probably be swayed and there isn't much anyone can do to aid you. All I can urge you to do is remind yourself of my  simple  steps to Heft Resistance and hope she does something off putting. If not, make sure you illegally purchase some vasaline from your prison "getter-guy" before Bubba and his four mates come-a-knockin' on your cell door, hot and horny for some "fresh meat".  Good luck,  DisSenter 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Greetings, droogies.  After a tantalising weekend with our esteemed colleague Zenny.dome, followed by an investigation of the Australian Centre for the Moving Image at Federation Square with Zork, I found myself, finally, heading back to Bendigo on the usual method of transportation: the V-Line train.  Having had a splendid weekend, I settled myself down stretched along the length of a three-seater and so reclined began reading Euripides'  The Women of Troy , a fascinating play about the women given as slaves to the victorious Argives after the fall of Ilium. These include Hecabe, former wife of Priam and Queen of Troy, her prophetic daughter Cassandra, whose uptaking by Agamemnon is one reason for his death at the hands of his wife Clytaemnestra, and poor Andromache, who having lost her husband Hector must also lose her infant son, Astyanax, before being taken, ironically, by Achilles' son as his consort.  Now, this is  fascinating  stuff, I assure you, and I was well immersed in said literature when I looked up and noticed a girl strangely poking her own hips for some reason. I found this somewhat amusing, and could not restrain a polite smile. The girl was horrified, for what reason I really can't say, and covered her face in embarassment. I watched with some mirth as she attempted to compose herself, but every time she caught my eye, would burst out laughing again. This behaviour continued despite her deliberately subdued efforts to avoid my gaze, such as wearing her sunglasses for a time, to no effect.  You should, at this juncture, be made aware that your humble narrator found this delightful chickadee to be tremendously gorgeous, and exceptionally hefty to boot. With that in mind, you could imagine my great difficulty in restraining myself from even occasionally glancing in said siren's direction. Needless to say, each time I did this elicited more of the same; a bountiful smile, or sublime laughter. These not being terrible things, I felt encouraged to do so at regular intervals.  These antics continued the entire length of the trip, ensuring that as yet I have not completed my reading of  The Women of Troy , namely because the Women of Castlemaine were far more alluring at the time. Unfortunately (or, as I will outline in a moment, fortunately) for I, this lithe goddess and her friend departed the train at aformentioned township, ensuring there would be no post-trip charm or speculation to be had.  So yes, my faithful readers, I was unable to catch so much as a name from said beauty before she swept away into the darkness. I was, however, rather unexpectedly rewarded with a seductive wave goodbye from the pair as the train lumbered from the station. At this point in time, my inclination to misfortune was somewhat alleviated, as my own modest estimate as to their age would have been seventeen or eighteen.  My friends, I implore you, if I am allowed to continue attracting the attention of said nubile sirens, and especially if they continue to arouse the same interest as this one did, there can only be one conclusion:  I am going to jail.
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As we all know, our dear friend Burke is a coke-aholic, but in a recent argument between myself and George, the details of which are not necessary for this post, we discovered the following list:    1886 Drink Coca-Cola.  1900 Deliciously refreshing. For headache and exhaustion, drink Coca-Cola.  1904 Coca-Cola is a delightful, palatable, healthful beverage. Coca-Cola satisfies. Delicious and Refreshing. Drink Coca-Cola in bottles - 5  1905 Drink a bottle of carbonated Coca-Cola. Coca-Cola revives and sustains. Drink Coca-Cola at soda fountains. The favorite drink for ladies when thirsty, weary, and despondent. Good all the way down. Flows from every fountain. Sold in bottles.  1906 The drink of quality. The Great National Temperance. Thirst quenching - delicious and refreshing.  1907 Delicious Coca-Cola, sustains, refreshes, invigorates. Cooling... refreshing... delicious. Coca-Cola is full of vim, vigor and go - is a snappy drink.  1908 Sparkling - harmless as water, and crisp as frost. The satisfactory beverage.  1909 Delicious, wholesome, refreshing. Delicious, wholesome, thirst quenching. Drink delicious Coca-Cola. Whenever you see an arrow think of Coca-Cola.  1910 Drink bottled Coca-Cola - so easily served. It satisfies. Quenches the thirst as nothing else can.  1911 It's time to drink Coca-Cola. Real satisfaction in every glass.  1912 Demand the genuine - refuse substitutes.  1913 Ask for it by its full name - then you will get the genuine. The best beverage under the sun. It will satisfy you. A welcome addition to any party - anytime - anywhere.  1914 Demand the genuine by full name. Exhilarating, refreshing. Nicknames encourage substitutions. Pure and wholesome.  1915 The standard beverage.  1916 It's fun to be thirsty when you can get a Coca-Cola. Just one glass will tell you.  1917 Three million a day. The taste is the test of the Coca-Cola quality. There's a delicious freshness to the flavor of Coca-Cola.  1919 Coca-Cola is a perfect answer to thirst that no imitation can satisfy. It satisfies thirst. Quality tells the difference.  1920 Drink Coca-Cola with soda. Delicious and refreshing. The hit that saves the day.  1922 Quenching thirst everywhere. Thirst knows no season. Thirst can't be denied. Thirst reminds you - drink Coca-Cola.  1923 Refresh yourself. A perfect blend of pure products from nature. There's nothing like it when you're thirsty.  1924 Pause and refresh yourself.  1925 Six million a day. The sociable drink. Stop at the red sign and refresh yourself.  1926 Thirst and taste for Coca-Cola are the same thing. Stop at the red sign.  1927 Around the corner from anywhere. At the little red sign.  1928 A pure drink of natural flavors.  1929 The pause that refreshes.  1930 Meet me at the soda fountain.  1932 Ice-cold sunshine. The drink that makes the pause refreshing.  1933 Don't wear a tired, thirsty face.  1934 Carry a smile back to work. Ice-cold Coca-Cola is everywhere else - it ought to be in your family refrigerator. When it's hard to get started, Start with a Coca-Cola.  1935 The drink that keeps you feeling right. All trails lead to ice-cold Coca-Cola. The pause that brings friends together.  1936 What refreshment ought to be. Get the feel of wholesome refreshment.  1937 America's favorite moment. Cold refreshment. So easy to serve and so inexpensive. Stop for a pause... go refreshed.  1938 Anytime is the right time to pause and refresh. At the red cooler. The best friend thirst ever had. Pure sunlight.  1939 Coca-Cola goes along. Make lunch time refreshment time. Makes travel more pleasant. The drink everybody knows. Thirst stops here.  1940 Bring in your thirst and go away without it. The package that gets a welcome at home. Try it just once and you will know why.  1941 A stop that belongs on your daily timetable. Completely refreshing.  1942 The only thing like Coca-Cola is Coca-Cola itself. Refreshment that can't be duplicated. Wherever you are, whatever you do, wherever you may be, when you think refreshment, think ice-cold Coca-Cola.  1943 That extra something. A taste all its own. The only thing like Coca-Cola is Coca-Cola itself. It's the real thing.  1944 How about a Coke. High sign of friendship. A moment on the sunnyside.  1945 Whenever you hear "Have a Coke," you hear the voice of America. Passport to refreshment. Happy moment of hospitality. Coke means Coca-Cola.  1947 Coke knows no season. Serving Coca-Cola serves hospitality. Relax with the pause that refreshes.  1948 Delicious and refreshing. Where there's Coca-Cola there's hospitality. Think of lunchtime as refreshment time.  1949 Coca-Cola....Along the highway to anywhere.  1950 Help yourself to refreshment.  1951 Good food and Coca-Cola just naturally go together.  1952 Coke follows thirst everywhere. What you want is Coke. The gift of thirst.  1953 Dependable as sunrise. 1954 For people on the go. Matchless flavor.  1955 Almost everyone appreciates the best. America's preferred taste.  1956 Feel the difference. Friendliest drink on earth. Makes good things taste better.  1957 Sign of good taste.            1958 Refreshment the whole world prefers. The cold, crisp taste of Coke.  1959 Cold, crisp taste that deeply satisfies. Make it a real meal.  1960 Relax with Coke. Revive with Coke.  1961 Coke and food - refreshing new feeling.  1962 Enjoy that refreshing new feeling. Coca-Cola refreshes you best.  1963 A chore's best friend. Things go better with Coke.  1964 You'll go better refreshed. 1965 Something more than a soft drink.  1966 Coke...after Coke...after Coke  1970 It's the real thing.  1971 I'd like to buy the world a Coke.  1975 Look up America  1976 Coke adds life.  1979 Have a Coke and a Smile.  1982 Coke is it!  1985 We've got a Taste for You (Coca-Cola and Coca-Cola classic) America's Real Choice.  1986 Catch the wave (Coca-Cola) Red White & You (Coca-Cola classic)  1989 Can't Beat the Feeling.  1990 Can't Beat the Real Thing.  1993 Always Coca-Cola.  2001 Life tastes good.     Pay special attention to the slogan from 1966 as it has a special message for Burke.    Coke...after Coke...after Coke   
    
</post>


</Blog>