<Blog>


<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      damit! no....dam you trent! i am week! so which bands playin tonight? 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      zenny returns from the bar with her jameson and coke, that she just had to nod at the barmaid to get *smiles*  I'm glad you guys are embrasing the pub atmosphere, just spread the word if you can. I don't have everyones email, so if you guys can either let me know, or get ppl to message me with it, it would be apprieciated.   The bar is back baby, and the drinks here are free! *laugh*
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      complements to zen for a excellent expierement, i think we are all going to get hours of entertainment from it 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      as vandal settles down with his coke trent returns from the bar with his bourbon... at this point vandal realises the days when he was satisfied with coke are long gone and he returns to the bar to purchase something he enjoys more.... is it a smirnoff black? is it a bourbon?&nbsp; only nick can answer this question  &nbsp;  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and thus vandal enters, buys his no alcholic beverage and settles in a corner to watch people as always. im glad this is here now.... back to my old ways.... ahhhh.... hello secrity blanket... 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was up in Sydney over the weekend when I stumbled across a promotion advertised at Shellharbour's local  urlLink Cellarbrations  retailer. The advertisement assured me that if I were to purchase a six-pack of the German&nbsp;imported beer,  urlLink DAB , I would be bestowed with a glass beer stein of gargantuan proportions. 1 litre, I believe. That's three regular earth beers! As my affinity for drinking beer from large containers knows no limits, I made the trip and purchased two. Pictures of me drinking copious amounts of lager will surely follow. Stay tuned.   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sweet....this is a cool idea, however one thing is missing from this wonderful place.   THE BEER...There's no beer.&nbsp; How can you have a pub with no Beer.&nbsp; To have a pub without Beer is like have corn chips without Salsa....   IT JUST ISN'T RIGHT   However to do the Pub things without booze may help us all in our quest to drink less and party more.   and just think no hangover in the morning...not that I get hang overs any more, you see I have a secret weapon againest hang overs.&nbsp; It's called Lynx Anti-Hang Over Spray and I think it works.   Mind you I haven't really tried it yet as I haven't been out drinking since I brought but the Radio says it works so it must....because in Australian Advertising they never lie.......MUCH   Catch you round like a donut   
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      still no word....  
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So there i was, drinking, when i did something wrong, those of you that have other halves know how easy it is to do something that is wrong... so then later i was at the pub, and i did more wrong, what i did this time i knew was going to get me in trouble more but i felt it needed to be done as i have certain principles that i live by, and i feel that being untrue to these principles is being untrue to myself, and if that ever happened it would be an endless circle to self destruction...   so this is where i am, in a predicament, can anyone help?&nbsp;&nbsp; i didnt think so.... unless someone has one of those 'no more feelings' pills.... which would be a great invention, lots of money to be made there..... i might suggest that one to my chemist friends.. once i get some chemist friends..  this is all for now Trent 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find the chairs in this pub a little bit more comfortable than the wooden bench of our last pub, however they do lack a certain charecter, not to mention the lack of beer, bourbon, jameson, scotch, lemon lime and bitters, and whatever else we may have been drinking....&nbsp; Well this is my first post and i hope to have many more... this is all i can think of writing for the minute, bye 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so here it is.  We sat at the pub in Shepparton pretty much every friday night for I don't know how many years. We drank, we talked, we drank, we laughed, we drank, we danced, we drank, we sung, we drank, and we drank.  Now we are spread all over who knows where and its time we had a pub to go back to. Well a virtual pub at least. So here it is. Talk about what your up to, the last movie you saw, complain about your job, tell us about your great weekend, leave messages, talk about the universe, whatever! Just talk.  Lets give this a shot, and keep in contact, before we all go get married, and pop out some babies, become the boss of some mega company, and get so busy we never speak again.  So get to it!
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i shall be missing from the pub this friday and sat. other night spots await and your all invited. friday night is abyss. it opens at 11 at inflation night club on king st and is $15. gothy. vey. should you want to come wear apropriate clothing.  strait black is fine. sat sees my frined matt playing at the termins in clifton hill. kinda blues/rock kinda thing. pretty dam good. dont know cost or anything but cheaper than fri for sure thought earlier. feel free to join me! 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      its quiet in here this time of week.... 
    
</post>


</Blog>