<Blog>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Recently I was told that I'm obsessive compulsive. I was even compared to the character Monica on the former  Friends  sitcom. At first I didn't agree with that idea. But then I realized how organized everything in my life is. How if even the slightest little thing is out of place, crooked, dirty, or mismatched, it will drive me up the wall. Even now, as I sit here tweaking the style of my blog I notice my obsessive compulsive behavior. Everything is lined up with everything else. Not because I'm worried about it's appearance and function, but because it  must  be perfect. Or at least my idea of perfect.  Here's another example: In high school, if there was a day that I took lecture notes in a different colored pen than usual, or different type of pen (say felt tip over ball point)...later that day I would rewrite that entire page of notes just so it matched the other pages in my notebook. Until now I never realized how crazy that was. I don't think my obsessive compulsiveness is that extreme. I don't flip out on people and tear them apart for upsetting my organization. But things do erk me to the point where I get up and put whatever it is improperly placed or mismatched to how it should be. I don't know why I brought that up. Maybe because I spent all last night getting all the blocks of text and images lined up on my blog, so much that it was 2 AM before I realized what I was doing.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been thinking a lot lately. Here I am, on the verge of turning 24 years old, living the life of someone twice that age. I'm tired of each day being routine. I wake up and instead of wondering what surprises will fall into my lap that day, I already know the answer. The same thing day in and day out. It's almost like I'm being forced against my will to live my own life. Inside I feel like I'm only 20 and there's a party somewhere with me in its absence. I suppose I choose that age because that's when my life came to screeching halt. I found out I was pregnant and decided to settle down a little. I didn't plan on dying all together.  Although it was my choice, I often feel like a small chunk of my life was stolen from me. Don't get me wrong, I wouldn't change a thing. I love my daughter with every piece of my being, but she is the reason I had to grow up so fast. Another was living under the hand of an extremely controlling partner. Luckily that hand has been lifted and I'm free to make my own choices again. And the only thing I choose, and desperately want...is my life back. That fun, exciting part of me. The party girl who could stay up all night, not this "in bed by 10" lame excuse of an adult.  Only problem, is I have no idea where to begin. The people whom I used to call my friends have since gone on with their lives or forgotten I even existed. I'm not my best in social situations. For some odd reason I always think that people are out to get me. Feel free to thank years of teenage torment and humiliation for that.  All I want to know, is where is the starting line to my former lifestyle. Maybe if I knew the answer to that question, I could work my way to the finish. I don't mind if it takes me forever to get there, just as long as I get there...
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmmm...shall I start back up and become an online attention whore? Imagine the fucking possibilities.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tonight I was organizing my friends list on yahoo, deleting people I don't talk to anymore and such. I realized I still have my ex-boyfriend's screen name listed. I very rarely talk to him, but its there just in case I ever need him for anything related to our child. But it got me thinking...it's been almost a year since I ended our relationship. Middle of next month to be exact. It honestly doesn't feel like that much time has passed. I guess one reason is because in a whole year's time, nothing major has happened in my life. I don't do anything or have anything that occupies my time, other than work. This past year has been rather uneventful. Other than taking my first "real" plane ride, there's nothing. No major memorable experiences or fun times. You would think time would drag when you're not having fun, but it passes by at the same rate as when you are. Too quickly. To me, it only seems like a few months ago we were living together. But it really has been a year. I need a fucking hobby, lol. Something to keep me entertained so that time doesn't fly by me anymore.  That should be my goal for my 24th birthday, to find a hobby. Something I'm "into." People always ask me that and I have no idea what to tell them. Some people have sports, others have social activities. True I'm into the arts, but I'm not regularly into it. Just when I feel like it and it quickly bores me. Mainly because art can be very frustrating sometimes. Hmmm...what would be a good hobby for a very artistic, non-athletic, unmotivated person? 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You know, I'm getting tired of trying to take a decent picture of myself. My camera equipment is not exactly the best and I'm never satisfied with my own work. Even worse when the subject is myself. Is the perception of one's self in a mirror completely different from the way a camera captures it. I mean, I look in the mirror and think "ok, I look great...let's go take a picture." But then after the shutter goes off and I see the image, its like "good god, I look like shit!" Maybe its something as simple as the camera being at a different angle than my eyesight. Anyways, I hope to have some new photos posted soon...even if it kills me. And it just might!  By the way, Kathy's Song (VNV Nation Remix) by Apoptygma Berserk is awesome, I can't stop listening to it!
     

    
</post>


</Blog>