<Blog>

<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You are the flame in my heart You light my way in the dark You are the ultimate star You lift me up from above Your unconditional love takes me to paradise  I belong to you And you You belong to me too You make my life complete You make me feel so sweet  Your soul and mind are entwined Before you I was blind But since I've opened my eyes And with you there's no disguise So I could open up my mind I always loved you from the start But I could not figure out That I had to do it everyday So I put away the fight Now I'm gonna live my life  Giving you the most in every way  I belong to you And you You belong to me too You make my life complete You make me feel so sweet
     
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I'm certainly glad that I went curling. Our end played our best game yet, everyone was just on today. Thumped the other end 12-4. Go us.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Uuuuurhghgh. Cops didn't show until 2:00am. Buzzed  me  to let them in. Woke me up. Left around 2:45am, but not before knocking on my door to ask a couple questions. Woke me up,  again . Decided to give up and grabbed a quick hot chocolate at the Blenz around the corner. Asleep at 3:30am. Up now. Feel like skivving off curling today, which pisses me off to no end as I really enjoy it. If I had a good night's sleep I'd be in a great mood and ready to go out. Right now I'm just tired and bitchy and I look like shite...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Figures. Go to bed fucking early because I need to get up at 7:00am for curling. So why the hell am I posting this at twenty after one in the morning? Because the assholes two doors down from me are having a blazing row. Much swearing, yelling and smashing of dishes. Guy goes to leave, not the guy who lives there, must be his partner. Yelling in hallway begins. Am now wide awake. Take frustrated piss. Elevator opens, pounding on doors start, buddy has come back to scream more. Am too frustrated to care, open door: "Hey, do you mind keeping it down a bit? There are other people in this building, I have to get up early and you've woken me up." "Mind your own fucking business, asshole." Words aggrivated assult pop into my mind. Resist said urge. Calmly close the door and call 911 to report domestic disturbance. Am second complaint, police will be here soon. Will enjoy gawping out the door at them. Then sleep... Am walking zombie right now...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Note to Self: Sugar-water, while being a wonderful hair-gel replacement, is very appealing to ants. Shouldn't they all be fucking hibernating or something? I mean it's nearly December! Perhaps I should stick with hair-gel for now...  On another note, it's absolutley sopping wet outside. Ah, Vancouver winter. I suppose I'd better dig out my mask and snorkel before I head out...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well after a week at work with my hair tied back people have all settled into their new nicknames for me. Strangely enough, they all seem to have chosen "The Samurai Warrior" as my new nickname, except for the one pressman who prefers "Goddamn Hippie". Randy in prepress now bows and says "Aaaaah! Sensei!" everytime he sees me, which is utterly hilarious seeming as he's forgotten more than I know about prepress, but it's kind of flattering I guess.  I  would  post a picture of it, but my goddamn digicam is busted. Oh well, I'll get the camera fixed soon enough and post a picture eventually.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, well... Here we go then. In keeping with the stark minimalism I've changed the Blogger button at the bottom of the page to black and white, the links are now grey, bold and underlined, and I've added pictures now. Of course the pictures are greyscale with a limited palette of eight shades of grey. Hooray! Fun!
     
    
</post>

<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I know there's likely a lot more going on that the general public doesn't know, or maybe they do and I just wasn't paying attention, but doesn't it seem a little daft to punish police officers that beat up drug dealers? Isn't that kind of the point?
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Quite a rainy walk home last night. I was soaked, and I was just walking from SkyTrain to home. I think I might start adding pictures to this little blog. We'll see.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wearing a Beckham style,  urlLink double pony-tail  today. Getting no end of teasing and flak about it at work. Don't really care, but it's interesting to note that a few of the guys used to have hair way longer than mine.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, got told off for walking down the street eating ice cream. Some bum figured they'd tell me I'm an asshole for eating ice cream and not giving them the change that I used to buy said ice cream. I just about fucking lost it. I didn't say anything for fear of flipping out and having them freak out more and end up drop-kicking them in the chin... The nerve though. I really don't bloody care if you're homeless. Call me hartless, but seriously: after a long week at work, putting in some OT and long commutes on public transit, I can't deal with people telling me that I owe them the money that I work so hard to earn, when all they do is sit on their ass all day...  On a slightly different note, this webpage looked like shite in Safari. Just saw it over at Ryan's place, hence the switch to the seriously minimal layout. I actually like it better though.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The afternoon has gently passed me by The evening spreads itself against the sky Waiting for tomorrow Is just another day God bid yesterday goodbye  Bring on the night I couldn't stand another hour of daylight Bring on the night I couldn't stand another hour of daylight
     
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Urgh... Up for curling... Yes that's only six hours of sleep since my last post...
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Just got in from a show put on by my friends  urlLink The Panic . I highly recommend going to see one of their shows if you're in or around Vancouver when they play. Excellent stuff.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Four weeks today. I love you.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well last night was better, but still a little sluggish. Network connections, I mean. On the other hand, I had my first ever Krispy Kreme doughnut last night. It was excellent. As good as everyone says they are. I wonder how the coffee was first thing this morning? Dave thought it'd be a wonderful joke to put our left over wasabi from dinner in with the coffee grounds... Bleh... Should be some interesting reactions...
     
    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well last night was, bar none, the least productive night I've ever had at work. Freaking computers. Sometimes I hate them. After multiple crashes, reboots, hang-ups, server meltdowns, Prinergy reboots and all around bad karma, Rod and I got basically nothing done. And I think the bad karma carried over to this morning as I got woken up at 8am by a jackhammer, 9am by the garbage truck, 9:30am by a telemarketer, and I gave up at 10am when the crows and seagulls woke me up... Things seemed to have stopped there though, as it's an incredibly beautiful day when it was forcast to rain...  *crosses fingers that computer problems are fixed*
     
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Urgh... I'm sick as a dog, and it's gross and rainy out and it's forecast to be gloomy/rainy all week... I hope I'm not sick all week.  Curling this weekend, so that's something to look forward to. Maybe I'll give Burgess and Vista a call and go out for dinner with them at some point. That is, if I'm feeling better... Bleh...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, just got home. Ahh, good to be back in Vancouver. Met Phil on the 424, in from England and had no idea where he was going, but I knew the hostel he was heading to and took him there, then caught a cab home. The cabbie had the most pungent BO ever. I seriously nearly threw up in the back seat. I could smell it when I opened the door. *gags*
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So yeah, nothing's really changed at all in this little town I used to call home. It's kind of nice to come to a familiar place and be welcomed by family. Having BBQ'd Steaks tonight and I'm really looking forward to it. Then we're watching T3 on the new DVD player. Not entirely looking forward to that, but eh... Flying out tomorrow. Kind of wish I could stay a little longer.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm posting this from my Mom's laptop in my old house in Cranbrook right now. Wireless technology, my parents are using it and I am not. I feel behind the times. Ah, well... Good flight in, considering we landed and didn't die. Was so foggy the pilot announced that we may have to turn back to Vancouver. He decided to attempt the landing anyways, and it was the roughest landing I've ever had in my life. I couldn't even see the tarmac from my window after we had touched down... Hopefully it won't be a life risking flight on the way back... Kind of weird to be back home but it should be fun.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I just watched Men With Brooms, and thoroughly enjoyed it. I feel utterly Canadian now, and strangely more proud of it, especially since I'm curling now too. Loved the little bits of humour thrown in as well: "and on sheet c representing Kingston, The Tragically Hip..." Muhahaha...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So went out for a nice walk today, saw a woman walking around with a German WWII jacket on... Not too sure how I should feel about that. Eh, oh well.  Got some Christmas shopping done, the most important stuff in my mind. Should all be ready to pick up next week. I'm excited about it and it's all really nice. Getting so close to Christmas now, I can't help but smile as I walk through all the shops and malls with everything all set out.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So yeah, I have this wonderful idea that I'll do laundry today because it's a day off. All I've got to do is go to the bank and get some change. Wait... It's a stat... Banks will be closed... Damnit... I'm getting into the recycling underwear stage and I've got to go in early to work on Wed/Thurs... I'm tempted to pack a suitcase full of dirty laundry to take home to do over the weekend... Hey, it'd save me $20...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh... A rainy day in Vancouver. Back to normal. Grey and dreary. Slept for twelve hours because I had nothing better to do. Ah well, going to Cranbrook this weekend, should be nice to see some family for a bit.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So yes. The Matrix utterly sucked. Good special effect but that's all the movie was. One big special effect... Such a painful let down with plot and character development etc etc...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, um... Just found out that a guy I used to train Karate with murdered his wife on Wednesday night... He works with my uncle so my uncle knows him and he was still training Karate with my mom so my mom knows him, and of course my old Karate Instructor knows him... He has two kids that were training in Karate too... I knew all of them... Holy shit... ...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Watched Minority Report last night. I really like that show, though many think it sucked. Speaking of sucking, I'm going to go see The Matrix: Revoloutions this afternoon. All the reviews I've seen have been like two out of five stars, and Rolling Stone magazine just out and says "At the risk of understatement, The Matrix Revolutions sucks." in the first sentence of their review... So I'm not sure what to expect... I'm meeting some friends after they're done car shopping. That's interesting too, I wonder if they'll find/buy anything today?  There's a chance I could be going to go see Kill Bill for a third time on Sunday, but I'm not sure yet. Yes, I like that movie enough to pay to see it three times... It does not suck.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Six weeks today. I love you.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Sun is shining, the weather is sweet yeah Makes you wanna move those dancing feet For the rescue, here I am I want you to know y'all, here I stand  As the morning gathers the rainbow I want you to know y'all That I'm a rainbow with you  Cause I'm a hero, like Robert DeNiro I know an Ital Rasta man I got to keep I heights Protection until time The sun is shining yeah War is Explosive, you got to demonstrate Demonstrate, you got to demonstrate Don't fight Cause the sun is shining for you There's nothing else to do  Sun is shining, the weather is sweet yeah Makes you wanna move those dancing feet To the rescue, here I am I want you to know y'all, here I stand  As the morning gathers the rainbow I want you to know now That I'm a rainbow with you  Test the eye, fear no evil Channel like a lion, channel like a lion  Some say, money in my pocket But I just can't get your love And the sun is shining, don't fight You got soul, and you're chopping it up aero For you, there's nothing else to do  Sun is shining, the weather is sweet yeah Makes you wanna move those dancing feet To the rescue, here I am I want you to know now, here I stand  As the morning gathers the rainbow I want you to know now That I'm a rainbow with you As the morning gathers the rainbow I'm rougher than rough Cause I'm a rainbow with you  Tougher than tough Channel like a lion yeah This is some fasion yeah Spiritual fasion yeah
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, got a clean bill of health from the Otolaryngologist which is nice. Nothing wrong with me an I've got perfect hearing to boot. Hooray!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I'm definetly going to go into work about an hour early every day. There's a high school just around the corner from SkyTrain where I get off and I can't stand all the snot-nosed brats taking over the whole freaking station/street/sidewalk etc. I feel like  I'm  in high school again. And I dislike that, very much...  Best of luck on your law mid-term Honey!
     
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Whew, just got back from the walk with Pete. Can hardly type my fingers are so cold. It's 5C here, but the moisture in the air just cuts to the bone. So we ended up meeting at the Blenz coffee shop around the corner and walking down Davie to the seawall, around to Science World, down through the scruffy tent city/industrial area, onto the Cambie St. Bridge, over to BC Place and finally up Robson back home. Needless to say it was a very good walk, and nice to be out in the fresh air. Took some pics with my camera, but ended up taking the best pictures right outside the apt. when I was just returning. Nice red sports car parked out front with no one in it, except for this big beautiful white dog sitting in the driver's seat, looking like an impatient chauffer waiting for the passenger who's late again. Couldn't pass up a shot of that.  Being back earlier than I figured is nice. Now I can make up my dinner for work, play a last game of FIFA 2003, grab lunch at The Dish, pick up FIFA 2004 and still head into work nice and early.  Received a phone call that made my day last night. Thanks. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      God, must figure out what I'm doing with my arm in my sleep to screw up my back. Second day in a row where the left side is all knots in my shoulder blade and sore as bloody hell.  Going out for a walk with Pete today, should be good. Don't know if I want to walk all the way to Science World and back, but we'll see...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy crap... I just got up. Must've needed the sleep. So much for doing the dishes this morning... Oh well, not that that upsets me a great deal ;)  Got the tickets yesterday, should be receiving an email itinerary soon. Hooray! My Angel will be home soon!  Arg. It pains me that I slept away such a beautiful morning and now the only time I'll have to go out is my walk from SkyTrain to work... Oh well...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Urrrgh... In from work. So tired. zzzzzzz...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      If anyone knows what music is used in the  urlLink Leggsy  "Supersub" ad, please  urlLink email me ! It's also used in Bend it like Beckham, but it isn't on the soundtrack...  In other music/movie news, Kill Bill is my favourite movie as of now. I bought the soundtrack for the song "Battle Without Honour or Humanity". It's so wonderfully cheesy. I also saw Bulletproof Monk. That is possibly the worst movie I've ever seen. Like Lord of the Rings the animated version badness. In fact it's so bad I'd recommend seeing it just so you know I'm not lying.  Anyhow, off to book some plane tickets!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, back to the grind. Many things to do this week apart from working. Menial labour such as: do the dishes (bleh), do the laundry (bleh), vacuum the house. There are less fun things happening as well like: doctors appointment on Thursday (bleh). But there are nice things to get to such as: buy plane tickets for my beautiful angel for reading break (hooray!). It's shaping up to be a good week. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha, two days and already I'm rethinking the format of what I want to do! Ah well, that's the way things go with personal websites right? Always under constant change... I'll still post song lyrics every now and again, but I think I can better represent myself by actually speaking my mind. Songs can represent so much, but sometimes it's only one or two lines that mean anything.  So I went to see Alien: The Director's Cut today. Never seen any Alien movies before in my life. Not actually as scary as I figured it would be, but a good movie none the less.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Look at the stars, Look how they shine for you, And everything you do, Yeah, they were all yellow.  I came along, I wrote a song for you, And all the things you do, And it was called "Yellow."  So then I took my turn, Oh what a thing to have done, And it was all "Yellow."  Your skin Oh yeah, your skin and bones, Turn into something beautiful, You know, you know I love you so, You know I love you so much.   I swam across, I jumped across for you, Oh what a thing to do. Cos you were all "Yellow,"  I drew a line, I drew a line for you, Oh what a thing to do, And it was all "Yellow."  Your skin, Oh yeah your skin and bones, Turn into something beautiful, And you know For you, I'd bleed myself dry For you, I'd bleed myself dry.  It's true, look how they shine for you,  Look at the stars, Look how they shine for you, And all the things that you do.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What else should I be All apologies What else could I say Everyone is gay What else could I write I don't have the right What else should I be All apologies  In the sun In the sun I feel as one In the sun In the sun I'm married Buried  I wish I was like you Easily amused Find my nest of salt Everything is my fault I'll take all the blame Aqua seafoam shame Sunburn with freezerburn Choking on the ashes of her enemy  All in all is all we are
     
    
</post>

<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy New Year, all.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay, I got a new CF Card for my digicam. And I'm attempting to grow a beard (badly).
     
    
</post>

<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm writing this post on my baby's laptop. Just to let anyone who actually reads this know, I likely won't be updating my blog daily over the holidays. So Season's Greetings, Merry Christmas, Happy Hanukkah, or anything else I may have missed.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Whenever I'm alone with you You make me feel like I am home again Whenever I'm alone with you You make me feel like I am whole again  Whenever I'm alone with you You make me feel like I am young again Whenever I'm alone with you You make me feel like I am fun again  However far away I will always love you However long I stay I will always love you Whatever words I say I will always love you  I will always love you  Whenever I'm alone with you You make me feel like I am free again Whenever I'm alone with you You make me feel like I am clean again  However far away I will always love you However long I stay I will always love you Whatever words I say I will always love you  I will always love you   Welcome home Jen. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ONE MORE DAY! OH MY GOD, I'M SO EXCITED!!
     
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Two Days! Whoo Hoo!!
     
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Three more days until I'm reunited with the love of my life. I hope I'll be able to work, and I won't be too distracted... I'm so excited.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I hate sore throats. Hurts to eat, hurts to drink, hurts to talk... Better go see if I need anti-biotics. Don't want to have a sore throat when my love gets home in four days! I'm so excited! Four more days! I love you so much!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This  will be the worst movie ever. My childhood has been ruined.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, went to a house party with Chris. Seems like this is becoming our weekend routine. It still boggles my mind how some people cannot have a good time without liquor and drugs. Quoth the 18 year old who looked like a 14 year old with stretchy track pants and pretty much no shirt: "Oh My GAWD! If I don't, like, get some marijuana soon I'll just, like, die!"  All the people, except Chris, Ben and I, were totally pasted. Eventually one guy got overly rambunctious trying to hug the other 18 year old who looked like a 14 year old, and tripped onto the kitchen table sending empties and half full bottles flying everywhere. A little while later the same guy dropped the fourty of vodka in the kitchen (smash). When the drug dealers in their pouffy jackets and sideways hats showed up, and the Aussies put on the Oh Brother, Where Art Thou soundtrack and started screaming/singing Man Of Constant Sorrow, we decided it was time to leave.  It was a fun party in which to observe drunk/stoned students in their natural habitat. I realised after we left that Chris, Ben and I were 5-7 years older than everyone there. Maybe we should stick with the pub crawling scene...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Urrrrghghghh... Had a wicked sore throat last night. Bad cough, y'know, the kind that keeps you up. Decided to have one tablespoon of NyQuil. Am never using NyQuil again. Slept like a stone, but it was everything I had in me to drag my ass out of bed this morning. And now I feel stoned. Well I guess I shouldn't say that, seeming as I've never done drugs, but if I had to bet money, I'd say this is what stoned feels like.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      That there, that's not me I go where I please I walk through walls I float down the Liffey  I'm not here This isn't happening I'm not here, I'm not here  In a little while I'll be gone The moment's already passed Yeah, it's gone  I'm not here This isn't happening I'm not here, I'm not here  Strobe lights and blown speakers Fireworks and hurricanes  I'm not here This isn't happening I'm not here, I'm not here
     
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hard to believe how many drunk idiots there are out on a Tuesday night. It's 1:45 in the morning and I could've easily gotten into three fights just walking up the street to my house. Drunk guys don't like my long hair, I've figured this out. It makes them feel insecure about their masculinity...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So the BC Ferries are on strike and a couple really good friends who live on the island are now stuck. Hopefully everything will get resolved soon as they were planning on bussing home to Cranbrook for Christmas.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "Some participants expressed a certain amount of annoyance at what is perceived as a systematic attempt by Canadians to make the statement that they are not Americans by sporting the maple leaf. This underscores the American sensitivity at feeling rejected by the rest of the world ...."  Awww, Boo Hoo. Poor Americans are insecure after their war and want us to stop being Canadian.   urlLink Read the story .
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Back to the grind...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Have to start cleaning things up a bit as it's only a week and a half now until I'm reunited with the love of my life. I'm so excited.  :)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh no... I just got a camera and now I want a  urlLink new one ...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Current Music: Peter Gabriel - Big Time
     
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, birthday money. I've just spent way too much on CD's... Oh well, I love music what can I say?  Going to go see The Last Samurai tomorrow. From what I hear it's very, very good.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's the day after my birthday!  But seriously, there's not much to tell. I just went to work as per usual and upheld the tradition of buying doughnuts for the whole company. Five dozen later... No one asked me the yearly trite question: "So, do you feel any older?", which is unfortunate as, for the first time in my life, I would've been able to say yes. But all in all it was a great day and I'm going to use all my gift money to buy way too many CDs.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's my birthday!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So  urlLink this  is pretty darn ridiculous. Not only am I paying levies on blank CDs that I don't even use to burn music, now  urlLink SOCAN  wants to tax ISPs because of people downloading music. So now I'll be paying more taxes that go to musicians even though I don't download music on my computer.  Note so SOCAN: All people who download music use the internet, but not all people who use the internet download music.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, lovely foggy walk home last night. I love the West Coast Fog. So moody. I feel like I should be in a movie or something when I'm walking around downtown Vancouver at one in the morning in the fog.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hooray for getting people arrested. Was on my way home last night when I witnessed a guy threaten a Chinese food take-out guy, along with calling him a bunch of racial slurs and kick in windows in two restaurants on his way up the street. Followed him and ran around an alley to cut him off where I knew there was a police office. Got the cops out there and they arrested him and stuffed him in the paddy wagon, but not before he told the cops that they're "not so tough, let me out of these cuffs and I'll kill you all." Nice guy.  Feel incredibly good about making a difference. Want to go be a cop now.
     
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Saftey Net . An excellent site about men taking a stand against violence and rape against women. Take some time to sit down and read it and then go tell all your friends about it.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Knew it was coming. Finally saw it today. Two people wearing the same type of Diesel jeans with the same "dirt stains" and "wear holes" in the same place. Of course these guys didn't know each other but one was walking down the street about five paces behind the other. I thought that was so funny. Pay $400 for a pair of jeans only to have some guy wearing the same exact pair, right down to the holes...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dieser Pfosten ist vollständig ein Witz. Ich verwendete Google, um dieses in Deutschen zu übersetzen. Haha.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, renewed my domain for another year. So, I wonder if it'll still be this format by the end of it, or if it'll be something completely different. Knowing me, it'll be the latter...
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just listening to The Beatles live on their first tour of the US on the radio. I can't quite grasp the mentality behind Beatlemania. They just finished playing a set on the Ed Sullivan show and the audience, whom were mostly women, just did not stop shrieking through the entire song. Not cheering, not whistling,  shrieking . I don't know, maybe you just had to be there. I should ask my Mom and Dad if they got swept up in it...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Starting to wonder if digital photography is really the thing for me. I love film, but then there's also the fact that you have to be plugged into a computer most of the time to "process" your "digital negatives". I spent eight hours a day working on a computer, and at least one hour at home surfing the internet. I don't really feel like spending so much time on the computer, and I'm starting to dislike how much time I am spending on it. Yeah, I think for me, film is the way to go still.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm on my way home last night, passed the Stone Temple Night Club and notice a heated argument between four people. It's starting to get a little physical. I've always had a fascination with street fights so I figure I'll watch some poor shit get his ass whipped. Big mistake. Let me break it up for you. Three obviously-on-steroids white guys arguing with one black guy. Black guy comes across the street (where I am) and starts lipping off the guys again. "The Group" comes across the street and things really get physical, one guy grabs black guy by the throat. At this point they're moving way too close to me and I'm starting to back away. Then black guy reaches into his pocket and whips out a big-ass knife and starts swinging. I move, guy next to me (one of "The Group") gets slashed in the arm, someone pulls out the pepper spray, and I get the fuck out of dodge...  Needless to say I think I'm through partying for now...
     
    
</post>

<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bills, bills, bills...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, what's up with the alarming number of sick individuals preying on the destitute women of the downtown eastside in Vancouver? It's hard for me to even try and understand the line of thinking that allows them to torture, rape and maybe even kill these women. If there's one area that makes me believe in capital punishment, this is it.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So there. That's the hairstyle that's earned me the nickname "The Last Samurai". Or "Goddamn Hippie" if you talk to that one guy in the press room...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did something to kink my neck pretty bad yesterday/last night. I think I slept on it funny. Hurts like the dickens and feels all swollen. Ouch.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What the heck is happening to January?? It's three-quarters gone already, holy crap.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, OK... I'm cleaning and doing dishes, etc today... Bleh.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh... Lazy weekends are the best. Then again I should probably be cleaning, but what the hell...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Take my hand You know I'll be there, If you can I'll cross The sky for you love. For I have promised, oh To be with you tonight And for the time that will come.  Take my hand You know I'll be there, If you can I'll cross The sky for your love. And I understand These winds and tides, This change of times Won't drag you away. Hold on, hold on tightly, Hold on and don't let go Of my love.  The storms will pass It won't be long now. The storms will pass But my love lasts forever.  And take my hand, You know I'll be there, If you can I'll cross the sky For your love. Give you what I hold dear, Hold on, hold on tightly. Hold on, hold on tightly. Rise up, rise up with wings, Like eagles you'll run, you'll run You'll run and not grow weary.  Take my hand, take my hand. Hold on, hold on tightly. Hold on, hold on tightly. This love lasts forever, This love lasts forever, Take my hand, Take my hand.   U2 - Drowning Man 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Laundry sucks...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy crap, where did that weekend go?
     
    
</post>

<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just woke up to a big Silverfish on the ceiling above my bed. Ew.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went out to see Big Fish last night. I really liked it. Great show. I can see that it's one of those "Love or Hate" movies though. It was free, and that helped too.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw the drunkest person ever last night. This Japanese business man on Robson St. waiting at a crosswalk, just kind of swaying. His umbrella slipped out of his hand, and as he bent over to pick it up he did this weird sort of 360 degree turn, like a dog getting comfortable, and proceeded to fall flat on his face. Now when I say business man, I mean clean cut, 3-piece suit, over coat, leather breifcase, etc. so needless to say it was a strange sight. Luckily he had a friend with him that laughed, picked him up and hailed a cab.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well. It's back to typical Vancouver winter weather (ie: rain). Unfortunately that doesn't mix well with the cold, snowy weather we've had. It's uuugly out. wet, slush, ice, slush, wet, slush and slush. Gross.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh... I love this weather Vancouver's having right now. Reminds me of home. Although the busses careening wildly down the street is a little scary and un-homelike...
     
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh... Back to the grind. Work, workout routine, eating healthy, etc. Holidays are a nice break though.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Witnessed an accident last night. Thank God noone was hurt, it was pretty bad. Everyone was stupid, driver A was beyond speeding, driver B doesn't shoulder check and attempts to pull a U-turn from his parking space at the side of the road. Talk about T-Bone... I think in the eyes of ICBC, driver B will be at fault. In my eyes though, theres no excusing driver A for shouting and yelling and swearing and threatening and screaming racial slurs... I think that's just uncalled for. Sure you can be angry, but when buddy has his wife and three kids with him that just makes it worse when you call them all: "Stupid motherf**king ch**ks". Jerk.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel good It's a fine day The way the sun hits off the runway A cloud shifts The plane lifts She moves on   Already counting the days to Spring. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TGIF! Again! Whee!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TGIF! Well, I don't work Fridays, so Thursdays are my Fridays if you catch my drift...
     
    
</post>

<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So generally I don't post more than once a day, but this here's an exception because  urlLink Jen  has issued a challenge and it must be answered. On a side note, I may as well post that the new-ish Sloan album Action Pact is utterly amazing. I bought it last year when it came out, listened to one song and put it away. I put it on yesterday and listened to the whole thing and I'm kicking myself for not doing that before. It's a great album and it's starting to embody my Vancouver spring 2004. OK, so, on to the challenge...   1. Favourite book and why?   The Lord of the Rings, all three, because I enjoy the fantastical elements.   2. Favourite movie and why?   The LOTR trilogy, because it looks exactly as how I pictured the books.   3. Best friend (other than current partner) and why this person?   Too difficult to select one friend out of the wonderful few that I've had as "the best".   4. What are you doing now?   Answering this challenge.   5. What do you wish you were doing now?   Taking a windy walk along the seawall with Jen.   6. Your personal motto OR a song that describes you perfectly?   Give your all, but never be afraid to fail, you always learn the most from your mistakes.   7. Personal hero and why?   Jen, for doing what she wants and never letting anyone/thing hold her back.   8. Why do you have a blog?   I figured my daily ramblings may interest someone on The Interweb... 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, so two of my New Year's resolutions were to get in shape and eat healthier. I'm happy to say I've accomplished both. One resolution that should have been made but wasn't was to cook more at home--yes it is possible to eat out healthily! So I'm making that another resolution as of yesterday. And so far I made a great lunch, and also cooked a nice pasta dish for dinner at work. I even have enough leftovers to switch it up today and have the pasta for lunch and a huge salad for dinner. And all that for about half the price of what it usually costs to eat out for four days. Nice!
     
    
</post>

<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bwahahaha... And we thought Dubya was bad...   "Reports that say that something hasn't happened are always interesting to me, because as we know, there are known knowns; there are things we know we know. We also know there are known unknowns; that is to say we know there are some things we do not know. But there are also unknown unknowns - the ones we don't know we don't know"  - Donald Rumsfeld   Note: If you have the Real Audio player click  urlLink here .
     
    
</post>

<date>20,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I've been really lazy with my blog this week. Forgive me, but Jen's home and I've also been busy at work, so I haven't had much time. As Jen's posted in her  urlLink LJ , I'm now sporting a Beck's style  urlLink Fauxhawk  haircut, albeit with no colouring. Sure it's, like, so two years ago, but I don't care. I've never been trendy...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A thousand years, a thousand more,  A thousand times a million doors to eternity  I may have lived a thousand lives, a thousand times An endless turning stairway climbs  To a tower of souls  If it takes another thousand years, a thousand wars,  The towers rise to numberless floors in space I could shed another million tears, a million breaths, A million names but only one truth to face  A million roads, a million fears A million suns, ten million years of uncertainty  I could speak a million lies, a million songs, A million rights, a million wrongs in this balance of time But if there was a single truth, a single light A single thought, a singular touch of grace Then following this single point , this single flame, The single haunted memory of your face   I still love you  I still want you A thousand times the mysteries unfold themselves  Like galaxies in my head  I may be numberless, I may be innocent  I may know many things, I may be ignorant  Or I could ride with kings and conquer many lands Or win this world at cards and let it slip my hands  I could be cannon food, destroyed a thousand times  Reborn as fortune's child to judge another's crimes  Or wear this pilgrim's cloak, or be a common thief  I've kept this single faith, I have but one belief  I still love you  I still want you A thousand times the mysteries unfold themselves  Like galaxies in my head On and on the mysteries unwind themselves  Eternities still unsaid   'Til you love me   Sting - A Thousand Years 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I reserve the right to be a grump today considering it's Valentine's Day and I'm alone... I'm glad Jen's home tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Was on the party bus back into downtown tonight. Am starting to see the rarity in being able to have a good time sans alcohol/drugs. "Well last weekend I was so drunk when..." or "Last night I was so baked and..." were the story lead-ins for everyone having a conversation on the bus. It's funny, I went through a small phase like that during my ten months living in Halifax, but the first time I ever woke up in the drunk-tank was the last time I've ever been drunk. But it seems like most of these people don't get it. They just party it up all the time and get wasted/stoned whenever possible. Bah, I feel old saying "it's a phase", and it's doubly weird since most of the people are older than me... Then again I've never been the party going type. I don't know, I'm just ranting now, but it boggles my mind how the majority of society can't have a good time without some sort of alcoholic/narcotic influence...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      She calls out to the man on the street Sir, can you help me?  It’s cold and I’ve nowhere to sleep, Is there somewhere you can tell me?  He walks on, doesn’t look back He pretends he can’t hear her Starts to whistle as he crosses the street Seems embarrassed to be there  Oh think twice, it’s another day for You and me in paradise Oh think twice, it’s another day for you, You and me in paradise  Think about it  She calls out to the man on the street He can see she’s been crying She’s got blisters on the soles of her feet Can’t walk but she’s trying  Oh think twice, it’s another day for You and me in paradise Oh think twice, it’s just another day for you, You and me in paradise  Just think about it  Oh lord, is there nothing more anybody can do Oh lord, there must be something you can say  You can tell from the lines on her face You can see that she’s been there Probably been moved on from every place ’Cos she didn’t fit in there  Oh think twice, it’s another day for You and me in paradise Oh think twice, it’s just another day for you, You and me in paradise  Just think about it  It’s just another day for you and me in paradise It’s just another day for you and me in paradise Paradise   Phil Collins - Another Day In Paradise 
     
    
</post>

<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God, why does dealing with the Government have to be so   freakin   difficult? I just want to pay off my $110 loan all at once. No I don't want a 5 month amortization period. Argh, I'm so pissed off I could just scream and pull my hair out. And it doesn't help that the people on the phone speak next to no English.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I've got a mouse in my house...  urlLink Abell Pest Control  was just by to bait my house. A few live bait traps and they also gave me some weird sticky paper, I guess it's kind of like fly paper for mice. I hope the traps work and I don't end up catching a mouse on this paper. I don't know what I'd do with it, though it likely wouldn't be what I'm supposed to: "just take it downstairs, roll up the paper and  stomp on it  and throw it in the garbage." I hope I didn't go too pale when the Abell guy said that...
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went out to the last night of the 10th Annual  urlLink Rock For Choice  show in Vancouver. Pretty wicked turn-out and hardcore rockin music. All for an excellent cause.  On a semi-unrelated note, am now completely into The Smalls, thanks to Ryan of  urlLink The Panic . I'd say The Smalls are an unclassifiable blend of rock, punk, country and speed metal. They hail from Edmonton, Alberta and it's a shame they're not making music anymore, but they did put out four awesome albums. I'm coming to appreciate Canadian music so much.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Through the water, from the sky On the wind or in our minds What is there for me to do Find my way back home to you Before the autumn air turns black Before the angry men attack Together when the sky falls through A flash of red, I'll fuse with you  Fuse with you, I'm dying to Running to your side Now it's here, the pain, the fear Tha fall have all arrived A kiss goodbye  In the city, unprepared Run and hide, stand and stare Buildings crumble in my head Wave a flag, raise the dead Money fuels the fires of war Only love worth dying for Together when the sky falls through A flash of red, I'll fuse I'll fuse with you  Fuse with you, I'm dying to Running to your side Now it's here, the pain, the fear Tha fall have all arrived Oh my dear, the pain, the fear The fall have all arrived A kiss goodbye  We're all the same, running from the flames We're on our way, don't you feel it The air will ring, oh the end of everything We're on our way, don't you feel it The air will ring, the end of everything We're all the same, don't they feel it   The Folk Implosion - Fuse 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bwahahaha, I  love  this weeks MacLean's magazine cover. "Canadians to Bush: Hope you lose, eh?"  ehehehehehe *snort*
     
    
</post>

<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I'm totally sick of the Janet Jackson thing. Why? Because I'm sickened with the media. "Jackson more over the top than usual", "Jackson bares herself on Half-Time Show". Hell even  urlLink canada.com  is running a poll "Were you offended by Janet Jackson's breast bearing Superbowl stunt?"  Pardon me? What the fuck? Why isn't the poll "Should Justin Timberlake be charged with assult? Yes/No"? Why are people saying "Oh she must've planned it, she had a 'pastie' on her nipple"? So putting a pastie on to prevent a nipple erection gives Mr. Timberlake the right to rip off part of her costume? Have people not seen the pictures, and observed how utterly mortified she is? How it's obviously not something that she intended? Someone should direct Mr. Timberlake to  urlLink The Safety Net  and have him read up on the subject of violence against women. Men like Justin Timberlake make me sick. And that's unfortunate, because there are too many men like that in the world. Grr.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In pitch dark I go walking in your landscape. Broken branches trip me as I speak. Just 'cause you feel it doesnt mean it's there. Just 'cause you feel it doesnt mean it's there.  There's always a siren Singing you to shipwreck. (Don't reach out, don't reach out) Steer away from these rocks  We'd be a walking disaster. (Don't reach out, don't reach out)  Just 'cause you feel it doesn't mean it's there. (There's someone on your shoulder) Just 'cause you feel it doesn't mean it's there. (There's someone on your shoulder)  There there  Why so green and lonely? Heaven sent you to me.  We are accidents Waiting waiting to happen.  We are accidents Waiting waiting to happen.   Radiohead - There There 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Blah... Feeling depressed, and the gloomy Vancouver weather is not really helping. Don't really know what's up, just woke up feeling down. Oh well...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Had one of the most abnormal, yet fun and satisfying nights last night. Ended up at  urlLink The Panic's  jam space and got thrown on the drum kit and we all messed around for a few hours. I'm not a spectacular drummer, but at least I can keep time. Not bad for the third time on a kit in fifteen years...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am exploring the inside. I find it desolate. I do implore these confines now as they penatrate, "Recreate me."  I'm hovering throughout time. I crumble in these days. I crumble, I cannot find reflection in these days.  If you listen, Listen close, beat-by-beat, You can hear when the heart stops. I saved the pieces when it broke And ground them all to dust.  I am destroyed by the inside. I disassociate. I hope to destroy the outside. It will alleviate and elevate me.  Like water flowing into lungs, I'm flowing through these days. As morphine tears through deadened veins I'm numb in these days.  I know what died that night. It can never be brought back to life. Once again I know.  If you listen, Listen close, beat-by-beat, You can hear when the heart stops. I saved the pieces when it broke And ground them all to dust.   AFI - Bleed Black 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been having fun with Jen for her short stay. Although she's quite busy with her LEAF seminar. Ahh well. She'll be home for the summer soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whee, off to pick up Jen.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aaaaaaaahhhhh. Ow. I'm so sore today. Good Lord, I can hardly move. Karate on Friday, Curling all day on Saturday and then rock climbing for a few hours on Sunday is probably not the best idea... Urgh... Wondering if I should skip my excercise routine...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw the funniest thing walking home tonight. Cops pulling up to the Starbucks at the corner of Thurlow and Davie, and the junior parter is stuck with the task of getting coffees, etc. for the both of them. Just as she's opening the squad car door, a pickup truck blows a red light turning left from Thurlow onto Davie going extremely fast, with some floppy haired teenager driving, hanging his head out the open window going "OINKY! OINKY! OINKY!". What the hell were they expecting? I'm not sure because they sure as hell look shocked when the lights went on, the partner shut the door, and the driver busted out one of those awesome movie style cop turns. You know the ones. Where the tires are squealing/smoking and they do a super quick 180. I felt like I was watching  urlLink Starsky & Hutch . Haha, stupid shits...
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, Karate went even better last night. I felt like I had more energy and stamina than the week before. Hopefully it won't be long until I get it back to acceptable levels. Went and watched Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels afterwards at Chris' place. Probably shouldn't have, as I didn't get home till 1:30, and it's now 6:45 and I've been up for fourty five minutes. Oh well.  Curling Bonspiel today. I'll be curling from 9am to 6pm. Should be a really good time.  Have had my hair re-cut. It's the full on Beckham Fauxhawk now. Colour and all. It's more subdued than before though, as the ridge doesn't stand up nearly as high. The colouring is pretty subtle too, only a couple shades lighter than my natural colour. And I've made sure that if I style it down it looks totally normal.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a week... I'm glad it's Thursday...
     
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The flowers are out and spring is in the air! Hooray! And the weather has been unbeatable lately...
     
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I knew there'd be retribution for Steve Moore's hit on Markus Naslund, and I was even pretty sure Bertuzzi would be the one to do it. What I didn't figure on was that he'd break Moore's neck with a sucker punch from behind. While I support retaliation on Moore for his vicious hit, Todd went about it the complete wrong, un-sportsmanlike way. Poor form Bert.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well... I meant to post yesterday, but oh well. It's 1:30, so I only missed it by an hour and a half. I went up to Lynn Valley on the North Shore on Saturday and it was pretty much a spiritual experience. I've never been in such a beautiful place in my life. I'm definetly going back, and I'm definetly going to be exposing a lot of reversal films in that place. I'm utterly speechless in trying to describe it though. Hopefully my images can do it justice...
     
    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lost again  Broken and weary  Unable to find my way  Tail in hand  Dizzy and clearly unable to  Just let this go   I am surrendering to the gravity and the unknown  Catch me heal me lift me back up to the sun  I choose to live   I fell again  Like a baby unable to stand on my own  Tail in hand  Dizzy and clearly unable to just let this go  High and surrendering to the gravity and the unknown  Catch me heal me lift me back up to the sun  I choose to live, I choose to live, I choose to live   Catch me heal me lift me back up to the sun  Help me survive the bottom   Calm these hands before they  Snare another pill and  Drive another nail down another  Meaty hole Please release me   I am surrendering to the gravity and the unknown  Catch me heal me lift me back up to the sun  I choose to live, I choose to live   A Perfect Circle - Gravity 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saw the most hilarious Juxtaposition on the way into work yesterday. Big Lexus SUV, Gold plated or something. Not chrome, it seriously looked like gold. Tricked out wheels, thumping stereo, urban-chic black guy driving it. Listening to possibly the most vulgar gansta rap I've heard. Lots of Niggas, and bitches and hos and mothafuckas and glocks and bustin caps, etc etc etc etc... As he rolls past me I notice his rear lisence plate holder, which oddly enough is gold as well, it says: "In God I Trust". And off to the right of that there's a little gold fish with "Jesus" in it. I just had to laugh out loud. This is the same kind of stuff I find funny as when the rappers themselves win awards for spewing more obscenity than last year, and the first person they thank on the podium is "Our wonderful Lord Jesus Christ, without whom, none of this would be possible."  Do they really think Jesus would listen to their crap? WWJLT? (haha)...
     
    
</post>

<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy crap have I ever been lazy... Sorry. I'll try and post more often...
     
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Writing this from work, so will be quick. Jen's home! YAY! All is right with the world.  :)
     
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a weekend. Didn't end up getting anything done at all that I needed to, except a bit of laundry, but not even all of that. I did, however, do some rock climbing and had the best day at the gym yet. Killed some routes that have been mocking me for a while. I'd like to try climbing with Jen when she gets home. Which is tomorrow. It's seriously hard to believe we've been apart for nearly a year now. We're one third of the way there. I can't wait to pick her up in the airport tomorrow. It's going to be really special. I promise to try and keep posting when she's home. ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, forgot to write about nearly having a new life experience on Thursday evening. Coming home from work, and I've decided to walk down Granville to Davie, and then up Davie in the alley through the back. As I've unlocked the gate and started to walk down the path, nothing is out of the ordinary. Now if you've been through the back of my apartment complex, you know that the pathway is below the level of the grass, and there's a bit of a corner where part of the grass protrudes out from the rest. As I walk past that corner a quick movement catches my eye. I look down and see a very tense, very scared skunk. I calmly try to keep walking, and thank God the skunk didn't let go. So nearly two life experiences actually: one, getting sprayed by a skunk and two, having to take a bath in tomato juice...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So on my way into work today I see a shirt in a womens clothing store on Robson that says "Shake your coconuts!" and has two strategically placed coconuts on the shirt. Now what would you call that? As a man I don't really think it's my place to say "That's inappropriate", but I appeal to the feminists I know and anyone who may read this, what do you think of that? Isn't that just inviting unwanted attention? I should also note it was a fairly low cut, spaghetti strap tank top.  That kind of leads into my new pet peeve: Club Wear. What the hell happened to sexy style? Now it seems whenever I'm walking down Granville at night, the women that are out clubbing are trying to do it with as little clothing as possible. To me that's not sexy, and (if I were single) I would be totally turned off of trying to strike up a conversation with that person. Then again, maybe the people in those clubs, men included, are just looking to get fucked. Literally. Not my scene.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So someone has taken to smoking cigarettes and marijuana out in the hallway of my apartment. Grr. Stinks so much.  In other news, I spent some time last night looking at some design websites such as  urlLink Computer Love  and  urlLink Newstoday® . I'm thinking I'd like to redesign my website. Now it would be something completely casual, as I just don't have the time or dedication do do a complete site overhaul, nor do I really have content with which to fill it. I think I'll just take out the image on the left and add a weekly splash page. Then maybe I'll slowly build on that, but who knows.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry I've missed a couple days. I've been so busy. Had the SunRun on Sunday, which I nearly missed, then Chris and I went and played soccer right afterwords so yeah, my legs are friggin sore. Yesterday was nicely busy at work and then I made it back into town soon enough to catch the third period of the game. Pretty exciting that Matt Cooke tied it up with 5 seconds left, we nearly blew the roof off Steamworks. Auld played really well, but where were his defencemen? Two huge stops, but impossible to not give up a rebound on that second stop. Someone should've been there to clear the puck. Ah well. Every bar was totally crowded afterwords. People going to drown their sorrows I'm sure. Montreal though hey? Sweet.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This just in:  urlLink Vegetarians make better lovers!  Seriously, give me a fucking break. I hate PETA.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I guess we won. Downtown just erupted. So much for sleep. If I don't sound enthused, it's because the way the Canucks have been playing this series, I'm not too sure how deserved the win is...
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Stopped at an arcade on my way home last night. Not something I usually do at all, but I couldn't help it. They had this "game" called Dragon Punch set up right in the front window. It was less of a game than a competition. You hit a hanging punching bag as hard as you can and a computer measures your power. The high score was 6980 and I got 6940 on my first shot, so that's not too bad considering a most of the people weren't breaking 5500. It was pretty fun, but eventually this guy came in and was just glaring at people as he pulled off flashy martial arts moves on the bag. He wasn't putting money in the machine or actually hitting the bag hard, just touching it, but I'm thinking he was wanting to get into a fight. He would, for example, walk right in front of someone about to put in a coin, glare at me for a second and then do some roundhouse kick. Technically his moves were good, but I just didn't understand what he was trying to pull. He never said anything at all. He'd single out one person, glare at them, then do a move. It was pretty weird. I put up with it for a couple minutes then left, I don't have the time for that sort of arrogance. I don't get people like that.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So Kill Bill Vol. 2 opens tomorrow. I think I'm gonna have to see that. I also want to see Hellboy. I hear the comic is just great, so I may pick one or two up at Golden Age Collectibles. Other than that, it's so fantastically busy at work we're all looking forward to the weekend.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I guess Johan Hedberg isn't quite the upgrade from Dan Cloutier that The Province was touting him to be yesterday. Oops. I'm sort of looking forward to reading The Province today to see the people who were poo-pooing Cloutier yesterday lambaste Hedberg today. Ahh, the media is so Fickle.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, back to the grind. A short week though, so that's okay. My laziness has caught up with me though. Now that I didn't do any grocery shopping on the weekend, there's nothing in the house, and I won't have time to get anything before I go to work. So now I have to eat out and there's not much in the way of choices out there aside from fast food. Bleh.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lazy day today. Didn't do too much at all. Just went for a walk and that's about it. Kind of sucks actually, I feel like I've wasted my day off. Oh well, it was a pretty good weekend, so that kind of makes up for it.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went on a shopping binge yesterday and bought way too much stuff. But it's all good stuff. Sporty stuff so it's stuff that I'll always be able to use. I picked up a Soccer ball, a pair of cleats, rock climbing shoes and a chalk bag. Thank god for MasterCard. Got to use my climbing shoes today. Chris and I figured since we'd been doing gym climbing so much, but now I had shoes, we'd go out to Lighthouse park and do some bouldering around there. There's nothing like being pasted on a wall 30 feet over the water with the hot BC sun beating down on you. So fun.  Got to hook up with my Uncle Ferdy from Cranbrook who's living here now. Ended up rocking out to a sweet heavy metal album that I just picked up by Probot. Got stoked to hear loud music and ended up a the Cobalt Motor Hotel on Main St. just by SkyTrain. Wicked hard, loud music that got better and better before totally breaking down at the end of the night when one of the band members of Goatsblood got into a fight with an audience member. The band kept playing as he ditched his guitar and took a flying leap off the stage to pummel the guy. "Just another night at the Cobalt," Ferdy assured me. Sweet.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Key to feeling good #1  (Listed out of order)  Drink water. Lots of water. Canadian health officials say to drink twelve 8oz. glasses of water a day. Try it. It's hard, because that's a lot of water, but you'll notice how much better you feel right away. Your joints will feel fluid, your eyesight will seem better and your concentration won't lapse. You'll feel fantastic.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went for a nice little hike around Buntzen Lake today with Ryan. Never been there before, but it's extremely nice. I'd love to spend a little more time around that area. Looks like there's some really awesome hikes in there as well. It'd be cool to go up there with some people and maybe do a two day hike this summer.  Can't stop watching the trailer for  urlLink Garden State . The more I watch it the more I see going on in the background. I also realise that this will be a very powerful and emotional movie. I'm starting to get emotional watching the trailer. It's the music. No not just that, the music, directors vision and the cinematography. It's everything. It's possibly the best trailer I've ever seen.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well. Super busy at work this week, so that's my lame excuse for not posting anything.  As a testament to how much I  don't  drink anymore, I went out for a drink with Brian, a buddy from work, last night after my shift. I had  one  drink and I was buzzing. No not drunk, I'm not that sad, just able to feel it. Oh well, I don't really miss it anyways.  Just looking around on  urlLink Apple  and found  urlLink this . All I can say is: WOW.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seriously, why do movie companies paste stuff on cool box sets? If I want to see the chapter listing I'll look at the booklet that comes with the movie. Don't, for God's sake, paste crap on nicely designed box sets. See The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers Special Extended DVD Edition for more details.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been pouring over all my graphic design books, which are mostly by Josef Müller-Brockmann and Emil Ruder, and I've decided that design nowadays is totally lacking in good typography. Designers of yesterday [being before computers/desktop publishing] that had a fundamental grasp on design methods and techniques could create typographic solutions to design problems with little or no reliance on photographs, icons or images of any sort. I've decided that that is what I'm going to strive for in my work: typographic emphasis rooted in classic constructivist [Swiss] design.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's a nice little site. Not much on it right now, but the dTree JavaScript is really cool, and it's exactly what I've been looking for to put on my new website that I'm developing. So, without further adieu:  urlLink Destroydrop . Go there.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, to be in Dublin for  urlLink this . Image Now Gallery is putting on a four week exhibition of Josef Müller-Brockmann's posters. 48 of them, so twelve every week. Admission is free. MB is my favourite designer ever and to be there to see his actual posters in person would be possibly the most inspiring thing ever.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whent to see Shrek 2 last night. It was great. Every bit as good as the original, which is a very good thing. It seems to me that so many movie sequels just pale in comparison to the originals, so it's nice to the the writing, directing, comedy, etc. all at the same levels. There were also some awesome trailers before the show. The new  urlLink Incredibles  trailer and  urlLink The Terminal  trailer. Some of the not so hot trailers included  urlLink Spongebob Squarepants The Movie  *shudder*
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Hell Media  has to be one of the most beautiful sites on the Internet. I love it.  I see that  urlLink Nintendo  is/was showing a really cool game to be released soon called  urlLink Paper Mario 2 . It looks awesome. A Mario Bros. RPG [as was the first]. I think I may have to pick it up. See  urlLink IGN  for more details.  Speaking of  urlLink IGN , I really hate the new redesign as I cannot use Internet Explorer with it anymore. Boo!
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Found some nice looking pixel sites.   urlLink Pixel Forest  [all in Chinese though]  urlLink Super Totto   I've found so many, I'll have to make a links page or something, as it would take up way too much space to try and post it all here. It's inspiring. I think I'm going to try my hand at some pixel art soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, much better. Didn't do too much today except some hardcore spring cleaning of the apartment. Everything looks shiny and new now. And much, much more organised.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While the new graphics and everything look bloody amazing, and I'm super hyped for the game, I'm also fairly disappointed that it seems the lovely cel-shading has been done away with. I guess that's from everyone crying sour grapes over "teh kiddie" graphics. Personally I was one of the people, whom were few, that were ecstatic about The Wind Waker's graphics and felt they suited the Zelda franchise much better than the OoT style graphics. Miyamoto-san says he wanted this adventure to be more "mature", but I think they could've easily achieved the same feeling with cel-shaded graphics. Imagine The Wind Waker with a dull, earthy colour palette and lots of volumetric weather effects. Would've been sweet. I'll still cling to the hope that, as Nintendo must've been developing this new Zelda in secret, they're doing the same right now with a cel-shaded game...
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, in keeping with my lo-tech theme, I'm completely enamoured with pixels. I've been finding myself playing around with Photoshop, and creating nothing but hand-drawn, little pixel-perfect artworks. Icons, pixel fonts and the like. I'm really enjoying myself. I figure over the summer I'll spend time just rearranging my blog and designing stuff for it until I finally redesign the whole thing. Huzzah for old technology. Vectors? Who need's em!  Well That's a little overly sarcastic. I still love my vectors too, but I'm totally diggin' the pixels. I'd love to be running an old version of Photoshop on, say, System 7.5.3. Yeah.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I realise that I'm a bit of a technophile. I can't get enough of technology. Curiously though, it's lo-tech stuff that I love. I'm going through a bit of a phase right now where I'd love nothing more than to just pick up an old PowerBook Duo 2300c or PowerBook 2400, an old copy of Quark and Photoshop, and just make icons and pixel fonts and upload them to a sparse webpage. That's not saying there's not a place for high-tech stuff, I'd also love a 15-inch Aluminium PowerBook and Adobe CS, which would likely bring in more cash, but I'm lovin the lo-tech stuff.  On a high-tech note, I see Nintendo is kicking ass and taking names with the new Zelda. See  urlLink IGN  for details.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My shadow's Shedding skin I've been picking Scabs again. I'm down Digging through My old muscles Looking for a clue.  I've been crawling on my belly Clearing out what could've been. I've been wallowing in my own confused And insecure delusions For a piece to cross me over Or a word to guide me in. I wanna feel the changes coming down. I wanna know what I've been hiding in  My shadow. Change is coming through my shadow. My shadow's shedding skin I've been picking My scabs again.  I've been crawling on my belly Clearing out what could've been. I've been wallowing in my own chaotic And insecure delusions.  I wanna feel the change consume me, Feel the outside turning in. I wanna feel the metamorphosis and Cleansing I've endured within  My shadow Change is coming. Now is my time. Listen to my muscle's memory. Contemplate what I've been clinging to. Forty-six and two ahead of me.  I choose to live and to Grow, take and give and to Move, learn and love and to Cry, kill and die and to Be paranoid and to Lie, hate and fear and to Do what it takes to move through.  I choose to live and to Lie, kill and give and to Die, learn and love and to Do what it takes to step through.  See my shadow changing, Stretching up and over me. Soften this old armor. Hoping I can clear the way By stepping through my shadow, Coming out the other side. Step into the shadow. Forty six and two are just ahead of me.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So,  urlLink Blogger  has redesigned. Not only have they redesigned, they've created all new templates [as you see here] and given the option to comment on posts now. Yay! So everything now is web standards compliant. All XHTML and CSS. No table tags to be seen. pretty impressive if I may say.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I know that I haven't been updating regularly. I'm sorry. Been busy with work and with Jen being home it almost seems pointless to be updating. I'm sure she's the only person that probably bothers to read this site anyways, ha. Work's going well, really busy, which is good but I just can't seem to get into work mode lately. The idea of Jen being in town and me sitting here pushing a mouse around instead of spending time with her is distracting. I'll try and be more regular about posting. Probably more like once a week though...   Who controls the past now, controls the future Who controls the present now, controls the past.  Rage Against The Machine - Testify 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!   Beat Les Bleus!
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You have GOT to be kidding me. System Requirements for the new Microsoft Operating System code named Longhorn. These are just the requirements to run the OS! JUST THE OS!   Microsoft is expected to recommend that the "average" Longhorn PC feature a dual-core [64-bit] CPU running at 4 to 6GHz; a minimum of 2 gigs of RAM; up to a terabyte of storage; a 1 Gbit, built-in, Ethernet-wired port and an 802.11g wireless link; and a graphics processor that runs three times faster than those on the market today.   Insane.  Pulled from  urlLink here .
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Jen  tells me two packages have arrived from  urlLink YWFT . That will be my two books. One of which will be  urlLink this , and the other one will be  urlLink that . I'm excited to get home and flip through them. Yay!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm writing this post from the Mozilla based browser  urlLink Camino . It's fantastic. I think I like it better than  urlLink Safari . It's fast and really takes advantage of web standards.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The  urlLink css Zen Garden  is a very nice site with a good message about the need for standards in webpage design. Pretty interesting to know that the XHTML code is the same, but just simply clicking on the different designs completely alters the page. I think "Revolution!" is my favourite.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, so I've already switched templates. I think I like the simple ones better.  So went out to see The Panic last night. They rocked the Railway Club. It was pretty strange though, as 3/4 of my old employers  urlLink Lightroom  were there. I didn't see if they recognized me or not. not that I care.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah I know  urlLink Ryan  is using this template on his  urlLink Blog - Song 2 , but it's so nice that I thought I'd use it for a bit too. I did change the background pattern though. Eventually I'll design my own template. Eventually...
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Urgh. My nose is a snot factory this morning. I think I'm getting sick. Thought you'd all like to know.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Waytion . Link pilfered from  urlLink Newstoday . Some nice stuff. I don't see the need to label that a temporary site though, I think the site as-is is pretty slick.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow, so I finally found a good browser. Mozilla development for OS 9.x stopped with version 1.2.1, but there was a start on the 1.3 version source code. A collective of developers finished it, and released it through  urlLink WaMCom . I now have access to tabbed browsing, pop-up suppression and such advanced features. Hooray!
     
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seriously, I'm 23 freaking years old, I should not be saying "What's the matter with kids today?", but what the hell... What's the matter with kids today? I like the fireworks for what they are, but I hate the crowd they attract. SkyTrain was full of rowdies, downtown is full of rowdies and I stopped at Subway to eat my dinner only to realise the rowdies were stopping there to go to the washroom. When they realised the washroom was full, they just urinated on the walls. INSIDE the restaurant. No crap.  I seriously hope rowdy, belligerent children running around getting wasted tonight either end up in the hospital with alcohol poisoning, the drunk tank or get beat by cops with night-sticks or shot with a taser or something. With any luck they'd be electrocuted to death. Disgusting little maggots.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm really liking the new  urlLink Oakley Half Jackets . If I can, I think I'm going to try and sell my  urlLink M Pro Frames  and buy a pair of Half Jackets.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeesh. It's funny how busy one can get. Busy enough to not even be able to update a simple website. Anyhow, it's been a fantastic summer for sports and records and stuff. First with  urlLink Greece , who had never won an international association soccer match, winning the  urlLink Euro 2004 . Then, of course, we have  urlLink Lance  winning his sixth  urlLink Tour de France  in a row. In the entire history of the 101 year old event, no cyclist has ever won six times, let alone in a row.  Congratulations Lance
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jen's bro is in town for a couple days for  urlLink Indy . He's staying the night and I think we're going out to lunch tomorrow with him.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You'd think that Concorde Pacific, well first you'd think a multinational real estate development company would have a webstie. Anyhow, you'd think that Concorde Pacific would have a little more organization than what they just did.  urlLink The Molson Indy  is this weekend. Concorde Pacific wanted some postcards printed for the event, to showcase some future developments that are happening around the Indy Track. They must've just decided this, because we got the files yesterday afternoon, printing right this minute, deliver by 10:00am tomorrow. Hello. HUGE international event. Last minute stuff is BAD.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow. Just got back in from the  urlLink Tour de Gastown , a presigious one day cycling race touted as the fastest in Canada.  urlLink Lance Armstrong  actually won it way back in 1991 when he was 19. It was a fantastic experience, and something completely different from anything I've ever seen. The  urlLink peloton  passed by me so closely on each lap, I could have touched a rider if I didn't keep my hands right down at my sides. These men and women are elite athletes, doing 50 1.2km laps (60kms) in 80 minutes. That's averaging 45km/h on a bicycle. When the  urlLink peloton  passed by, it felt as if you were waiting for  urlLink SkyTrain  it was so breezy. So yeah, I'm going to try and make it out to this event every year now. As an added bonus this year, I met  urlLink Trevor   urlLink Linden  and got his autograph!  Also, on a different note, received an email from my Uncle Ferdy, who's on  urlLink The Feminists Third Wave Crashing Tour  right now. In the email he mentions his friend  urlLink Ben Millard  who was the singer/songwriter for a band Ferdy used to be in called Cellar of the Sun. They were fantastic, and I see Ben is continuing a solo career. Listened to most of the stuff up on his site, and it's great. You should email him for a copy of the CD.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The elegance has returned. The  urlLink iPod  is stunningly beautiful again. I love the new redesign. To be perfectly honest, I thought the last revision was ugly. This revision however, surpasses both other versions. Amazing.  Oh, and  urlLink iPod Minis  are now available in Canada. Nice.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went and saw Arthur last night. Unfortunately, came out a little disappointed. I have to agree with Jen, it's like they took the names of the characters in the legend and put them in a totally different story. Not a bad mindless action movie though. I definetly want to go see The Bourne Supremacy next weekend.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Holy Good Lord. Jen and I needed to get some new light bulbs for the washroom. Jen wanted something bright and white. So we got some good ol' 100W Soft White lights. Five of 'em. Thank goodness my Oakleys will be repaired soon...
     
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So the weekend guy is on vacation and no one planned for a replacement. On Tuesday I get asked, could you please, please, please take Wednesday and Thursday off and work Friday and Saturday? Please?  Blah...
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, someone keeps trying to get my password for Blogger. Every few weeks I'll get an email from Blogger saying:   This email is a response to your request for information about your Blogger account. To regain access to your account, please click on the following link:  **********  Clicking on this link will take you to a web page that will let you choose a new password. Once you've submitted your new password, you'll be able to log in to your Blogger account.   What the hell...
     
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I had a bit of a strange weekend. Excluding Friday, that was nice to spend time with Jen. Saturday however, the weirdness started. I went to an open casting call for martial artists to be in the next  urlLink Jean-Claude Van Damme  movie  urlLink Kumite . I actually got a call back and had to go in on Sunday. But I think I was too skinny. And not flashy enough. The guys they seemed to like were either 300lb monsters or skinny chinese guys that could do standing double backflips and stuff. So yeah. But it was fun none the less, and neat that I got a call back.  I also found out that  urlLink Oakley  has  never  had lifetime warranties on their eyewear. It's always been one year warranties. They did however provide free repairs on frames, which some dealers translated into "lifetime warranty". Three years ago they realised that they were losing money providing this service, as people were just sending in broken frames with requests for different colours and such, so they started charging a fee. Anyhow, they also don't offer to replace your glasses with new ones if yours are outdated. So, that means I get a $60 credit on my outdated Eyejackets, because they can't repair them and replacement frames for my  urlLink M Frames  cost $50. So with a $10 credit left I lose one pair of glasses and get new frames for my  urlLink Positive Red Iridium Heater  lenses.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jen had yesterday "off" and tomorrow off, so we actually get to spend some time with each other. I feel like were dating again. I actually called her up from work last night to ask if she wanted to catch a movie.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so that was way too long of a hiatus. But I've been super busy so I can't really blame anything.  urlLink Jen's  mom was down for one weekend, then my parents were down pretty soon after that. Couple all that with trying to watch the  urlLink Euro 2004  as much as possible. I've also been trying to avoid the computer at home since I work on it all day. But I should be updating again. In fact, it'd probably be a good way to keep in touch with  urlLink Jen  during the week, since I never see her any more...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Super busy this weekend in Victoria, visiting Tammy and Adam and also cleaning Jen's Grandma's place out as it's now sold.  My  urlLink Lance Armstrong  Bracelets came in today. As well as my new  urlLink Oakleys . I'm happy as they asked what colour I wanted and I said black, but received carbon fibre styled ones instead. Nice.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>