<Blog>



<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      squeeeeeeeee
       
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This blog is dedicated to Leigha Horton, an actress in the Twin Cities metro area. It's for Leigha sightings, Leigha news, Leigha reviews, and Leigha gossip. It is also for Leigha squeeing.  It is run by two fangirls who think Leigha Horton is the best thing since sliced bread. She's just that great. We're both straight and in relationships (one married, one long-term), so it's not some creepy sexual thing (though Leigha is hot!). We're also not stalking her, at least not in a bad way (we do enjoy knowing all we can about her, though).  All great performers need fans, and we are some of Leigha's. 
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Leigha is performing in a  urlLink one-woman show   right now  (well, ok, Friday).  We haven't seen it yet but expect it to be awesome, as always.
       
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Leigha performed at  urlLink NARAL: Pro-Choice Minnesota's  5th Annual  urlLink Comedy for Choice .  Leigha was, of course, brilliant and funny and the best performer behind the genius  urlLink Kevin Kling  (but he's awfully hard to beat, even for someone as great as Leigha).   And  she's pro-choice.  What a woman!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      (the full article from the  urlLink Montreal Mirror )  Sneer campaign   >> The Unbearable Lightness of Being American takes the piss out of all things USA     Making fun of Americans is hardly foreign in these parts. Chalk it up to an inferiority complex if you want, but it's not like those fatsos ever do it themselves. Well, okay, they do - take Minnesota's Ministry of Cultural Warfare, in town this week for the Fringe, for one.   What's appealing about this Minneapolis company, beyond their poking fun at the right, is their poking fun at the left. Their one-woman show, The Unbearable Lightness of Being American dishes up 13 snippets of Americana, satirizing everything from war to malls to fleeting lesbian chic. "You know when all of the sudden it became über-cool to be gay?" says actress Leigha Horton. "One of my favourite monologues to do is about this clueless valley girl talking about the love of her life, Emily, who she just met on Wednesday. We take pot shots at lots of things. If we're going to be attacking other people, we should definitely attack ourselves."   "My favourite thing that's been said about the play is that I'd picked my targets so democratically it felt patriotic," says Ministry writer and mastermind Matthew Foster. "The only thing all the characters have in common is that they're all women. They range from very annoying university students, to the cat lady who's anxious about becoming middle aged - it's 13 aspects about American society that bug the hell out of me."    Foster, who claims to be wearing a John Kerry baseball cap on the other end of the phone, could almost pass off as Canadian, peppering his sentences with "I guess," expressing his disdain toward Stephen Harper and hope for the Flames (this was Monday), theorizing that Canadian Stanley Cup victories coincide with Democrat victories in the U.S. "Well my friends in other states call Minnesota ‘Baja Ontario,'" he justifies. I asked him if he's proud to be an American. "I guess I'm not really proud to be an American," he says. "I'm proud to be a Midwesterner, and I'm proud to be from North America. You add that North there and it gets rid of the nationalist bullshit that comes with saying you're proud to be an American."   As for Horton: "I love being an American, but I'm not proud right now. I love the fact that we can criticize our president openly and not, oh, dissappear, but the things that Americans have done to other countries… there are so many things that don't get press attention, at least here, that we're doing all the time and that's really frustrating. I think that right now America's in a really gross transition, and I hope it turns out okay.   THE UNBEARABLE LIGHTNESS OF BEING AMERICAN, JUNE 11–20 AT VENUE 4 (BAIN ST-MICHEL, 4247 ST-DOMINIQUE), SEE PROGRAM FOR PRICES AND SHOWTIMES » Matthew Woodley  
       
    
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Leigha on the cover of the  urlLink  Montreal Mirror  !    There is also  urlLink an article  (at the bottom of the page) about her show,  urlLink  The Unbearable Lightness of Being American   (exerpts of which she did at NARAL Pro-Choice Minnesota's Comedy for Choice), which she performed at  urlLink Le Festival St. Ambroise Fringe de Montreal .
       
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh yes, oh yes!  The  urlLink Ministry of Cultural Warfare , home of Leigha, is performing in the  urlLink Minnesota Fringe !  The show is called  In Defense of Sin (My Friends' Best Stories) , and we hear it is just that...Matthew Foster was gathering stories at parties with other theatre kids, so maybe we'll hear some we know (we are hoping for the one about the dead cat)!  Five shows, five nights...can we make it to all of them?  You bet we can!
       
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A short  urlLink review  of Leigha's show,   urlLink The Unbearable Lightness of Being American  , from various reviewers (we can't determine who):  "The Unbearable Lightness of Being American - Leigha Horton is incredible--intelligent, provocative, self-reflecting, and funny, too! Her 13 scenes via a multi-media approach were clever to the point of irony! A thinking person's comedienne! Get an agent and shamelessly self-promote--you're a winner and more audiences need to see your talent!"  Squee!  And, a photo of Leigha in the beer tent at the Montreal Fringe, swiped from  urlLink Matthew Foster's  blog:   
       
    
    
</post>


<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       we will never order from you again.  sure you snagged us in with the niced looking menu (in comparison to the million other chinese delivery places) and your effort in displaying your delivered foods. but clearly, after delivering us a mess of plain steamed spinach looking stuff (and charging us 13 dollars for this stuff) instead of what we actually ordered, then the fight on the phone... then when the originally ordered dish came quite some time later, the dance of the delivery boy was completely innappropriate. do you think we're grade schoolers, when you expect us to give back the wrongfully delivered dish before giving us the rightfully ordered dish?  i mean, what the hell?   with service like that, i almost want to start a rumor about you using cat and dog meat in your dishes. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       one of these days when i have time, and a copy of my high school transcript, i shall make out a list (perhaps a spreadsheet?) of all of the classes i've failed.  note, i never failed classes for the year (thank goodness) but due to my strange high school experience at a school that stole away potential valedictorians from other schools, in the law of averages there was a lot of room for failing.  when i was a freshman in high school (at the tender age of 12) i failed art.  this was mostly due to my judgmental art teacher (who hated me the first semester, but loved me the second due to a new-found friendship in the german teacher's daughter)  hating my penciled self-portrait final.   she was one of those teachers who would give grades according to who you were, instead of the effort you put into the piece.   and i believe this point was proven during a switch between one of the best kids in the class, with the work of the worst scoring kid in the class.    of course this didn't help me from bawling my eyes out over a horrible note scratched into my semester final.   but thankfully for me, making art wasn't apart of the curriculum after that and i've avoided art classes ever since.  until now... i have a design requirement i need to fulfill for my master's degree, and of course in the great class shuffle of 2004, i got stuck in a drawing class.  i tell myself it will be a useful use of my gigantic looming student loan bill, because well it will be useful in another class i'm taking, it will be easy in that low-stress sort of way, and when i unleash my flash animations on the world it will be helpful to sharpen my lost drawing skills.  that being said, i almost cried during the first class.   already.   most of the class was cool, and it was refreshing to take sometime to just focus and draw.  (i was only slightly annoyed because due to people not bringing in supplies, i ended lending out all of my drawing utensils that i had explored the city to find.)   at the end of class we hung up two pieces of our work, and discussed everyone's work.  it was mostly pleasant (even though at times i wanted to shout to a pretentious class member that their work was total crap), until it got to me.  fuck.  i begin to wonder if there is something about me that just provokes art teacher meanness.  15 minutes were spent, by my prof, critiquing my choice in lines that i used for drawing a still life.  he thought it looked too comic, and that it is a good thing this is only the first class because he's going to work that out of me.   one thing i really hate about art teachers, is their want to shape you into their kind of artist instead of allowing you to be your own.   but on and on the critique flowed, even after points of people in the class being cut off for saying they liked it.  class left me in a funk, instead of feeling inspired.  add that to getting double charged to ride the over-priced subway, the evil evil snow filling up the ground, and other things..  i almost contemplated becoming one of those crazy people on the subway system.  not yet.   i'll just have to save that for another day.  but still, i would've dropped the class if i could.  (drat, drat, drat)  i hate the showing your work shame... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       there is a certain image in my head that i conjure up for a person named billy or a person named frank.  in my mind, a billy is youngish, lanky, wears v-neck sweaters, and is always slightly disheveled.  a frank is someone at least in their 60's, white, grandfatherish, completely gray and prolly bald.  in my new classes, it was shocking to see how my new profs (a billy and a frank) are nothing like my idealized versions.  frank is youthful and jolly, and billy would fit better if his name is frank. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i wish there was a way to transform a messy apartment, where you can see the dust settling on the last suitcase and all of the forgotten item, into a clean apartment...  somehow it is depressing to come home to an extremely messy apt, reeking of single boy with dishes still in the sink from when you last left, and feeling upset over his grandiose attempt to do the laundry instead of  cleaning..   and doing the laundry of course means that he did all of the laundry in that pile of gentles that aren't supposed to go thru a dryer, and now they're all sitting shrunk and crumpled in a pile in a laundry basket. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       somehow, life seems more profound when you're using your thumb (and the wonders of t-9) to make a limited string of characters post.  somehow they seem cringe-worthy the day after.   is it the memories of all of the angry fliers because their flight was cancelled?  or was it because i almost missed my flight because  they couldn't figure out how to open the airplane's door . stale hot air plus agitated people who have stood up only to be crammed into the aisleways of an already late flight like sardines waiting for the door to open.  they had to send in the technical support people, thus it took 20 minutes until the door was openable.  all the while, over the intercom we're reassured that the door will be opened any minute now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is like waiting for godot, except for the deplaning to occur.  btw this is my second flight of the day with technical problems.  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Test)I am amused authe ability to blog whilest waiting for my absent airplane.  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Airports)People are strange whilst waiting to go somewhere else. Slightly agitated, and hyper sensitive yet still unaware.  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       going to hawaii was one of my most looked forward to events of 2003.   what is better than interrupting wintertime (and a winter break between classes) to live it up in the land of sun, sand, laziness, and pina coladas?  i gave up shaving my legs years ago (when i quit being a sorority girl, no less) because i find it rather pointless.  why should i constantly be at war with the hair growing machine which is my legs?  i had enough hair follicles to produce toupee for men, and to compete against men (who've never removed hair from their legs in their lives) for furriness quotient and won.    i know there is a large part of the population which will gag in horror.  but if they were equipped with legs that would never feel smooth after a shave due to the always-at-work hair factory, i think they might understand.  shortly after discovering that i was going to hawaii, i decided that pre-hawaii hair removal was in order... just because how often does one go to hawaii, and also because i had completely forgotten what my legs looked like.  (good logic, right?)    i quickly decided that i would have to get my legs waxed, because i believe shaving to be stupid and knew i wouldn't want to bother with quick stubble and nicks that go along with pressing a razor up to innocent skin.  and whilst i procrastinated during the 6 months of knowing i was hawaii bound, i failed to do any lovely stomach crunches and i failed to really do anything about my growing leg bush.   unsurprisingly, i ended up not doing anything until the dead last minute, so instead of finding myself a nice salon to rip my leg hairs out for me (and having someone else to curse out whilst in pain) i found myself struggling against the sea of holiday shopper crowds, and stores that didn't stock wax or anything to remove hair.  at the 11th hour, i found the only tube of peach (ick) scented wax.  i got to work at dusting myself in a cloud of baby powder, in hopes of lessoning the pain of ripping skin with hot wax.  i nervously dallied with making sure the wax was the perfect temperature, and allowing myself to be in a zen-state where pain doesn't exist.  pain is all that exists when you're quickly ripping up strips of cloth which contain a fascinating display of hair follicles and orange colored wax.   every time the second hand hit the 3, a ripping sound could be heard.  i turned the ordeal into a strange mathematical problem. maximizing the rectangular strips effectiveness over my non-rectangular legs.    but eventually, after sharing the waxy stickiness with the rest of my apartment (some of which i'm still discovering weeks later) i discovered my legs.  hot damn, i'm pale in that  unexpected translucent way.  i mean, i could always see my hair follicles after a shave, but with them all temporarily sitting in the garbage can, i am really fucking pale.  i wonder if i can glow in the dark, i'm so damn pale.  with the leg hair gone, i was completely unsurprised when my grandmother (who several years ago questioned me if i was going thru "a faze" slightly hinting that leg hair automatically equates lesbianism) made a comment about seeing my legs.   the additional bonus of not having leg hair was that it was one less place for sand to stick.  which is a good thing when every shower produces a sandbox quantity of sand. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       my immediate family rarely, if ever, sees my exponentially large extended catholic family. which makes us the black sheep of the family because everyone else's kids are best buddies,  belong to the same churches, or spend large quantities of time on the phone with each other. we also are the only ones who are not local, and are the ones closer in age to our aunties than our rapidly multiplying mass of cousins.  this is why it is completely surprising that one of my 5 year old cousins was more excited to see My Dad than to receive gifts from santa claus.  what five year old is more excited about seeing a person, than getting stuff?  there are a few things in this world that i don't understand, this being one of them.  i have reasons to suspect that my dad's brainwashing of my cousin's mom (aka my dad's sister) left a mark in her genes.   this aunt is otherwise known as the aunt my dad convinced light is actually dark (at times we'll point to light bulbs, say "Daaarkkk" and giggle in her presence.) which might've been due to my aunt being born 17 years after my dad.  she adores my dad.  now my cousin was often found drapped across my dad and at times drapped across my dad's kids due to association, in an almost minor-deity sort of way. she would bat her eyelashes and sweetly sing my dad's name. strange behavior for a kid who prolly hasn't even seen her uncle/my father in a year.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (otherwise known as the ponderings as why the hell i'm not sleepy yet.)  recently i've transversed 5 time zones whilst trapped in an airplane's window seat.  although, i managed to get in a good four hours of sleep (on an airplane, which usually counts as negative sleep) i haven't been able to reaquaint my sleep cycle with my native time zone.  it is well past my usual bedtime, and i haven't even been able to fake a yawn. and i've tried.  boring reading materials, jammies, warmth, darkness, and the hour of the night have no jurisdiction over my body's relative sleepiness.  to the point that i wonder if i was fed radio active airplane food which has mutated me into a human who needs no sleep, even though i crave a good night's rest.  perhaps all will be better when i end up being trapped on another airplane's window seat, going backwards 3 time zones.  this is what i hope, whilst i ponder more ways to force sleepiness. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i guess this should be the spot where i introduce myself to you (the new blog, and the new blog's readers),  because isn't that what the first few blog entries are for anyways?    of course, i'm not entirely sure how to introduce myself.   okay, here's an attempt.... other people find me to be rather strange, i'm not entirely sure why (because i'm not other people, i just happen to be me) but i think it might stem from my introverted and analytical nature, or that other people seem to think i'm on drugs when really i'm not (to my knowledge). i have a unique name, which i will not disclose here because it plagues me. usually i love having an unique name, but it has been rather bothersome lately.   although i still get a good laugh at finding shit i wrote when i was 14 (almost a decade ago) floating around in cyberspace. i've been online longer than you.  no, really.  and if you're one of those freaks who has been online back in the days when computers filled up entire rooms, at least i've been online for a larger portion of my life than you have. sometimes i speak in multilevels/meanings.  and sometimes i'm unsure which meaning is the intended. i fear i'm growing shorter.  there is no other explanation for all of my siblings to dwarf me in height, as well as my li-BF.  my grandmother (who never hit 5 feet) was the tallest kid in her 5th grade class and the shortest by 8th, so i wonder if this has anything to do with my recent shrinkings. i get really excited by some silly things. take today, where i discovered i have enough frequent flier miles to go somewhere for free (again).   i also have been known to giggle when i find things that are theFUTURE in reality.  (read: things that involve technology that could've been on the jetsons.) i'm in a graduate program that focuses on theFUTURE, otherwise known as the bleeding edge of technology.  i'm doing stuff that goes over the heads of the general population. it is very fucking cool. and you should visit me to come check this stuff out.  i have a futon that's booked at least 2 weeks in advance. i wake up (when i'm actually at my home base) to a view of glittering tall buildings, shining in the sun.  these buildings' lights romantically bleed into the body of water (that separates me from them) at nightfall.  it is beyond picturesque, and it is a view that can be seen out of 8 of the windows in my tiny little apartment. i'm a city rat, as in the type of person who gets nervous around empty spaces, country lanes, as well as gigantic parking lots.  i'm afraid when my eyes can't grab onto anything in the surroundings. i'm a travel junkie. i only want a job to support my travels, and if it required me to live in england a double bonus.  what else would you like to know? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it is a new year...  maybe i should try something different... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       dear readers,  i have adopted a cat, and have been struck by lack-of-name-itis.   do you have any suggestions?  here is a bit about him:  he's a purr machine.  purring and rubbing against people seems to be his speciality.  he's mostly black, with a white belly (he loves belly rubbing) and white slippers.  he already owns my apartment.  he's terrified by bubbles.  absolutely terrified.  he can leap over large hurdles whilst fleeing the catnip bubbles.  even if he's taking a nap, if someone leaves the room that he's in..  he'll rouse and chase after them.  he's 2-3 years old.  he was found on the 14 of feb, and taken home on the leap year.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (((if your name rhymes with "bank" or "free" perhaps it would be best if you skipped this post.   let it be noted that you have been warned.)))   at first i rolled my eyes at the pretension, the first room of this particular art gallery only had one piece, a naked man and woman kissing.  i didn't bother to look anymore at the piece, and was expecting the rest of the gallery to be a quickie-in'out.  yet, this wasn't the case.  inside there was a collection of sparkling white materials, sculpted to depict individuals with romanesque faces and deformed bodies.  it was a new type of voyerism for me.  in the past, i have seen a large amount of classically beautiful people, sculpted into stone, and the only deformity being the age of the piece has caused body parts to chip off and go missing.  but still you know in the original state, there were arms, legs, heads, and noses.   in this gallery the missing pieces were in fact missing from the models.  i wanted to examine every inch of these bodies, bodies of people of whom you're not supposed to stare or examine.     there is the divet where the arm that never was, would've gone.  there are limbs too short, and toes curled under as if they were the originators of the lotus foot fetish.   an armless mother with her fully limbed baby on her lap.  perky breasts and a missing leg.  body contortions that lead you to almost believe this person has the proper number of limbs, but from a different angle you can tell.    i found this to be a beautiful exhibit.  simplistic beauty in the sculptures that was trying to combat the ugly culturally seen in these individuals.   certain people around me were quite disturbed by the whole display, especially because everything was modeled after real people.  they gasped and quickly left. i think i will go back.  and the couple kissing in the first room, his left arm was only long enough to place his deformed hand on her shoulder, and on the other side she was missing an arm and he was hugging her tightly.   i wiped a tear away from my eyes and went for the door. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       there is a certain image i get in my head, when one says we're going to go look at art galleries.  to me this definition includes some of the following:  a ground floor room on a commercial street front.  darkness and almost a feeling of claustrophobia.  the possibility of buying things.  a person who is present, and might be the artist, but they really want to make a sale.  instead my first gallery crawl in chelsea, in the city of verticality, completely fucked with my version of an art gallery. first off, these places have a thing for elaborate "art" doors.  which was was the beginning of the fodder for snarkiness with others.   are they going for the industrial look, or the frosted glass and private appeal?  how does the handle cause investors to blow a money load? secondly, they always seem to have a person working at a desk near the front door.   this person will never make eye contact with you. thirdly, despite being in one of the most expensive cities in the world, these galleries are spacious if not empty.  which somehow ooozes, "yes my scrawling on a piece of paper will bring in at least 5 figures,"  just look at all of the empty manhattan wall space around me. fourthly, it is not the trend to leave a title of your work on the wall near your art, or even your name.  because the people seeing your art, just know. fifthly, there are only art galleries in chelsea. a sprinkling of boutiques or eateries, does not exist.  commerce does not exist. everything is a gallery.  there a buildings with galleries on every floor.  to the point that i seriously don't understand why there are all of the galleries in the first place (they don't make money off of the common plebians who might wander into their gallery as there is barely anything to show, and they have nothing for the plebs to buy.)  the art world baffles me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       when i was little, i wondered how other kids could attain perfect school attendance.  this is because when i was a kid, my siblings and i traded sickness like some kids trade Yu-Gi-Oh cards.  one of us would get strep throat, then another, then another, then the person who started it, then the person who hadn't gotten it, and so forth.   it was almost a goal to make it thru a month without a visit to the family doctor's house. (i say house, because his practice was out of a house.  it was personal medicine, that seems to have been swallowed up in the motion to large practices.)  i highly doubt there was a single month without at least one of us having to go to the doctor's.  fast forward to now.  after living awhile without real insurance (c'mon, i'd love some socialized medicine.  this is a top priority in deciding which country i defect to, incase the Texas Souffle wins another election.)  i'm terrified of going to the doctors for fear of the bills i can not pay.   which, for the most part is okay because i haven't been sick enough to warrant a trip to the doctors for awhile.  well, in the computer lab i work at, which has hundreds of children churning thru each day, we've recently gotten headphones for the computers.   as soon as i started testing the levels on the phones, one girl complained about getting headphone caused ear infections.....i came down with an ear infection of my own, which for the last week i've been trying to ignore in the hopes that it will get better.  faster than you can say earache, i've managed a nice minor addiction to an over-the-counter drug.  as not only did it dull some pain, it had a side effect that graduate students around the world love...  sleepiness blaster. perfect timing for the first week of midterms, when even though i feel crappy i can pop a few pills and manage to stay somewhat alert on 3 hours of sleep.   it's a miracle!!!  and it even makes me feel less likely to cry on the subway due to ears hurting.  (just so all you folks who've had childhood ear infections, but maybe never experienced them whilst moving underground in a tube, ear infection+ subways= a very very bad and painful thing. and this is partially the reason why i caved into going to see a doctor.)  and over-the-counter is nice because it doesn't require a scary visit to the doctor.  of course, today i caved in and visited a clinic which takes my minimalistic grad student health insurance.   these nurses/doctors weren't as amused by my sickperson shtick ("Am I going to live?"), but maybe it was because it has been a long week for them and maybe i'm not as funny to the world when i can barely hear myself or my audience and i should really just stay in bed.   i scored some drugs.  and i have a whole weekend to get better and to frantically prepare myself for midterms week two.   i hope to catch up on some of my slept debt, in hopes that half of the month of may won't be set aside for erasing some sleep debt.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "What happened to your hair...  it was so beautiful." -a 4th grader  i'm pondering taking up wearing the veil and/or wearing hoodies for the rest of my life. also, i want to crawl under a rock and cry.   one of my methods of massive procrastination is the compulsive search for the naughty split ends.  using a pair of scissors, i can cut away large chunks of time when i should be doing something else.  (as it seems, the more things i have to do on the computer... the more i avoid even turning the damn thing on.)  well, this time i came up with a brilliant idea.  i'd give myself just a little trim.  file this one under "famous last words" which reside in the kitchen of half-baked ideas.  just a little trim turned into a seesaw act, as one side was never the same length as the other.  when evening out the other side, it would become too short..  and soon enough, my bathroom floor was covered in a sea of over 8 inches of hair. seeing the shorn locks everywhere, woke me up from the fun little daze of cutting-hair-is-fun.  guilt rises, because i was growing out my hair for Locks of Love..  fear rises because i have yet to look in the mirror to examine the damage...  and there are 8 inches of hair on the ground that will never reattach themselves to my head.  8 inches and i have "Angry Inch" stuck in my head.  Over 8 inches, and it is really fucking lopsided. perhaps, the lopsidedness wouldn't be so bad if half of my hair must be on an exchange program from someone else.   in fear, i dropped the scissors. in a moody wave, i became a puddle on my couch. in an intelligent move, i put the scissors far from reach.  now, i'm terrified and embarrassed.  no one has said a word about my missing hair (except the obligatory bf reassuring me that it looks okay, which of course i don't trust due to that whole "he's dating me thus he must say it looks okay" syndrome) except a girl today who was upset, and the teacher i work under made some strange remark today about my hair smelling nice but not the missing hair.  in my little neurotic world, i take this as a REALLY BAD SIGN. thus, i return to being a puddle on my couch, wishing i knew someone i trusted who was skilled with scissors.  i fear hair salons, especially their visions for my hair.  especially because my hair type and my ummmm lack of effort when it comes to hair, isn't quite understood by hair stylists. i fear, as my hair is already too short to stay in a pony tail, that my hair can only get shorter if i visit a stylist.  which my only lead to a rather big puddle on my couch. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it has recently been rediscovered that i  loathe  potatoes.  see, i've never really liked americana fare (french fries, hamburgers, potato chips), but i had myself convinced for awhile that i really enjoyed something which contained potato byproducts.  convinced until one day, i realized i couldn't spit said item out of my mouth fast enough, for i had realized the potatoey-ness lurking inside.   that gritty starchy taste that really makes me wonder how half of the family tree survived eating the damn things, when i can barely stomach the idea of the things. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       At the toy fair, we managed to hit visit all of our favorite toy manufacturers (from when we were kids) just to see the future...   And actually managed to speak with a woman (from an all time favorite company that i won't disclose here) who lamented the decreased toy development time. See, once upon a time, a toy company could spend 4 years developing a toy.  Four years of tweaking and testing, researching and quality.   Now, most places spend 2-4 months developing a toy until it is ready for the shelf.   This might be why people think "the toys of today are crap, now the toys of my youth..." 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        !!!!tmi warning!!!!    Usually Miss P's entrance is dainty and slightly tardy.  her tardiness, i suspect is somehow related to my own complete lack of speed in matters such as leaving the house (a field in which i'm notoriously slow, and i'm not a person who "applies her face" everyday, i'm just not entirely motivated to leave bed-dress- feed myself- and locate the things i need for the day), her tardiness is completely welcomed.    Her daintiness usually only lasts a day, which she pulls a Mr Hyde and goes into a rage of turning toilet water pink (which amuses me so), turning turning other things red (which doesn't amuse me, as i hate doing laundry), and turning me into a crampy angry person (which never amuses those around me).  Yet this morning, her entrance was far from dainty as it was more of an explosion.  I'm talking about an explosion near the size of the collapse of the twin towers, the type of explosion that covers an entire metro area and they're entirely confused about what hit them.   I almost want to watch the news just for the leading headline of, "menstrual blood  bomb coats entire city, police mortified."   Hell, I'm afraid that if someone came into my apartment, they'd wonder where i stashed the body.  I honestly wonder if she's trying to kill me on this visit.  And I'm currently unsure if she's conspiring with my current illness, to make me one large wanting-to-slit-my-wrists body of pain.   !!!!end of the tmi!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (i wonder if i've ever been so mentally exhausted in my life)  there is an industry-only annual toy event, that i got to spy on today due to my field of graduate work....  the toy fair is where all the big deals are made for local toy shops and chains, and there are rows upon rows of toy presentors hoping to make the big sale.  some of these presenters would treat me and my fellow classmate like we didn't exist due to the fact that we weren't wearing the color coded name tags that said we were buyers. but that didn't matter, because we were there to spy... to look at what's being produced, and what our future competition will be.  at this point i'd like you to know how mind-boggling big this toy fair is...  it is at a convention center, and we spent an hour and a half walking around looking at toys and thinking that was it, but were slightly confused by the lack of toy-names we recognized.  (we did know that a lot of stuff goes on behind closed doors, and weren't worried about that..)   but then we realized, there were TWO more floors of booths full of toys that were larger than the first level we explored.  i'm in the state of mental/visual overload.   imagine a never ending toy r us, but with smiley people everywhere trying to grab your attention with their product (that they're playing with, of course) until they realize you're only Guest status.     at first, when we started to walk around we didn't quite understand why there were back massage places... but it all began to make sense after several more hours of seeing toys and no end in sight.  disturbing things to note, before i collapse into a heap.. 1. most toy buyers are very old white men. 2. a disturbing amount of toy presenters are older women in skirts. 3. a section of these women are dressed up, like mermaids, in a leather catsuit, showing what should be illegal amounts of clevage. 4. i got more swag that i could carry, even though i was trying to *not* get swag. 5. the more clevage i showed, the more swag i got. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (The Bus)How likely is it for vomiting to happen when i am trapped on a bus with a woman filing her nails?  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        is it possible that the people downstairs have been invaded by a different (loud) life form?   the people who live directly under my apartment (duma) are a rather quite bunch, quite unlike the elderly couple in the apartment across the hall from them whose fights are louder that i'd ever image coming from people of their age.  the duma's are a married couple with a young child, are from some country i couldn't place on the map, and are quiet....  or at least were quiet.  is it possible that the insilation melted away and that they were always this loud?  or have they been replaced by simlar looking inviduals who are quite the party animals?  whatever happened, i'm having a harder-than-usual time at actually concentrating on my homework.  to the point that i haven't even started on the stuff that's due tomorrow.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       imagine me, waiting outside of class in the hallway... reading a graphic novel on a couch.  no, not a  porno graphic novel, a  graphic novel is just the "adult" name for a comic book for those of you out in teeveeland.  intro: random stranger who is reading over my shoulder.   the random stranger who i will be seeing gyrating completely nude in a a few minutes.  which i didn't know at the time, but in a department where i at least recognize all of the students and i didn't recognize him (and i knew there was going to be a nude model)...    i show him the book...  and thus the hitting on begins.  every little break from drawing, he has to run up to me and talk.    and i being the stupidly nice person i am, i give him a granola bar (i always have a granola bar to give to street people asking for money for food.  but they never take the granola bar) because he asked about nearby vending machines, and the closest food would require going outside and most likely not be the place one wears a bathrobe.  thankfully, he was shooed out the door after we were done drawing him and gearing up for critique time, right as he was attempting to get my digits... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Internet Is Dead)Why are you dead oh internet darling? Please come back, please!  There is only so much i can do on my phone. *cries*  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i will never, ever, ever, ever hand grate carrots again.  feel happy.   today, in that moment of domesticity of preparing marinated pork chops, whilst still imagining that i could possibly become a vegetarian (seeing companion animals in cages makes me wish i had a love of tofu, or a supplier of mock duck) i decided to chop some carrots.    but these carrots were clinging to life, "please don't eat me, don't eat me for dinner," they seemed to emanate...   instead a memory of something i wanted to make came to mind.  this is where i admit to being a spice catalog junkie.   i can spend a morning or an afternoon, leafing thru descriptions of spices and imagining the recipes they could be used in.  i'll reread the same articles about how they harvest Mace, or about the different meshes.    and sometimes the junkie goes on huge spice splurges, just because  i need  expensive spices in my larder.   (and i've visited people who have only a few spices in their spice rack, and i start to twitch just because how could anyone live without _________?)  yeah, so back to the spice catalogue...  the most recent issue spotlighted something i never liked before,  urlLink carrot cupcakes .    and i've decided now, after dirtying my entire apartment with orange paw prints, that i will never hand grate carrots again.    one of the levels of hell must involve grating foods by hand.  of course, i had thought grating carrots would be a breeze (how quickly i forget how much i hate even grating cheese, let alone a hard, wet, flimsy carrot) and i'd whip up some healthy treat in minutes.  my logic circuits must get blocked when the spice catalogue is involved.  i think even the recipe suggests a food processor, which just happens to be one of those million other kitchen applicances i actually don't own.   but, now that i've grated part of my thumb off, i must chant  "carrots go into the food processor, food processor, food processor.... or else blood gets into the carrots, the carrots, the carrots..."   -- baking is apart of my world domination as a granny plan.  nothing else in my life is planned out except the fact that i will be  that   crazy old woman who lives close to a college campus, and tells all the youngins about life ever so long ago, as i tempt them with my old fashioned treats.   by then i hope to unlock the mysterious of my genetic ability to make candy and other sweets, which i know will one day come to me like a little burst of irish luck..  of course, after my irish forefathers decide to forgive me for hating their beloved potato. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i will be getting a cat for my anniversary. (somehow i find is strange that my friend who has been with her guy for one day longer than i've been with mine, is already married with a child and a cat.... and i'm only now possibly getting around to having a cat.  it's like that day difference is several decades...)   this weekend we visited the pound, my first trip ever to a pound.   and there is something about the smell of the decaying animal food and excrement plus the constant yelps of dogs who fear the chamber, that makes me want to adopt every kitty i see.  or at least, if i can't adopt them all, it makes me want to free them from their cages and just have a good little play time.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        side side side thought: there are certain phrases that in my mind have a significance which only a few other people might catch.  we're about to come up to one of those  it has been decided  still makes me burst into giggles,  should i post a backstory?  anyway, back to this post  that i am to become a stereotypical embittered graduate student who drinks lots of coffee, perhaps i could even find some blazers with elbow patches for added ambiance (but i won't be picking up cigarettes for kicks).  maybe i could also flaunt my ability to wear all black for many days in a row, just because that's all that's left in semi-clean laundry land.  last week, graduate school began in full force with kicking me in the ass.   last week, i was near slitting my wrists in the misery in ways that only graduates students might know.  see, last week, i started the lack of sleep program and i didn't pick up any of my newly acquired love....  coffee.  on the whole, i'm not particularly found of coffee.  in delis in new york (and essentially everywhere in the world) it tastes horrible.  there is that overriding bitterness which can only be doused away with insane amounts of sugar.   it isn't supposed to be bitter (ah, those years working at a coffee shop) but the world sucks at brewing the stuff and the stuff they brew just plain sucks.  but you reach this point when you don't care, and all you do care about is the ability to stay awake thru classes and to actually function mentally.  hi, i'm now a little ray of sunshine happiness due to coffee.  i might even break out into song about how i love coffee, and how i love the fact that i've only had 3 large cups today.   happy, happy, happy.  oh, i love coffee.  (holy hell.  i wonder if this qualifies for my most ADhD post ever.  but seriously, coffee! coffee! coffee!!!!!!!!!!!   i need to invest in a coffee maker, stat.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Need Sleep)Is it even possible for me to be more tired and yet still so very very far away from a good nights rest?   --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       minor experiement du'jour : depending upon what a child is shown will affect what they produce.  the topic of the class (for two different classes of 2nd graders)  was squares, circles, and lines.   the kids were supposed to draw something on the computer involving squares, circles, and lines, and then write about the number of S C & L they used and what they drew.  with one class, they weren't given an example..  and what they drew completely varied from flowers and trees to trucks and towers.     but the other class was shown an example of how to use S C & L to make something, the example being a truck.   even though the image of the truck was on the screen for a short while, nearly all of the kids in this class drew a truck exactly like the example truck, including the same color scheme.   i've noticed this phenomenon before, when kids were picking out online pictures to use for stories.   if the example was one, they'd all go for the same picture...  if there wasn't a picture shown, they would all do something different.   i wonder what the connection between creativity and the inspiration for creativity,  just as i'm working on a homework project and am almost unable to think of something outside of the teacher's example.    is the authority of the teacher, something that replaces creative thought whatsoever?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i love being able to file my taxes online, and have some computer try to figure out all of the numbers for me.  (have i ever told you how horrible i am at mental math and simple math?  and it's not because i'm a girl and "math is hard,"  sometimes i wonder what would've happened if i pursued a math major... )  but, i've caused an error on my taxes according to the online system...  see it believes i qualify for Earned Income Credit,  which sends me back into a loop of filling out the qualifiers, and then i don't qualify but the program doesn't seem to understand why and thus it sends me back to the qualifiers.    i might be really fucking poor, and earned half of what is accepted as the poverity line last year, but i don't qualify for the EIC for one reason i don't understand (nor can control).... i'm still under 25.   (and what is so magical about the age of 25? )   due to my 4 digit year earnings and my 5 digits (soon to be 6 digits) in student loans, i confuse the system.   i might actually have to file my taxes the old fashioned way, because a credit i could receive is 1/3 of what i earned..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i have a fairly uncommon last name (and a fairly uncommon first name, which makes me an easy target of googling), but somehow i find it really shocking that there would be anyone in the entire world with my last name that i don't know already, but i don't even know that many people with my last name.   although i'm related to more people in my first cousin ring, than the populations of some small towns in north dakota, only two of my cousins (as well as my 3 siblings) share the family name.   it seems as if both sets of my grandparents were really really fertile, but the birth of boys didn't seem to go along with the law of averages.   the biggest bummer out of this plight of male children, is i can't as easily stalk family online.  my cousins have more last names than i can ever remember (if i can even recall their first names)...  so even though i have a large entended family, there aren't a lot of people sharing  my  last name.    it makes me feel ultra special because i have the ultimate rock star name.  well, a family member of mine recently died, and i became obsessed with trying to find something mentioning her death in the papers or with google.  and there is a slew of these other people running around the world, with my last name.  most of them might even be related to me.   they're most likely the kids of my dad's cousins several times removed, who comprise these news about sports and academic scores.     these strange people who are running around freely, even though they're tied to me because we share the same last name. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       should you choose to accept it, is to manage 3 fifth grade boys as they perform "community service" by "helping" out in the computer classroom.   actually this means you find yourself spending more time trying to corrall the boys away from causing trouble and also hitting on the girls in the current computer class. what this involves is giving them menial tasks, which you could accomplish quicker than it takes them, and to combat their desire for rewards for their work......    i understand that community service is a great idea, but whose wise idea was it to have kids help out in classrooms of their peers? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (i've noticed my phone posts are no longer coming with a little tagline, how odd)     how i love skipping steps when i go up the stairs, but how it is impossible to skip steps whilst going down.  the vulvabed is no more.  we were making a batch of cookies, and she turns to me.  the light went off. "i understand why 13 is a baker's dozen"  nyc commuters don't make for interesting bus rides.  a previous (from a former life) commute on a bus, every ride came with a story.  why didn't anyone ever tell me about mixing sundried tomatoes + pesto, eggrolls + chocolate, or chicken n dumplings with apple bread, before?    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It is like the future with a new bus smell.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (and if only i could clap off beat... then i'd be set.   years of dance lessons have ensured i will always know the beat, and i'm always puzzled by those who have the ability to completely ignore the beat and clap to some irregular rhythm.)  today i have a song stuck in my head.   oh but it isn't an ordinary song in english, which i could belt out the chorus over-and-over again till i mildly annoy my boyfriend and it flees my mind.  it is a song in another language.  i can't sing in foreign languages.  the phonetics of my own language trip me up frequently, and foreign lyrics twist up my tongue.    but i need to sing the song, and infect my boyfriend's mind with the song in order to release the song from its temporary lodging in my head.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       clearly, my cat's tail is not  powered by mere kitty muscles...  it is powered by animatronics.   old animatronics, of the sort that you find in theme parks and chuckie cheeses.   as there are two types of movement, that which could be found in nature and then the type that is animatronicized and supposed to resemble nature but fails to resemble anything actually found in nature.  of course this must mean that my cat is part robot.  it is the only way the movement of his tail can be explained, as it jerks as if the cogs are grinding away..  poor little microchip that powers the tail, it must've gotten accidentally wet once.  the tail jerks in ways that disclose their animatronic nature.  as a tangent.  with all of the technology we're supposed to  have, we still can't get  urlLink robots to dance  in a way that looks realistic.   but then again, robots dancing (as well as animatronics) amuse me greatly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think i just lost a year of my life. i would point to some news article about the accident in the lincoln tunnel, and the 1.5 hour wait in purgatory, but there is no news about this yet.  hell, the last accident was only a few weeks ago....  and i really hope that the 90% complete plans for the black wind of death do not involve my tunnel or my metropolitan area. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       image a crowd of theatre goers participating in a full out balloon fight.  lobbing long sausage shaped balloons into the air and at each other.  this might rank as one of my most favorite theatre going moments ever, to the point that i would consider viewing  urlLink carnival knowledge  again.  and i'm not the type of person that ever sees anything twice (unless of course it involves being coerced by a gushing fan girl and carlo rossi)...  but seriously, nothing is more amusing than a bunch of new york theatre goers going crazy with the balloons, to the point that the cast was shocked (from what i heard as i left the theatre) how long the massive balloon fight was.  it was akin to a snowball fight, without all of the messy cold shit.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       there seems to be a game of war going on between the spider plant and the cat, lately.  the cat attempts to eat (or play with) the leaves of the spider plant, whereas the spider plant is becoming skilled at the Drop.  as i don't quite understand spider plant logic, i'm assuming it is trying to attack the attacker..  but of course it could also be trying to flee the situation... or even alert the humans that that cat is being naughty.  thankfully all of the other household plants have stayed out of this current war.  i hope it stays this way, as i fear what will happen when the orchids and the cacti gang up on the cat. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (as i slowly become a cat lady, i'd just like to clarify that fetch is the game one can play with a dog, and not the ftp program by the same name  or maybe i'll a little bit more geeky to think of the former first rather than the latter.)  how to play fetch with a cat in a few easy steps.   take a wad of tin foil (al-ew-min-eee-ummm, for all of the british persons reading this) and make it into a ball.  (or you could take a store bought ball, but that takes away the thrill of wading up a ball and it is much more expensive than tin foil.)  find the cat  throw the ball  watch as the cat jumps in a gravity defying manner and scampers after the ball  giggle as the cat looks at the ball, and decides he needs to study it from a distant view point  throw the ball again   to add some extra spice, try a fake throw.  my Unnamed cat (whose intelligence isn't as high as we were hoping) will run after the ball that doesn't exist.  he'll leap as the fake ball should be in mid-air above him, as if he would catch it.   he never bothers to  touch  the ball of foil (seeing as it is a lower being than he) but he loves to run after it and flee.  i wonder if he's the type who could never be a mouser, because he'd be terrified of the mouse. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the day had started with a drive around an island in hawaii, and a heated discussion, led by my asian boyfriend, about what actually is ironic versus what alanis morissette sings about being ironic in one of her songs. alanis's song mentions things that are actually coincidences, and as she says "ironic". (just for the record, i never liked her music... but the younger siblings needed a bit of education surrounding irony.)  for those of you who have been living under a rock here is a sampling of the lyrics...   A traffic jam when you're already late, A no-smoking sign on your cigarette break, It's like ten thousand spoons when all you need is a knife, It's meeting the man of my dreams and then meeting his beautiful wife  And isn't it ironic... don't you think?     these are all coincidental situations, that do not flow with the definition of irony...     Irony : incongruity between the actual result of a sequence of events and the normal or expected result (2) : an event or result marked by such incongruity b : incongruity between a situation developed in a drama and the accompanying words or actions that is understood by the audience but not by the characters in the play -- called also dramatic irony, tragic irony    (thank you  urlLink merriam webster )  so, while driving around the mountains and by the seashore in hawaii, we were discussing things that actually were ironic instead of alanis-flavored-ironic.  a discussion which was thus forgotten when we found the perfect beach we were searching for.  yet later, irony came back for a little haunt.  my little brother had gone on a search for some  urlLink maui wowie , the previous day and decided to sample his purchase in the hotel room, instead of on the balcony or on the beach for fear of what would happen if he got caught.  he also didn't want to smoke up in his hotel room (seeing as he was sharing a room with my dad and my still innocent youngest brother) so he decided it had to be done in my hotel room which also contained my sister and my boyfriend.   let it be noted that my boyfriend did not want to be apart of my brother's smoking ordeal.  let it be known that this was a non-smoking hotel room.  but then again, so were the hotel rooms from high school fieldtrips and dorm rooms in college, but this didn't stop smoking from happening.  there are certain tricks to be known, covering the door opening with a wet towel, covering the air vents (with fabric softener sheets), opening the windows, and lastly turning on the shower to full blast.  as my brother went to  light up, i turned on the shower full blast, opened the shower door and......  the smoke detector went off.  my sister begins to tell us how a smoke detector works, as this was something she recently learned in high school.   you see, it isn't about detecting the smoke, it detects a change in air pressure.  as soon as i opened the shower door, the radical change of pressure around the smoke detector (it was above the bathroom door) set it off.  the security guards for the hotel come by, i run and hide in the shower to continuate my sister's story about the moisture from the shower setting off the alarm (it went off as soon as i shut the bathroom door) not anything else that the bone-headed guards could smell in the room. try to explain air pressure to guards, and see if they understand or even believe you.  for an extra dose of irony, my siblings and i ran to our other hotel room for fear of what could happen (and what was overheard on the security guard's walkie-talkies).    my boyfriend, who didn't want to have anything to do with the pot smoking, ended up fleeing the hotel room with us, but somehow lost the memo about fleeing into the other hotel room.  worrying about the whereabouts of the boyfriend, we went to look for him in the lobby and on the beach.  where would he have gone?  the fear of the bad possibilities flashed through my head, as i wondered how he'd survive in the strange land.  45 minutes later, the hotel called my cell phone looking for my father....  he went down to the hotel lobby, where he was detained by the security guards for being someone who looked like a local in a room with two white teenagers smoking weed (remember i was hiding in the shower).    he was subjected to intense questioning in the hotel's boiler room, where they threatened him with kicking him off of the hotel's premises because he was asian, had a different last name than the name on the room's registration, and he didn't have a key or a lying tongue.  but he eventually got the hotel lobby to call my cell phone (the only number he remembers) after dialing the room number to find my father.  nothing ever happened to my brother, besides his making money off the weed as he resold it to other relatives.  but the boyfriend had to fight for the right to be in the hotel, to get his license back, and to not spend some quality time in jail for something he didn't want anything to do with.  ah, my siblings now have an understanding of the true meaning of irony. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       oh teflon, the wonderful invention that makes pots i don't want to wash a little bit easier to deal with when they are washed. i have given it little thought beyond handling it nicely without using metal objects against it.  (unlike other people who've borrowed and ruined lovely teflon coated pans.)   does anyone give teflon a second thought, beyond the paradox of how teflon can stick to the pan if nothing else can stick to it? well, today i'm here to warn you that teflon has a melting point and even worse a boiling point, which can be achieved on a simple gas stovetop. also, when teflon has reached its melting point, a smell that is reminicent of roasting coffee arrives, which is turned into the worst possible smokey plastic smell imaginable once it boils.  how to boil teflon in three easy steps   decide to reduce some homemade stock for the purpose of the convient idea of storing it in an ice cube tray, to use later.  throw this into a teflon coated pot, and turn the heat on high.  become distracted by something or other and go to a different part of the house, where you completely forget about the stockfilled pot.   we were about to leave the house to go to the big city when the boiling pot of telfon was discovered, which could've caused a nice kitchen fire if left unattended for much longer. this would be the second time scatterbrainess nearly burned down my place of residence.  there was a lovely amount of smoke, but the smoke alarm which mocks me decided not to even beep. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       it was the spring break that wasn't actually spring due to the repeated snowfalls in the area.    after a day of trudging around the city after the snowfall that didn't want to end, my houseguest and i turned to cooking as an escape from the evil breath of winter. i'm talking about cooking the way old women used to cook, in the ways that Slow Foods people would approve. the delicious way to survive the winter storms.  and it provided all the more reason to giggle and drink copious amounts of tea. we baked and cooked until there was not a single clean dish remaining.  because even though we were being domestic goddesses, the one thing neither of us wants to do is clean.  that is work for the menfolk. we baked and cooked to the point that the fridge and freezer are full of leftovers, to the point that if the food supply was cut off tomorrow, the entire world could subsist on the contents of the fridge.  i'd just hope that they'd help out with the daunting pile of dishes threating to take over my apartment. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'll sheepishly admit that i live in the state with: the most idiotic roads to the point that i wonder if a tangle of wires would produce a more logical road pattern that what exists out here; the rudest drivers where flipping people off becomes more natural than using a steering wheel due to the fact that no one understands  1.  merging,  2.  driving slower than double the speed limit,  3.  pedestrians will dent your car,  4.  appropriate uses of the horn. i highly wonder if there are any other states that exist solely to provide cheaper residences for other states' metropolitan areas.  it seems like an almost natural thing to do (i enjoy having 5 times the square footage than something of comparable price in the big city.) but then again, i grew up staring at another city from across the water in a different state.   skylines seem more manageable when they're framed by a body of water and the sky, a view that is only accomplished away from a vantage point away. as i'm staring out at the tall buildings from my apartment window, i believe this post has been entirely derailed.  let it be noted before i go back into the intended rant, that i do love the view of 8 windows into the glittering city, i'd be much happier if the sun didn't rise so early in the mornings and if the other 3 windows didn't serve as reminders into the state i'm in. i feel like the upcoming rant has already lost it's steam, but here goes. this state where i currently reside, happens to be extremely dumb.  i sort of wonder if that has to do with the shopping malls per capita ratio,  the fact that most shopping areas are closed on sundays,  the horrific accents, or the fact of a brain drain which pulls many of the intelligent minds across the state lines to enrich their gene pool and continue to damage the future of those to come in the left-behind state. and then for some strange reason, this state is one of the few where it is against the law for common people to pump their own gas.   see what happens when the brightest leave, the remaining aren't deemed intelligent enough to fill up their own cars, of course this might hold a grain of truth considering this is the car accident state.... recently, it has been noted that  urlLink gas prices are really high , which of course is leaving all of the suv owners angrily shaking their gas cards.   but i find it very strange that one of the only states that still has Full Service Only, is on the near-bottom of the list.   thus factoring the usual additional cost of full service (i think it is an additional 10 cents a gallon if not more), this state has the cheapest gas in the union.  what the hell?  the only rationale i've come up with is that this is the trick to entice people who've fled this state for the concrete living of another state back into the land of cheaper rents, shopping malls, and a view you can't touch.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (St Pats)What other holiday causes so many people to consciously wear the same color?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay, so it is snowing and i am extremely bitter, i'm only finding amusement in my small town's lunacy.  i live in a small town outside of a really fucking big city.  the town is quaint and a nice retreat from the city, but sometimes it is really strange how much of a small town mentality it has considering it is 10 minutes away from one of the largest cities in the world.  today's example: it is snowing, and when there is snow on the road people aren't allowed to park on the main (2 lane) street.   this information is of course posted along the main street, along with the PICK UP YOUR SHIT signs that amuse me to no end.   it is snowing and the cops are bored or maybe they're always bored especially when it is snowing.  but the cops decide to slowly go down the street with their sirens and a loud speaker.  perhaps i would understand what they're saying if i was outside, or had all of my windows open.  but the snow is coming down at a 45 degree angle and i like keeping my apartment warm.  whatever they are saying, i could guess it has something to do with the snow on the road and the inevitable ticket and tow that will happen to the unfortunate cars still parked on the main street.  what amuses me the most is that they'll slowly drive down the street with sirens blaring, and will stop to talk  when they reach a car , as if the car will understand and decide to move itself.    their owners are most likely still at work, but the cops somehow believe the loudspeakers will move the cars and will alert the people who don't read the signs that their cars need to move.  the other amusing twist, is that the loudspeaker talking resembles english.  most of the people who live around here are not native english speakers. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i fear i am doomed and that the clouds which bring snow love me.  this week is supposed to be my spring break from school, and the last few days have seemed like spring (the forgotten season where i used to live) and the last month there hasn't been a need for heat to be on in my apartment.  but now it is snowing.  little by little, i really despise the snow.  here i was looking forward to a week in city with my house guest, with a camera instead of a winter coat, to go around checking out the budding leaves and the springing flowers.   curses. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       no one ever says they want to be an information architect when they grow up.  maybe because information architects didn't exist when most adults were kids. hell most people most people don't know what information architects are.  all i do know, is that after today's guest lecture in one of my classes, i wanna be an info architect.  just the name alone sounds sexy.  at this point, i'm guessing, most people are lost.  well for today's educational piece we'll talk about information architects.  they make information sexy by making it easy to the point that users don't need to think.   here's an example to make this less abstract: have you ever been to a website (or used some product) where you were completely lost?  where navigation makes you want to bang your head against the wall?    well, this is the example of someone who didn't use an i.a.   of course at this point the thought might be brewing of, "jesus, *ialmostslippedandtypedmyrealname*  i've seen the state of your room/apartment/desk/backpack you can't honestly be an organized individual."  ah, but i'm a perfectionist when it comes to organization.  the reason for the mess is completely a result of my laziness of maintain perfection all the time.     (i love pyschotically organizing things.)  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yes, after only a week of having the still unnamed one living in my house, it has been determined that he is the cutest cat ever.  here are some examples of his cuteness  (examples in list form, because my brain is mushy due to midterms.  i'm at the point where i'm having panic dreams involving the 20 page papers on world domination [i wish the topic of my schoolwork was world domination]  which was due and i'd only typed a few sentences. of course it was meta-amusing to be dreaming about the things i wanted to write about world domination.  i also, must admit whilst continuing this off-topic thread of thought, when i woke up the bf told me, "you're even a predictable procrastinator in your dreams.")   most cats seem to love to jump up on the kitchen table, whereas NamelessOne loves to take a seat at the table and look cute whilst he tries to listen in on the conversation.  he is aware of bad days, and knows just how they can be fixed.  i've heard that there are cats who like to jump on your face in the morning to alert you to the fact that it is food time.  well, instead NamelessOne slinks into bed beside me purring and nuzzling, after the alarm clock has gone off (and been snoozed).    nothing like waking up to a purring kitty.  he attempts flight.  he attempts flight to scale over the computer chair into my lap.  seriously, i've always wanted a computer lap kitty.  gush, gush, gush.  it has been only a week, and i was near to tears with the recent fear that the pound might want him back.  there was a little drama involving phone tag, and the fear that he wasn't really a stray (he has obviously been trained, and it has been revealed that he wasn't a stray) through phone tag made me fear that the previous owner was located and wanted the cutest cat back.   but, it turns out that his previous family lied to the pound, said he was a stray when they gave him to the pound.    they had actually adopted him from a foster mom, and fostermom just wants to make sure NamelessOne was adopted to a good family. i have no idea how previousfamily of NamelessOne wouldn't want him, but i'm glad he's mine now.    possible name list: kermit chairman miao salientia grimalkin or defaulting to his pound name...  harry (sucking at the naming process.) 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Midterm)Losing sanity. Spring break is too far away.  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
            he's been named for awhile, but we still seem to call him "cat". his name is actually a combination of common pronounciations my bf's and my last names. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm having a hell week, all of my finals (which unfortunately requires you) are due this week.   If you crash one more time in the middle of a VERY IMPORTANT YET NOT RECENTLY SAVED final project one more time-- I will resort to violence. Hell, I might even switch to a Mac. It is imperative that you do not crash and ruin several hours of work.  I have shit due tomorrow, and you should be on my side.  love, your disgruntled user 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Dear whites, do not say the n word  on the brooklyn train.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Goddamn)I hate cars.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Coachella)Coachella + spring + finals =  strange combo  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       tomorrow, the poorly paid adjunct professors at my school are scheduled to strike.  there are two weeks of classes remaining.  we're calmly told to ignore the picket lines tomorrow.  to continue on with our classes. that we must show up or else it will tar our grades.  people are stressed about crunch time.  and do not have time for this nuisance.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today, i struggled with finding the symbol for multiplication on my keyboard. no, not the asterisk (which is the cheater's way out of multiplication) because it hadn't crossed my mind...   i was seriously scouring my keyboard's top row for the little "x".   until, i realized...  well.  "X" is a letter and "*" is for computer multiplication.  and it is only monday. and i'm already exhausted. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       goddamn it.  what is so wrong with triangles?    you give me squares, rounded edge squares, circles, spirals, and stars.  but no triangles.  i love triangles.  why the hell must you torment me? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       taken from  urlLink mary ann    Grab the book nearest to you, turn to page 18, find line 4. Write down what it says.     myList = [101, 103, 104]  mmmm, code.  taken from my  Advanced Lingo for Games  book.  (i have a love/hate relationship with arrays.) the second closest book  "THERE'S MORE WHERE THIS CAME FROM." YOU CAN GET"   taken from   Cyberia  Life in the Trenches of Hyperspace   save me from computers. (i'm struggling to find a book in the piles around my computer which isn't computer-related.)   Stretch your left arm out as far as you can. What do you touch first?  the window, with a nyc skyline view (hi, empire state building)  whose window sill has a spill over of stuff from my disorderly desk.  (ink bottle, money, letters, pens, tape, L.E.D.s, resistors, and a ruler are all balanced on the sill.)   What is the last thing you watched on TV?   in one of my classes we watched a blip from School House Rock, my first experience with the show beyond the title on hipster's shirts.   i'm still unsure how i missed watching school house rocks, considering all of the television i watched as a kid.   With the exception of the computer, what can you hear?    urlLink 97x web broadcast , and video game noises from the other room.    When did you last step outside?  i actually left my apartment last night.  (which is quite surprising because i'm in lock down, due to impeding finals... which i'm currently procrastinating.) this actually shocks me more than it might shock you, considering sometimes i manage to go 3 days without leaving my apartment.   Before you came to this website, what did you look at?   adobe fucking illustrator.   i have this problem with computer art programs, as they never make what i want an easy task.     What are you wearing?  a phone headset around my neck, a porch king tiny tee, snowflake pj bottoms, a necklace, and a hair clip.  plus i have a sketch book and a phone in my lap.   When did you last laugh?  when i was on the phone, a few minutes ago.   What is on the walls of the room you are in?   on this side of the room.. Celestial curtains which i seriously like in a cheesy way; a Marc Chagall print; an original piece of art with a crescent moon, stars, planets, and a floating person; a wooden mirror which wraps up the celestial theme and pulls and pulls together color combinations in this room that make me giggle...    on the other side, the asian theme from the sitting room is creeping in.   Seen anything weird lately?   last night, there was an african-american man pushing a baby carriage (with child) and blasting 1950's music with a ghetto blaster.  new york excels in strange things to see.   What do you think of this quiz?   i was amused by mary's responses... but now i wonder if i should really publish thing..  because my answers seem so... mundane and un-interesting. i feel like the answers are clipped and the questions do not flow together.     What is the last movie you saw?  ummmmm... *thinks for five minutes* it was a collection of Dali movies at a teeny nyc arthouse theatre.  i see plays with the same frequency most people see movies.... and the last play i saw, was   urlLink who killed woody allen ...  which was worth seeing purely for the Christopher Walken character.   If you became a multi-millionaire overnight, what would you buy first?  a personal assistant robot.   Tell me something about you that I don't know.  i've been unsuccessful at building a robot army thus far....   If you could change one thing about the world, regardless of guilt or politics, what would you do?  teleporters would replace all methods of transit besides walking.   Do you like to dance?   yes, yes, and yes. (club dancing, partner dancing, and Dance dancing.)   Imagine your first child is a girl, what do you call her? Imagine your first child is a boy, what do you call him?   reason number 20453 of why i won't have kids: it took me 2 months to name my cat.   he won't resent me for his name for the rest of his life.  hell i'll be lucky if he'll actually respond to his name during the rest of his life.    Would you ever consider living abroad?  well, seeing as i've already lived abroad and the fact that i'm currently plotting my escape from this country if the current president is reelected... the answer is an easy "yes".    i wish i had dual nationality, to the point that i would marry for citizenship.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today's question: i am my own person.   but do i count as a dependent upon myself because i'm attending college?  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i know you're extremely excited about your recent discovery of open windows +window sills,  it must be extremely entertaining to have more things for you to study in between naps.  but do you have to get stuck on the bathroom windowsill?  you got up there somehow, why can't you figure out how to get down? you know i'm a sucker for your pitiful cry, thus i rescued you three times today.  but what happens when i'm not home to rescue you from the bathroom window perch?  in case you've forgotten, cats land feet first.  you'll be okay.   the jump looks more daunting than it actually is.  btw, how the hell are you jumping up there anyway?  love, the woman who gives you catnip 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       there was this point when i felt sorry for kids growing up in the city.   because they didn't have a big house and a backyard.  i remember a children's story about a girl that didn't have a yard, and the only flowers she had in front of her house were ones she drew in chalk on the sidewalk.  but after working with kids who are growing up in the city...   i'd trade my childhood-backyard  for their plethora of cultural institutions in a heartbeat.    i'd give up sled riding on those few snow days, mud walks, the great wall of china (a bank of the creek covered in pieces of colored rocks), the island of nimh (past the point in the backyard were i couldn't see the house, and i'd always get in trouble), the stinkbomb wars, and hot chocolate picnics all for the city art safari....... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       you're not helping.  i'm having one of those moments where i realize how much crap i need to accomplish in the next month, where every moment is important..  and this whole losing an hour of time only makes me more stressed.   fuck fuck fuck, i'm almost done with my first year as being a grad student. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       usually technology and i get along wonderfully.  but today i was present for multiple computer meltdowns, (tim- macs suck), server meltdowns (the computer at the bank  broke  today. couldn't get money and couldn't deposit.), and other things that result in my choice of  urlLink The System is Down  as today's theme song. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       to survive the last few weeks of work.  (i'm counting down the days left of their school.)  all of the children were already dreaming about the moment they leave school and go off to their favorite vacation spot, their country home, or whatever for the long weekend.   what is the point of holding class?  two girls might get suspended for a silly thing they did today.  the kids were organized like this..  A. - G. - M. -and then a bunch of other kids.  G got up for whatever reason, and possibly had a party in the boy's room. who knows.  (i've broken up little bathroom parties before.  i wonder if i could link this to something.)   He had left his Text Document window open, and so  A and M started "passing notes" on his computer.  when i was passing by the computer, it was all silly and cute.  but something happened after i walked away from them (actually causally walking away from any kid's computer doesn't actually nowadays.  imagine something more on par with a child yanking at my clothing, or my person  for attention because they  need  help  NOW !   usually i barely have time to pause and catch my breath.)  which i didn't see until my teacher made a huge scene.   G. *lastname* I WILL KILL YOU!!!!1   was typed into their innocent note.  my teacher yelled, and there was a huge group of kids gathering around A. and M.  there was a lot of crying (these kids fear any black mark will cause them to get shafted in their middle school applications.  and thus cause a ripple affect of ruining their lives.) and a bunch of people defending them.  saying that they didn't know what they were writing, or that it must be a joke.  of course in certain matters schools aren't good at handling a joke.  after my teacher stops yelling and goes off to help one of the other kids with their problems.   i tell the girls about why this is a big deal.  about school shootings (which i have a strange interest in, partially due to knowing someone online who escaped from the columbine shootings... and partially because it is absolutely insane.)  and about the stupid things kids have been suspended for as a result of school shootings.   they didn't know that such things had happened, and couldn't believe that kids younger than them ("how could they do that? they're babies!") have killed.  -- the thing i've noticed about dealing with kids who do bad things, is how i have a extremely different approach than my teacher.  i hate punishing, and i manage to keep a cool head so i don't yell (except if no one can hear me).  also, i always feel like talking to the kids and possibly explaining what is wrong and making sure they feel okay even if they've done something bad.  i'd rather the kids love me, and realize what they did wrong  instead of blame me for being a meanie.  i feel rather bad, but several kids have expressed to me that they wish i was their teacher (instead of the teacher i work for) and then they've told me i should be a teacher.   i have no real intentions of teaching. mostly because i hate the school systems, i don't really like children (i like them when i treat them like my peers, but i don't like being the authority... and usually i see kids at my school more as if they're my little brother's friends instead of as the kids i'm in charge of), and well i want to do something where the years are different...     
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        taking the silliness of BundtÂ to a whole new level   there is a time in your life when everyone needs a BundtÂ pan.   okay, not really.  but just say, you were temporarily cataloguing your own collection of silly gadgets to recall if you do, in fact, own a bundt pan.  or you might be puzzling over what the hell this bundt thing is.  a bundt pan is a glorified (trademarked) cake pan, although it seems like it could hold other purposes.  it is special because instead of being a traditional flat shape, it is fluted and thus the resulting cake hugs every drop of frosting applied to it.  up until recently, i didn't own a bundt pan.  now usually (for those of you who stay as far away from the kitchen as possible) cake pans are created out of some sort of metal. something that will be able to withstand its time baking inside of an oven.   but the bundt pan i acquired is special...    (note to self for later, i should take a picture instead of using amazon's picture.)  not only is this bundt pan not made out of metal, but it is flexible and flaming red.  i must repeat: flexible and flaming red!!!  seriously what more could you want in bakeware? this is quitpossiblyly the silliest kitchen item i own.  more silly than my milk frother, and better humored than my beautiful blue glass cups. (i currently have a theory that everything tastes better out of thcobaltlt blue cups. i like looking a the blue-tinted world thru the bottom of my glass.)  the bundt pan imesmerisingng like silly putty. it bends, twists, springs back to shape, and you can bake cakes in it.   and the whole thing is made out of silicone, which adds another dimension of silliness?  (arsiliconon breast implants as bendable and can be used for cake baking?)  i'm easily amused by kitchen gadgets. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       [recently, i have decided that for some reason my cursing tongue has dried up.  i blame working with children, and having to censor myself around them.  i don't even fucking say my favorite phrase of "bloody hell" any more.  what's happening to me?  i actually wonder if i should hang around the  urlLink visiting sailors  to revitalize my cursing tongue.]  will i ever be able to find a yoga teacher in this fucking city, who has at least been practicing yoga for longer than i have?  it seems like all i can find are ex-dancers who were certified a year or so ago at some questionable institute. certified yoga teachers scare me.  perhaps they shouldn't scare me because they're  certified , but to me that means they paid for some course that might've taught them a few things and now they feel like they can teach.  which seems very american and anti-yoga. to counteract the fucking certified yoga teachers, i only want to take yoga classes from old hippies (cause i'm more likely to believe that they've been practicing for a long time, unlike the certified) or from people actually from India. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       at the elementary school i work at, the children have slowly become monsters.    it has to do with them brewing all day inside of a soupy humid building, and the promise of freedom and summer on the horizon.  {i remember thinking as a kid that it was criminal to have to go to school in the non-air-conditioned buildings during the almost unbearable months of May and June.  and i felt sorry for the boys in my high school who had to wear pants (dress code didn't allow shorts) as i wanted to die in my short skirt.}  classes are becoming harder to maintain, as previously sweet classes require several rounds of Clap Once If You Can Hear Me  (each round, the number is bumped up, until there is silence) just to get any attention.   i have a group of 5th grade boys who come in to the computer lab for community service, who i've grown rather attached to them despite their rowdiness. i'd almost think of them as friends  and they think i'm cool because i can talk about video games, cool technology (the subject of my master's degree), and i've been known to bring them candy.  on a day they usually come in, they'll help clean the lab (like cleaning headphones which are the topic of parental lice scares), they'll help a younger class with the computers, they might "test" a program for me, and they might create things on the computer which i could easily do but it keeps them occupied.   a breakdown of the boys:  D.- a dorky boy. Seems a little starved for attention, because he's talking to me every moment he's got about something cool and tech related. Very sweet, intelligent, easily excited, and dorky.  C.-hyperactive. He isn't tech savvy (he'll get lost when helping the little kids with their computers) and he's a bit of a spazz.  LOVES MadTV, loves dancing around, and loves asking for candy.  Q.- a "bad kid" during class time but during community service time he's really willing to do whatever i say.  will most likely be taller than me in a year. extremely opinionated  and loud.   now at the beginning of their community service time, D. asks if he can Puhleeeeze have time to go online and check his email.  which gets the other two to ask him what's so important about D's  email and they wanna go online too. D reveals that he wants to see if his girlfriend has written him.  C blurts out, "You don't have a girlfriend!"   Q exclaims, "I don't have a girlfriend, how can  you  have a girlfriend?" D. says, "Well... She's in England." C responds, "England? have you met her?" D responds meekly, "I meet her online?" Q shouts, "ONLINE?  ONLINE?" C continues for Q, "I BET IT IS MICHAEL JACKSON. YOU'RE GOING TO MOLESTED."  (i giggled to myself about D's online girlfriend. especially because online girlfriends from england almost seem like a stereotype...  and after the MJ comment, i could barely keep from giggling while i told all of them to calm down and get back to work.)  for D, michael jackson was a sore spot. his face scrunched up and veins started to pop out of his head.  D shouts, "SHE IS NOT MICHAEL JACKSON. Her name is L.  She couldn't be Michael Jackson because she's a girl and she lives in England."  C starts teasing and harassing D.  D starts to cry.  Q keeps on teasing D. Then the punches between Q and D start to fly, while C is in the background teasing D about dating Michael Jackson.  i physically broke up the fight. D was burning like fire, and was still flailing whilst Q and C couldn't stop the teasing. i had to impose a quite time for the rest of the period, and D who knew he was going to get in trouble for the punching tried to run home.  instead i made him sit in a chair for timeout while C and Q cleaned. i talked to D about how people you meet online might not be who they say they are, and to use caution with "kids" online because they might be paedophile adults.   and i talked to Q and C about how teasing  hurt D's feelings.   Q did end up making a card on the computer apologizing to D, but D was still too upset to accept the apology.  the whole time, my teacher wasn't in the room.  i almost didn't want to tell her what happened for fear of what would happen to the boys, and also because she isn't the calmest of people.  she decided to kick them out of doing their community service in the computer room, which was something they protested....   now i'll have a new set of boys helping me out for the rest of the school year...    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this post is merely for my own personal scare tactic.  meaning: i'll feel more likely to follow a schedule and accomplish things if i trick myself into fearing others shaking their collective heads at me for not accomplishing things.  i'm entirely unsure if you'll find the following worth reading.  but it might be worth mentioning that in drawing up this schedule i'm inspired by the lives of monks.  --weekday schedule--  (time to be determined)- arise   (hopefully more of the rise and shine variety, instead of the slunking out of bed cursing the morning sun dripping thru my curtains.)  15 minutes - harass the cat  (it is either i harass the cat, or he'll harass me.  and it seems like waking up is slightly related to the moment the cat decides to walk across my bladder.)  1 hour - yoga/meditation   (because i like being able to tie myself up in a pretzel.)  15 minutes - breakfast   (this might be the hardest thing to accomplish.  on freeballing days, i easily forget to eat... or procrastinate it.) ---on days i work... work would go here and would be followed by decompress (30 minutes) and dinner. ---  15 minutes - harass the cat.  (kitty playtime)  1 to 4 hours - demented projects  (freelance, teach my self webstuff, my website of evil projects, and other things off of my todo list)  1/2 hour to 1 hour - computer putz around time.   (i will need an egg timer for this, to make sure it doesn't end up being a depressing 8 hours.)  15 minutes - stretch    15 minutes - midafternoon meal   1/2 hour to 1 hour - chores   15 minutes - harass the cat  (nap in the sun)  2 hours - freetime without the use of technology   (read, knit, other projects, more cat harassment, dinner contemplation...)  or work on the demented projects.  1/2 hour to 1 hour - computer putz around time.   1/2 hour to 1 hour - dinner prep   15 minutes - dinner --if i have a summer class dinner would be ultra quick, and i'd leave now.  when i come back i'll unwind for 15 minutes, possibly putz around on the computer, harass the cat, and harass the boyfriend.--  4 to 6 hours - freetime   (computer, read, demented projects, see a play, harass bf, harass cat, go to the park/the river/the city, etc.)  sleep   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       in my further decent into being a crazy cat lady, i have taken up blaming my cat for missing objects.  Damnit Ginkgo, where did you hide my library books?   --or--   Ginkooooh,why did you have to steal my left sandal?  I know you want me to stay home with you, but seriously I need to leave the house.   i blame him when i can't find my phone, housekeys, tax forms, homework, nalgene, clothing, cds, pens, as well as other things.  i do believe he has found a secret vortex to another world somewhere inside of my apartment.  this is his hideout for when he knows i want to torment him, and it is location of all of my lost things.  this hideout is connected to the hideouts of other house cats, who also hide their owner's things for tormenting purposes (btw, mary did you ever find those keys?) and conspire together for new ways of making their mindless owner do everything they want.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i had  the perfect  weekend. it gives me hope that the rest of the summer won't be as bad as  urlLink last week . 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i am terrified by strangers with scissors who have the intentions of cutting hair for money, and the industry that supports them.  it seems like people have a common fear of the dentist.  i love the dentist, but FEAR the hairdresser as there is something quite frightening about the promise of a stranger with scissors.....    combine:  decisionitis (my inability to make up my mind) + being ultralow maintenance (there are 12 year old boys who spend more time on their hair than i do) + growing up in the near south (home to big hair) + a couple of horrendous hair cuts (perhaps a couple of stories should be inserted here) + a childhood fear of hair cutting hurting   to create:   someone who has been known to skip out of hair appointments, avoided hair cuts in general, bought hair scissors and had horrific results, and today...     i have been procrastinating for several months (years?) to get a hair cut, to the point that i butchered my own hair a couple months(link) ago and then ignored the quick salon fix.  and i have been completely content on continuing to say "i need a hair cut"  but to do nothing about it.   for i fear the moment i walk into a place-- with brainless lady's magazines strewn about, and potential hair style books-- where someone with visions of topiary grandeur would attack my hair and turn it into  the mushroom  (or some other horrible haircut i've yet to had) and expect me to smile, tip, and spend a lot on styling products.  today was the day f. had decided to get a hair cut, after my push for procrastination for several months.  i didn't *have* to go (during the ride out to the salon up till the point i reached the door i contemplated my escape from the scissors) but i had previously agreed to a group haircut outing.  i got a woman who had very cute hair (although, i was afraid to comment on it for fear that my hair would take-on an ugly mutation) who spoke little english, and had a desire to do more with my hair.  (a desire which sends chills up my spine. one horrific haircut was when all of my hair was the same exact length if i tilted my head a certain way. another was when someone decided i'd look good with bangs...) yet what she did is simple and safe.  and now i'm free from haircuts for another year!   -- the whole ordeal reminded me that i love the hair washing bit.  is it possible for strangers with scissors to only wash my hair?  perhaps this would require my adoption of an old-lady-do', for a weekly wash'n style without the taint of scissors....   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       and my mind has already rotted to hell.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       there was a certain time, before my beloved  urlLink google  existed, that i loved  urlLink ask jeeves .   AskJeeves was a brilliant idea, to use natural language for searching.  when Ask Jeeves came out, i was enamored by him, but i believe this might be because i'm a search engine junkie. (i love love love google.)  but i lost my faith in jeeves, his answers started to suck after Ask was gobbled up by some other dotcompany.  (but i guess this isn't about how i'm bitter towards jeeves. i really wish he'd listen to the questions of others.  and i really wish he'd get over that whole top frame, making sure people never really leave him.)   today in the computer classroom where i work,  the teacher decided to use Jeeves as a research tool for our second grade class.  there is always a flock of kids who won't understand anything that goes on in the computer room at any cost.  but then there are the handful of kids who'll get really excited about whatever today's activity entails.  certain kids, became more excited over the idea of posing a stumping question to Jeeves, than what their results may have been.  these are my favorite questions:  Why do humans create animals?   What am I? (i'm amused by the idea of 2nd graders sitting around having conversations about metaphysics.) Is GOD REAL?   (followed by the kid saying to me.  "I'm Jewish.  I want to know.") 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the summer has officially begun for me, and i have already begun to worry if the World's library system has started posting warnings about me.  you might be wondering why, or perhaps how could such a sweet little cynical girl could have a library problem.  i'm notorious for overdue books.  notorious to the point that i've maxed out my library card in 6 localities, 2 universities, and several counties. i've also maxed out the cards of others.  they knew fully well about my habit yet allowed me to check out books on their card.  (point and laugh shall we?) i try my damnest to keep my cards clean, but the fines always seem to exponentially stack up.  i believe it all began when i was a small child and the fact that my favorite book at the time happened to belong to the library. but it is still in my possession. i've been told that the book was "paid" thru the fines, and not to long after my family moved to a different city for fear of the wrath of the librarians.  fast forward a bunch of years, and i wonder if the only reason libraries lend me books is in hope of the late fees paying for their new section.  "Ah, yes the the new ydeleK wing..."      despite my trouble with fines, i truly love libraries. it is the combination of orderliness, air conditioning, information, and mostly free library books.  ah, so the summer has officially started.  i have a pristine new library card (why are librarians suckers?) and an  urlLink amazon.com wishlist  full of books i should get around to reading.      do you have any recommendations for summer reading? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i failed at giving an artworld kiss.   you know the type, a kiss on one cheek and then a kiss on the other cheek? of course i haven't been initiated into the art world, so it  could  be a little bit more complicated than it looks like from the outside.  person comes up to me, for what i think is a hug. they kiss my cheek and stunned i fake a cheek kiss.   this is the point where i step back, and completely forget the second step of the art kiss.  embarrassing myself and the initiator of the kiss.  after the kiss is finished, i don't want to make eye contact due to my faux pax.    in the strange moments after, they're already shredding my artistic license. i could possibly apply for another one in the fall- but...  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm not going to work tomorrow...  just to recover.  and to possibly hope that woxy will come back when i awake. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this might be the saddest i've ever been. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       air inside of the lincoln tunnel (a tunnel that goes under a river from nj to ny) only exists because of the air bubble circles on the tiled walls. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       my group visited our professor's manhattan office today, to give our final presentation.  and something about waiting momentarily in the lobby maybe me feel like a little kid waiting for daddy at the office, except my feet aren't dangling in the air when i was sitting on the lobby chair. i wonder if the toys around the lobby, and the telephone walking tour guide around the displays, increased my feeling-like-a-little-kid-ness.   (i don't want to patiently sit in the chair and think about the presentation, i want to run across the room and play with that  thing  over there.) i'm rather sad that the class is over, and that i'm staring at a summer (i hate the summer) with no structure  and a summer without  urlLink woxy . (bah, yesterday they were on the letter "I" and now they're on the letter "M,"  urlLink fuckfuckfuck  its ending too quickly and i haven't recorded as much as i've wanted to. *sobs*) hell, i would like the chance to be a little kid again. on that note, on my walk home from public transit... i had an elderly asian (most likely korean, knowing my area) crossing guard help me walk across the street.  [random ydelek trivia: i never got the chance to cross the street with a crossing guard as a kid]   amusingly, he said an asian accented "adios" after my thank you.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today a pair of my underwear scared me.  it leapt out of the laundry pile in such a way i thought a new species of animal had been lurking around in my bedroom.   i screamed in shock, and felt silly a few seconds later when i realized it was only a crumpled pair of underwear. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i am a puddle, as  urlLink my favorite radio station   (the only one out there worth listening to) is going off the air this week.  where will i go to listen to music?  where will i go to listen to music that isn't just the same 20 songs played  ad nauseum  with loads of commercials in between?   where will i go for the mix of new and old, imports and unsigned cincy bands, techno and hip hop?  this is worse than the break-up of my favorite band, that i idolized during my teen years.  this is worse than the last death of a family member.     urlLink woxy  is apart of my daily life, as i'm constantly streaming it when i'm home (cleaning, doing homework, surfing, etc.)   i'm afraid of the silence that will follow.   i'm afraid of life without the  urlLink future of rock 'n roll .   and i'm a huge puddle of tears. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       if you miss a flight, especially the last flight of the day from your chosen east coast airport going to your west coast destination,  groveling cannot make another airplane appear.  but it can rescue your ticket (instead of paying a thousand bucks for a replacement) if you focus all your happy energy at the ticket agent.  honestly, i'm unsure where my happy energy came from... after missing the flight we were very close to giving up on the whole "flying off to the other coast and seeing a music festival" thing, because it was a terribly long week of horrid final projects (for me) and horrid working overtime (for the bf) which essentially meant very little sleep all week.  (i believe i averaged 4 hours of sleep a night, that week.)  but from somewhere came that chipper person buried deep inside of me, to convince the ticket agent that we could stay in minneapolis overnight, keep our regular ticket, and fly out early in the morning to california.  after a stressful time, calling everyone in our party that we weren't going to be on the airplane as scheduled (3 groups of people from 3 different places were all going to meet up on the same airplane to california.)  and there is a certain amount of hell we received from the hotel industry, when trying to change the reserved name over to the name of someone who'd actually be in california that night.  stand-by was our only hope.   stand-by to minneapolis worked in the computers, but we'd have to later beg our way onto the stand-by list to california a day later.  thankfully the stand-by gods were smiling at us.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the scab glistened, nearly resembling a capital A, on the tender underside of her forearm.   there was something scary and yet glamorous about the thing at the time, perhaps because it was on someone slightly older than me, that i admired. i was still a pre-teen, and the fresh scab seemed beautiful. i just didn't understand the reason, yet.  i was never a self-injurer. though i could see the romance of the pain and the flowing blood, to the point that i became fearful of scarp knives.  i might've dreamed about all of the different ways i could kill myself, but i never actually had the guts to start the process when others did.  ... she had puckered stripes on her arms.  lines that tangoed with her veins.  lines across the veins of someone i cherish..  she made up a horrible lie when i causally asked about a few whose cover slipped away. i dropped the subject, but am still unsure what to do... what happens if she hits cutting success?    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I have no sense of direction.  If you ask me for directions, for your own safety completely ignore whatever i tell you as it has a very low chance of being correct.  Love, The Girl who has gotten lost under the Eiffel tower 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Please ignore me, I have no money and I really don't care about your troubles.   Thanks, The Girl who seems to attract crazy men like gas guzzling cars attract americans.  --  Whilst attempting to parallel park in the ex-FratBoy neighborhood, an old african american man comes between my car and the place i wanted my car to be.  Slowly shouting: D-O  Y-O-U  S-P-E-A-K  E-N-G-L-I-S-H? I was in the parallel parking zone, so i was puzzled by what he was saying and its relevance to his body being in the way of my parking car. D-O  Y-O-U  S-P-E-A-K  E-N-G-L-I-S-H? I'm in one of the whitest american good-ole-boys neighborhood around  and i wish i could pass for a nationality other than american.  wanting him to to move out of my way, i mumble "yes" slightly fearful of what a "no" would produce. cue sob story.  cue sob story that sounded familar to the sob story of the men up in midway who wanted enough money for a bus ticket to the VA hospital, but it was slightly different it involved a different hospital. C-A-N  Y-O-U  T-R-U-S-T  M-E? C-A-N  Y-O-U  G-I-V-E  M-E  M-O-N-E-Y? does he realize that my car brings down the property value of cars around it? does he realize the slower he talks and is obstructing my spot the more i desire to run him over? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think i've previously ranted about the condition of the roads in new jersey. (the idea of a handful of tangled spaghetti being tossed on a map, and then made into real roads... seems like the best description i have.)   well, we have rarely dealt with traffic on these roads.  especially the friday afternoon new york commuter traffic variety. little did we realize, nyc traffic is never on your side.  we set out from our place with plenty of time before take off, we would've been sitting around in the boring newark terminal for a rather long time if it had taken the usual 20 minutes to get to the airport.  little did we expect that we'd get stuck at an intersection that leads to a highway onramp (tollway?) for a large chunk of time...  only to find out after another large chunk of time that that this onramp was closed.    and the next onramp for this highway was on the other side of 20 red light intersections which were  crammed to gridlock with cars.  i have been close for flights before.  i actually am still amused by the pre 9-11 days of being the last person on the aircraft, and how i'd beat the airport wait system.  (i've begun to wonder if hell isn't actually centered in the mall of america, but actually inside of every airport terminal.)  i had hopes that we'd be able to have the travel gods smile upon us with a slightly delayed flight out of newark.  but would i be writing this if they had?  we know we're short on time, i make it thru phone prompt hell to coerce a customer service rep to hold the flight.... we're only a few minutes late, we can run once we're at the airport.. right?  the plane of course has an ontime departure.  and we make it to the gate a few minutes too late. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i've been too mentally exhausted to go anywhere near unpacking the items crammed into my suitcase.   it feels like i've been half across the country  in the past few weeks possibly because i have  (8 different states and a district of columbia).   in reinventing an old form of mental diversion possibly because my last trip left me with a bitter taste, i've taken to dreaming about the trips that could be.  this involves travel mags, and a little too much time comparing the cruelty of international flights being cheaper than domestic.  well, except of course flights to asia which floor me just by being 4 digits in price.   i'll prolly compulsively scout for 3 digits, if just for the thrill of seeing where the connecting flights land, until time stops being fickle.  i am absolutely afraid of wide open spaces (inverse claustrophobia, i guess) places where there is nothing to visually grab on to protect me.  a prime example of such a place would be found in parking lots near amusement parks (notably king's island), and i'm terrified that i will float off just because there is nothing else around.   if you've seen me ice skate (i'm a bar hugger who is terrified to let go), you might have an image of how i act in wide open spaces.     well, it seems the same exists when i am given a vast empty space of time. i'm struggling not to get sucked into the empty vortex yet... but...   i hate free time.  (cursed being a P yet needing to be a J.)   on another note, i have added 2 more states to the list of states that ought to be destroyed during the revolution.    Alabama (imagine driving for hours on an uninteresting 2 lane country road, where the only excitement is trying to pass cars in the incoming traffic's lane at 80 mph. pure waste of space.)  Delaware  (it has a city named dover in it, what other reasons do you need besides it is a evil waste of space? for those new to the game dover, england is competing for the prize of worst place in the entire world.)    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink don't do it.    (london thinks she is ready for tall buildings.)  i understand that you could use a little extra space and besides covering the thames with concrete (or riding yourself of the tate modern) you have no were else to go but up.   but let me let you in on a little secret: all of the people who knew how to build in your country, their great-great-great grandchildren have long since rotted away in your soil.   to put it simply,  your people do not know how to build  if they knew how to build it was a recessive trait which has long since ceased to be in the gene pool.   any building you've built since the last century will most likely burn in the next round of city fires, or fall apart in the near future.  hell, the building i lived in when i resided in your beautiful country, caught on fire whilst i was living there and i still wish it had burned to the ground.   it was a building designed with major electrical and heating oversights, as well as additional exits in case the off chance ground floor would've caught on fire. (which it did.)   and all of this occurred in a recently built building.  also your people can not be trusted to design a beautiful building.   i say you use a psychic to contact christopher wren, if you must build anything.  lastly, why must you taint the square mile of historic london?  why must you plan to build things that would conflict with st paul's cathedral?  couldn't you build your tall buildings over by the stupid stupid millennium building?  far enough away that the sky around beautiful london will not be raped by tall buildings.     central london, you are not ready for tall buildings.  nor will you ever be. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       now that i'm no longer on the road, i would like a moment of silence for  urlLink mary's   urlLink uncle bernie .                       i wish i could be there for you and your family.     (mary, a strange thought... we've known each other longer that my baby brother has been alive. he and i were talking about the news of your uncle, and said something along the lines of we've been friends forever.  and i guess in his book that's true.)  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       --stop reading now if the subject makes you squeamish--  --you've been warned--   once upon a time, it seemed like i always had a nearly circular dark red scab adorning my knees.  (yes, i was a clumsy kid who grew up into an adult that has perfected the art of running into walls and twisting my ankles.)  although the pain associated with receiving the scrapes isn't a good thing, the fresh crop of scabs was.  scabs were one of those things i likened to opening presents (releasing my hair from sponge curlers being another) because it was always a surprise to see what exactly hid behind the wrapping.  essentially, i loved to pick my scabs to see what would happen.   would there be a creamy white dot of new skin like a lump of ice cream in a frozen malt lurking beneath the scab?  or would there be a pattern of blood rushing out to produce another scab?  or would there be a bit of both?   i still pick my scabs, but they're usually not as deliciously large as the ones who rented out skin real estate on my knees.  (and i'd still like an explanation why seeing my blood = not icky, but cutting up dead things for the sake of science = extremely icky.)    except...  i've been monitoring a scab on my elbow, due to an unfortunate trip down a water slide.   it was a beautiful scab of grade school proportions, and i've slightly picked at it but didn't rip it off.  (f. yelled at me for even contemplating such a thing.)  of course i've been dying to see what was underneath.    well, the scab decided to fall off on its own.  damn scab.   i've slightly contemplated sending a search mission to find it, just so i can enjoy the pretty patterns of inside of the scab.   of course, not knowing when it decided to go free makes the quest for the scab a bit more difficult because it could be anywhere.  damn it for getting away. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (Do  U Know What Sux)A flight that gets in 20 min early only to spend 30 min waiting to get to the gate.  --  Mobile Email from a Cingular Wireless Customer http://www.cingular.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       in one of those nearly predictable moves, my little sister graduated from high school. (slightly amazing in the fact that she didn't get booted from school,  unlike other extended family members, and she managed to be an academic show-off despite genes for academic laziness.)  but in one of those unexpected moves, my dad decided to overcompensate for the loss of his daughter to the collegiate machine with a dog.  a dog in a historically cat-friendly household.  when i was 4 my family had a brief stint in dog ownership.  i seem to only remember pieces stiched together from photo albums, that frodo (the dog) had floppy ears and vaguely resembled a doggie pull-toy, i briefly enjoyed before i moved onto the bouncing horsey.  frodo did something really bad (maybe attach my baby brother?) and i was told he would be happier playing at our family's farm....    i grew up loving cats, for their happy human ambivalence and their safe stature.  --at this point i'm being attacked by family cat cuteness.  yessss you're the cutest kitty in the world. -- where ever my train of thought was going, it has been temporarly derailed.  oh yes, cats are cute, independent, cute, and cute.   whereas dogs (in my experience) have been cute from a distance, but evil yappy creatures who will attack without provocation, and require humans.  i guess my dad has grown accustomed to the low maintence levels of cats... a little food, little water, a few shakes of the litter box, and a few affirmations of their cuteness and they're happy campers.   but he got a  dog.    a small dog possessed by demons....      
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       if i was myself (which i hope i am) where would i hide my sunglasses?  it seems i have a higher probability of losing something (or convenient placing something somewhere where i'll remember it, but in fact forget) right before leaving on a trip.  and this doesn't help matters as i become slightly neurotic before trips so every lost/misplaced item magnifies the pre-trip neurotic jitters.  perhaps my sunglasses are inside of something (thus i'll have an excavation of every purse, bag, drawer, and suitcase i own), or on top of something but now hiding under something.   i wish i knew what i was thinking when i hid them, in hopes that would give insight into their current location...   (if i can't find them, maybe i'll have to take a trip to the airport lost-n-found and seek out a new pair of glasses...)  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i remember the time when it was cool to see what would happen (if anything) if you typed in a word or name.   (i think this is how i managed to stumble upon  urlLink hell ,  who introduced me to a lot of weird web art.. which is sadly not showing up in the archive or on the current site.)   well, today we're going to take a walk down memory lane, with the wonderful assistance of my beloved  urlLink archive.org .  do you remember orbitz, the sci fi drink of potential?  the drink that was beyond a drink because it had globs of gelatin  defying gravity ?  the only time i drank it (c'mon i was supporting  the future , and i love the future) was at a party, were it was discovered that it made for a shitty mixer. (the globs sink to the bottom when the density is changed, and you find yourself at the bottom of a glass being attacked by globs of jelly.)   well, at the time i didn't bother to rush out and see if the drink had a website of the future... and the drink was mostly forgotten.  well.  orbitz had a website.  urlLink the oldest archived version (from 1996), is only amusing because it requires netscape 2.0... unfortunately, one can't explore further into the depths because it wasn't archived.  *sigh*  a year later, in 1997,  urlLink orbitz's site  gets exciting.  go explore for a good laugh.      hi, welcome back.  now, i hate to break it to you but orbitz the drink is no more thus there hasn't been a need for a website about a drink that no longer exists.  but in one of those silly dotcom moves, the website itself became something else.  a travel website i use, whose name i've questioned yet never connected back to the balls of gelatin suspended in a beverage. somehow i find it strange to watch  urlLink the birth of orbitz the travel site ..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       as a kid, i cried when reagan left office.  i didn't understand why he couldn't stay and why they needed someone else because he was the president for  my entire life  at that point.  this is where i begin to think i could be completely happy with a little bit of monarchy, someone who is a figurehead and has no real power except the power of media distraction.   too bad we have a presidency instead.  --  we went out to a diner last night, to escape the oppressive heat that turned my mind into mush and my butter dish's butter into liquid.  and it was hard to escape the constant broadcast of the corpse of reagan.  at least i wish we could see the corpse of reagan, not the buttons down the back of nancy's dress or the draped american flag.  and i don't understand why they shipped the dead reagan body across the country for a little expo of his flag draped coffin in d.c., only to ship it back across to california for the final resting spot.  i wonder if i'm the only person who doubts there is a reagan in that coffin, and would really like to see some dead reagan for my tax dollars.   the russians managed to display lenin's corpse (is he still on display?) for a rather long time... why couldn't the smithsonian have an exhibit of presidential corpses, instead of the dresses of first ladies?  it would be nice to know that i could visit and see for myself the corpses behind the scratched plexiglass, and i think it might be a nice way to weed out potential presidential candidates... as they would know their body was doomed to be behind plexiglass instead of a soft coffin for all of eternity.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       and i'm already contemplating calling up my blog to randomly sing (poorly) at it.   i'm not even drunk (yet).  this would be to dislodge the catchy earworm (is that the decided upon name for songs that get lodged in your head?) i currently have.  of course, being that i'm sober, i realize that i'm the sole person here rocking out to this song in my underwear in front of the air conditioning. (yes, i have no will power when it comes to heat and the air conditioner is cranked, after pretending all day i didn't need it.)  and my singing will not inspire others to rock-out to this song (although it is a  perfect  rock-out song).  i'll just silently dance over hear, with myself.  you can sing the song (if you know what it is, which i doubt)  if you want.  also, dear readers.  you've been warned about the potential blog songs.  be afraid, cause i know i'm terrified.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (i currently have a lice-free head.  and intend to keep it this way for the rest of my unnatural life.. mwahaha.)  part of my fear of the lice (see that other entry down there a bit, yes.. to the left a little bit more.  ah, yes you've gotten there. and i'm too lazy to link) was exponentially increased because i was trapped in the nurse's office on friday with all of the lepers, i mean lice-heads.  a girl in one of my classes, J, completely flipped out.  we're talking about a flailing tantrum of beautiful proportions (i only wish i could throw tantrums like that) during class.  she also had recent (visible) wounds on her body that might explain part of the tantrum.  i had the pleasure of escorting J down to the nurse, to get her checked out and the possible injuries reported to the officials.  of course this was the worst possible day to go to the nurse.  as this was the day where they were screening children's head.. and when J and i arrived there was already a party inside the office.   kids were exchanging the counts ("well i have 10 nits and 3 lice"  "i have 15 lice!!") and the whole room was a party.   while waiting (for the nurse) i taught the kids one of my silly games. (everyone is in a circle. and they put their left arm ontop of the person next to them's right arm.  then you go around the circle, with one clap [on the table] equals a continue in the same direction and two claps equals a directional switch.  if you mess up, the offending hand is taken away.  this also works as a drinking game.)    while waiting for the nurse, a overly excited boy told me his life story all the way down to finding out he had nits.  while waiting for the nurse, the girl calmed down and nearly chewed the ear off the bunny toy i took from the classroom to comfort her.   i managed to rediscover my multiple voices (as a kid, i'd giggle about the different voices i could make) to create a story with the bunny and a magnifying glass.  while waiting, J, turned sweet and slightly disturbing.     it started off with her seeing the ice, as the nurse was zipping all over the place.  (the ice came out of a silicon ice tray, and had silly shapes.)  she wanted some ice for her injuries.  doe eyed and tilting her head, she starts begging for ice. batting her eyes "i'll do anything for ice.. anything" she coos in such a way i wish the office wasn't full of lice-ridden-kids and had a councilor could talk to her about......  what might've caused the in class outburst.  the sad thing was, after waiting inside of the nurses' office for a good 45 minutes, the girl was dismissed and would possibly be looked at later.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today's confession:  i lived in this state for a few months shy of a year, and i still haven't bothered to get a new driver's license.  there are loads of excuses (i know, i know i was supposed to get a new license within the first 60 or so days of living here.  i've been chewed out at the DMV before) which i'll condense to two things.   grad school (which made it easy to put everything off for that next day in the near distance future when i'll get enough sleep and everything will be shiny-happy)  insurance    i wonder if this state realizes that advertising it being  the most expensive state for car insurance in the union  is really going to make anyone want to get rid of their previous insurance.   i might be okay with paying double my previous rent, but to quadruple the insurance?  uh, i've been in no hurry for that.  but it is nearing that time when getting a new license is vitally important.  (that whole fear i have due to whenever i temporarily lose my old license, plus can't renew car tags in a state i have no residence.)   and i'm now terrified that i'll fail the driver's knowledge test because i don't know the finer points of the graduated licenses and stuff of that pointless nature.  ...   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (cue the theme to attack of the killer tomatoes)  there has been an outbreak at my job (an elementary school, for those of you new to the game) of head lice.  the school has brought out backup troops, and has been scouring the head of every child in search for the bugs.  which has depleted classes of most of their students.  the nurse's office has become an overfilling party room/ quarantine area where kids compare how many where found on their heads.  and i'm terrified.  see, i've never had head lice.  as a child i somehow managed to keep my head safe during the grade school outbreaks, always slightly jealous of all the kids who'd get to go home...   i'm still scarred by the times i was attacked by chiggers and ticks, to the point that i still fear the great outdoors.   -- she grabs my hair to get my attention.  "Yyyyydelekk, i think i have lice." as she scratches her dreads.    i'm not sure if i am a responsible enough adult to not freak out at those words.  distancing myself from her, i told her to go to the nurse. -- there are nearly-broken headphones in my computer lab.  everytime a child has a problem with their headphones, they want me to test them and make it all better. i can only test them by having them on my head.  -- kids love using headphones, be it to hear silly program sounds or to find their own sounds online.   plus they love sharing with me, where i'll usually feign enthusiastic interest.   sometimes this will involve the children thrusting their headphones at me.  --  i'm unsure of how exactly kids catch lice. (breebot, would you know?)  i'm terrified that they're crawling all over me trying to find a resting spot as i type.  i hope i'm just being a hypocondriac and scratching the bugs that aren't really there. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm beginning to wonder if my body purposely gets ill the first free moment i have.&nbsp;&nbsp; i guess my body is just trying to be  polite  by not wrecking a work/school week or a vacation with illness, and i'm quite thankful for this   but      ....   since i dropped my little sister off at the airport  (after a two week visit)  a few hours ago&nbsp;my temperature has been rising as well as my general feeling of being sick.&nbsp;&nbsp;i have rapidly evolved from a happy host&nbsp;to a cranky ball of ache.&nbsp; ugh.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; i had really wanted to clean my apartment after the storm of tea cups and biscuit crumbs, but now all i really can do is whimper at the cat and obsessively take my temperature.&nbsp;&nbsp;  (although, i do love a reason to obsessively&nbsp;take my temperature.)&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;   atleast i'm spending some quality nap time with the cat before i leave town for the next adventure.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        maybe not all of new york has a large price tag.     &nbsp;  my little sister and i were out walking from one place to another in hopes of shooting pictures when the flooding&nbsp;downpour began.&nbsp;&nbsp; it was one of those downpours that weather.com failed to predict, and wouldn't have happened if either of us had thought to bring an umbrella.   as the rain hammered down there really was no where to run for cover, and it was one of those&nbsp;warm summer rains that didn't seem so bad as it soaked through our clothing.&nbsp;  until we started to catch a chill, of course.   it was one of those few instances where i'd catch a ride with a stranger, or hail a cab...&nbsp; but the road was&nbsp;empty.   we walk further down the road, our flip flops start sliding around on our feet and water is dripping thru our eyebrows...&nbsp; when a cabbie calls out at us if we want a ride.   we slide onto the leather backseat, dripping water into the cab.&nbsp;&nbsp;   driving us to our destination  (which if we had walked it, we would've been able to start our own swimming pool with how soaked we would've been)   and i try to hand him some money.    "No Charge."&nbsp; he says with a smile.&nbsp;    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       new york city seems to constantly battle my pocketbook.&nbsp;&nbsp;this is mostly because this is&nbsp;a city where it even costs money to breathe.&nbsp;&nbsp; which mostly seems at battle with my experiences in the city i truly love (london, for those of you new to the home game)&nbsp; where although many things are expensive, you can still love socialism for providing fun free things,&nbsp;ah. &nbsp;whereas new york city, the center of the capitalistic world, seems rather hesitant to offering anything for free.   my little sister and i have a knack for ignoring everything except the sale racks in clothing stores.&nbsp;&nbsp; we like to maximize our fun for the least amount of money possible.&nbsp; thus the new york city pricetag seems to cause a little bit of conflict.&nbsp;&nbsp; especially when the things that are free seem to be free for a very specific reason.&nbsp;&nbsp; like for instance the walking tour that didn't move...   back in my london days, i loved walking tours.&nbsp; it was a wonderful way to soak up some of the history from the winding streets.&nbsp;&nbsp; so in trying to replicate the fun of a walking tour with my sister, we tried out a freebie.   somehow i wonder if these speaks volumes about americans in general, but during the first hour of the tour the tour group moved from one side of the street to the other side of the street.&nbsp; that's it.&nbsp;&nbsp; the tour guide did seem knowledgeable, but because we were in a place where there are more people living on this particular street block than in small town usa&nbsp; it was hard to hear a damn thing.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; i was personally holding out for the great revelation in the tour, and something that involving actually moving around, but as it never happened we ditched the tour group.  &nbsp;&nbsp;  i'd like to stress the this tour group only managed to cross the street in the time of an hour.&nbsp; and it wasn't a very wide street to cross.    
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         i never ever ever want to go to another college orientation for parents again.    due to being the oldest child of a single parent, i embarked on a college orientation adventure this week for my little sister...&nbsp; meaning i was pretending to be the parent becoming orientated to the idea that  *gasp*  my  little baby  was growing up and going to  college .&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; (i would say please save me from hell for saying the following things, but i think this past week has absolved me of any past or future wrong doings, and should&nbsp;grant me sainthood.&nbsp;  sorry mary, i guess i won't be&nbsp;your &nbsp;co-pilot on the bus to hell .) let me tell you a little secret: this was the&nbsp;  MOST PAINFUL  &nbsp;experience of my life.     my reasons      two little words:&nbsp;  my child  . &nbsp;&nbsp;i never noticed this before, but this phrase drives me batty.&nbsp; i guess it is because it is said by smug individuals who really seem to have no life outside of bragging about their  horrible child .&nbsp;&nbsp; example utterance, "Well," said ultra smugly with a nose pointing upwards and eyes looking down upon the other people in the pseudo conversation, " my child  is perfect in every way."  &nbsp;i discovered that i am in fact allergic to something...&nbsp;  the country .&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; this was discovered when i couldn't stop sneezing and my head couldn't stop throbbing until i drove back to civilization to breathe dirty air.&nbsp;&nbsp; also, i am absolutely terrified by a pitch black sky and the silence of the middle of nowhere.  parents are really fucking stupid.&nbsp; honestly, i had hopes that these parents would disprove my theory that the majority of the population is composed of idiots because these are the parents of children at a smart and elitist college.&nbsp;&nbsp; but i was wrong, so very very wrong.  to keep myself slightly sane and to keep from gnawing my ears off, i decided to keep tallies of idiocy.&nbsp; my favorite moments where the parents absolutely flipping out about the meal plans.&nbsp; see the kids can have unlimited meals in the dining halls during the regular hours of operation, and they get an additional $200 to spend at other campus eateries.&nbsp;&nbsp;  eight  parents made a huge fuss about this, in a comical way as if their poor little johnny was going to starve to death... which leads into the next point (and makes me wonder why i'm numbering these points in the first place)  people do not listen to other people.&nbsp; most parents (like in the starving issue above) wouldn't listen to the previous questions, and would ask the same damn questions that had already been asked.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; it seemed that most of these parents were ultra eager to open their mouths and spew the toxic waste about how perfect  their child  is, and would only wait for the lapse in conversation to spew.  two words:   GOOD MORNING  .&nbsp; i guess i'm just not&nbsp;a chipper&nbsp;enough to be amused by speakers who repeat good morning until the audience is loud enough.&nbsp;&nbsp; i'm okay with waking up early in the morning, and i'm completely okay with other people who are early risers, but i really do not need the multiple good mornings.  one piece of punctuation: the  exclamation mark .&nbsp;&nbsp; i honestly wonder if i was suffering from an allergic reaction to the overuse of the exclamation.&nbsp; it peppered the speeches of the speakers and it decorated all of the handouts.&nbsp; it made me wish it was a symbol of gouging a brain (or eyeball) out.  something that was completely missing:  sarcasm .&nbsp; previous orientations that i've been forced to endure, i've managed to find other people to make-fun of the entire event.&nbsp;&nbsp; everyone on this parent orientation was brimming full of happiness and were completely free from sarcasm.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; i felt slightly bad for being an enabler, but i let my sister escape from her orientation just so we could be the only people on that campus who was laughing at the entire event.  my sister is going to go to a school that is mostly full of boys.&nbsp; (around 75% of the campus is male.)&nbsp; i don't think i like boys.&nbsp; (for what it is worth, i don't really think i like girls either.)&nbsp; but the entire campus reeked of boy.&nbsp;&nbsp; everything from the directions to the campus, to the lack of names (in obvious places) for classroom buildings.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; the women's bathrooms were complete with urinals (ah, i've peed in enough men's rooms that i should have honorary membership) and everything seemed designed by a man.&nbsp;  which reminds me, i need to start working on my subversive side project that ties into this.   i was shown pictures of campus cops hanging out with students...&nbsp; playing the guitar with students around them... ice skating with the students...&nbsp; playing sports with the students...&nbsp;&nbsp; all while a very enthusiastic campus cop decided that he had to turn around and admire how wonderful these pictures were.  two words:  formal dining .&nbsp; i understand the school is making a grandiose effort to blow hot air up the asses of the parents who pay the outrageous tuition&nbsp; (thank goodness my sister is there on a scholarship) but they forced us to eat all of our meals in a formal dining hall.&nbsp; i couldn't just grab food and hide, i had to sit at a circular table and pitter patter with the other parents.&nbsp; i had to wait for food that i didn't really choose (which was much much better than what they served the students, i bet) to be served to me.&nbsp;&nbsp; and then i had to be polite to everyone at the table.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; it really amused me that one mom was slightly confused because she had never been served a meal before...&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; and the whole thing made me recall my years in  the house  and how i know how to place my napkin and that i'm not supposed to touch any plates.  i was subjected to eating a meal with a father who was sad that his wife wasn't there, not because he wasn't having an enjoyable time but because he knew how much  she loved  that kind of torture, i mean orientation.  i was subjected to people who had the mindset that they couldn't let go of  their child .&nbsp;&nbsp; the parent orientation and the incoming student orientation were on different sides of the campus, specifically so the parents would start to let go.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; one story, "my wife and i dropped our son off in his dorm room.&nbsp; he said, "c'ya, bye." and my wife nearly lost it there.&nbsp; all she wanted to do was make his bed and he was already done with us."  i was subjected to more "oh my child is so wonderful" than a person should ever be exposed to.&nbsp;&nbsp; of course i guess i could've combated it all with a spewing sequence about how wonderful my sister is, but her wonderfulness was diminished because i was subjected to all of these ultraproud parents and their gushing stories about their absolutely wonderful kids.   i could possibly go on for another 15 points, but life is interrupting this rant.&nbsp; perhaps later i will entertain you with stories from the trenches of hell.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i've noticed that after a lifetime of computer usage, i have never taken a class where i actually learnt how to use a computer program.  usually, i've learnt how to use computer programs the same way i learnt how to use a computer by a combination of luck and disaster on my own.   i have been the person in front of a room, explaining how to use a specific computer program, but i've never been facing the computer while a teacher talks in the front of the room.  it is the strangest sensation. (i must keep my ego in check.)  i have already jumped to the aid of a fellow classmate.  it is like during the class i know i'm just a student, but as soon as the call for help  i swoop in and help because everything we've learned thus far makes complete sense to an old-time computer user.   but, there is also a problem with everything making sense and seeming easy...  essentially it means my mind starts to wander or want a fast forward button for parts of the class.  i've caught myself wandering and then find out that i missed a quick explanation of something i don't already know.    there is also something very strange about learning how to use a program correctly, instead of a explorations leading to discovery and insight about a program. when i've learned programs on my own, i'll have to rely upon help files or google-- it is strange to have a living body in the room for questions and problems.   of course that self-learner inside of me would rather figure it out on my own, or eavesdrop on the help the teacher gives to the completely clueless students. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (i'm currently angry at broadway.)  in the strange contradiction of being annoyed at how prudish americans were over a nipple at the superbowl -- i've reached my limit with senseless nudity in theatre.  it isn't the nakedness itself that troubles me, it is all in the framing.  from a historical standpoint, acting has been a male profession with most female roles (if there were any) were played in men in drag or by female sex workers.   this has trickled into the modern era, where it seems there are fewer parts for females in comparison to males and the parts for the few females seems to include a rather lot of nakedness.  pointless nakedness.   nakedness that usually fails to further the plot, and only shows the audience how perky or saggy the breasts and buttocks of Miss Naked Actress are.   in a way it kills the plot because the director could only resort to using one of the few female actresses as shock value.   how shocking, what a spectacle, a naked lady!   in helping fuel my anger, it seems that there are a plethora of male characters and roles but females are typecast into a few.   she's either the sex-pot, or the crone, insane or motherly.... seldomly a positive role model, and usually only an accessory to the male actors.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i am the happiest little girl.  it has been two painfully long months and now  urlLink my radio station , WOXY, is coming back from the silent airwaves!!!!  i'm off to do a happy dance dedicated to the anonymous donors and the rebirth of wonderful radio. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       why must you apply cheesy thunderstorm sound effects to your watering cycle?  -- confused shopper   i've heard that at certain grocery stores, people aren't just shopping for groceries...   but besides some strange words exchanged to me in the freezer aisle once, no stranger has ever hit on me whilst grocery shopping.  this is most likely due to the fact that i rarely shop alone, and i rarely shop at a place where people speak english as their native language.  now i have been officially hit upon in the grocery store, and i don't know if i should be disturbed or flattered.  it happened in the organic section.  i was contemplating how "eating well" is actually related to having wealth, as i was eyeing a display of expensive but possibly tasty organic produce.  (i actually dream of the time when i can afford to eat only organic foods, and will have wonderfully sharp chopping knives.  this most likely won't happen anytime in the near future.)  and here comes this person who starts chatting me up, and broke my organic thought process.  i would rate this attempt to hit on me rather low.  it was too cheesy, but not clever or funny.  (i could've fallen for a "Hey, you dropped your name tag" and then being handed a packet of sugar.)  and then the individual seemed hurt that i started walking away towards the conventional produce without offering my name, my number, or the likelyhood of sex. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (i'm frightened by individuals who purchase a cart full of doggie toys.)  if i am not mistaken, usually if one is going to use a coupon they must surrender it when they decide to purchase something.  people cannot go to a store, after purchasing stuff, and decide  now is the time  to use coupons for a previous purchase.   just like every time i go to my local craft store i lose a part of my manhood, every time i go to the petstore i lose a bit of my sanity.   there was some stuff i had to get for my cat, thus requiring a little trip out to petstore hell. i spacecadeted while waiting in the line to give them money for their goods.  perhaps if i was concentrating on the actual pet store, with the barking puppies and that lingering petstore smell, i would've noticed the woman holding in one hand a single can of cat food  (it was supposed to be free because i bought X) and a fistful of expired coupons.  and i would've quickly line jumped my way out of there.  in that horrible notion that the "customer is always right" (except when they're absolutely insane) the clerk manually typed up the woman's long receipt for the couponing to begin.    personally, if i was the clerk i would've killed this woman.  she was... not the nicest of individuals.   sadly, that is prolly how she got away with purchasing stuff awhile ago and brought in all of her coupons later for some change back.  i notice how everyone in the line behind me, has jumped to another line and are already out the door.   while i'm still waiting behind this woman who complains over every single item, and uses the standby of "well, i was told when i was here last week that that coupon would work.  i don't care if it is expired now, i bought the stuff last week."  frequently i forget coupons, but i'm not terribly upset over losing the twenty cents i could've saved. and although i'm related to someone who used to coupon to the point that her grocery shopping usually involved a huge cart of food plus change, i would never dream of returned to the point of purchase demanding money back for coupons.   it is not worth a chunk of my life.  but this crazy coupon carrying cat lady, was still loudly bitching when i left the store....  i might dream about becoming a crazy cat lady when i grow up, but not  that  crazy.   
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       previously, calls to poison control have been due to me being slightly retarded.  this includes all of the times where i have mindlessly placed poisonous objects into my mouth or writing utensils that had previously taken bathes in poisonous chemicals...  as well as the time i had decided to wash my windows with a small bottle of windex, but instead of making sure the spray bottle was pointing towards the window, i sprayed windex directly into my eyes (a burn worthy of hell) and my mouth.   i mentally file these events into my "i'm a klutz" category, which also involves the current war of me versus doorways and walls.  this month the walls are winning, as they've taken a bite out of my shirt, temporarily captured me by my hair, and caused more bruises than i'm willing to admit.  this most recent call to poison control was due to a plant, (and not the tasty tasty mojitos, robyn) my beloved pencil cactus.   (for a sense of scale, the pot is larger than my two hands put together.)  it is a very strange looking plant originally given to my family (i have just a small cutting from a pencil cactus tree larger than me) by a strange old german woman who liked smuggling plants from other countries.  its pencil thin "branches" grow in every direction in an almost gravity defying way, and it is completely without needles.  (never make fun of cacti with needles, by the way.)  and for the most part is it a really happy low-maintaince plant.  except i learnt the hard way that it is poisonous.  i had decided that it was time to switch my plants around on my plant stand, and it was time for this pencil cactus to move to a new location.   although the plant looks rather flat in the picture (it is hard to capture its looming evilness and strangeness with my digi camera), the branches reach out all over the place..  thus making it difficult to hoist the plant up without branches poking me.  in the few seconds i carried the plant from one point in my room, to another... a few branches poked into my mouth and caused the mouth burn of the century.  i'm talking about a burn where i could no longer tell if there was any spot in my mouth not burning.  i possibly should've taken photographs of my taste buds as they were freaking out, and vibrating with burn.  and it didn't help much when the web tells me that i might start hallucinating, i might stop breathing, and i could possibly die... all due to a plant i've had for years.  this is where i'd like to thank poison control.   they are one of the few places left where if you call you're not automatically put on hold but instead you're talking to a calm individual with helpful advice. i seriously love poison control, especially that such a thing exists.  in the end, my mouth burned for awhile and nothing else happened.  and i went off to do other things. only slightly afraid that my taste buds had burnt off when a cafe gave me unsweetened lemonade.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       now seriously, what is a year in my life without at least one call to poison control? 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (previously mentioned  urlLink here ) kirby was several parts cute, a couple parts sad, and an unknown amount of demon.   which i think makes for a bad pet equation.  my theory is that kirby was a puppy mill dog, and his previous owners couldn't deal with his emotional trauma and gave him to the pound..  or he had a size issue and tried to make up for his small stature with being a demon dog.    or previous owners got kicks out of abusing little dogs.   whatever it was kirby wasn't a completely happy dog.  one day when i let  him out in the front yard, some neighborhood children decided to come up the driveway and play with him.  he returned the favor by chasing after the kids and barking (i was alerted to the whole things by the nearly-fake sounding screams of a little girl, "Wooo AAAAAAh!  Wooo AAAAAh!")   thankfully the kids weren't hurt, and the dog obligingly went back into his cage.  he had other displays of demon dog, which were interspersed with displays of being cute and being tormented by the cats.  (i'm talking about a dog so small that he can't go up or down steps, and one of the cats was twice his weight.)   but dad didn't really react until...  the dog broke my youngest brother's skin. and dad returned the dog to the pound.  "We'll keep quarantine him for 10 days, and see if he dies from rabies."  the people at the pound said. Sometimes the ambiguous use of pronouns is scary, especially when there is a potentiality of rabies.   perhaps i should research a bit into the symptoms of rabies, because apparently "foaming at the mouth" isn't always a symptom.  it was strange how quickly attached my dad had become to this demon dog.  (they were only together for a month or so.) and there is something bittersweet about the impending death of a dog you don't like, but elicits tears from my dad..... 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the only thing i really remember about 2nd grade was that was the year we sang songs about cicadas.  [that might've also been the year my younger brother would only venture outside with the protection of his "butterfly hat", which somehow kept him safe from flying insects by being wildly colored.]  i wish i could remember the songs but the only songs i remember from grade school are: my old kentucky home,  urlLink  muppet babies poopoo sha wa wa , and a bunch of patriotic songs.    i also remember hating/fearing those damn cicadas.  17 years later, when those cicadas are supposed to be popping out of the ground, i'm in a different part of the country waiting.   some news article told me that those cicadas of my 2nd grade year were going to visit my new residence.    and i've been waiting....  i've been both terrified about their return, and yet hoping to get the chance this time to crush them whilst my feet are protected by shoes.   thinking that  this  time they won't be such scary little creatures because i'll have the upper hand.  but either i was cheated out of the return of the cicadas, or the cicadas were so terrified by my presence they decided to stay underground for another 17 years.   either way, it has been a cicada disappointment. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       slouching as humanly as possible on my kitchen chair with his left paw moonlighting as a cane for back support, my cat loves to pretend he's a human audience member of my kitchen's private cooking show. and i have begun to wonder if such behavior is normal for cats.  ginkgo loves to watch as the knife severs pieces of vegetables. he'll study the process as if he's a kitchen spy preparing to give up my secrets, or as if in his next life as a human he'll be a chef. his eyes are focused upon my hands and the things that they are doing with the magic of the knife, the cutting board, and that hidden cold place of the fridge.  sometimes he'll strain his neck from his seated position on my kitchen chair, to make sure he knows where every piece of food goes. he'll watch as things are chucked into skillets, bowls, or accidentally slide onto the floor... which of course causes him to temporarily slink down to watch the escapee. it is never extremely interesting to him, thus his head will quickly resume its gaze at my hands.  when i move on to working on the stove top, he stands with his front paws on the back of the chair to get a good view, as if sauteeing onions transmits secret messages. i wonder if his gaze somehow affects the flavor of my food, or if he's trying to transmit messages back to his fellow cooking show cats in someone else's kitchen.  unlike other cats who only seem interested in human food if the meal includes chicken in any form, he seems completely satisfied just to keep me company in the kitchen. to the point that the times i'm feeling ultra lazy cooking-wise, he'll still humanly contort himself on my kitchen chair and will meow at me as if to guilt me into preparing something before his eyes. it is as if after an entire day of sleeping, i am his evening entertainment.  although i find it extremely strange that he chooses to cook with me, it is quite nice. especially because unlike any other cat in the world, he keeps his perch on the chair and never the counter... plus he's strangely polite, as he always seems to wait to chomp down his cat food until after my food is done.  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         i've began to see why certain people dread going to the dentist      despite all of the years of braces and drillings, i never feared the dentist office. mostly because i love the feel of freshly cleaned teeth and the painful parts always involved sedative-induced dreams. my childhood dentist (who also starred as a puppet in one of my gassed dreams) was a friendly guy, the wall had a mural of cartoon characters, and his assistants were bubbly. (i vaguely recall times when their bubbliness bothered me, but that was mostly because the entire office was open air.. thus meaning 4 kids would be in chairs and all of the assistants would be chattering away with each other.) i slightly wonder if my childhood dentist would still be my dentist if my family never moved. and i would still go with my parents after my teeth were cleaned, to the meeting room near the exit where my childhood dentist would talk about teeth with my parents.  fast forward to the present, where i'm struggling with something i actually learned at the horrible  urlLink Parent Orientation  of a little bit ago... after an entire life of having parents schedule doctor and dentist appointments, it is very weird for children to finally make the jump into scheduling such things for themselves. i guess the college was hinting at the fact that most college freshmen will have to endure this, but i've realized in regards to dentist check-ups..... i've never scheduled one on my own (thanks to my parents with insurance who scheduled dentist appointments for me during breaks and holidays), and this might explain why i've slightly procrastinated the whole ordeal. i guess i'm trying to ignore adulthood as much as possible.  i have dental insurance through my school which covers procedures (like check-ups and other regular dentistry type things) and all of last year's school year, i'd tell myself that i need to make an appointment for an appointment and then i would somehow manage to forget about it for several months. until it got to the summer time, where i got rather annoyed at myself for having dental insurance that i haven't taken advantage of, i made an appointment for a teeth cleaning. all i really wanted was that ultra-clean feeling of going to the dentist, to have my teeth scraped and polished.  of course sometimes it seems like what you come in for is not what you get....   i have a korean soon-to-graduate dentistry student assigned to me. sometimes i can't completely understand what he says to me in the first few minutes of me being in the chair staring off at a picture of twigs that mangaged to be apart of a museum college. he asked me if it was okay if he x-rayed my teeth, and recalling the quick x-rays of my childhood i thought it was okay.  just so you all know my head is the only part of my body that is big (23 3/4 inches, according to the measurement i just took) everything else is small compared to the average female  (neck: 12 inches[i could never wear chokers as they were too big for me], hand length: 6 inches [i should prolly wear little kid gloves], height: 5 ft 3 3/4 inches [i should get illegal height surgery], feet: 8 1/2 inches [i can fit into little girl shoes]... my goodness the measuring is getting out of hand.)  it doesn't come as a complete surprise that i have a small mouth. small enough that the x-ray films cut nicely into the top of my mouth and the bottom of my mouth when my mouth was shut.   i thought it was only going to be a few x-rays, so at first i didn't complain... but then it ended up being a nevering ending "Open your mouth" the taste of rubber gloves and plastic met with a plastic thing being arraigned into place and then "Bite down". i broke out into a sweat under the protection of the lead blanket, and when the dentist said "You only have 4 more" i possibly could've killed him if i wasn't restrained under lead.  18 x-rays in total. (i had to ask, as anything after 4 seemed astronomical.) my poor little mouth was shot with an invisible x-ray 18 times, and my mouth was opened and closed onto piece of plastic more than 18 (because near the end i could barely close my mouth in the proper way for the x-ray.) it left my mouth feeling raw, but i thought it was all about progress and making doubly sure that i have no cavities and my teeth are happy.  with the hell of biting down into mouth cutting plastic being over (and while the x-rays were being sent to the machine) it was time for the next bit of personal hell.... a jaw examination.  i don't ever really remember a jaw examination in my life (but i also have no recollection when the fillings i have came from, partially because i was always amazing at what teeth ended up being the naughty cavity keeper) but i'm fairly certain i don't want to experience another. and i especially didn't want a jaw examination only to be followed by the teacher re-examining my jaw to judge the student dentist's outcome.  1. my jaw doesn't open as far as it should and/or could  2. the left side of my jaw makes popping noises (especially after 18 x-rays)  although the jaw examination didn't really hurt at the time, later that night i couldn't fall asleep until i drugged myself into sleep and the following morning i began to contemplate life on a liquid diet.  i told the dentist that previously i would have times where my jaw would either refuse to open or it couldn't open after a certain point but that has mostly cleared up. only after i left the dentist office did i remember that the big ugly bicycle accident i had when i was 14 (and biking in europe) caused my chin to receive a bunch of stitches and whacked the left side of my jaw. (and in that slightly horrific moment of "Oh yeah! so that is why..." my mouth wouldn't open at times, it was probably due to my ugly bike accident in germany.) crap, now i have something to worry about and maybe i should discuss with the dentist on the next visit and it might also explain why my tension headaches are quite frequently in my jaw. crap, crap, crap.  the dentist decided it was time to actually examine my teeth (after the horrible jaw examination and the fucking 18 x-rays) which are still mostly happy, frequently flossed and brushed babies in my tiny mouth. during the examination i realized a horrible evil thing as i was staring at the bose speaker in the ceiling, i actually like  urlLink lite fm . it is one of those inoffensive radio stations that play all the music which should really make my ears bleed, and yet i was jamming along to the radio station in my dentist seat. i'm hoping the only plausible reason is that it was a source of escapism during a horrific dentist appointment, i'm really hoping that this doesn't mean that i should give up on life now. looking at the current playlist, i hope i was on drugs at the time. but maybe i should listen to it and give up on my beloved  urlLink WOXY  (which you ought to listen to NOW)..... nah.  well, the appointment time had almost run out (of 2 hours) when the dentist realized that i hadn't gotten the one thing i had wanted from the beginning... a teeth cleaning. the next available time slot wasn't until the time i'll be away, and of course the office will be closed immediately after i get back. i'll have to wait until the beginning of the school year, the receptionist told me, and the dentist looked a little disappointed in himself for failing to give me a teeth cleaning. of course after this experience, i wonder if i should really bother with the student dental services... of course on the other hand, how long will it be until i have dental insurance again? how long will i go without a professional teeth cleaning? i could hope for socialized medicine by the time i graduate from grad school in the spring, but i'm unsure if that'll happen. the future seems questionable.  maybe all i need is a cool dentist. someone with a good sound system, good music, or maybe just lets me wear headphones as a i gaze into pretty pictures above the dentist chair. i recall my dad had a really cool dentist back when i was a child....  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       as a child of the 80's, i quickly associate the word "disco" with "suck" without really ever knowing if disco actually sucks. i don't know if word association came from my parents  (i only remember their absolute  Hatred  of the beatles as well as early rock/pop that has been fodder for the oldies stations)  or from growing up in the disco backlash decade.  recently i read a book,  urlLink Playback:  from the Victrola to MP3, 100 Years of Music, Machines and Money   , which makes me want to love disco.  (You really ought to read this book, it is about the history of recorded music and how the history repeats itself in the fear of new technology.)  just so you know, i am a big sucker for bad techno  (as well as bad bad bad pop... y'know the music i should be ashamed to like because it is an overplayed evil song with great pop hooks.)  and i love the idea of dance parties and music worthy of dance parties.  (actually, now that my little sister has left the apartment and i've returned to being healthy my apartment has returned to Dance Party ydeleK!)    thus, i've speculated that i would love disco if just given the chance...     urlLink  Take Me to the Disco    in launch's amazing prediction of my realization that disco might actually not suck, it plays a fantastic plastic machine's song that i haven't heard for awhile  (and had always bothered me due to a song sample that i can't place, but this is me going off the music nerdom scale. the lowest/highest music nerdom point was during the roadtrip to washington dc where F. and I managed to spend several hours listing off bands in alphabetical order)    and i think i might be in love with the disco dancer in the video. i speculate that perhaps disco might be a hidden gem of coolness, and instead of focusing on actual disco music i turn to something more awesome than awesome....     urlLink  Learn to Disco Dance    (what language is this? matt k. is it austrian, german, or something else?)  if anything this post might show that i've clearly lost my mind due to my recent illness. because this instructional video which is in someother language   i don't understand  , has been watched by me countless times... complete with me dancing along to the really really bad music at the end.  it is amazingly wonderful video from the 70's with an older guy (in his 40's?) and a heavily made-up woman who seems to be channeling a different decade. i'm slightly confused as to why the disco party at the end of the intructional part of the video are all coupled dancers, as i thought disco was the first non-couple dance... but i still love the dance party at the end of the video.  i wish i knew where this video came from, and something about the awesome soundtrack. as i do realize that i have actually heard popularized "disco" songs  (now that i've researched   urlLink  allmusic    for some disco musical tips)  but i'd really like to listen to some club disco and see if it is still dance inspiring.  
    
    
</post>


</Blog>