<Blog>

<date>28,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Slashdot raises lots of  urlLink interesting thoughts about banner ads .  The idea is to let users control the ad delivery, and even to allow users to comment on ads.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink  The Merchants of Cool  , a Frontline documentary featuring Mindjack advisory board member Douglas Rushkoff, is on PBS tonight.  Check your local listings for the time.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink ATMs dispensing music?   I don't quite see the logic in that.  I'm not entirely against paying a nominal fee for music, or any other media, but if I do have to pay for it I'd be much more likely to buy stuff from my own PC.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My chair started squeaking a few days ago and it's driving me nuts!
     

    
</post>

<date>20,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The New York Press has a  urlLink lenghty article  about the post dotcom crash scene that's worth reading.  
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Francis Collins'  urlLink 10 Most Surprising Things About the Human Genome .
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink FILMSPEED  has great movies you can download for free.  The Third Man, in particular, is one of my favorite films of all time.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
       For sale:  An STB nVidia ZX 8MB 3D Accelerator (AGP) and a 40X NEC CD-ROM drive.  Interesting trades considered.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've started uploading stuff to my live365.com radio station.  There's not much there yet but you're welcome to  listen .  (cable/dsl or higher required)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      FEED's latest special issue is an excellent  urlLink examination of video games , with contributions from Carl Steadman, Steven Johnson, Justin Hall and others.  Don't miss it.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      New DVD!   urlLink The Maltese Falcon .
     

    
</post>

<date>14,February,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I once had a personal homepage, long before weblogs came into fashion, but never managed to update more than a couple of times a year.  Here's hoping I'll be a bit more successful with this.  Big thanks to  urlLink Bopjet  for hosting this and  urlLink Mindjack .
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Register reports on "war driving"  - the wireless equivalent of war dialing.  Instead of having your modem dial into thousands of networks until you get in, you just drive within range of a wireless net with your wireless-equipped laptop and hack away.    related:   urlLink The latest issue of CIO  has a great feature on wireless.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Short documentary on digital filmmaking and Star Wars Episode II. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Rumour has it  that the parent companies of  urlLink Inside.com  and  urlLink Brill's Content  will be announcing a merger as early as next Monday.  Apparently the two print magazines would fold into one called  Brill's Inside Content  and the two websites would form  Media Central Inside.com .  Rolls right off the tongue, doesn't it?
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Destroy All Monsters - Survivor: Monster Island .  My money's on Mothra.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I just spent some time playing with the beta version of  urlLink Atmosphere , Adobe's new 3D environment software, and thought I'd give a couple of quick impressions.    I've always been interested in VR and spent quite a bit of time working in VRML, but I think the inherant problem with VRML was that not enough attention had been given to community.  You could build all these really cool places but people couldn't interact in them.  You also couldn't easily move from one 3D environment to another without going back and forth between 2D web pages.  I was involved with a project that tried to solve some of these problems with VRML (anybody remember Terra Vista?) but it didn't as far as we would have liked.  Atmosphere appears to have addressed these problems.  It's not the first product to do so, but maybe Adobe has enough muscle for it to gain wide acceptance.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks to  urlLink Onebox.com  I should now be able to receive faxes.  Not suprisingly, they don't have local phone numbers for Fredericton so I chose a New York City area code.  If anyone wants to give it a whirl, my number is: (212) 894-3748 x2690.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I was supposed to be working.  But, through a long trail of procrastination, I ended up redesigning this site.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Quotable Mindjack!  From Mike Sugarbaker's  urlLink review of Lemon :  "If you have no patience for the lengthy ruminations of brilliant madmen, Lemon isn't for you. But you read Mindjack, so you're probably into that sort of thing, right?"
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack is featured in the links section of this month's  urlLink Netlife magazine .  It doesn't seem to be online yet so here's a scan:   
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Well, the big Yahoo news yesterday was that Tim Koogle is stepping down as CEO and that they'll miss forecasts in the first quarter.   urlLink Today the stock tumbled .
     

    
</post>

<date>07,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Times reports  that the  urlLink Trogan Room Coffee Machine  webcam is going offline for good later this year.  That pot should go in a museum.    
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink It looks like  there's some big news due from Yahoo later today.  
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The new issue of  urlLink Mindjack Magazine  is now online, featuring a first for us - a live concert review.  With original photos even.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      It's not good when a box of Sinutab describes your day.   Sinus pain, headache, congestion, itchy, watery eyes.   Ugh.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The End of Free  - chronicling the demise of free stuff on the net.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm not sure I like the direction  urlLink FEED just turned .  "The filter", a new weblog linking to outside content is now featured more prominently than FEED's original content.  It's also not clear what the difference is between the filter and  urlLink Plastic .
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Hey now.   urlLink Jon Lebkowsky  has started a blog.  Coolness and wisdom is to be found within.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      What looks like the  urlLink new PalmOS PDA  from TRG looks mighty impressive.  The official launch is rumored to be on Monday.  If it's priced reasonably enough it might get me to upgrade from my 512k PalmPilot Personal.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Stick figure fighting action  like you've never seen before.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Evan Williams of Blogger has more on  urlLink How the Trellix Deal Happened -- and What It Means .
     

    
</post>

<date>16,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Need a  urlLink logo ?  Maybe a  urlLink website ?   urlLink Email me .  I will work for  urlLink toys .  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      It was just announced that  urlLink Trellix is licensing Pyra's Blogger technology , giving Pyra a much needed cash infusion.  Dan Bricklin has a fascinating account of  urlLink how the deal happened  on his site.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I recently got the  12 Monkeys DVD , which is excellent.  It's worth picking up just for the included feature-length documentary,  The Hamster Factor and Other Tales of Twelve Monkeys , about the making of the film.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       Redesigned again.   
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Inside.com reports  that Economist business editor Chris Anderson has been named editor of Wired, replacing Katrina Heron.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The new issue of  urlLink Digital Web Magazine  is out today.  Lots of interesting stuff.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This is  one of the reasons I'm a vegetarian. (washingtonpost.com)
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Justin's  urlLink back from Japan  with stories and pictures.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Something screwy's going on with my computer.  Things are crashing, my mouse is stuttering, MP3s are skipping when they didn't before, and sometimes it just slows to a crawl.  I've got a nagging feeling that I'm going to have to do a complete format and reinstall Windows but I  really  don't want to do that. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Mikel.org  pointed me to this rumor that  urlLink Automatic Media is in trouble .  Automatic is the company that consists of Feed, Suck and Plastic.  Hopefully it is just a rumour.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Home of the Underdogs  is an amazing resource for anyone that loves computer games.  Not only do they have hundreds of games you can download which are no longer available from the companies, they also have a wealth of information about many of the games.  It's not entirely legal, but I think it's a great public service.  It's even better now that they have one of my favorite games,  urlLink Gabriel Knight .
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink There's a great article  by William Gibson in the The Observer's  urlLink Special Japan Issue .
     

    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink 'We reinvented culture the way we wanted it - with great big shoes' .  David Bowie writes about glam in today's Guardian.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a while since I played around with customizing  urlLink My Yahoo!  so I don't know how new this is, but you can now use themes in additoin to plain colors.     
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Streaming video from the Reboot conference , featuring Justin Hall, Dave Winer, Evan Williams, Douglas Rushkoff and others.  It'll make ya think. 
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack is now in deep development mode and, through the magic of blogs, you can  urlLink follow the action as it happens .
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Shift is back  with a design that looks  urlLink vaguely familar .  It looks good but those javascript scroll boxes are slooooow.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      If I had heard Doves  urlLink Lost Souls  album last year, I would have included on my  urlLink best of 2000 list .    Hawksley Workman's  (Last Night We Were) The Delicious Wolves  will probably be on this year's list.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      CNET has  urlLink video of Steve Jobs tour  of Apple's new retail stores.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Ain't It Cool News  has some great clips and pictures from the new Coen Brothers film, The Man Who Was Not There.  I'm excited.  
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Yet another redesign.  I think I'll stick with this one for a while.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Sure, it's advertising.  But it's  urlLink damn good advertising. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      DSL!
     

    
</post>

<date>09,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Feed has a great  urlLink interview with Cory Doctorow  today.     The overlap between Doctorow's day job at OpenCola and his night job writing fiction makes for a unique combination: It's almost like William Gibson launching a company that sells neural plugs and stim-sims.  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Douglas Rushkoff's Frontline documentary,   urlLink The Merchants of Cool   is being rebroadcast tonight on PBS (check your local listings).  Set your Tivo or VCR, or watch it as it's on even.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,May,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm DSLless for 10 days.  I suppose compared to most other companies that's pretty snappy service, but it's still 10 days without DSL.  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink FEED  gave the official word today that they're sutting down, at least for the foreseeable future.  The same goes for  urlLink Suck , although it looks like  urlLink Plastic  will be continuing for now.    Both FEED and Suck have been online for six years, and have been excellent throughout.  Hopefully they can pull out this funk and come back in one form or another in a few months.
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Jason Kottke has some  urlLink great pictures from the Louvre  today.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Great roadtrip article by Mark Frauenfelder  in One magazine.   "A half-century ago, the streets of Southern California were filled with flamboyant towers of consumerism -- spires and obelisks and beacons -- transmitting neon-fortified messages of optimism to families riding in cars with space-age tailfins. Life was good, and the marvels of modern science were making a world as new as tomorrow." 
     

    
</post>

<date>30,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Bill Frisell's latest album  Blues Dream  arrived in the mail today and it only confirmed what I suspected.  I have got to get more Frisell.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink blogdex  is a spider that crawls blogs and generates a list of the most linked to sites.  Ten bucks says blogdex itself is number one by tomorrow.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       living dangerously  I haven't hotsynced my PalmPilot in a couple of months.  How long can it go before craping out?  Stay tuned.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      This year's Webzine conference in NYC looks like it went over well.  We have coverage in the  urlLink current issue of Mindjack .
     

    
</post>

<date>21,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Looking for some summer reading?   urlLink Canadian Media Theorists: Canadian Media Resources .     found via  urlLink mikel.org  
     

    
</post>

<date>17,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I've been reading  urlLink Boing Boing  since before it was a weblog but I just noticed the links to  urlLink Mark  and  urlLink Cory's  garage and flea market finds today.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Man.  I uninstalled McAfee Viruscan and my computer seems twice as fast.  Now, to find a virus scanner with less of a memory appetite.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Mindjack is back  and there's more to come.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
         They don't make keyboards like this anymore.  This is the Underwood Portable I mentioned the other day.
     

    
</post>

<date>30,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink StarOffice 6  looks like it will be a big improvement over the current version.  I've been using StarOffice as an alternative to PowerPoint, but the sluggishness mentioned in this article has stopped me from using it regularly for much else.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Synapse  is now offiicially open.  Come and stop by.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Synapse is live!  Almost.  It will publicly launch late tonight, but we're looking to get some conversations going before that.  If you'd like to help out  go to  urlLink synapse.mindjack.com  and join now.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My copy of  urlLink Words! Words! Words!  arrived the other day.  It is good.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I seem to have unintentionally started a typewriter collection.  I was given an Underwood Portable Typewriter in near perfect condition yesterday.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      More cool stuff.  I picked up this Egyptian painting on papyrus at an estate auction the other day.        It's actually in better condition than this picture makes it look.   urlLink Here's an image  I found of it online.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      We've finally set a definite launch date for Synapse, Mindjack's long in development online community.  Monday, next week.    Stay tuned.  It'll be good.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink APOD: 2001 August 20 - The Lagoon Nebula in Three Colors .  My new wallpaper.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I went to Atlantic Canada's largest flea market in Sussex, New Brunswick yesterday and got a sun burn and this:                  For 25 bucks.  According to  urlLink this site  it's a 1911 model.  It works great apart from a few sticking keys.  Now to find some ribbon for it.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Staples was selling  urlLink Kensington Videocams  for $20cdn yesterday.  The result?  This ain't a webcam.   Reload if you want to, but it ain't changin'.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Holy shit.  According to Advertising Age,  urlLink the Industry Standard is ceasing publication .
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink blogBuddy  looks useful.  It's a Windows-based Blogger interface.-  urlLink via Evhead 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Via  urlLink Doc Searls Weblog  I discovered a  urlLink great weblog all about 802.11b .  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Village Voice: Features: High Speed, Freed by Peter Meyers  -  Good article on 802.11b wireless networks in NYC.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      New!  In the mini-blog over there you can take a peek at some of my recent media consumption.  Even better, if you buy it too I'll get $$.  Which may be some added incentive for me to keep this thing updated.
     

    
</post>

<date>13,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Today's DaveNet  is a great explanation of  urlLink Blogger API  and what it means.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
      My copy of  urlLink Words! Words! Words! Magazine  is on it's way to me from New Zealand.  Is yours?
     

    
</post>

<date>10,August,2001</date>
<post>


       
        today's best spam    DEAR SIR / MADAM :  HOW DO YOU DO !  WE CAN SUPPLY HIGH QUALITY FLYING SHOES, SUCH FLYING SHOES LET YOU BOTH CAN WALK NORMALLY, AND CAN SLIDE AS FLYING. IT IS A SORT OF FASHIONABLE PRODUCT.  THE FOB PRICE IS USD 7.70 PER PAIR, WELCOME ORDER !  PLEASE LOOK THE DETAILS WITH PHOTOS FROM : http://www.chunpai.com/flyingshoe.htm   ALSO WE HAVE WOOD SHOES, BAMOO MATS, WOOD FLOORING, ALUMINU PLASTIC DECORATE PANELS, ETC, LOOK THEM FROM : http://www.chunpai.com/first-english.htm  BEST REGARDS !  MR.TAN LONG  ( SATRAP ) GUILIN LINGUI SHENGPING XIAOXUE BAMBOO & WOOD MANUFACTORY ADDRESS: No.229 RONGSHAN ROAD,LINGUI,GUILIN,GUANG,CHINA TEL / FAX: +86-773-5592687 E-MAIL: chunpai@public.glptt.gx.cn WEB SITE: http://www.chunpai.com/first-english.htm
     

    
</post>

<date>24,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Now in Mindjack is  urlLink an excerpt  from Cory Doctorow's novel-in-progress, Eastern Standard Tribe.  Cory's also taking part in a discussion in  urlLink Synapse .
     

    
</post>

<date>23,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
      You skip reading a few issues of Wired and you miss something really great:   urlLink My Own Private Tokyo  by William Gibson
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Coltrane at 75: the Man and the Myths  - New York Times
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Photgraphica's been down for a while , but in it's absence I've discovered two other great photologs (when they started being called that I'm not sure).   urlLink PixelPile  and  urlLink Common Threads .  Now, if only I had a digital camera.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>


       
       It Came From British Columbia!   urlLink Great space art  made with found objects. -  via  urlLink robots.net  
     

    
</post>

<date>30,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack's been  urlLink slashdotted .  And  urlLink BoingBoinged .
     

    
</post>

<date>29,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink prolific  has David Bowie's excellent  urlLink cover of America  by Paul Simon in real audio.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Novemember is  urlLink National Novel Writing Month .  The goal is to write a 200 page, 50,000 word novel by November 30th.  I think I might start by trying to write a short story in a month.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink A great gallery of low-res pictures  taken with a PenCam.  Not to mention a very cool interface.    urlLink via boingboing  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks to the very cool  urlLink BlogBack , comments are back.
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Odyssey made it .  Yes, I am a space geek.   
     

    
</post>

<date>23,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Watch as Odyssey enters Mars' orbit .  Cross your fingers.
     

    
</post>

<date>22,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Mindjack  is looking for writers, preferably ones that can commit to writing at least one article per month.  We can't pay anything right now, but I can promise that we'll pay you as soon as we make any money ourselves.  If you're interested, drop me an email:  urlLink editor@mindjack.com .  Include a few samples of your writing if you can, and I'll get back to you real soon.  Feel free to pass this along to anyone you think might be interested.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Special features on the new  urlLink Monty Python and the Holy Grail DVD :  • Region 1 encoding (US and Canada only) • Color, Closed-captioned, Widescreen • Commentary by Terry Gilliam & Terry Jones, plus general complaints and back-biting by John Cleese, Eric Idle & Michael Palin • Theatrical trailer(s) • High definition widescreen presentation with pink frilly edges • Subtitles for People Who Don't Like the Film (taken from Shakespeare's Henry IV, part II) On-Screen Screenplay: read the screenplay while you watch the film • Exciting "Follow The Killer Rabbit" Feature! • A special version for the Hard of Hearing • A glorious extra 24 seconds absolutely free • Three Mindless Sing-Alongs • Join Michael Palin and Terry Jones in their special documentary: The Quest for the Holy Grail Locations • How To Use Your Coconuts (an educational film) • Monty Python and the Holy Grail In Lego • "On Location with The Pythons". Genuine 18 min. location report made in 1974 by BBC Film Night. (broadcast December 19, 1974) • An Interactive Cast Directory - discover just how many roles Michael Palin plays • Tons of Terry Gilliam's original sketches plus posters • Behind-the-Scenes Photos - hitherto unseen by human eyes • A Load of Old Rubbish - a surprise package of mystery items specially included for the mentally challenged • How the directors' recce used up the budget • Widescreen letterbox format  I can't wait.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Cory Doctorow has started recording  urlLink audio versions of all his stories , starting with   To Market, to Market, The Branding of Billy Bailey , which I'm downloading now.  Where do you find the time, man?
     

    
</post>

<date>08,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Matt Hinrichs (a.k.a  urlLink scrubbles ) has done some great illustrations for  urlLink Synapse .  Join now to see them all.   urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>04,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Redesigned.  Again.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Crap.  I ordered the new Citizen Kane DVD  urlLink from one place  the other day, and today found it ten bucks cheaper  urlLink somewhere else .
     

    
</post>

<date>21,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Infinite Matrix  is back.  Whoohoo!
     

    
</post>

<date>12,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Now in Mindjack:  urlLink Marketing The X , an examination of Microsoft's marketing of the Xbox and Windows XP, and the first of hopefully many articles by Jane  urlLink umami tsunami  Pinckard.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Justin's site  is turning into a wonderful resource on all things cool and Japanese.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I have got to start writing more.  Anybody want to pay me to do it?
     

    
</post>

<date>08,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I watched  urlLink No Maps For These Territories  the other night, a great documentary that director Mark Neale was kind enough to send me (running a magazine has it's perks).  The whole thing consists of William Gibson sitting in the back of a limo musing on everything from cyberspace to religion.  I'll be doing a full review in Mindjack within the next couple of weeks.
     

    
</post>

<date>02,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Here's what the Slashdot effect looks like.   
     

    
</post>

<date>31,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      New Mindjack today.     urlLink Twenty Twenty : Astronomical Vision by Chris McKinstry   "Very early on a cold February morning in 1979 I looked with one of my highly astigmatic eyes through my first professional telescope at a setting Jupiter. Even with my flawed vision, the long white metal tube so finely manufactured it could have been a piece of sophisticated medical equipment, let the cloud bands of our solar system’s largest planet and the bright points of a handful of its moons into my mind, making me feel a shadow of the shock that Galileo must have felt when he saw the same sight before any of us. " 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I redesigned  urlLink Mindjack  a bit.  It should load quite a bit faster now, and look better at lower resolutions.    New this week,  urlLink Design for Community  reviewed by David Brake.  Next week, an interview with Derek Powazek.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      The new Infinite Matrix is up with a long excerpt of Cory Doctorow's new novel,  urlLink Down And Out In The Magic Kingdom .  The Liberty Square ad-hocs were the staunchest conservatives in the Magic Kingdom, preserving the wheezing technology in the face of a Park that changed almost daily. The newcomer/old-timers were on-side with the rest of the Park, had their support, and looked like they might make a successful go of it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm the top left corner on Cory Doctorow's  urlLink Four blogs on one page , which is one excuse why I haven't been posting to this blog very much lately.  I'll try to give myself a kick in the pants over the x-mas break and get this thing going again.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Wonderful gallery  of Atari concept illustrations.   via  urlLink BoingBoing  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I redesigned the Mindjack front page a bit to include the entire  urlLink Daily Relay blog , rather than just excerpts.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink denizen  is a new weblog about classic gaming from the creator of  urlLink Home of the Underdogs .
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Now in Mindjack, a review of the  urlLink Xircom Wireless LAN Module  for Palm m500 handhelds.  A subject that only Cory Doctorow could make this interesting.   Four or five years ago, I had a sea-change in my computing experience. One day, I realized that I had started to view any computer not connected to the Internet as just a fancy game-console-cum-jumped-up-typewriter. Working on an airplane or from a café just felt wrong.    This feeling deepened and magnified a thousandfold the day I got my first iBook and Airport Base Station. If you've used wireless networking on a laptop, you know what I'm talking about -- snatching the Internet out of the very air is an experience you won't go back from willingly (another one is TiVo -- I've stopped watching TV in hotel rooms because I can't choose among thirty hours of custom-recorded programming and skip commercials). Just as TiVo ruined me for dumb TV, 802.11 ruined me for wired networking or no networking at all.    And it keeps on getting better. 802.11 isn't just a technology, it's a movement, an ad-hoc world of open base-stations around the world. Just haul out your 802.11-equipped device and start hunting about for a network. If you're in a major city, chances are you'll find one before you go a block. Forget 3G and Blackberry and all those other pale imitations of connectivity: community wireless is the real shit: fast, unmetered, insecure and out of control.    
     

    
</post>

<date>16,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack T-shirts are  urlLink now available .  These are high-quality, genuine screenprinted shirts, not the Cafe Press stuff.  Thanks  urlLink Brunetto !  If you're looking to get some shirts printed I highly recommend them.     Also available are  urlLink Mindjack coffee mugs , featuring an illustration by  urlLink Matt Hinrichs .  These are Cafe Press ones.  Please buy some.
     

    
</post>

<date>14,January,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Build your own robot!  urlLink CAM-08 – The Perpetual Humanoid Model .       I want one.  Especially if it comes with the sound effects in this  urlLink video .
     

    
</post>

<date>28,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
      February needs at least five more days.  I still have loads of work that was supposed to be done by now.
     

    
</post>

<date>26,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Well, this blog is back and oranger than ever.  Now just to get  urlLink Daily Relay  back up and running.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
      My mindjack.com email should be working now.  Let me know if you still have problems.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Crap.  All my @mindjack.com email addresses are messed up.  If you need to reach me please use donald@melanson.ca.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Who'd have thought Mattel is still making classic  urlLink electronic football games .        I used to think these were the most amazing things ever.  Then I got an Atari 2600.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2002</date>
<post>


       
      There's a great little Chinese grocery down the street from my apartment where I always find something I've never tried before.  Today:  Iron Buddha Tea.     It's really good tea.  Try it.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Jim Lai reports on Digifest 2002  in the new issue of Mindjack.  	  I didn't have much in the way of expectations going in to Digifest 2002; pretty pictures, glitzy art/advertising pieces, and possibly some cool tech. I was pleasantly surprised by the breadth and depth of the presentations.   Wednesday night.  Hit the media session and got to see some graphics on a really big screen. The theme of this international digital media festival was the "4-D challenge", to go beyond the third dimension. I would deem this festival to be a success overall, as by the end of the festival it would be apparent that there was much speculation on what constitutes this fourth dimension. Now that I've spoiled the ending and gotten that out of the way, on with the festival itself.  The original vision was for local (Toronto) participation, but it quickly expanded in scope with the arrival of international submissions. There was a soirée before the keynote where attendees could snack on catered food and mingle. Quite a few people were there, many of them either dressed hip or stylishly. I almost felt that I was underdressed, but I just put on my best casual face and it was all cool. Business cards flowed like water.  
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I got an iBook!  OSX sure takes some ajusting to but I'm really impressed with it so far.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Neil Gaiman  on whether someone should or should not be a writer:  And in answer to your question, if you worry about job security as a writer, that's a very good indication that you aren't a writer. Hating writing is another good one, although I know writers who hate writing. (They are miserable.) 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      In the new Mindjack: a  urlLink report on SXSW Interactive  by Jon Lebkowksy, with photos by  urlLink Paul Bausch .   This year's South by Southwest Interactive conference was lean and mean - attended mainly by the core group of edgy 'net whackadistas, the conference had an interesting vibe, like "Wow, glad the goddam dotcom splurge is over, let's get back to what we were doin'…" And what we were doin' had real depth, it was way more compelling than ecommerce or net.publishing, the kinds of projects MBAs brought to the table when they started calling the Internet an 'industry' and creating the concept of the IPO casino. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack is back from a short break with a great article by Douglas Rushkoff:  urlLink Conforming to the Machine .
     

    
</post>

<date>10,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      If you aren't reading  urlLink futurefeedforward , you should be.   NEW YORK--ABC news magazine "20/20" reporter John Stossel, accidentally decapitated late last month while shooting a segment "debunking the myth of wind power," returns to the air Wednesday in a special interview with 20/20 anchor Barbara Walters. "It's really an amazing story," explains Walters. "Most people wouldn't even survive decapitation, let alone have the guts, the determination, to keep doing their jobs. It's a real triumph of the human spirit." 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Everyone's favorite Cory Doctorow, Cory Doctorow, has gotten a  urlLink new gig  at the EFF, which reminds me that I haven't suported them nearly enough.  So, for the rest of March I've decided to donate $5 from each  urlLink Mindjack t-shirt  sold to  urlLink EFF .
     

    
</post>

<date>02,March,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Daily Relay  is finally back up.  We're using Blogger as an interim solution and will probably switch to Blogger Pro if I can't get the Moveable Type problems sorted out.
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      This week's Mindjack:  urlLink Reading McLuhan  by Melanie McBride.  If there's a message of the 'for dummies' age it's that nothing is beyond our grasp. And our desire to believe this is reinforced by trends like usability, which privilege economy over elucidation. No one anticipated it all better than Marshall McLuhan, who whittled big insights into sound bites in order to engage an audience beyond the lecture halls of the University of Toronto. With the help of Tom Wolfe and others, the scholarly McLuhan became a cool media prophet. It was, and still is, a practical strategy in anti-intellectual times. But in the process, much of McLuhan's meaning has been reduced to a one-liner. This has as much to do with the absence of commentary on McLuhan's literary, philosophical and cultural influences as it does with the way his work is taught.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      The new issue of Mindjack deals with one of my favorite topics:  urlLink Robots! 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      My submission to the  urlLink Burn Baby Burn  mix CD swap, with dispraportionate amounts of Bowie and Reed, of course.   urlLink     (click to read tracklist)  
     

    
</post>

<date>14,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack advisory board member Douglas Rushkoff has started  urlLink a blog .   Expect good things. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Not that you''d expect anything less, but the  urlLink Criterion Collection  website is really excellent.  It's similar the old  urlLink Criterion Goes To The Movies  CD-ROM, which is also worth checking out.  Although it takes some work to get it to run on any computer made in the last six or seven years.  Both are filled with great essays on some of the best moves ever.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2002</date>
<post>


       
      We've got a  urlLink great interview with Simon Singh , author of  The Code Book , in the new issue of Mindjack.  
     

    
</post>

<date>28,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Gadzooks, it's been a long time since I last posted.  Sorry.  I interview  urlLink Derek Powazek  in the new Mindjack, in which he talks about online community, his book and weblogs as journalism.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack is trying out a new guerrila advertising campaign.  Feel free to use either of this ads on your weblog or website.         More to come soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,September,2002</date>
<post>


       
        urlLink Mindjack  is back!   Now to get back to work on this site.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Mindjack interviews Warren Ellis!     So why aren't you reading comics these days?  Really, it doesn't seem to me that there are many comics being written for me. I want something with a little more muscle and bite than standard-issue power fantasies, whimsical romance, the autobiographies of people who never do anything and things with elves. The Western medium has cycles, and it's currently in a creative downturn. That doesn't mean there isn't excellent work being done. That simply means there's not much of it. And, on a personal level, little of it is talking to me. Not many comics reflect the fact that I live in a multicultural society fitted with a global communications net, nor do they reflect the fact that I don't own a pair of Superman underpants.  
     

    
</post>

<date>26,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Howard Rheingold  urlLink interviewed on NPR  (RealAudio link).  I still haven't gotten my copy of  urlLink Smart Mobs  yet, but hope to soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack's Jim Lai checks out an art exhibit in the form of a billboard:  Transmedia 2002's  urlLink 15 Seconds of Fame.    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Now in Mindjack:   urlLink Cybersecurity Nosebleed  by Sarah Granger "Security is the newest over-hyped commodity in the United States. I keep visualizing driving down highway 101 past billboards that read: "Big government wants big security" along with a picture of an ape beating on its chest. Somehow as seriously as they say they are, I'm not convinced." 
     

    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Mindjack's back , with a proper relaunch this time after a bit of a slow start last month.  We've got a lengthy article on Lawrence Lessig by Bryan Alexander this issue, plus my review of the neat little l'espion digital camera.  Spread the word!
     

    
</post>

<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'm kicking myself for missing the  urlLink David Bowie concert  on BBC Radio 2 today.  But at least I was able to find a couple of the songs  urlLink somewhere else .   Bewlay Brothers is amazing.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      In case anyone's sitting on the edge of their site, rest assured the Mindjack relaunch is still on track for Monday.  Get the word out.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I can't get enough of CBC's  urlLink 50th anniversary  specials.  I wish they'd start a cable channel and show nothing but stuff from the 50s and 60s (and 70s and 80s too).
     

    
</post>

<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I just got  urlLink Syberia  and  urlLink Post Mortem , two promising new adventure games from Montreal-based developer  urlLink Microids .  As you might be able to judge from some of my posts here, I'm a big fan of adventure games.  The traditional kind, where you can carry an enormous inventory in your pants, and explore the game at your own pace.  I've been thinking a lot about the genre lately and plan to write something about it soon, aside from reviews of the aforementioned games.  I'm interested in hearing your thoughts on adventure games.  Do you think there's a place for them today?  What are your favorite games?    src="http://www.quicktopic.com/18/iaMjuWreTAS.js">   urlLink Comments   document.write("(" + ct_18_iaMj + ")");    
     

    
</post>

<date>22,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      This doesn't bode well for me getting much work done this weekend.  The Adrenaline Vault's  urlLink Best Shareware of 2002 
     

    
</post>

<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Justin Hall on South Korea:  urlLink korea will be televised .  TVs in cabs, TVs in subways, and stacks and stacks of tiny, tiny televisions to take with you.   But I was still able to enjoy more television, this time in the Seoul subway. Televisions up in the subways, instead of static ad bulletin boards! This is the future! It's fun to see and fun to watch now. Soon it might be annoying or normal. But this first brush with more constant televisual stimulation was definitely exciting. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I'd like to comment on  urlLink Movielink , the new studio-approved online movie rental service, but unfortunately this is all I'm able to see:  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Sign #249  urlLink CNN  needs some sense slapped into them:  it's the day after an election, Republicans have taken control the Senate, Dick Gephardt is stepping down as House minority leader and right now, on Larry King, they're talking about the Winona Ryder verdict.  At least they took down the  BREAKING NEWS  graphic.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      There's a  urlLink new trailer  for Steven Soderbergh's  Solaris  up today -- one of the movies I'm most looking forward this fall.  I got a copy of the great DVD release of Tarkovsky's  urlLink original film  from  urlLink The Russian Cinema Council  a short while ago.  Which I hope to review for Mindjack before the new film's released.
     

    
</post>

<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Cory Doctorow  urlLink reviews Smart Mobs  in the new Mindjack:    Smart Mobs are the Slashdot effect applied to the meatspace zeitgeist. A squillion like-minded souls who don't know each other and will never meet pop out of the transmetropolitan brickface and break the white-noise balance of atomic viewpoints to speak with one voice, roaring a righteous YES or an adamant NO without organizers, without leaders, without manifestoes or forethought.   Also this issue, an in-depth look at  urlLink the Internet Archive  by Doug Roberts.   Tucked away in one of the seediest neighborhoods of San Francisco is a roomful of over two hundred computers with a terabyte of data stored on every three. Stairs from the street lead up an intimidating hallway that opens into a room with 15-foot ceilings and just-this-side of hip ductwork in the ceiling. To the right is a storage area with a single desk, to the left are Baker's racks tightly packed with off-the-shelf HP desktop machines, each turned on it's side to maximize the space. Somewhere in all that ductwork, a fan is squeaking painfully. Walking into this echoey, over-warm warehouse space, it's easy to be underwhelmed until you realize what you are looking at: spinning away on these computers is nothing less than a copy of the Internet from 1996 until today.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack is back after a short break.  The new issue has  urlLink a report  on the Supernova conference by Doug Roberts.  Supernova 2002 was an ambitious conference and Kevin Warbach, the organizer along with pulver.com, acknowledged that from the outset when he said that he had crammed a three day conference into two days. The conference was touted as a glimpse into the decentralized future. Decentralized systems, as may be obvious, are systems that have no single point of control - the Internet is a perfect example. No one entity or agency controls it, no single server provides the service, and no single point of failure will bring down the system. Warbach sees these types of systems as the fundamental issue in computing for the next decade. By then end of day one, however, it became clear that the conference was going to be about one thing: blogging. 
     

    
</post>

<date>14,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      I just discovered through  urlLink Smartmobs.com  that Clive Thompson has a  urlLink blog .  It's great.  Which reminds me, I really need to update the blogroll on this site.
     

    
</post>

<date>09,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Doug Roberts is covering  urlLink Supernova  for Mindjack and  urlLink blogging it live .  
     

    
</post>

<date>08,December,2002</date>
<post>


       
      Sometimes Amazon.com is just plain eerie.   
     

    
</post>

<date>29,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      If you're going to be in Los Angeles on February 15, don't miss  urlLink Live from the Blogosphere , a panel discussion to be put on by Rhizome.LA and moderated by Xeni Jardin.  "Live from the Blogosphere!" brings together six innovators in blogging: Mark Frauenfelder, Heather Havrilesky, Evan Williams, Susannah Breslin, Doc Searls, and Tony Pierce. The panel will discuss the birth of blogging, the emergent tension between blogs and traditional journalism, innovations in blogging such as video-blogging, audio-blogging, and mobile-blogging, the shifting roles of race and gender in the Blogosphere, the state of the blog economy, and the way blogs may be reshaping contemporary media.   (cross-posted from  urlLink Daily Relay )
     

    
</post>

<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I review a cool laptop bag today in  urlLink Daily Relay .
     

    
</post>

<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Douglas Rushkoff meets Al Gore and is  urlLink suitably impressed .   He was a much brighter, open-minded, and - if I might add - cosmic thinker than I gave him credit for, before. I felt like he was really one of "us," if you know what I mean: the kids in college who got those wild thoughts about how everything in the world, and even beyond, is connected somehow. And evolving. Only Gore found this organic view of reality reflected in the Constitution of the United States, and sought to enable the extension of this Enlightenment thinking into practical reality. 
     

    
</post>

<date>24,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      New Mindjack up today!  Cory Doctorow on  urlLink William Gibson .  Justin Hall on  urlLink Super Monkey Ball 2 .
     

    
</post>

<date>23,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Check out  urlLink this preview  of Warren Ellis and Colleen Doran's new graphic novel,  urlLink Orbiter .
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Ah crap.   urlLink Shift magazine publishes its last issue .  Shift has pulled out from dire situations before, but this looks to be the end, which is a real shame.  They've been a consistently great magazine and an important voice in the ever-changing sphere of digital culture.  The final issue is due out in two weeks, I urge everyone to pick up a copy.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack's been  slashdotted .
     

    
</post>

<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Fray  redesigned for the first time in over six years.  Blog coming soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Deepsky  have posted their remix of David Bowie's "I Took a Trip an a Gemini Spaceship" on their website.  Not as good as the original, but worth a listen.   urlLink RealAudio link 
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This post  by Warren Ellis to his blog isn't just cool because he linked to Mindjack:  At Bruce Sterling's house in Austin, Texas, Howard Waldrop beams Cory Doctorow an mp3 of some swampy old rock'n'roll from the dawn of time. The next day, across town, his powerbook scorching the flesh off his legs, he beams it over to me in England. I put it up on a private server for Fraction in Kansas City and Laurenn in San Francisco, while reading the first few chapters of Cory's new book, which he sent to me from an airport a few days before, squatting by the power outlet next to the public toilets.  urlLink continued...  
     

    
</post>

<date>29,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Slashdot launches  urlLink games.slashdot.org  and, holy cow, it's ugly.
     

    
</post>

<date>10,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Mindjack contributor and game reviewer, Justin Hall, has written a great article on  urlLink ethics in video game journalism  for the Online Journalism Review.  The first print magazine covering video games Electronic Games was co-founded by Bill Kunkel in 1981.  Kunkel describes those early days in a recent interview: “To an extent, we were cheerleaders for the industry -- we loved these games, we wanted to see more of them, we wanted to keep writing about them.”  Not much has changed in the past 20 years.  Game publications and Web sites still mostly employ low-paid hobbyists who are easy targets of lavish marketing events that encourage inappropriate ties between game makers and game critics. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,April,2003</date>
<post>


       
        This is incredible.  Scientists have discovered a "Colossal" squid in the Antartic, much bigger than the previous biggest giant squid found.  And it's not even fully grown.  Deep sea exploration is nearly as fascinating to me as space exploration.  Just imagine that there's something like this that no one has ever seen alive.  It's interesting that the article notes the funding for the research is from the Discovery Channel.  While it's great there's some funding available, just as with space exploration, there should be much more.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Googling for sites that mention Mindjack, other than mindjack.com, suprisingly results in 5,800 links.  I like the description on  urlLink this one .  Mindjack Magazine. One pusle showing the osmotic swelling of Digital culture as the norm. 
     

    
</post>

<date>26,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      New Mindjack up today.   urlLink     Josh examines the online, interconnected groups of people that you turn to for advice on music, art, fashion, books, etc., and the broader implications of these taste tribes.  Also, Justin Hall  urlLink reviews Panzer Dragoon Orta  for Xbox.  The illustration, btw, is by  urlLink Matt Hinrichs , who will hopefully be doing semi-regular ones for us.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I review  urlLink Soul Calibur 2, Syberia, and Post Mortem  in the new Mindjack.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Via  urlLink scrubbles.net : a (nearly) complete index of  urlLink Alfred Hitchcock's cameo's .
     

    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My article,  urlLink Reunderstanding Movies , about how DVDs and the Internet are changing the way we watch movies, is in the new  urlLink Mindjack .
     

    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've started a film blog:   urlLink melanson.ca/movies .  No promises on how often I'll post to it, but I try to do as many reviews as I can.
     

    
</post>

<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      For your linking pleasure, a new Mindjack ad.  More sizes coming soon.  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been blogging more at  urlLink Mindjack's Daily Relay  lately and hope to be able to keep it up.  We've got lots of good stuff coming up in Mindjack in the next few months, so keep your eye on the blog for further updates. 
     

    
</post>

<date>21,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Apparently from a sidewalk in Austin.
     

    
</post>

<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Derek Powazek's comment over in  urlLink this entry  at Blackbeltjones reminded me of Amazon.com's incredibly good  urlLink Friends & Favorites  area.  Mr. Bezos, if you're reading this, please add this to  urlLink Amazon.ca .  Canadians have friends too.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been playing around with  urlLink Flickr  lately, the latest toy from the mad geniuses at  urlLink Ludicorp . You can find my Flickr profile  urlLink here .  I've also started a  urlLink Mindjack group  as a bit of an experiment.  If it works out I may try to integrate it into the site.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now in Mindjack:  urlLink Is Nothing Sacred? Digital Music for a Digital Age  by Ian Dawe. Antero Alli's  urlLink Hysteria  reviewed on DVD by Jesse Walker.
     

    
</post>

<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       	 		 		  		 		 		 			 urlLink     			 				 			 urlLink 1250_img0028 			 			Originally uploaded by 			 urlLink QuizMaster2000 .			 		 	      urlLink    Posted by  urlLink  Don Melanson   from  urlLink Flickr .    urlLink    
     

    
</post>

<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The new issue of Mindjack is  urlLink now online . In this issue:  urlLink Linked Out: blogging, equality and the future  by Melanie McBride. Plus  urlLink Kill Bill Vol. 2  reviewed by Jesse Walker.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There's a  urlLink new issue  of Mindjack now online.  In it, the first article from Mindjack's newest contributor J.D. Lasica; he writes about copyright law in  urlLink "The Killing Fields" .  Also, I review DVDs of  urlLink Breathless, Russian Ark, and Z .  Spread the word.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "An idea is a funny thing.  It does nothing unless you do."  
     

    
</post>

<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm looking for someone to be Advertising Director for Mindjack. Must have advertising sales experience and be willing to work on commission.  This is a contract job that can be done from home.  If you're interested, please email:  urlLink donald@mindjack.com  (no attachments).   Also, we're constantly looking for great new writers.  If you want to write for us, drop an email.
     

    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm pleased to announce that VRML creator and all-around visionary Mark Pesce has joined Mindjack's ever-growing stable of writers.  His first article,   urlLink Redefining Television  , is an insightful examination of the state and future of the medium.  Here's a snippet:   In the earliest days of television, writers like George Orwell in  1984  and Ray Bradbury in  Fahrenheit 451  projected television as the instrumentality of a totalitarian future - a monolithic entity dispensing propaganda. And, if any of you occasionally watch Fox News, you can see they weren't that far off the mark. But here's the thing: the monolithic days of television are numbered. Actually, they've already passed - though, as yet, very few people realize this.  To understand why, we need to go back to first principles. What is television? Here's a functional definition:   Television is the capture, encoding, transmission, reception, decoding and display of moving images.   This definition applies to the Golden Age of television, and to the present era. Yet the definition of every word in the definition of television has changed, because of the introduction of digital production, encoding, transmission, reception, decoding and display technologies. 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm using this blog to play around with  urlLink Blogger's new features .  It will return to normal shortly.
     

    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm blogging a lot more on my  urlLink film blog  than I am here.  If you like movies, check it out.  And, of course, I continue to write and blog at  urlLink Mindjack .
     

    
</post>




</Blog>