<Blog>


<date>28,September,2000</date>
<post>

     
      Roommate sleeps soundly.  Music blares from the speakers.  Nothing wakes his sleep.   Anguished faces stare  At symbols on the black board.  Understanding comes.  Change is good my friend.  Man never sits by idle.  Live and change, or die. 
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2000</date>
<post>

     
      Names disguise desires.  Well hidden thoughts are made known  By our choices here.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2000</date>
<post>

     
      Beer bottles topple  Spilt beer-another party foul.  Too much fun to care.  Country music whines.  I can't believe what I hear,  "Romancing the sheep."  
     
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2000</date>
<post>

     
      Bear's hibernation begins in earnest; to end With the spring's warm sun 
     
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2000</date>
<post>

     
      Math Computations  Maple Five and Fourier  Series curve fitting
     
    
</post>

<date>03,December,2000</date>
<post>

     
      Snow is coming down. Soon streets will be slippery. A car on its back.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
        Love, peace and harmony.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2001</date>
<post>

     
      D-S-L is here. Frustration grows to anger. Why can't I connect?
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
       Seasons go quickly.   Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter   Cycles eternal.     Friday Afternoon--   A cold Winter's day wind blows.   Warm Cocoa and sleep.    Love, peace and harmony.     D-S-L is here.   Frustration grows to anger.   Why can't I connect?     Bear's hibernation    begins in earnest; to end    With the spring's warm sun     Math Computations    Maple six and Fourier    Series curve fitting   reams of paper gone ink stained fingers red and raw thesis presented.  Waiting for breakfast twenty-five minutes to wait eggs, grits, ham and toast.  Wake and get going work all day and party all night. Tomorrow comes quick.  Anguish faces frown the test is too tough, they say. guess-A, B, C, D.  Warm Winter's day, grin, wearin' shorts and birkenstocks, soon spring days arrive.  Flying @ 10k Reagan international in 4-7 min.  to travel to town; time's ticking toward talking the thorough thought.  Can Kenny convince completely compentent crowds " commit correctly"?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      I try to sleep nights. Dreams of theses keeps me up. When will it be done?!?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      foolishly thinking  "Thesis is done!" I once said. Oh, what a surprise!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Wouldn't it be great when the world doesn't obsess  over math theses?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Adventure began fourteen years ago today. Left on a bus.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Skaters, pucks and checks--  Great! Hockey season is here.  Isn't Autumn nice?  debates go awry  A Candidate's doublespeak  Both parties seem tied.  many days go by  no blogs and haiku written  Days are incomplete  Don't know what code brings  Sometimes it works, sometimes not  Endless Frustration.  Polite discussions,  Many things need to be said.  Some heed, some ignore.  Squirrel in the tree,  human hands working walnuts,  Was hungry, not now.  Heute ist Freitag.  Morgen ist Samstag, und nächst'  Tag ist Eisbecher.   (Just kidding around. !grin!)  Enough for today-  Let someone else have their turn  Creating Haikus.  Static comes in clear.  Race the dial across the band.  Dits and Dahs I hear.  No work, too much time  Write Haiku-use the time well  What would our friends say?  Dry autumn days; brown leaves  Will be here instead of red.  Dancing the rain dance.   Cool Autumn mornings  Sleep fades as I look outside;  See Leaves change their hues.  Tossing and turning.  Warm milk and pills are no use.  Insomnia sucks!   Roommate and iMac  Telephone lines are busy  Chatting with his friend.  Friends writing Haiku,  Putting the seasons in words,  Pay tribute to Chris.  Fall's bright Harvest moon  leaving the tree limbs behind.  reflects the sun's light.   Up at dawn, fires start.  Cracking eggs, campers awake.  Aromas, Stomachs growl.  Steamy breath escapes  bodies shiver in the wind  campfires warm campers.  Have you noticed how time seems relative to the number of eyes watching your every move? The more people watching the slower time seems to flow. If you don't believe it, teach math.   Forty bored faces  Eighty-two eyes watch the clock.  The bell's ring ends class.  Sleep in the cool shade  Bees buzz, birds fly, children play  Summer's memories.  White chalk and green board  Homework written makes sense now.  Right answers at last.  Random Creation  A day's discussion over.  He and I agree.  Cypher, secret notes  keeping others in the dark.  Cracking codes is hard.    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Seasons go quickly. Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter Cycles eternal.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Friday Afternoon-- A cold Winter's day wind blows. Warm Cocoa and sleep.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well, how does one say Thank you for all the work done? Thank you Teresa!
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Going home to work Ayden isn't home but it's close A-P-D again.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,March,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Backup plans to make. Thesis is coming along. Can't wait to finish!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

     
      No letter, a call; No Job yet to pay the bills, Feel Disappointment!
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

     
      What would the brothers think when I get there ready? "ora--labora"
     
    
</post>

<date>13,March,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Rain tapping outside It's another sleepless night. rat-ta-tap-ta-tap.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Spring leaves budding green. Grey branches erupt with color. Shady afternoons come.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Flowers peek from soils Colors fresh and tender smells Spring arrives in May. 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      "Your dearest wish will come true." --Chinese Fortune Cookie. I could only hope.  :)
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Hey you! Welcome Back.  I bet you thought we forgot  In ten days? No Way!  A Haiku I sent to Chris for the occasion of his return to Johnson City from Indy, IN.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      U-V-A-W Cavs I begin work in August Teaching Teachers Math
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Tomorrow will come And the next day will follow Summer marches on.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Looking for old friends...I like the web!
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Visiting old friends,  Weekends go by too quickly.  Homecomings are grand. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      trees reflect green hues    limbs sway in the summer breeze    shade cools midday sun.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I am here No phone, no 'puter Well, I am here.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      new places, newer faces Oh boy! it's going to be fun Wise, Virginia
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Discovery is the key to my home.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Boxes packed, stacked, hauled Men tired, thirsty and hungry the move is Friday.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Wow...Today is warm Sweat beads and runs down my face Fans run--moves warm air.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Good evening. Today, our fellow citizens, our way of life, our very freedom came under attack in a series of deliberate and deadly terrorist acts. The victims were in airplanes, or in their offices; secretaries, businessmen and women, military and federal workers; moms and dads, friends and neighbors. Thousands of lives were suddenly ended by evil, despicable acts of terror.   The pictures of airplanes flying into buildings, fires burning, huge structures collapsing, have filled us with disbelief, terrible sadness, and a quiet, unyielding anger. These acts of mass murder were intended to frighten our nation into chaos and retreat. But they have failed; our country is strong.   A great people has been moved to defend a great nation. Terrorist attacks can shake the foundations of our biggest buildings, but they cannot touch the foundation of America. These acts shattered steel, but they cannot dent the steel of American resolve.   America was targeted for attack because we're the brightest beacon for freedom and opportunity in the world. And no one will keep that light from shining.   Today, our nation saw evil, the very worst of human nature. And we responded with the best of America -- with the daring of our rescue workers, with the caring for strangers and neighbors who came to give blood and help in any way they could.   Immediately following the first attack, I implemented our government's emergency response plans. Our military is powerful, and it's prepared. Our emergency teams are working in New York City and Washington, D.C. to help with local rescue efforts.   Our first priority is to get help to those who have been injured, and to take every precaution to protect our citizens at home and around the world from further attacks.   The functions of our government continue without interruption. Federal agencies in Washington which had to be evacuated today are reopening for essential personnel tonight, and will be open for business tomorrow. Our financial institutions remain strong, and the American economy will be open for business, as well.   The search is underway for those who are behind these evil acts. I've directed the full resources of our intelligence and law enforcement communities to find those responsible and to bring them to justice. We will make no distinction between the terrorists who committed these acts and those who harbor them.   I appreciate so very much the members of Congress who have joined me in strongly condemning these attacks. And on behalf of the American people, I thank the many world leaders who have called to offer their condolences and assistance.   America and our friends and allies join with all those who want peace and security in the world, and we stand together to win the war against terrorism. Tonight, I ask for your prayers for all those who grieve, for the children whose worlds have been shattered, for all whose sense of safety and security has been threatened. And I pray they will be comforted by a power greater than any of us, spoken through the ages in Psalm 23: "Even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I fear no evil, for You are with me."   This is a day when all Americans from every walk of life unite in our resolve for justice and peace. America has stood down enemies before, and we will do so this time. None of us will ever forget this day. Yet, we go forward to defend freedom and all that is good and just in our world.   Thank you. Good night, and God bless America.--President George W. Bush's Statement made on National Television on 9/11/2001
     
    
</post>

<date>11,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      terror grips fast loved ones gone, friends not coming Too many lives lost.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,September,2001</date>
<post>

     
      My weekend passes.  Friends' faces blur. Clock--no friend--  sweeps the short days by.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Once the words were said, Then taken back, regrets born Best sex never had.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Soul mates once and 'gain, Years go by, loves and lives grow Perhaps together
     
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Cool autumn winds greet A special day for a friend-- His Birthday, Birthweek.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Fall's warm wind blows the  Once yellow leaves across the sky. Bare limbs scratch upward. 
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Success, sweet success I am happy to get this page  Working finally.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      The day draws nearer.    A celebration of sorts,    A friend gets older...
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Stars, stars, and more stars- To be surrounded by stars, Space Travel is great!
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Why does it seem our world is getting smaller?
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Five Weeks without rain Dust, fires, smoke make skies hazy  Come rain, dance for rain.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,December,2001</date>
<post>

     
      Nativity comes Blue and white drapes across streets St. Nick is coming
     
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2002</date>
<post>

     
      New Year's a coming The snow is falling and white Sound carries with winds
     
    
</post>

<date>14,February,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Just another day Red Hearts and white ribbon box A date with a girl
     
    
</post>

<date>17,March,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Green Beer, green hats, Green Cold winter's winds give respite Blue spring's days arrive
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Daffadils yellow Trumpets sound Sunshine flowers Bees float in midair
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2002</date>
<post>

     
      noisy neighbors Mowers cut the morning bliss green sprayed fans on walks.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Just getting back here Been gone for way too long Maybe I will get it.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Rockets bang silver Fire and crowds glow in twilight Sulfur breeze the water 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Heat shimmers, dances Cars vanish in far waters cloudless skies meet haze
     
    
</post>

<date>30,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Greek week. Rival Frats. In Jail.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Haiku read aloud Images and sounds conspire Create your own sight.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Banned Books Week 2002 -- War on Words: Censorship in Times of Crisis   Papers fly. Flames burn. Ideas die.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I am not sure if this is correct, but  urlLink Haiku definition - jr  gives a cool idea of how Haiku and other forms of Japanese poetry came about.  
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Pink and Green cactus  In the warm afternoon sun  Silent Observer.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      WE MEET AT DAYBREAK. Steps, pistol shots--bodies fall. Over a lover.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Contact off Port Beam. Range 8000 yards closing. Waiting to see lights.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The Gray ships depart; Cheers--Cries leave the fading pier. Sailors begin work.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The alarm chime sounds Email--it's haiku from Chris. Weathering the Storm. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Soon, birds will fly south; Gray will again color the hills. Winter rains pour cold.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      To teach in a school Oh so close to the ocean A good dream come true.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Students ask me "Why?" A clear answer seems ignored. Refuse to see it.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      X's and Y's Dance Across the board.  Students squirm  In pained frustration.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Waiting to hear news, The days slip by, the books read. Meet the Admiral.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The day has ended. Cool mornings, warm afternoons. Night brings friends and cheer.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Cry over pizza Boxes filled, labeled and taped. Moving van honks bye.  Barbi is moving. Smaller town and larger sheep. See you on Sundays.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The bell is ringing. The downtown square fills with folk's "Red-White-and Blue" cheers.  War is tragic, sons killed. Tears are wept and noses blown. The list is published.  War is tragic, its clear. Simple to send other's sons. This war is unjust.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Jets stream overhead. Mission's critical--Iraq War. Man's foolish dream--Death.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink 5-7-5   Clouds give way to sun. Morning's rain leaves the air cool. Ducks glide on the pond.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Fall colors creeps down. Starting at the top most limbs, Leaves change to bright hues.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      A few minutes pass. Blank stares and sullen silence Greets the careless prof.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      good morning to you. I know that the weekend nears. I hope to be there.  I have plans unmade. Trey's house, Judith's birthday gift. Lots to do Friday.  I play it by ear. Friends to see and food to eat. Perhaps you'll be there.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The day has blossomed. Dark clouds give way to blue skies. Fall trees spendid hues.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, I am here.  So what? What's there to do now?  What?!? Give you advice!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Bottoms up! Man's joy!!!  Beer Bottles, Rum, Three Hurrahs!  Bottoms up! yes indeed!
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The Days creep on by. The hours, longer not shorter, Have become wasted.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Yep, it has been since June that I sent a blog, sigh. I just don't know why.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Early Morning comes The fog lifts and the sun shines. Colorful leaves blaze.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Sunday Grey, dense fog Daylight hidden, dark shadows. Sunny Tomorrow.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Wish they would decide. My fate is determined when? Impossible dreams.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      My final tribute. A week is finally gone. The weekend begins
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Red ink to grade by. I am glad students can count. My money is safe.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      One more test to give. The class checks logic and more. Anticipation.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The end is nearing. Hours counting down to travel. The first half is done.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      National Coming Out Day Hurrah! Let's hear it for gays. Happy as a clam.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Just an hour left We leave for homes and harths I cannot wait.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      A friend sent email. He's been looking for awhile. Message sent. Come home.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Spend the night with friends. A trip to Kingsport for laughs. A long drought over.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Time is coming fast. A week without college life. Fall break in three days.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Heard bad news today.  Door is locked, entrance denied. The Window's open. 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
         To meet the public: My fans have requested pics. Aren't they crazy?
     
    
</post>

<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Thinking of my friends. Noting their strengths and talents. Why should I depart.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Morning Dew, green grass Sun streams create long shadows. Another day starts.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Toscha, sister seen. Tears in her eyes, regret filled. He loved you, yes you!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Sun warms bodies oiled. Skin reddens, dries, and ages. Life endured vainly.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Warm October Wind Leaves tossed hither and thither. Scarecrow's arms receive.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Silence suits the men. Hands heavy with the coffin. Feet follow the women.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Crispy Autumn Leaves Drift from branches in silence; Land on mouners' grief.  
     
    
</post>

<date>23,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Cold weather arrives. Cinnamon drifts from cookies. Holi-daze presents. 
     
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Windshield frosted white Morning breath mists the crisp air. Winter has arrived.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,December,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Rain pours over the roof. Lights twinkle on distant trees. Christmas Day begins.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,December,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Angry faces watch. Snow melts and road crews work; Winter white and brown.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Snow, white and fluffy, Formed figures from falling flakes. Snow ploughs scrape white roads.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Cold winds blow, flakes drift Winter bites noses and ears. Spring approaches slow.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Heat input equals Heat output of a system. Thank goodness for heat.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

     
      In the navy now Cannot afford to fuck up Anchors aweigh, mate!
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      School's out, school's out, Wow! Another year is over. Summer breezes in
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The big day arrived. Newport: cold and blustry days. Five Weeks and I'm done.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      New Mortgage,  headaches. New house causes pains in life. New furniture, new pets.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Men Aloft, Rising up Fit in body, fit in mind Kilo company!
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Delight in my work A few seconds and I am done. A secret of mine
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Rubaiyat 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Summer's humid days sticky nights, Max A/C rains pour from the sky
     
    
</post>

<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Relived, relieved, loved, A voice over the phone tells, A heart breaks open.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Footprints in the sand. Little kittens placing "stones" The Zen litter box 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Badges checked and scanned Keys jingle--the lock opens Boards and chalk greeting
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Sailors dressed in white Greetings exchanged and bags checked Morning has begun.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Time spent studying Voices reduced to whispers Books and papers wait
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Breathing is the thought Clear the mind of distractions Summer sun--breezes
     
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      How do I keep work Nothing is what it seems here Working hard is nuts.  
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The first test went well Heat Transfer and Fluid Flow Passed: Three point four five.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Dirty Grime walking Daniel's new job in the hood. Not bad for a day.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This is a posting To check the java scripting Let's see this Haiku 
     
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Houses built with brick Walls white, carpet beige, doors blue, New houses smells new.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Winds bend trees and boughs Stormy sea, waters surge in Hello, Hurricane
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I am sure today Tomorrow will be funny. C-T-E Lecture
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Sitting in classes This subject should be easy. My headache worsens.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Time grows short this week I must pass two exams now Days dim with the stress
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Arrows up, down. Lights burning on the back porch. Arrows flying by.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Leaves dropped from above Cause ripples in the water. Tree frogs sing the blues.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Lives lived and words said Missing the companionship Buddies united...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Bell Rings--Web Hellos. Old friend IM's to say hi.  Time heals broken hearts.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Mornings' chill startles Frost on the windows glares white. Traffic stalled, horns blare.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Terror Alert Level :    urlLink       
     
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am not sure why The page won't be posted now. Life is sweet today.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The new year is here Trumpets blare and fireworks blast The new year arives.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This day comes rarely People born too early/late. Are you one of them?
     
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Waking from slumber, The poet writes seasoned verse. Rise and be heard pen.  (To celebrate the return of Hiro Protagonist's pen.)
     
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Yeah, this is childish Colored candies from my youth. Fun Learning colors 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yellow tulips bud Blossoms open for the sun. Flags the passing wind.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thunder echoing Fast cars stream by screaming fans. Darlington's spring race.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The days are counted. Encouraging words arrived. Leader will be back.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sun Shines through glass panes Cats lay purring in the light. Warmth is all around.
     
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Fighting a bad cold Headaches, coughing, congestion. New spring illnesses.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The years tick on by. I am getting older, Fuck! Just another year.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Visited a friend Putting product on the shelves. Offered underwear. 
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Commander watched me Students bored, commander bored. Of course, it was good.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Solitary men-- Sit and eat hot chicken wings. Throw celery out.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Water bottles chill.  Runners strain the last half mile.  Skin burns in bright sun. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Its "Made in Heaven", If you want to find peace-Go! Oh, I wish I could.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Young lovers parking The early hours tick-by-tock Boy and Girl talking.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
        At home, no gray seen. Faintly-ocean's spray lingers. At sea, life is swift.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I think, so I write Counting syllables, yawning. Tomorrow starts soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
        urlLink From Hiro Protagonist :  The idea blossoms. Oh, I get it--a couple. The beach seems too far.  (After reading Kim's Blog and the Hawai'ian Baby posting.)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       The short cut returns Many months without the link. Posting made easy.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Given Cold waffles Sent comment to their website. Free food for a while.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Clock Hands move forward Sunshine brays "The day's started!" Mowers purr "Yard Work..."
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Imagine my awe. Kim-A new member to the team. Interesting post.  (A cross posting between Hiro's and my bloggers.)
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Getting future planned Dealing with good investments. Retire made easy.
     
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My arm's in a cast. Silly mattress incident. Tug and Pull--wrist's sprained.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Going to the beach Sunshine, waves, shells, and hot bods. Boat Drinks on cool decks.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Bookcrossing  is fun. Read any book and release. Track it on thier site.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Walking through the mall I spy some young eye candy. Oh, the passion's come.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      At the game tonight 3 runners on the bases. SMACK! It's outta here!
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Watering the grass Rainbows appear from nowhere. Color halo smiles
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Drinking favorite: Bloody Mary's-extra ice. Cold temp, spicy taste.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Run, curl-ups, push-ups Physical Readiness Test Pain--weakness leaving.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ocean waves crashing Whitecaps spray, frothy water. Naked bodies gleam.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Late, sand on the beach C-17s fly over. Waves wash over me.
     
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Creating Haiku Not a syllabel Wasted Not even rhyming.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Another day gone. Today's achievements succeed. Tomorrow's come soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love yellow stuff. Yellow seems to brighten life. Yellow flowers bloom.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Terrific Dinner. Some shopping for brownies done. Visit the beach soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My friend's special friend, Taking it all when he wants. Morning, noon, or night.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yellow of God's Sun, Blue of the mighty ocean. These our colors be.  (Adapted from Anchors Aweigh)
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Morning egg sandwich Coffee hot--cream and splenda. Vitamins follow.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Rat-ta-tat-tat Sounds Grass stays greener with water. Mowers cut green grass.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Candles lit, melting. Cream cheese icing made for me. being Thirty-six.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Happy Birthday to me! I am hoping for a card. This day will be great.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Mom is long gone--Bye. Seven years flashed quickly by. My birthday is nigh.  **Rhyming is not a traditional haiku element, but I am experimenting.***
     
    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Summer winds whisper, Green grass wet with morning dew. Worms dry on side walks.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Quantum-Jasmine play Tumble across the floor play. Friends intertwined play.
     
    
</post>

<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Graphics-pronounced Wail. Concepts un-American.  Humiliation. 
     
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Iraqi news looks grim. Soldiers do what they shouldn't. The pictures sadden me.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Karna gets to Cert He passed R-P Three Friday. Soon he starts teaching.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Operation Pee Standing there with a bottle. Pee, just fucking pee.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yellow Pineapple Sweetest thing in the morning. All I need are leis.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Virginia Tax Day Oh, part year tax filing sucks. Math formulas blues.
     
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sitting, thinking--sigh How do I write another? Summer heat weary.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Numbers are missing. Friends move--change their phone numbers. Why not notify?
     
    
</post>


<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A while back I bid $2 on a James Barber cook book (Quick & Simple - TV Companion Recipes) on ebay and won. It arrived today! Since Kim has taken to chicken thighs I thought I'd post a recipe utilizing them here: 
 
 Chicken, Celery & Cider  
 
   4 chicken thighs
   2 sticks celery, sliced diagonally
   1 clove garlic, crushed
   1 onion, chopped coarsely
   1 bay leaf
   1 apple, peeled, cored and sliced
   1 bottle cider
   1 tsp sage
   1/3 cup cream
   Salt & pepper
 
Heat a dry frypan over high heat and place the chicken thighs in, skin down. When browned on each side, add the onions, bay leaf and celery. Stir for a few minutes until coloured and add the apple, salt and pepper. Stir until well coated and pour in the cider. Keep the pan pver a high heat and let the cider bubble. Sprinkle in the sage and cook 5 more minutes. Just before serving, stir in the cream.
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some minor difficulties with the template. I think I have that all straightened out. It seems there is a problem with either the use of paragraph tags (&lt;P&gt;) or setting Blogger to convert line breaks. A workaround seems to be the use of two breakline tags (&lt;BR&gt; &lt;BR&gt;). *shrug* It seems to work now, nonetheless. BTW, I've been using the &lt;PRE&gt; tag (be sure to close this tag!) to do the ingredient sections of my posts, but one could also do it with &nbsp; (non-breaking space).  

I re-added the Alton Brown links and, also, added links to recipes and info on James Barber, the Urban Peasant.   

I remember watching his show back in the early 90s at my grandmother's house. One time I decided to do some sardine-potato-cake thinggy. My parents were out while I did the cooking. When they returned they were ticked that the whole house smelled like sardines. Ah, but that was a crucial step in my love of cooking.   

At that time I think he was on TLC or something. Now it seems he is on FoodTV Canada. So, too, is Martin Yan (of  Yan Can Cook ).  
 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       1/4 cup unsulphured molasses
1/4 cup prepared mustard
  3 tablespoons of vinegar
  2 tablespoons Worcestershire sauce
1/4 cup catchup
  3 cans (4 oz ea.) Vienna sausage, drained  

Blend together unsulphured molasses and mustard in small skillet. Stir in vinegar, Worcestershire sauce and catchup. Place over heat, bring to a boil. Add vienna sausages; simmer 10 to 15 minutes, turning occasionally. Serve with woden picks.  
YIELD: 8 servings 
 I found this recipe while at the local used bookstore. It came from the  KITCHEN TESTED RECIPES  section of an instruction booklet - well, more like brochure or flyer- for a Rossini hibachi from 1969. The instruction thinggy wasn't for sell, I think it had fallen out of some other cookbook, but I picked it up and kept it. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
1/2 lb ground beef
1 pkg (14 oz) frozen pepper strips
1 cup shredded Monterey Jack cheese, divided    
1 can (10 oz) mild enchilada sauce, like 
       Old El Paso, divided
8 flour tortillas (8")

     Makes 4 servings
 


Heat oven to 400F. In nonstick skillet over high heat, cook ground beef 5 min., or until browned, stirring often. Remove skillet from heat.  Add frozen pepper strips, 1/2 cup shredded Monterey jack cheese and 1/4 cup enchilada sauce to skillet; stir to combine. Pour 1/2 cup enchilada sauce in pie plate. Dip each tortilla in sauce, covering both sides. Place 1/2 cup meat-pepper mixture down center of each tortilla. Roll up tortillas and place in a greased 13" x 9" casserole or baking dish. Top beef enchiladas with remaining sauce nad shredded Monterey Jack cheese; bake 10 min., or until enchiladas are heated through.

 
      work time : 5 min
      total time : 20 min
 
   
 Easy Cheesy Enchiladas 216 Ways 
Whip up your own Mexican favorite by replacing the ground beef with an item from Column A, the pepper strips with a selection from column B, and the Monterey Jack cheese with a cheese from column C.
 
   COLUMN A             COLUMN B             COLUMN C             
 1  sausage          green bean blend     Cheddar 
 2  grilled pork     broccoli-            mozzarella
                   cauliflower mix             
 3  grilled turkey   pea blend            American  
 4  cooked           sugar snap peas      Gruyere  
  chicken
 5  cooked shrimp    Kidney beans         Jarlsberg
 6  Cooked shrimp    Italian green        feta
                   beans  
 
Of course some sort of Tofu or soy-protien thinggy could be used as well. 

     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ingredients & Directions
  
1/2 lb boneless pork
  3 tablespoons soysauce
  8 dried lily buds
  4 Dried Chinese mushrooms,
  4 dried tree ears
  6 cups (homemade) chicken broth
  3 tablespopons rice wine vinegar or white vinegar
1/2 teaspoon pepper
  8 ounces of fresh tofu
  1 tablespoon cold water
  1 tablespoon cornstarch
  1 beaten egg
  2 tablespoons thinly sliced green onion.
 
 
partially freeze pork; cut into 1 x 1/4" strips. Sprinkle meat with 1 tblspn of soy sayce. Meanwhile, in three bowls soak lily buds, mushrooms, and tree ears. Cut off & discard stem end of lily buds. Slice each lily bud into 1-inch lengths. Thoroughly rinse tree ears under running water; drain well. Cut off  & discard mushroom & tree ear stems. Cut mushrooms & tree ears into thin strips. In large suace pan bring broth to boiling; stir in pork, remaining soy suace, lily buds, mushrooms, tree ears, rice wine/white vinegar, and pepper. Simmer, covered, 10 minutes. Slice tofu into 1/4-inch wide strips. Add to soup. Simmer, covered, 3 minutes more. Blend cold water into corn starch. Stir into soup. Pour egg slowlyy into hot soup  in a thin stream, beating constantly with fork until egg cooks and shreds  finely. Cook soup until slightly  thickened & bubbly. Remove from heat. Stir in thinly sliced green onion. 
serves 4. 
Usually doubled.

  

     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quick recipe with mostly prepackaged or instant ingredients. 

      1 can  (20 or 24 oz) Beefstew
   1/2 cup  shredded Cheddar cheese
 
  Potatoe Topping   
 1 1/3 cup  water               1/3 cup  milk
   1/2 tsp  salt              1 1/2 cup  instant potato flakes
     2 Tbsp margarine 

  
Warm beef stew in a 1 1/2 - 2 quart casserole in a  350 degree oven for 10 minutes. Prepare potato mixture (see directions on potato flake package). Spoon potato mixture over hot stew. Top with cheese. Cook uncovered for 10 minutes or until cheese has melted.   

prep time: 10 minutes 
cook time: 20 minutes                                    
4 servings 


     

    
</post>

<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           1   2-ounce bird's nest
    1   quart chicken broth
   1/8  teaspoon sherry
    1   boned chicken breast, finely chopped
    2   teaspoon cornstarch
   1/4  cup of water 
    1   eqq white
   sesame oil (optional)
   peanut oil 

Soak the nest in water overnight. Next day, sprinkle several drops of peanut oil on the nest. Rinse nest with warm, clear water. Feathers should float to surface, making removal easier. Repeat oil-and-wash treatment until bird's nest is clean.  

Place bird's nest and 2 cups chicken broth in large bowl. Add sherry and chicken breat. Steam for 1 hour. Transfer mixture to 3-quart saucepan. Add rest of chicken soup and boil for two minutes. Mix cornstarch with water, then add to broth. Bring to boil, turn off heat. Beat in egg white. Sprinkle with sesame oil. Serve hot.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>