<Blog>

<date>29,September,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I saw a show on discovery about the Komodo dragon, and they mentioned that it has a "mouth full of putrefaction" while showing an ox dying from an infected bite wound. Sounds like me when I wake up. I had to switch to all-cotton pillows because I kept melting the polyester ones.  "No E-mail, only hot dog." -sony commercial. "Psst! It's me - Death. I'll see you soon, OK? I know you can't hear me, but try to feel what I'm about to say, deep down in your soul - Don't eat the gazpachooo."                                       -Manny Calavera, "Grim Fandango"                
    
    
</post>

<date>29,September,2000</date>
<post>

    
       So, Here is the first entry into my  Blogger  powered pseudo-journal. wait - meta-journal. no... um... "Journalesque Stream Of Thought." (Journalesque Stream Of Thought &copy; 1972 eclipse studios) So, if this works, I shall have a place on my website which I can use to post random thoughts that wouldn't quite fit into anything else. I already have a section for this (core), but that is more for structured rants and such. At this point in time I would like to say "Eugene" 4 times: Eugene Eugene Eugene Eugene. I would also like to state that Escargot is a really bad name for snails. They should be labeled "Snails" in bold print. just to let you know, so you don't order them while trying to show off for a date or something ("Ah kin reed fraynch, gimme one of them thar escargots"). The menu should say in large text just above the name of the dish: "NOTICE: There are snails in this dish. If you order it, you will be expected to eat multiple snails" 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM FREE OPERATING SYSTEM LINK  
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I am Tiger Woods. And I'm not even too sure who Tiger Woods is. I am Tiger Woods&copy; wearing Michael Jordan&copy; cologne and Nike&copy; sneakers in my Buick&copy; listening to the Britney Spears&copy; cd I got from McDonalds&copy;. Did domebody say McDonalds&copy;? uh, Yeah, I just did. Anyway, I got the cd for only 2.99 when I got a Big Mac&copy; after I saw the commercial on NBC&copy; that came on during the Olympics&copy;, which took place in Australia&copy;.  Oh yeah, Mir isn't gonna be scrapped after all. Turns out, somebody raised enough money to buy all that space-lysol, and they won't send Mir spiraling into the earth in february. The space-fungus was unavailable for comment. Somebody needs to make a movie about the heroic space-lysol. SPAAAAAAAAAAAACE LYYYYYYYYSOOOOOLLLLLLLLL  IN THE 21ST CENTURY!!!!!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM DIGITAL ART LINK   urlLink RANDOM FREE PORN LINK   My life is missing something. I don't feel like a whole man. Trust me - I checked an awful lot to make sure I felt like less of a man than I should. What I'm trying to say is, I've never seen "First Blood" all the way thru. In fact, I think the only Stallone movie I have seen all the way thru was Demolition man. I think I am less of a man because of this, and I need to get tough and go rent all 17 rocky movies and watch them straight thru. Or I could go look at flowers. No. Flowers are the wrong thing. I could...... Step on some flowers. No. Uhhhh...... well. I could always be an alchoholic womanizer with a beer gut and 5 o'clock shadow all the time... I'd be a real man then. Of course, I could just have some deep seated psychological problem with Stallone. Yeah, maybe I saw Sly naked when I was a kid or something and it scarred me for life, and now I can't see him in a movie without getting the urge to change the channel. But then again, I might just not like any of his movies. Sylvester Stallone, if you read this, Lemme know if you used to expose yourself to little boys, then my questions will all be answered. well, that one will be. the one about having grilled cheese sandwiches with the lead singer of INXS on a spaceship will have to wait. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       The Mir Spacestation is getting a lot of press of late. Apparently, there is some nasty space-fungus eating the plastic on the old rustbucket. If MirCorp (the company that is in control of Mir) doesn't get 7-10 million dollars (presumably to buy lots and lots of lysol.) within a few weeks, they will have to scrap Mir next February. another problem: NBC is going to have to think up something quick, because they had a new survivor-esque series in the works, wherein the winner gets to go to Mir. Fat chance of getting on Mir if it's destined to crash into the Earth. now, on top of all that - James "I directed Titanic, and you?" Cameron is actually going to be going to Mir to spend some time. I assume he is trying to get ideas for a new movie, since he went on a sub and saw THE Titanic, and then shortly thereafter made that movie "Bismarck", or something to that effect.  urlLink RANDOM "I WANNA BE LIKE MARTHA STEWART" LINK  (Random "I wanna be like Martha Stewart &copy;1987 eclipse studios)  urlLink RANDOM COOL MUSIC LINK  (Random cool music link &copy;1849 eclipse studios)  urlLink RANDOM UNCOOL MUSIC LINK  (Random uncool music link &copy;1850 eclipse stu-stu-studios) On another note: "Space-Fungus" would be a really cool name for a band. Ditto for "I wanna be like Martha Stewart". maybe a ska band could use that second one.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       "Heck, I've had more advanced lifeforms evolve in my fridge and I live alone. I'll clean it when they demand equal rights."  -found on  Slashdot  
    
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM EXTREME FETISH LINK  (random extreme fetish link &copy;1982 eclipse studios) 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM WEIRD LINK   urlLink RANDOM BODY MODIFICATION LINK  and now, I present a play: "Sex on downers" Our main players will be Ignatz and Natasha. Ignatz had a hard time in school because of his name, and got hooked on morphine. Ignatz also has narcolepsy. Natasha has been hooked on Horse tranquilizers since she hooked up with "Boris", a guy with a squirrel fetish. Natasha has Tourette syndrome. The scene opens - Ignatz's bedroom. The walls are covered in Flock of Seagulls concert posters. (ignatz) uh, yeah. I'm gonna give you my big hard manmeat as soon as I can get it up. (natasha) Hmmmm? (ignatz, ok, hold on, I can probbly get it up if i think of radar from M.A.S.H. (natasha) radar? what kind of fetish isJESUS LIVES IN MY(twitches) PUSSY! (ignatz) yeah. whoohoo. I'm gettin hot now, bab----ckzzzzkzkzzzzzzzz...... (natasha) uhh.... get up boris-uh... Iggie. (ignatz) zzz-huh? (natasha) nothing. I EAT PUPPIES BITCH LOVING FUCK!!!! (ignatz) uh, ok, I think i'm getting it up now, lemme check. (natasha) (twitches) (boris enters) (boris) NATASHA! I'm sorry, I love you darlink. (natasha) Hmmm? (boris carries natasha out) (ignatz) ok, I'm pretty sure I got it this time, lemme just get your pants off and...... hey.... where did you go? (natasha)(from the other room) I PISSED IN THE SOUP!!!! (curtain) 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I've noticed a few things during my time online: 1: You should not name your band after anything that might turn up sex sites on a search engine. Case in point - Orgy. 2: Some things just don't need web pages.  urlLink Case in point.  3: Nobody cares how many awards your website won from your friend wheo runs an awards website, but everybody still proudly displays their awards. 4: Some people just don't care about older browsers. I have decided to be "Browser Hostile" in that I am ignoring 2.0 browsers, but at least remember that not everyone uses IE 5.5 or the latest NS6 beta.  5: searching for just about anything will turn up a few porn pages. searching for "sex", however, doesn't return as many as you'd think.   Has anybody else noticed that Britney Spears is an obsessive-compulsive? look at her song titles: "Hit me baby, one more time - Oops, I did it again - (I can't get no) satisfaction"..... She has a real repetition thing going on. Maybe she's just a slut. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM WEIRD SCIENCE LINK   urlLink RANDOM ALTERNATIVE MEDICINE LINK  "Sponges grow in the ocean - that kills me. I wonder how much deeper the ocean would be if that didn't happen?"  -Steven Wright.  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       It's better to have loved and lost, than to be gang raped in a Turkish prison 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I that monkeys are a fine comedic device, and as far as mammals go, they're A-OK. Just stop using them to reenact movies.  RANDOM QUOTE CORRELATION: "There is no spoon." -the Matrix. "SPOON!" - the Tick (random quote correlation &copy;1991 eclipse studios)  I think that as you get old, things offend you more. I listen to that 60's and 70's music (led zepplin, rolling stones...) and they have some nasty ass lyrics. I mean -"sqeeze my lemon til the juice runs down my leg"???? and "everybody must get stoned", and "I get high with a little help from my friends." and - perhaps worst of all -"keep on dancin' to the rock and roll - on saturday night, saturday night." Now, the same people who groove to this music and have blurred memories of a party in 1975 where they dropped their first microdot, these same people will publicly protest against marilyn manson because he talks about drugs. the only difference is the terminology. If I say "when I get that feelin' I want sexual healin" nobody will be offended, but if I say "I want to fuck you like an animal" - people get all irritated and start to complain. I don't know, maybe in 20 years I'll get offended when some young punk plays the latest single from hanson starship and the lyrics go something like "gimme my dick back, bitch" probably not, since I would pay good money to see hanson sing that now...  Damn, no links today..... lemme go get one................. urlLink RANDOM "JUST BECAUSE" LINK  (random "just because" link &copy;1988 eclipse studios) 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Random Goodie Mobb Quote "Who's that peekin' in my window? pow! Nobody now." It's good to be random. Chaos is the root of all evyl. note, that I spelled "evil" wrong, I did that because I wanted you to pronounce it like "EEEEEEEVYLLLLL", like Hedley Lamar on Blazing Saddles. Also note that evyl is cool. If evyl is cool, then Chaos also is cool.  I would like to note that the last entry contained a really cool potential band name, and I only now noticed it: "Mouth Full Of Putrefaction"  RANDOM ALTERNATIVE FARM ANIMAL LINK  (RANDOM ALTERNATIVE FARM ANIMAL LINK &copy;2011 eclipse studios)  Luke Skywalker was a moisture farmer. Moisture. I can farm moisture off of my lawn in the morning, and I don't try to make a living out of it. I don't buy droids from Jawas, either, but that's just because a Jawa screwed me out of an R2 unit a few years back. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       And now for some random garbage off the top of my head:  I say random an awful lot. Not as much as this one guy I know, Randy R. Randomner. He was off in Pakistan a few years back and got arrested for spray painting "elect a duck fart" on the wall of the US embassy, and then the Swiss army came in and tried to extract him which is odd since A: He isn't Swiss, B: he doesn't even know anybody in Switzerland, and C: Switzerland doesn't actually have an army. So he was all in this jail trying to figure out how this army that didn't exist and had no reason to be there anyway was trying to get him out of a jail in pakistan, when he realized his cellmate was the one and only Mr. T. Mr. T was there because "foo" apparently means something to the effect of "overthrow the government" in whatever the hell language they speak over there. So Mr. T was going on and on with his "I pity this foo" and "I pity that foo", and Randy suddenly vanished into this air, only to rematerialize on the campus of M.I.T., with no clothes on, and a bowling pin stuck halfway up his ass. Well, needless to say, he was instantly known as the coolest guy on campus, and even though he never got around to putting any clothes on or taking out the bowling pin, he still managed to to become an olympic foosball player using the math skills he learned in college. and he would have made it to the Olympics, except that he kept saying how it was the most random thing he had ever seen how he had come to be on the olympic foosball squad, after being in a prison in pakistan with Mr. T only a few years prior, and his coach eventually got tired of it, and kicked him off the team. He did end up going to the olympics, though, as the flagbearer for the Swiss team. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Damn. I missed Firday the 13th. in october, no less. Oh well. I did find a really odd link or 3.  urlLink Somebody hanged an elephant in 1916 for killing a man.   urlLink The Flat Earth Society  After reading the FAQ's, I can only hope this is a joke. I know there are some flat earthers left, but I would hope they'd be smart enough (both of them) to provide actual data instead of saying the earth rides on a turtle's shell, or there are green-skinned women hanging off the edge of the earth.  urlLink  A fairly cool webpage created by someone with an odd sense of humor.   urlLink The ten coolest video game shirts   urlLink I love bacon  A collection of random funny and bizarre stuff.  urlLink The VisionStation  Monitors are soooo 20th century.  urlLink Bored.com  4 pantloads of links to just about everywhere.    
    
    
</post>

<date>10,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I was thinking of ways to improve my website. Maybe I'll put up a emotion meter or something. or I could just say it here. I'm feeling: Greasy. damned popcorn.  urlLink RANDOM FUTURE TECH LINK  I'm feeling: pain in my ass. damned chair. I'm feeling: Damp. damned 37 Dr.Peppers. So, If I rob a gas station and kill the guy who works there, would it be morally wrong to apply for his job the next day? I'd like your thoughts on this, so send them to   Lord_Ian@hotmail.choad  
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I haven't been posting much lately, so I figured I'd just dump some random links, note that I will break from the RANDOM x LINK format, just because this is easier.  urlLink Geek Porn.  Check out the girl with Fermat's last theorem on her nekkid skin.  urlLink Planet Twinkie 2000  the twinkies website, complete with scottish twinkie fritters, which are batter dipped and deep fried. yum.  urlLink Richard Cheese  This guy has an album out with covers of a bunch of popular rock tunes, all in the style of "lounge". weird stuff, make sure you get the sampler mp3. if you can't play mp3 files, you shouldn't really be online, and you can just ship your computer to me.  urlLink Levitation  Levitating a frog and water using magnets? yup.  urlLink The potato gun technology center  pretty much says it all.  urlLink The Waco aircraft company  They make full sized Biplanes! Only 180 grand!  urlLink Mass Multiples  Ever wanted 3 or 4 flat panel monitors on one stand? here you go.  urlLink The Bit Calculator  A Spiffy little tool for converting bits to bytes and other stuff. good to see how many K a second you can get thru your 56k connection.  urlLink Poetic Technologies  Makers of the coolest desk in all the world: The Aura. I'd sell my children to have one of these - if I had children.  urlLink Violet Crumble  Australian candy that is really hard to find here in the states. I fell in love with these a few years ago, and then everybody quit selling them. damnit. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM SELF LOVE LINK   
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM PENILE ENHANCEMENT LINK  
    
    
</post>

<date>27,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Mir: The saga continues.  I've decided to post any news on Mir crashing into the earth/not crashing into the earth, just becase I've kept up to date on it till now, but to tell you the truth - I'm bored with it. I mean, first they have this cool space fungus, and Mir is doomed unless they get 40 million bucks to save it, then they save it, then they just decide that they need more money to keep it in space or they will have to crash it anyway, then they say they won't be crashing it, then they will, now they aren't going to crash it. I figure in a week or so, I'll see a news story about how MirCorp needs 77 million dollars or else they are gonna have to crash the damned thing in February.  let's get random for a while... I am Nonlinear. I own 14 Subaru dealerships and Canada. Some people call me "Steve", even though it isn't my name. Grapes. My head is on fire. I found my thrill on blueberry hill. When I step into the place, you know I step correct - whoo haa, I got you all in check. 42. Explosion - bang. I look like Japan. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I feel weird when I miss a day posting to my blog, like I'm letting down my millions of fans. The only problem is - I don't have millions of fans. I probably don't have A fan. well yeah, I've got a fan, but it's on high sitting on a table in the room with me, but you know what I meant. I also want to post another one of those random links, but I don't have any. I cleared out my favorites in the last few posts, so I'll go find a link for you millions of loyal fans, and then maybe I'll deflate my head.  urlLink RANDOM COOL JEWELRY LINK  there, happy? Btw, if anybody would care to buy me one of those Clapton-Richards skull rings, I'll make a donation to the charity of your choice in the amount 20 Pesos, which I think translates out to around 1/3 of a cent. Also, if you happen to have some old appliances or computer hardware that you don't feel like throwing away, send it to me and I'll send you some pictures of it meeting it's demise at my hands. I really like to break things, but you can't break stuff that has value or people will get upset. So mostof the time I can't break stuff, so I spend that time on  the computer. It's a wonderful life. &lt;RANT&gt; On another note, yesterday I mentioned Unreal and Quake, but there is a problem - I can't run Quake III because of my crappy video, and I have to run Unreal Tournament in software mode at 320X240 to avoid dropping frames, but I still play UT, and I still play QIII whenever I get on somebody else's machine. I've always played first person shooters, I was playing Castle Wolfenstein on my Uncle's shiny new computer when it first came out, and I never stopped. but nowadays, all the games are becoming multi player only, and I am stuck here behind this pitiful 56k, so my only choice is either a LAN game or slaughtering bots ina  single player game. Of course, very few of my friends with computers want to play LAN games of UT or QIII, and those that do want to play actually have lives, so they can't be training 24/7 like I do, so I end up dominating and boring everybody because they can't get a frag in. Boy do I hate being Godlike. To top all of this off, I live 14 miles south of the middle of nowhere, so there aren't any local groups that do the community LAN party thing. I think I understand now - I just hate my life. I'm not happy with my computer, I'm not happy with my location, I'm not happy with my connection to the internet, I'm not happy with the fact that I am the only person I know that would rather play UT than sleep. And don't even get me started on all these damned feathers growing out of my head... &lt;/RANT&gt; 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Your computer actually does hate you.   urlLink The first good use of lasers  And the first real advance in lawncare technology since the weedeater.  urlLink BEATERz  Hey..... That's my car!  urlLink I think I may have found myself a monitor.  BTW, check out the rest of the stuff on that site - like the whole wall projection monitor, so when Klesk or Dessloch shoves a rocket up your ass - you will fear the rocket. (OBSCURE FIRST PERSON SHOOTER REFERENCES &COPY;1992 ECLIPSE STUDIOS) Oooooooohhhhh.... I just had an epiphany. Or maybe I hit my head. Either way, I just thought up a very cool game: Unreal vs. Quake. Think about it - Xaero fires off a volley from the BFG while dodging a 5 rocket spread from Xan Kriegor on the highest building in the Morpheus map, only to catch a sniper's bullet in the head - which was fired by Drimacus. It'd be interesting to restrict the Quake chars. to Quake weapons, and vice versa. Would a Quaker survive against a skilled UT player with an eightball or a flak cannon? Can a UT player with a ripper defend the flag against a plasma rifle toting Quaker? And who would win in a headshot contest between a Quaker with a railgun and a UT'er with a sniper rifle? and what about the almighty Redeemer? what does a Quaker have to stop a guided mini-nuke that can chase them around a corner? Of course, this has been argued since Unreal came out to compete with Quake 2, but I don't think anyone has actually attempted a mod to decide. Then there are the copyright issues. Making a BFG and a Daemia or a Uriel to carry it in UT would probably upset the brass at Id. Oh well. I'm done spewing my head wound inspired idea.    
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Mir - The Saga Continues  Turns out, MirCorp couldn't raise enough money to save the old beast, so Mir will be crashing into the earth next February. AWWWWWWW..... Everybody feel sorry for the poor widdle space station. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink RANDOM ARTIFICIAL LANGUAGE TRANSLATION OF A HOLY BOOK  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Have you ever noticed how those "gangsta" rappers will have 125,000 dollar platinum and diamond teeth, a 200,000 dollar necklace, a few bracelets worth 40 grand per, a half million dollar car (usually several), a gigantic house worth more than every house you've ever lived in combined, and wear a 3 dollar t-shirt? Why wear a Rolex, Fubu pants, and a hanes t you got in a plastic package with two other ones just like it? All I know is that if I ever spend 125 grand on my teeth, those suckers are gonna drive my car or something.  urlLink Heavy  Spend the rest of your life here. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
         Quick poem: Old woman. Her hat contains many mysteries. And her head. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Election? Hell, that's this year? I totally forgot. I really like syrup. I would drink nothing but syrup if it didn't give me that "I just drank a bunch of syrup" feeling in my throat.I like my bacon burnt, my eggs with a pound of pepper on them, my biscuits swimming in gravy, I like my coffee in as large a container as possible, and I like maple syrup poured over the whole mess. now that's a damned breakfast. by the way, here is an idea I'd like to see passed into law: after an election, the loser has to go clean up all the signs. I think we still have Dukakis signs littering up  the woods around here. oh yeah, an update on EARTHBOUND: THE MIR STORY - wait, maybe I could call it NOT WITHOUT MY PRESSURE SUIT: THE TRAGEDY AT MIR - yeah, that's a good one. Anyway, Mir is indeed gonna be crashed into the earth sometime in February. Whoo-freakin-hoo. Maybe it'll hit a black hole on the way down, a black hole that is growing between the earth and the moon, and which is destined to eat our planet. that'd be cool. for a while, anyway. hey, try saying "svelte" a lot of times real fast. svelte svelte svelte svelte. I like that. I'm sort of a weird guy though, so you may not get the same thrill from saying "svelte" over and over again that I do. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Jeez. It's been nearly a month since I last posted to this thing. I'd love to tell you that I had a family member die, or I decided to go to truck driving school, or I found the love of my life - only to find out she was inflatable, but I can't. I didn't post because I am a lazy son of a bitch - simple as that. I've been playing a lot of the sims (I did kill off a few family members in the sims, but only to make tombstones). I almost bought Jupiter, but the guy got arrested for stealing a goat before I could sign the papers. Of course, you would think that I would have lots to say after being gone for almost a month - and you'd be thinking wrong. The problem is that I post when the thought strikes me, and I post what's on my mind right then, so it doesn't really build up. I do, however, collect odd links. Here are some for your browsing pleasure:  urlLink Screw Radio Shack!  Use tortillas to make your circuits.  urlLink NerdPerfect  Like Slashdot, only different.  urlLink You can't just fuck the fish  - You gots to make looooooove to the fish. (Ok, I know dolphins aren't fish, but I don't care - it's sounds better this way.) By the way, that last link mentions that male dolphins have a 10-14" long prehensile penis, meaning they can pick stuff up with it. And when they orgasm, They can shoot love gravy 14 feet. Lucky bastards. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Maybe I should just change my name to Nick. I have a problem with nicknames. On this web log thing, I call myself Twilight Jones (which I've used off and on for maybe 8 years), but I'm also known as (in no particular order): Firebug, vYrus, BUTANE, 11-Wires, eclipse, and PAIN (in games). I have also used variants of most of those, like _vyrus_ or (eclipse), and I was once known as angrycowdisease, and once when I first installed aol instant messenger, I had to use Phyrebugge, because there are 200 billion people on aol, and aol doesn;t just give you a number like icq does (note that I no longer use AIM, and I'd rather hang myself by my penis than actually USE aol.)  Damn. I harshed on AOL pretty hard there... so like, everybody go to aol and sign up. or don't. or hang yourselves by your various gentialia. I don't care. OK, New subject: WHY I THINK MEN HAVE IT BETTER THAN WOMEN. (notice that I did NOT say we ARE better, although I think we are. This is why we have it better)  Men can write their names in the snow. Men with lots of self control can print their names in the snow. Men only bleed when they are injured. Men only cramp after running or something. Men can't get pregnant. When a man's dog dies, he gets sad, usually telling somebody "I loved that fucking dog, man!" Men do not take it further than that, and usually see it as a chance to get a new dog. Men enjoy violence, which happens to be just about the only thing on tv. Men can be really scary and intimidating if need be. Men don't have to get help to pick up heavy things. Men can get stuff off of any shelf in the house by themselvs. Men can open their own damned jars. And a bunch of other stuff that I don't care enough about to write down. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       So, Gore just conceded, and it looks like the dubya will be the next president of the United States of America. Good thing I was planning on moving to that sewer in Berlin. In a way (a sick twisted way), I kinda like that fact that dubya is gonna run the country until he screws up, just because HE WILL SCREW UP, and when he does, he will probably already be spending most of his time in courtrooms saying "I did cocaine once (sniffle) but I did not inhale, (rubs nose while sniffling) and I was only high for a couple minutes. (dubya's lawyer leans over and whispers something to him) Oh, uh, nevermind." Hell, we ALL loved Clintion, and we wanted to cut off his love wand just because he got a blowjob. dubya was a drunk for years, a cokehead for who knows how long, and can barely read as it is. What's gonna happen the first time dubya goes to some country and has to pronouce a name like M'beghu Go'Latta M'butu or Hermanz Fleichenschwitzsenhauer?  Daddy can't pull you out of this one dubya, and your dealer won't have anything ot do with you unless he wants to write a book. Looks like it's time to go talk to your old friend Martin I Vodka. 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       ....and here I thought I was gonna have a problem putting 74 chickens and a linebacker in a toaster oven.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       (cowboy twilight) HI BOYS AND GRRLS! (boys and girls in unison, except for llama boy, but nobody minds him) HI COWBOY TWILIGHT!!!! (cowboy twilight) DO YOU KNOW WHAT TIME IT IS!?!?!?!?!?! (children in unison, except for llama boy) IT'S RANDOM LINK TIME!!!!!!!! (announcer, speaking very quickly) randomlinktimeiscopyrighted1952byeclipsestudiossomerestrictionsapplyallrightsrexervedexceptforllamaboyoffernotvalidinpanamacubaortexasbecausetexassucks (cowboy twilight) THAT'S RIGHT! SO HERE WE GO!!!   urlLink Best Toilets  Somebody actually maintains this list of all the best public restrooms in various cities. And I thought I was weird.  urlLink Tetrachromats  There is at least one woman in the world who can see more colors than everybody else because she has 4 sets of cones in her eyes instead of the usual three.  urlLink International Space Station Visibility Data  Now you can get up real early, look at a twinkle in the sky for 2 minutes, and go "Gee".  urlLink THE CLAW  Not quite a joystick, but not a keyboard either. Probably the most innovative game controller since the joystick. Or maybe the Power Glove.  urlLink Being Seen Technologies  Makers of electroluminescent strips, which are like neon, but better. And cheaper. And really flexible. I gotta get me some of that.  urlLink Interlink Electronics  They make these badass mice from stainless steel that you can beat on with a hammer. (I can do that to my mouse, bit I'd have to buy another one afterwards).  urlLink Pricewatch  Ok, Ok, so I'm a nerd. But I like this place. It's the quickest way to get the lowest price on computer hardware on the web.  urlLink Happy Pipes  I don't actually have a use for this, but they do have some really cool handblown glass bongs and stuff. I just wanna spread the love is all.     
    
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I hate it when programs install shortcuts and the like without asking you. Real Player, for example, puts a shortcut on your desktop, in your start menu, and it installs several other programs that should be kept seperate (like realjukebox, netzip, download demon and comet cursor - all of which I despise). even worse, many programs suffer from terminal bloat. let's take a look at icq for a moment. Icq is like a 6 or 7 meg download. when I first started using icq, it had all the functionality it does now (more on that in a momet), and it weighed in at less than one meg. Now, where did all this extra meggage come from? from useless crap. I looked at icq's homepage builder, shuddered, and deleted the directory it kept all of it's graphics and templates in. I have never, and will never, use random chat, or phone/follow me, or the email "feature", or the browser, or voice messaging, or E-icq (whatever the hell that is). So where is the good old icq with messaging, file transfer, chat, and away mode? still there, but buried under a bunch of useless "features". To add insult to injury, when mirabilis decided that their program was too large, they removed the one thing I thought was actually useful: the mesage archive. oh yeah, they also removed the IP address from the info screen. now, "ftp to my IP as anonymous" takes longer because I can't just click on the info button and see the IP. So, as a result of Mirabilis being a bunch of stick-in-the-mud bloatware designers, I will issue this statement:   I Twilight Jones, being of mostly sound mind and vaugely egg-shaped body, Hereby demand that Mirabilis, the creators of the program ICQ, release a "stripped down" or "classic" version, with all the extra fluffy features amputated, and the core program intact. When Mirabilis releases this "classic" icq, I will stop bitching. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       What if Alice was offended by the "Eat me" sign? She would have never gotten out of wonderland. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Radio Coop: You've got questions, we've got chickens.   A 911 call to remember: -- (911 person) 911, what is your emergency? (lucky) I seem to have a bear eating my intestines. (911) excuse me sir? (lucky) I woke up this morning and there was a black bear eating my intestines. I guess he ripped me open during the night sometime. I figured he'd go away after a while, but it's been about 6 hours now... (911) ok, so you say a bear is eating your intestines, and has been doing so for 6 hours. (lucky) at least. he was eating them when I woke up. (911) ok. uhh.. can you give me your address so we can- (lucky) oops, now I'm on fire. (911) excuse me? (lucky) well, I was trying to light a torch to scare the bear off, you know, like in the movies? (911) yes sir, in the movies. (lucky) well, I made this torch, but when I tried to light it, I guess I spilled some kerosene on me, and well - now I'm on fire. it did scare the bear off, though, so I'm ok there. (911) ok, is your whole body on fire, or just a part of you? (lucky) well, most of me, really. not my head, though. well, my hair, but I figured you kinda assumed that. (911) uh, sir, can you just give me your address and we can rush somebody out- (lucky) hey, is it bad for an arm to just fall off? 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       I will now post a link. BEWARE! PELIGRO! YUCKY AND MOST LIKELY HIGHLY OFFENSIVE THINGS AHEAD! before I post this, I must inform you that, although I thought it was the funniest damned thing I've ever seen, most people (even highly jaded, usually non-offensible people) WILL BE OFFENDED and will grow to hate me because I posted this purile, sick, sex-and-religion-don't-mix link. so consider yourself warned. Actually, don't consider yourself warned, so you can get the full-on shock this site will offer you. Also, if you are a sick pervert of historic proportions (like you think Caligula was a prude and the Marquis De Sade was boring in bed), you might wanna buy something from here. I'm just providing a public service here, if you don't want to see bad things - BAD THINGS SHAPED LIKE RELIGIOUS FIGURES AND INTENDED TO AID FEMALE MASTURBATION - you shoudln't click here, and you should go to confession just for reading this far. Now, if you are like me, you will laugh your ass off and spend the next couple weeks freaking out all your friends with this. But you probably aren't like me (thank your lucky stars), and you will go EWWWWWWW!!!! and quickly call your mom to tell her how much you love her. Anyway, here goes. and don't send me hatemail or dead animals. well, you can't really send dead animals thru email, and a picture would just go into my folder full of pictures just like it.  REALLY OFFENSIVE LINK - DON'T EVER CLICK HERE FOR ANY REASON, EVEN IF YOUR MOM TELLS YOU TO  urlLink THIS LINK IS BAD, DON'T CLICK IT.  DON'T SAY I DIDN'T TRY TO WARN YOU. THIS IS BAD - WAY BAD. CHER-AND-KENNY G-DOING-THE THONG SONG-ON-A-CHRISTMAS-ALBUM-BAD Btw, be sure to check out my favorite one - the baby Jesus buttplug. And, to balance it out, here is some nice stuff.  urlLink SHINY HAPPY LINK. GOOD LINK.   urlLink GOOD LINK. STICKY IN A GOOD WAY.  I love that site. I've always wanted a glue information portal. and I never knew how to glue ceramic to leather before this. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Hey, is there anyone who CAN'T walk and chew gum at the same time? That would be really freaky.... take a few steps, stop, chew a little, stop, take a few steps...  urlLink For your inner 12 year old.  Ahh... I remember a time when fart and barf jokes were funny. A time when saying "Penis" in front of a teacher was both the worst and funniest thing you could ever possibly do. A time when I sang soprano and had no bodily hair. I remember it like it was yesterday, because it was. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       So, how would the economy be affected if it rained quarters and we used pepper instead of Susan B. Anthony Dollars? Actually, I think our cars would be affected if it rained quarters, and we'd never need change. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       WHAT AM I GONNA DO WITH ALL THESE OSTRICHES???? 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       On Roses and Posies (an essay on the state of flora in the world, and how they relate to the chaos created by man) -------------------     Damn. I hate flowers. Flowers suck, maybe I should plant garlic or something. Or a tree. Yeah, I could plant an oak tree, come back in 50 years, and chop it down - thus pissing off countless squirrels, and scattering acorns everywhere. I don't even like trees. Why am I still writing this? Just a bad idea to start with, if you ask me. I also dislike the way the tab key works in non-word processing programs. I expect it to tab over 5 spaces, and it sends my cursor to a different field.  I got your cursor right here, bud. I bet it would be bad to play catch with a keychain. I know whenever somebody throws keys at me and I catch them, I go "Ow" and rub my hand for a minute. Would you rather watch the last half of Rain Man or all of Deep Blue Sea? What if Rain Man was Superman and Deep Blue Sea was The Abyss? Heh. I just noticed that in one of those earlier posts (the reallly bad one), the bad link is purple, as in "has been recently visited", and the disney link is blue, as in "ain't been there". You should all go out and buy "renegades" by rage against the machine. every last one of you. they cover lots of classic rap and rock stuff, they even cover Devo. I gotta fill whitespace here, so I'm gonna start typing the lyrics to "I'm Bad" by ll cool j (back from way before he did Deep Blue Sea) No rapper can rap quite like I can, I'll take a musclebound man and put his face in the sand. Not the last mafioso - I'm a mc cop. Make you say "Go LL" and do the wop. If you think you can outrhyme me, yeah boy, I bet - cause I ain't met a motherfucker who can do that yet. Trendsetter, I'm better, my rhymes are good, I got a gold nameplate that says "I wish you would" and when battles begin then I gotta join in and before my rhyme is over - You know I'ma win. That works, I guess. Maybe nobody has read this far, and I can start being really weird. Nah. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,December,2000</date>
<post>

    
       Radio Snack: you've got questions, we've got twinkies.  Hey look - I found a quarter! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       yeah right, like I'm gonna fall for the old "I just shot a cop and you gotta help me hide the body" routine again.  I think Phenol would be a good name for a band. So a mushroom walks into a bar, and the bartender says "get outta here, we don't serve your kind in here". and the mushroom goes "aww, come on - I'm really a fun-gi once you get to know me." (nyuk nyuk nyuk) I don't mean to influence anybody here, but go buy Homeworld: Cataclysm right now. Go ahead, I'll wait. and while you're gone I'll steal your stuff and blame it on your little brother. seriously, I'm not a fan of space sims, I have owned 3 of them total in my life (freespace, freespace 2, and now cataclysm), but this game rules. When I first encountered the beast, I got all tense and sweaty. The beast is a biomechanical virus that infects your ships and makes them try to destroy you, and all larger ships carry weapons that can infect a whole squadron of your ships from weapons range. cool stuff, deep story, neato cutscenes (they are in black and white and look almost like cartoons), and lots of big nasty weapons, like the almighty siege cannon, which can vaporize capital shops from several K away. Anyway, go buy it. Right now. don't worry, it'll run on a 266 with a 4 meg video card. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I now present you with  urlLink a picture of a hamburger.  you know you have too much time on your hands  urlLink when...  Are you Amish? Yes? Then shame on you for being on a computer, but since you are commiting this atrocity anyway, you may as well buy a new churn  urlLink here.  I was reading the "about" part of that website, and it said "many of our customers live 'off the grid'", and went on to talk about non-electric appliances. soooo.... if you don't have power, how are you supposed to be getting to this website? is the computer hooked up to your windmill? Maybe carrier pigeon for the data transfers? Something to think about: Do you know why there aren't any klan rallies in China? (besides the obvious) Answer - because they would get run over by tanks. We Americans are weenies about that kinda stuff. If I was in charge, I would have a special branch of the army just for running klan members over with tanks. them and all those people that buy tickets to concerts so they can protest the artist. I got two words for you: STAY HOME!!! you know, I *really* hate country music. I consider country music to be the devil's music (The devil is the father of lies - would he send his message thru evil music? Nope. It would be on a garth brooks record.) but I don't own any country albums, and I don't go to country concerts. Why? Because I hate country music, of course.Obvious, isn't it? Not to everybody, it would seem. There are people who buy marilyn manson cd's just so they can analyze the lyrics, and they go to concerts just to bitch and moan and hold up signs to a bunch of people who paid good money to see an artist they enjoy. Don't preach to the choir. Go stand outside the record store, and put your money back in your wallet. Before you buy the damned music, grab your signs. maybe somebody will see it, and it will influence them. "I think I might get that cd by that Marilyn Manson guy and see if I like it...hey, that guy doesn't seem to like manson very much. Hmm, maybe I'll get something by Judas Priest or Christian Death instead." See? Problem solved. &lt;/SOAPBOX&gt;  
    
    
</post>

<date>01,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       hey, whoohoo. happy new year. I don't wanna sound like one of those mathie people, but it is actually the first day of the new millenium. 01-01-01. last night I went out in my driveway at about 10 til and stood there, in the freezing cold, in snow up to my ankles, watching people pop fireworks all over town. I *love* fireworks. I've been a firebug (pyromaniac, almost an arsonist) since I can rememeber. I burned the hair off my legs in a friend of mine's grandmother's garage when I was in 6th grade, I've had more fuse burns than I can count, I've been engulfed in waaaay too many fireballs, and I can sit for hours watching a fire dance on a pile of logs. So I just stood there, ignoring the cold, catching the occasional whiff of sulphur and black powder in the air, naming off the fireworks people were popping. ("Looks like one of those 2 dollar rockets, and that was a saturn missle battery. pretty nice floral shell...) It was kind of like time slowed down, and all was right with the world. Some guy across the street shot a pistol a few times, somebody down the block was shooting saturn missle batteries (those blocks with lots of tiny red rockets in them) at an angle, amd I was just standing there. In the cold. Like an idiot. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Music I enjoy: Heavy Metal, Old School Rap (mostly early "gangsta" rap), Neo-Metal type stuff (like korn, system of a down, orgy, stuff like that) Primus (because they don't really fit anywhere else), the occasional hardcore techno-esque song (Aphex Twin's "Come To Daddy" was genius). I have a dark past. I used to listen to pop rap. Yup. I who worship Nine Inch Nails and the Beastie Boys, once owned two tapes by marky mark and the funky bunch. I also had vanilla ice's first album, and I was way into the fat boys. I'm over that now (thank {your deity here}), but I have a new vice - Cover songs. I don't know what it is, but I really love it when a group takes a classic song and perverts it just the right way. Marilyn Manson's "Sweet Dreams" and "I put a spell on you", The Mighty Mighty Bosstones "Detroit Rock City" and "Enter Sandman" (and I don't even like the bosstones. at all),  anything like that, I love it. Music I DO NOT enjoy: teeny pop, country, whiny alternative garbage. pretty much anything written before 1980 (and most of what was written in the 80s), manufactured bands (like n*stync, backdoor boys, and the countless other new kids/menudo clones) britney spears (both personally and musically - I hope she gets attacked by killer bees and stumbles into traffic, where she would be run over by christina aguilera's tour bus, which would then careen off a cliff, exploding in a glorious fireball upon impact with the cold hard ground.) christina aguilera (she learned spanish so she could record a spanish language album because she wanted to be true to her roots. her roots are in new england) and I'm not too fond of the elevator music crap that people like enya keep oozing all over us. ok, feeling better now. I got some rare old anthrax off napster (gives finger to "The Man") so I'm great. Speaking of napster, it's nice to see the true artists coming out in favor of napster. most artists are pretty neutral on napster (the "who gives a shit?" attitude is cool), some are really pissed off about napster (not to name any names *COUGH*metallica*COUGH*), and are trying to get it banned. those artists are money hungry, and not interested in making music for the sake of making music. and then there are some artists (Like prince and rage against the machine and chuck d and offspring and limp bizkit) who actually like napster, and encourage it's use. rage against the machine's management actually banned some users, so RATM apologized by offering a bunch of cool music on their website (to make up for some of their fans being denied the music they wanted). uh, what was I talking about?.... To Hell with it, I'm finished. (gives another finger to "The Man" just for fun) 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Did you ever notice that the waitress always comes to the table during the worst part of any conversation? "...and here I am with my fist up this horse's ass, being chased by the cuban national baseball team, and on the fbi's most wanted list - and all because I bought mustard instead of ketchup! Oh, hey, I could use some more coffee, thanks." "...so now I have to smoke crack so my girlfriend won't break up with me, and I was thinking of doing heroin too, just to be safe. Yeah, I think we're ready to order now."  Of course, the conversations at the tables I sit at tend to get a little..... off color. And by off color, I mean that both of those statements might actually end up being made at a table I sit at. Here's a cool thing you can do: act like you were in the middle of the worst possible conversation when the waitress walks up. "Yeah, I was thinking of calling in sick today, but I figured I had to go so I could pay my electric- hold on, here she comes.... so I said 'thanks but no thanks, Mr. Castro, I'd rather not be raped by a dictator today' so he got all pissed, and he grabs for the rifle, but he misses and grabs the strap on and- oh, can I get a refill here? thanks." Actually, the waitresses at the places I frequent expect that from me and my circle of friends. if the waitress walked up and heard "...my electric bill, plus the landlord was bitching about the rent today", she'd get freaked out.  urlLink RANDOM LINK IN BAD TASTE  You can watch webcasts of actual funerals at that site. It's so you can watch your grandma's funeral while still being a pathetic shut-in who lives in the glow of a computer screen, just like me.   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Everything I know, I learned by killing smart people and eating their brains  hey, go listen to "mope" by the bloodhound gang. following is my favorite part of the song. (my favorite part of any song so far):  (song stops) Pac-Man: "yo yo yo yo yo! What it is motherfuckers?" band: "Aw shit, here comes Pac-Man." "Hey Pac-Man, what's up?" Pac-Man: "ME you bitches! I'm high on crack! Wanna freebase?" band: "No Pac-Man - Drugs are bad!" "Nope, can't help you man." Pac-Man: "PUSSIES!" (sounds of someone taking a hit) WHOA! HOLY SHIT! (music is the Pac-Man theme over a drumline) (song resumes)  I also feel the need to quote Pantera now. Actually, I think I need to go to church, stand up in front of the choir, and sing this over the p.a.  Pantera, "Good Friends and a Bottle of Pills" (mostly spoken, with a nasty "i fucked your girlfriend last night" kind of drawl to it)  I fucked your girlfriend last night. While you snored and drooled, I fucked your love. She called me daddy and I called her baby when I smacked her ass.  I called her sugar when I ate her alive till daylight.  And I slept with her all over me, from forehead to ribcage I dripped her ass. Sometimes I thought you might be spying, living out some brash fantasy, but no. You were knocked out.  But we were all knocked out you know. In a way I serve too many masters. We didn't know you'd break the bottle that the magic came in to use those jagged shards to slit our wrists and neck. And you'd do it too, you're that kind of dude. But you wouldn't know what you were doing because I didn't, your girlfriend could have been a burn victim, an amputee, a dead body - But god damn I wanted to fuck. I'm serving too many fucking masters. I told you. I told you motherfucker  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Quick question: would you rather be addicted to heroin or crack? I mean, if you aren't already addicted to one of them (since that would bias you), and if you for some reason absolutely had to be addicted to one of them, which one would it be? I think I'd go for crack. Why crack? Well, for one thing, you get the neato pipe instead of that boring old syringe and rubber tubing - and crack is easy to transport. You can even send  urlLink Virtual Crack  to yourself thru email. Well, you're supposed to send it to other people, but why do that when you can be your own pusher?  Hey, did you ever wake up in the middle of the night, screaming "OH MY GOD! IS ABE VIGODA STILL ALIVE???!?!?!?!"? well, if you do, you seriously need some medicinal assistance, and maybe a long vacation to the nutbar inn - HOWEVER, while you wait on those nice young men in their clean white coats, you can go  urlLink HERE  to check up on ol' Abe.  Hey, just what I've always wanted!  urlLink Coffins!  I think if I was going to spend 500 bucks on a coffee table, I'd get one of those coffins and put some flowers on it, then like go find a dead cat or something to put in it, and then I could scare everybody off when I wanted to open it. I think I'd have to throw some fresh earth around it to make it more convincing.  Ok, I like loud music as much as the next headbanging metal fiend, but at some point  urlLink it just becomes silly.  beyond the obvious hilarity of this thing, you have to think for a second "wait, there are several thousand dollars woth of speakers back there - and they all point towards each other when the doors are shut." I'm sure that sounds wonderful once you get all those big speakers in ther together with no place for the sound to go. It must sound just like wrapping your headphones in a towel and throwing them into a pool.... You should also check out  urlLink this travesty  and keep saying to yourself "they did this on purpose, and they aren't in a circus or a parade or anything..." Like a minivan needed any help being ugly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Primus, they don't sound like anybody. There are so few bands that you can say that about. how many bands sound like some other band? most of them. Not Primus, though. Primus sounds like.... Primus. That makes it tough to describe them to somebody who hasn't heard them. it's like trying to describe blue to somebody who has been blind from birth. Primus is quirky, funny, rock, alternative, almost bluegrass sometimes.... they like fishing and Tom Waits, lots of their songs tell a story, usually of one odd person. And Les Claypool can play the hell out of that bass. I've never heard anybody that can do some of the stuff that Les can do for 8 minutes while singing the (also challenging) lyrics to "tommy the cat" live.Were I forced to make a list of my 5 favorite bands, Primus would be right up there at or near the top. Ok, so, more links now.  urlLink SmellyPoop  Now if you really don;t like somebody, you can send fresh feces to them via this wonderful little site. I'd go for the camel poo, myself, that stuff has got to be nasty.  urlLink Not the best idea we as a people have had.  Seems that people down under are shoving their poop in each other's poop chutes in order to fix poop-related ailments. Myself, I'd rather just deal with irritable bowels. I could just get them to switch to decaf or something.  urlLink Rotten  Just plain wrong. be sure to browse the "fuck of the month". Boy, I really hope my family never gets a look at my bookmarks... They would be absoultely horrified. Why does adding the word "monkey" to something make it funnier? I mean, "ass" isn't really a funny word, but "assmonkey" is giggle-inducing. I also like "monkeyfucker". "stumpfucker", while not containing "monkey", is quite funny. At least that's what I think. But then again, I'm a big ol' freak with the bookmark folder from hell. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       A dissertation on cheese:  Cheese. Cheese is always shown in commercials streaming out of every gooey orifice of the hamburger/taco/pizza in an attempt to make you want the product more. If you were to eat this product, with its vast rivers of cheese all oozing and stretchy, you would most certainly burn the piss out of your mouth. So why the need to use a potentially hazardous product to sell food? Easy, gooey cheese=tasty food. The ad people figured out this equation some time ago. They know that even though cheese at 700 degrees farenheit is not something anyone wants in their mouths, cheese at 700 degrees farenheit LOOKS very appetizing, and makes the host food look better by proxy - flavor by association. I propose we as a society start to like cold cheese. I enjoy seeing a taco with the cheese just starting to melt, and, having delivered pizza for a while, I know that molten cheese is not only dangerous - it makes the food less attractive by allowing the other ingredients to slide around in seas of cheese. so, rather than sailing the seas of cheese (primus references notwithstanding), rather let us salivate to *slightly* gooey cheese, or cold cheese.  I'm so bright, my daddy called me "sun". my future's so bright, I gotta wear shades. I wear my sunglasses at night - so I can see.  urlLink I am not a random link.   urlLink Neither am I.   urlLink I am kinda random, but not TOO random or anything, just kinda confused.   urlLink I'm not really random, but I am totally wacked out.   urlLink You're so vain, I'll bet you think this link is about you.    
    
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Soapboxers Of The World: Shut Up.   So, I'm watching the superbowl, and I see like 3 or 4 ads from some group whose goal is apparently to make sure you never take another drag off another cigarette, ever. the ads featured people who had lost loved ones or had some various nasty diseases all because they smoked. There was also a commercial where n*sync showed up at some guy's house and thanked him for not letting his kids drink. I take issue with these "Sopaboxers", these people who use every oppoutunity to climb on a soapbox, to force their opinions down your throat, who will spend millions of dollars to get a commercial on the superbowl to preach anti-smoking and anti-drinking ideals to a bunch of drunk people with a pack of smokes in their pockets. I have an idea, a solution for all these soapboxers that will make everyone happy -SHUT THE HELL UP! Easy, wasn't it? If you want to influence people, put a sign up in your yard, stand on a corner near the hospital with a sign, hold a conference or a meeting where you can show people what you want to show them. Holding up pictures of dead babies in front of the clinic is only going to offend - not influence - anyone. if someone is on their way to have an abortion, or on their way into the store to buy beer, or already drunk - you've lost them, they aren't going to listen to you - go somewhere else. Of course, if you are dedicated enough to your cause to go forth and try to "Educate" (or "force your opinions down the throats of") the people, you are dedicated enough to not listen to a word I'm saying. because I am not of your cause, I am in the wrong, I am only trying to sway you from the right and true cause which you are crusading for, blocking people's paths for, killing people for, being a callous ass for, annoying and offending everyone for.   In case you haven't noticed, I have very strong opinions about having your own opinions -  let me restate that - I encourage you to have your own opinions on everything, don't let other people tell you what you should think, and don't tell other people what you think they should think. If your opinion is the right one, other people will come to have the same opinion as you - all on their own. I don't wear my seatbelt. I don't wear it, not because "it's uncomfortable" or "it messes up my clothes" or anything like that. I don't wear it because I can't stand the fact that I am legally compelled to wear it - I am being forced to make myself safe. If it wasn't a law, I'd be fine with it, and I might wear it. I stop at stoplights, I use my turn signal, why not the seatbelt? Because those other things make *everyone* safe - those are things that are right, and that need to be done to ensure the safety of others on the road. The seatbelt, however, protects only me. Why should I have to be safe? If I want to "live on the edge", it should be my right to do so.  
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Death Notice. Music was found dead on the 50 yard line of Raymond James Stadium in Tampa, Florida on Sunday. Time of death was around 8 pm, 7 central. Cause of death is believed to be a fatal mixing of genres, combined with an overdose of commercialization. Music had spent most of it's life in high spirits, but it started on a downward spiral when Fred Durst performed with Christina Aguilara during an awards show last year. Music was reported to have gone to it's home in Cleveland and freebased vanilla ice that night. the problems continued until tonight, where music met it's demise at Superbowl XXXV. During the opening ceremonies, the backstreet boys overpowered a healthy injection of Ray Charles by butchering the national anthem. Then, during the Mtv produced halftime show, Music suffered a fatal heart attack during the performance of Aerosmith, N*Sync, Britney Spears, Mary J Blige, and Nelly. Apparently, all the artists performing "Walk this Way", an old Aerosmith favorite, simultaneously, was enough to cause total pulmonary failure. Music is survived by Sculpture, Poetry, Painting, Theater, and Dance. Music will be mourned by all those who loved it. Memorial services will be held at the rock and roll hall of fame museum in Cleveland.  They say the heart of rock and roll is still beating, and from what I've seen, they couldn't be more wrong. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       If men got pregnant there would be a lot more c-sections.  urlLink MC Hawking.  Somebody has been using that text-to-speech thingie to make raps as Stephen Hawking.  
    
    
</post>

<date>06,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I've been on that there internet for a coon's age, and I've seen many things, some of which were quite entertaining, some of which would make a 60 year old tranvestite stripper cough up her 4th tequila and semen cocktail. Through all my journeying, however, I've found that there is one truth to the internet - one constant. One thing that we all need to see as the horrible problem it is, and that we must rise up to stop:   It's "YOUR", as in "Maybe a dingo ate your baby.", and "YOU'RE", as in "There's a party in my pants, and you're all invited."   I cannot stress this enough. We as a society need to find all instances of this travesty, and squash it. We must rise up as one and find all those who propagate this abuse of the english language. Did we not take english class? Are we to the point where we can no longer distinguish between "your" and "you are"? I've been to all corners of this, the world wide web. I've seen the dark offramps and gutters lining the information superhighway, and this one thing keeps attacking. It's worse than any virus, it's more infectious than the hampster dance (or hamster, if you want to be snooty and spell it right). So many times I've seen an otherwise hopeful webpage throw itself away by using phrases such as "Welcom to my webpage, your welcome to look around, but I created theses pages, so don't take whats not you'res". Now the lack of the apostrophe I can deal with, but  the extra one ? Why? What caused you to add the extra punctuation, when you had previously omitted it? The only answer is sheer, blinding, painful stupidity. I know I don't use proper punctuation, and my grammar leaves much to be desired - but it's my style of writing. I write this way because I can express myself more efficiently this way. Saying "your" where you should have said "you're" is just wrong. "you're" instead of "your" is worse. "your'e" or "yo'ure" is just wrong regardless.  And now, some offensive rap lyrics: "Tell your girl to stop changing her lipstick - I'm starting to get rainbows around my dick." "Face down, ass up - That's the way we likes to fuck." "...and when I'm finished, there's gonna be a bloodbath of cops dying in L.A.. Yo dre, I got something to say: Fuck the police" 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Damnation, I need to proofread these things before I post. Hey, it was valentine's day a while back. like I care. Valentine's day is one of those pure commercial holidays that has long since lost all of it's original meaning. Christmas has almost lost it, but there are still people who celebrate it for the reason it was intended. much like Thanksgiving. Thanksgiving is not a holiday where we give thanks to turkey farmers. I wonder what the mexican guys from the line in the outlaw army scene in blazing saddles are doing now... "Adult diapers? We don't need no steeenking adult diapers!... well, yeah, probably we do." Hey, why do beaches make otherwise unspeakable things OK to put on tv? Viagra commercials show a guy (Dole, usually) walking on a beach. Summer's eve: beach. Tampax: beach. If erectile disfunction/feminine hygeine are so icky, what makes you think somebody walking on a beach makes it less icky? the message is the same: "Here I am, walking on this beach and, thanks to Viagra, I can lay it to the old wife again." "Thanks to tampax, I'm not attracting sharks up onto the sand and ruining my pants." Beaches and flowers. Walking thru a field of flowers is ok, too. and tennis. play lots of tennis and it's ok to talk about your malfunctioning peepee or your aunt flo.  This is the face of erectile disfunction:  :-/  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I almost wet myself when I saw  urlLink This  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I wake up screaming in the middle of the night. It's happening again. I thought I could control it, but some things just can't be controlled. All the medications, all the counseling, all worthless to me know, as I slip into madness again. I can't make it go away, I can't turn it down, it keeps echoing thru my head. It keeps getting stronger and stronger, and the more I try to fight it - the worse it gets. The haunting melody begins, then the voices...... "........they're a page right out of his-to-reee." damn you bedrock, damn you to hell. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I'm a damned tech junkie. I really love new fangled tech toys that I will never have a use for and will never be able to afford. Example: I think those 50 inch plasma tv's are the coolest thing since - well, since the tv. I don't really watch that much tv, and I can't exactly buy one, since they run about 25 grand and I don't currently have a job. But I want one soooooo bad. I also think it would be neat to have one of those 4 thousand dollar laptops to play the sims on at the local truckstop. yeah, I want an 800mhz laptop computer, with 128 megs or more of ram, 20 or so gigs of hard drive space, and I would spend my time playing mp3's wth it and playing games. Now, any gadget can be cool and "must have", but to truly rock, it's gotta have a useless remote. Like those car stereos with a little tiny remote control, even though you are never going to be more then 2 feet from the damn thing. I want remote controls for everything I own. I want a toaster with no external controls. Yeah.... My toaster could have a usb cable on it, and I could bring up the toaster control panel (toaster.cpl) to make toast. Or if I prefer, I could use the 2.4ghz remote, and make toast from a mile away. This would all be pointless, since I'd still have to go load bread into the toaster, but I would still show it off to all my friends. Actually, I want one of those whole house control things, except with the functionality of the fantasy toaster i just mentioned. I want to be sitting in front of the computer, pick up a bigass remote with an lcd touch screen or fire up a program, and make toast, record a rerun of "newsradio", let the dog outside, fire up the stereo to play some fear factory, fire a warning shot at the zealot passing out flyers at my front door, warm up my car, pet the cat, get the newspaper, call a friend and make plans to go somewhere, celebrate the chinese new year, donate 1 dollar to the "shut sally struthers the hell up" foundation, scratch my balls, clean the toilet, and scratch my balls again for good measure - all from the comfort of my heated, massaging, sound system having, fridge having chair. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Man, I have got to do something about all these people driving thru my yard. I mean, I thought living on the interstate would be neat, but it's just getting to be a hassle - what with having to put on that orange vest and run across 6 lanes of traffic to check my mail, which is usually just a bill or one of those damned asphalt roofing tiles. I wish I knew who kept sending me roofing tiles. I did get enough to redo the roof on my toolshed, but I still think somebody is trying to move in or something. Actually, I was thinking it might be this old friend of mine stealing someone's house again, and trying to us eme to cover his tracks. he used to do this all the time, but he used to always send the chunks of wall and stuff to his mom, and then she'd repaint them and pile them up in the backyard, and he'd get back and go take all the chunks and sell them to somebody. He made a nice living, but I just think it would be too much work. Anyway, he's gonna have a hole in his roof 'cause I'm keeping those tiles I redid the roof of my toolshed with. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Lately, two questions have been racing thru my head: 'Why do I feel the need to set my head on fire at family reunions?' and 'Did I build that hedge maze out front just to piss off the mailman?' No answers seem to be in sight. At least I've got my sanity. And my army of lawn gnomes. Oh, and those neato pieces of that guy's fence that look just like the top of a cherry pie. I wonder why he won't let me mow his yard anymore? They say idle hands do the devil's work. what about hands holding a bloody chainsaw in a nursing home? what kind of work are they doing? Hey, If I got shot 30,000 times, would I be a tragedy? I mean, when one person dies, the news doesn't seem to care as much as when somebody kills off a whole big group of people. So if I was to get kshot enough times to kill a whole herd of people, would I qualify as a tragedy? What if I made up a new religion right before I got killed? would I be a martyr then? I think it would be neat to be a martyr, it's just that I don't really like the idea of having to be dead first - I couldn't enjoy it if I was dead. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       I was thinking of naming my blog Gordon or something. I could be like 'Gordon Blog, meet Twilight Jones. Twilight will be making the blood vessels in people's heads explode - with your help.'  Warning: This Page contains both secure and insecure elements - do you give a shit? An error has occured in line 9842, char 746 - do you want to run a debugger that will further break the page? Notice: there is a syntax error on line 14, char 27. expected 'proper syntax', got 'improper syntax'. Peligro: one error was found on this page. Microsoft Internet Explorer will now reformat the page to contain more, and possibly cause a slew of those ugly 16 bit errors when it pukes, taking your shell down with it, since your shell and Microsoft Internet Expoder are one and the same. Also note that you will probably have to reset your system, since only explorer holds the secret to correctly shutting down. GDI.exe, msgsrv32, and rundll will likely fall over as well, causing what we at Microsoft call 'the domino effect', or 'up-shit-creek-sans-paddle mode', wherein you will see many variations of the ever-popular blue screen of death and disfigurement, which will be hiding self-propagating error messages, which of course, will end up crashing some module or kicking your physical memory in just the right spot so as to cause Microsoft Windows to spew forth more blue screens of rape and pillaging. Caution: since Microsoft Internet Exploiter and Explorer.exe are linked at the hip, any further crashes in any program will likely cause Microsoft Internet Extorter to die a violent death and killing half of your programs as it thrashes towards the land of memory leakage, which of course will either crash the shell or cause enough crappage to force you to reboot, because we on the Windows team think rebooting is the right thing to do, regardless of what you think. Go Ahead and reboot now and get it over with?   (Yes)  (OK) Alert: Microsoft Windows will probably go ahead and reboot into safe mode, or maybe just reboot again, just to be extra safe. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
       Is it ever really Tuesday? Is Tuesday just a relative term? what if some aliens came to earth and thought us to be savages because we use this wildly inaccurate and archaic system for measuring time? I just noticed that my last two posts invloved getting pants damp, so I'll just go ahead and make it a hat trick:  Damn, I should have rolled up my cuffs before we walked across that gigantic sponge.  you know, I'm pretty sure the person that invented the toilet paper holder knew which way the free end was supposed to hang. So like, I was reading about lake vostok, which is this lake under 2 miles of ice near the south pole, and I got to thinking "why do we even care about other planets when we haven't got this one figured out yet?" I am just in deep thought mode here. I was thinking about making some new team members (who would still be me) to post different things, but that would be kind of a hassle, so forget it. If I took advantage of those little buttons at the top of the 'edit your blog' screen and started using excessive  bold   italicized   urlLink hyperlinks , would that annoy anbody? wHaT aBOUt mIxeD CaPS? or I could be all 3733t and use hacker-speak so 1/10 of 1% of the people could read it. or I could just use latin. or spanish, but I don;t know much spanish. I know prostituta, amplificador, gordo, burrito supreme.... I want to learn how to say "Excuse me, do you speak spanish?" in spanish, and then go to mexico and annoy people.  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2001</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink The Cynic's Sanctuary  Oh, sweet cynicism.  
    
    
</post>

<date>14,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       The following post will be in canadian as well as english.  The following post will be in canuck as well as english - eh?   sorry about the lack of posts. I just noticed that it's been about a month since I last posted.  soory aboot the lack of posts, eh? I just noticed that it's been aboot a month since I last posted, there - eh?   urlLink The End Of The Internet.  At least somebody put up a warning - I might have fallen off the edge.   urlLink The End Of The Internet there, buddy  Eh? I missed what happened - I stepped in some moose dookie.   urlLink File Not Found.  It takes a while for the story to unfold, but it's well worth the wait. Hands down THE best 404 error I've ever seen.   urlLink Soory, I couldn't find it.  I think that-uh, somebody stole my webpage there, eh?   So, there are a couple of links for you. oh, and about the canadian translation - I just thought I might help a few people out. learning by association works pretty well - I learned Moron that way.  Soo, there are a couple a links for you there, eh? oh, and aboot the canadian translation - eh? hey! we speak the same language there, bucko - eh?      
    
    
</post>

<date>18,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
       So, I noticed a while back that Menudo (the eternal boy band) changed their name to mdo. I can only assume that someone finally told them what menudo is... "So Menudo is getting ready to record another album, and-" "uh, hey man - I need to tell you something about the name of the band...(whispering)" "....uh huh.....yeah.....they make it out of tripe?!?!?!?!"   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Must....play....the....sims.....   I just had a thought. Yup. All by myself. A whole thought. Oh.... you wanna hear it? Oh, ok. So, I was thinking that if some evil overlord wanted to take over the U.S., he should just buy enough computers for everybody and install the sims on every one of them. Seriously, once that was done, we'd all be addicted and mr. evil overlord could just walk into the white house and declare himself king of the United States. What I find interesting is that the sims is incredibly addictive, but it is essentially a  life simulator . I mean, people are playing this game for hours and hours, pretending to interact with their families and friends, instead of ACTUALLY interacting with their families and friends. Do we suck that bad? Are we as a people just so boring and idiotic that we'd rather play with a virtual family instead of a real one? of course, when your real family pisses you off, you can't wall them into a bedroom until they die...... or can you? I've seen houses uploaded on various websites with the description "this is my house". People are simulating their homes in a simulation of their lives while they sit in their real homes missing their real lives. Am I the only one who sees the gargantuan steaming piles of irony here? And there is another problem - even worse than the sims: When I mentioned the evil overlord, I said "he", and I bet nobody noticed. if I'd have said "she", everybody would have been upset because I'm a sexist. and it doesn't even occur to you that there could be female evil overlords... hell, look at cruella de vil, or the wicked witch of the west. What I'm really trying to say is.... hey look - it's my sims cd.... so nice and shiny..... I could probably just play for a little while. yeah, that'd be alright. Just a while...... 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        damn'em addendum   I forgot to mention the OTHER purple reptile that predates barney.... Dino. The lovable pet dinosaur from the Flintstones. I always wondered why Dino was the only dinosaur that couldn't talk. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Ce n'est pas un sujet   This is not a post. This is a figment of your imagination, speaking of figments, that makes two purple reptiles that predate Barney. Figment was a little purple dragon at disneyworld&copy;, the happiest place on earth, no guns, smoking, alcohol, whoring, drug-taking, partying-down, cursing, spitting, happiness, or pets. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        The Urinal Wars   I just had a neat thought. what if earth went to war with an alien race because they looked like urinals? you know, they show up, all diplomatic  then, while the leader is meeting with the president - some tourist pisses on an elite guard. "... that's right, Jim, and if you can see what is going on behind me - the aliens seem to be bombarding the planet with some type of small white disc.  They have a clean, chemical smell to them, and they look like large asprins except- wait -something is happening..... PISS!!! THEY ARE URINATING ON EVERYTHING!!!!! RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!!!" 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Here in my car I feel safest of all   For the past month or so, I've had these visions of car wrecks with Gary Numan's "cars" playing in the background... weird, huh?  I tried to write a poem from the deep depths of my heart but the only word I can think of that rhymes with heart is fart  I'm trying to come up with the ultimate country song... I was thinking of something along the lines of: "my wife ran off with my best friend, stole my truck, and backed over my dog on her way out of the driveway. so now I'm sitting in this bar, drunk, spending my last 876 million dollars that I got from all you poor depressed suckers who bought my last album,  in which, my wife ran off with 7 different people, my dog, and a parking meter. and my best friend got ran over by a tractor being driven by his wife, who had caught him cheating with her sister. now I'm so sad that it makes me want to repeat some cheesy broken-heart lyric over and over again until all of you buy this album. maybe the lyric will be -  I'm stuck out of love, drunk, with a dead dog and no truck" 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Topics are good topics.   I think I've decided to start adding a topic to the top of each post. Makes it look a little more pro-am, instead of the am-am it was, which is just silly - seeing as how there really is no am-am web league. Oh hell, now I've gone and mentioned the web league. Now I'll have to kill you all.  and now a haiku:          poor little puppy running so fast down the hall    give back my sandwich  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Infectious wearables  Not as bad as it sounds. they sell ties and boxers with pictures of disease on them. I'm pretty sure they aren't  actually  infectious, but you oughta wash them first just to make sure. The proceeds go towards finding cures, although I doubt the proceeds from the plague tie will go towards curing the plague. The HIV boxers might not be the best thing to have on when you take a date home.... "hey, what's that on your boxers?" "well.... HIV" "oh.... I think I oughta get going."   urlLink This Planet Earth  NASA rocks. this site has a bunch of videos made from satellite imagery zooming into various cities. I saw the washington, d.c. one, and it zooms from space all the way to what I think is the white house, all seamlessly. Neat stuff.  QUOTE "It is inhumane, in my opinion, to force people who have a genuine medical need for coffee to wait in line behind people who apparently view it as some kind of recreational activity. I bet this kind of thing does not happen to heroin addicts. I bet that when serious addicts go to purchase their heroin, they do not tolerate waiting in line while some dilettante in front of them orders a hazelnut smack-a-cino with cinnamon sprinkles." - Dave Barry END QUOTE 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Happy Cinco De Mayo!   YAY!!!! People the world over are rejoicing now. For now we celebrate Cinco De Mayo, which is apparently a celebration of the fact that it is the fifth of May. Kinda like celebrating the fourth of July, only you aren't celebrating the fourth of July - you celebrate Independence day, which falls on July 4. I know lots of people who celebrate the fourth of July, rather than Independence day. These are the same people who pronounce Illinois with an "S" at the end and think Jesus was an American. I propose a new holiday: Lost Day. We would celebrate Lost Day at midnight on February 28 - a lot like we do for New Years now. Then, on leap years, we could have a big day long celebration, since we found the day we had been missing. I really think people would get behind this, I mean, it's a really good reason to stay home from work and get drunk. Maybe we could declare March 1 "Hangover Day" or something. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,April,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Grapples!   Apples and Gravy, together at last! Grapples are located in your grocer's meat section. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Concerted Effort   Party over here. Party over there. Party over here. Party over there. Now just the ladies. Now the back row. Now the front. Good night, Seattle. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
        If I spell it "tyre", does that make me british?   uh, here are some links, cuz I feel like posting and can't think of anything to post that doesn't somehow involve giant killer robot monkeys.  urlLink Visual Elements  The periodic table of elements represented as images. neato.  urlLink MattTracks  Wanna spend 15 grand replacing the tires on your truck with tracks, like they have on tanks? go here. Neat stuff abounds.  urlLink Sixties Stuff  Now, I wasn't born until the 70's, but I had a lot of this stuff when i was a kid. that damned videosphere goes for 700 bucks, and I had one! damnit!   
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Pay No Attention To The Man Behind The Giant Killer Robot Monkey.   This is a test. Had this been a real emergency, people would have been running around screaming for a good 3 minutes by now, and you would be wondering "why the hell are all these people running around screaming?", but that is not the case, as this is indeed a test. Should this test coincide with an actual emergency, you should look outside and note any screaming running people, and take appropriate action. Now, we may just be messing with your head here - this may be a real honest-to-goodness emergency, and we might be just stalling you so we can loot the stores while they still have some good stuff left, but we probably aren't, since we have good jobs pretending to have emergencies every couple of weeks. It isn't really a glamourous job, it isn't even a high paying one, but - well, we were coming to a point, but now we are depressed and don't feel like talking about it anymore. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
        There Is Nothing To Fear But- AHHHHHH!!!!!!!   I wish I knew somebody that was really paranoid. I would have that poor sucker wearing a tinfoil hat in a week.  We have nothing to fear but the giant killer robot monkeys. and fear, I guess.  A friend was telling me how she wanted to start an urban legend and get it all over the internet. Now I know how they get started... I think I might do that, except I've always been partial to idiotic chain letters, so here goes:  This is absolutely True!!! I have verified every single person in this list is actually dead or suffering from the affliction described!! And I should know - I'm a doctor!!! Before you read any further: forward this to everyone you know. go find other email addresses and send it to those people. If you can manage to send it to at least 400 people, you MIGHT avoid a HORRIBLY PAINFUL DEATH!! James Sanderval, a steel worker from Detroit, forwarded this letter to 360 people, and as a DIRECT RESULT of not going the extra mile, he is at this very moment THE PRISON BITCH IN THE WORST JAIL IN MEXICO!!! By the way, if you have not already sent this to AT LEAST 35 people, YOUR FATE IS SEALED!!!! Pray that your death will not be like that of Margeret Boycanth, who had only sent this letter to 3 people by this point. Poor Mageret never finished reading the letter, because A BEAR BROKE INTO HER HOUSE AND RAPED HER TO DEATH!!!!! You MUST send this letter to AT LEAST 400 people. Dave Macau sent this letter to 400 people exactly, and he is currently DYING OF CANCER OF THE BRAIN, LIVER, LUNGS, PENIS, AND HEART!!!! So you see, you absolutely must, for your sake, send this letter to as many people as possible, but NOT MORE THAN 700!!!! Illyich Andropov sent this letter to 1300 people, trying to secure his good luck, but in doing so he UPSET THE BALANCE OF THE UNIVERSE and we are all doomed to develop a HORRIBLY PAINFUL allergy to celery, AND IT IS DIRECTLY HIS FAULT!!!! So there you have it. Send this letter to at least 400 people, but not more than 700, and you MAY NOT DIE OF SCURVY!!!!!!!!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Be Afraid, Be very Afraid.   I just read on  urlLink IBM's website  that 2% of the world is online.... 2 percent. Yeah, I'm scared too. 2% of the people in the world have turned a noble and just venture into this orgy of stupidity and bad spelling, this world wide web. I wonder when AOL will decide to tap into the vast resource of people too stupid to get online by themselves. They'll start shipping specially equipped computers to Arkansas and Texas that will boot straight into AOLOS, and then automatically connect to the internet, then we can all rejoice because another 5% of the lowest common denominator has been added to the list of idiots with "screen names" like "johnsmith846723" who can barely speak, much less type. But they won't have to type, thanks to the redneck voice recognition software installed on these systems. So when johnsmith846723 says "gimme that thar chat winder again", the system will automatically bring up every chat system known to man, connect him to every channel and room, and send these words to everyone on the net: "WCW kicks ass, it's way beter than that WWF garbage. all them WWF peeple are fake wrasslin" 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,May,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Darkness, And Lack Thereof.   I am in love. I've never been in love before, and it's a new and exciting time for me. My  newfound love, the one who completes me, whom I love without compromise, is published by Lionhead studios and developed by Peter Molyneaux. I'm talking about Black and White, the most amazing game to ever be released for any platform. I'm not biased or anything (go buy it now) but it is my honest opinion (even if you have to sell your body to afford it) that you should buy this game, and soon you will pledge your undying love to this masterwork, this opus, this bar-raising product of pure genius. In Black and White, you play a god, created by the prayers of some poor little suckers/innocent islanders. when you arrive, you start helping out the village and learning about your godly powers, you can be nice to the people, or you can be evil and kill them with wild abandon, giggling the giggle of a wicked god throwing his followers into the sea at several hundred miles per hour. I took a mostly neutral path. I will sometimes be a little nasty and roll a boulder thru town or something, but I'm quick to call up a food miracle or heal the village. Oh yeah, and you have a creature. Your creature is your avatar, an extension of your powers and your representative in the physical world. I have an ape who throws cows but eats sheep. The creature is a miracle of coding. the AI is astounding - they will learn from your actions and can take care of themselves if you teach them well. My ape knows to eat when he's hungry, drink when he's thirsty, and poop on trees when he, well, needs to poo. Your environment changes when you change - if you are evil and spend all your time terrorizing people, your land will become dark and evil to match. your creature can change as well, becoming evil or good depending on how you trained it. when I first got my creature, I beat him senseless  (you can slap or pet them if you want to punish or reward them), of course, I felt like an abusive parent when my badly bruised ape had to go to this guide creature to be trained. There are several "neato" features in the game that set it apart from pretty much everything else: the game has a built in email client, and can name members of your village after names in your address book. The game also has a weather system built in so you can go register the game and where you are, and while in the game, the weather on your land will match the weather in your real life area. Did I mention the gestures? you can draw shapes with mouse movements (called Gestures) to create miracles and such. some are a little tough, but it really helps in blurring the line between the game and that other thing that happens outside the game (I think somebody called it "a life"), since you don't have a bunch of menus clogging things up. I would also like to mention the amazing look and feel of the game in general. it starts with the lionhead logo - it consists of a bunch fo blakc and white spheres floating around, which eventually form the company logo. You can interact with this logo as it forms. moving the mouse makes the spheres swirl around in response. Once inside the game, you can zoom right up to a single person, then zoom out to above the clouds, all in one swift seamless motion. All the movement is smooth, and when the in-game cutscenes activate, the camera moves under its own power, and there is realy no indication that anything has changed, except that you are no longer moving the view. There is just too much in this game to mention without writing a book about it or something. Go get it, now. this game is beyond amazing, it is beyond anything ever made. It will be remembered in 20 years when many more games have copied it. You will fall in love and forsake your real life and wish that you could just live in the game world. I need to go play Black and White now, so you people all go buy it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
        A Toast is in Order   HAPPY 85TH POST!!!!! This is the 85th time I've bothered you. I've had 85 posts to this weblog. Well, 84, and this one celebrating. I guess this qualifies as a post, but it doesn't seem right, being a post strictly about how many posts I've made. Hell, I've had posts consisting of some random link... I even had one that said simply: "What am I gonna do with all these ostriches????" So yeah, happy 85th post. Here's to another 72!!! 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Damn Monkey   So I figured I'd post a quick update about my creature in Black and White, just for the hell of it. My ape was a kind, if fairly maladjusted creature. I had taught him to cast the shower miracle on fields, and I taught him how to put trees into the village store. when he came across a cow, he threw it, since I used some cows to teach him how to throw. So he ate sheep and threw cows. And then he developed this compulsion to water fields. This is all he would do. My damned ape would walk around watering the hell out of farmland until he passed out. He also turned the wood gathering ability into a potentially nasty habit - he kicks trees. So now my ape will decide to kick random trees in random directions. He does this because I was neglecting him. I spent probably half an hour chucking fireballs at a nearby village that was out of my circle of influence, and my poor little ape became a little bastard. Did I mention that he has an affinity for making breeders? I led him to a village to try and win it over to my side, so he starts watering farmland like a good little monkey, so I went off to tend to other godly things. I come back to see my ape creating breeders as fast as he could pick up villagers. Oh yeah, now he eats people. I have Black and White installed on a friend's computer, since my GhettoPC won't run it. This friend played for a while on my profile instead of creating another. When I get back to the game - I'm partially evil, and my ape has developed a taste for villager. So now I have a creature who: Eats sheep but throws cows, Poos on trees, but is just as likely to kick a tree instead, Has a compulsive need to create breeders and water farms, and eats humans... 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2001</date>
<post>

    
        tH1S p0St HaS b33n HaX0r3d!!!! W00T!!!   The International Consortium of Web Bosses has determined, after much deliberation, that Hackers do indeed 0wN j00. Much has been done to stop this threat, but it appears that the hackers are just too l33t. The Hacker Coalition of Earth (Fargo Office) replied with the statement "r0X0R!!! W33 0wN j00!!!" The complete illegibility of this response was attributed to the fact that the average member age in the HCE is 13. I can't sympathize with these idiots who hack for fun, but I think I know why they do it. They hack for the same reason I used to set fires to pools of gasoline and staple junebugs to the wall; they can. had I been exposed to computers earlier, I might have become a hacker. Although, since I have subversive and destructuve tendancies, I would have most likely been a Cracker (ATTN MEDIA: CRACKERS ARE BAD, HACKERS NOT SO MUCH.) I spend my time online looking at disturbing webpages and downloading massive amounts of pirated software and violating copyrights with wild abandon (ATTN "THE MAN": EAT ME.) These hackers' lives are consumed by the one activity - hacking. They spend all day organizing denial of service attacks and looking around for credit card numbers. (well, that would make them crackers, but let's not mince words). Most of these hackers are what is known as a "script kiddie", which is the cyber equivalent of a wannabe. They will spend all day using programs written by other people - programs they do not understand and can barely use - to do their evil deeds for them. Had they been without computers, they would have been with the big group of white kids wearing red and calling themselves "Bloods", while actually being terrifed that a *real* gang would become irritated with them and kill them all. Both groups work off the same principle: there is strength in numbers. If you're in a gang, you're a lot less likely to be beaten up, since you have a dozen or so of your closest g's with you. In hacking, much of what they do involves multiple computers, or multiple hackers coordinating one event. Maybe if we gave these kids something else fun and antisocial to do, they'd cut out all this foolishness. I say pellet guns. Pellet guns kept me out of (serious) trouble, because I would spend most of my time taking pot shots at animals and milk jugs. Pellet guns for all, and all our problems will be solved - and quickly replaced with all new pellet gun-related problems. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Why Can't Johnny Read?   I think I spilled my brains out a month ago, 'cuz I haven't had the inspiration to post here. Right now I'm flying by the seat of my pants, and the seat of my pants has worn thin from all the sitting on this chair in front of this computer missing this life. Maybe I should become a dominatrix... hold on, I think you have to be a woman to do that. What is a male dom called? Dominator. Yeah... I AM THE DOMINATOR!!! I like it. It has a real "I am the Dominator" ring to it. Anyway, I was thinking I might become a Dominator so I could not post for a month and blame on all the worthless scum who read this thing. Something like "I didn't post for a month because I didn't feel like it. Deal, scum."  Naw. I'm not a born leader, which is weird, since I'm a leo and I'm supposed to be a leader. Fuck it, here's some links:  National Geographic has a page all about Coffee (All hail Coffee). Coffee (Coffee be praised) is my god. I worship the holy triumverate: Coffee (Coffee bless me), Juan Valdez, and a blurry, vibrating frog (what? it's not as strange as the stuff in the bible.) urlLink Go read the page , and leave an offering of non-dairy creamer or sugar by your Coffee Maker.   urlLink Galileo is flipping you off.  Galileo's body got moved at some point in the past, and when it was, somebody yanked the middle finger out of his right hand. I can only assume they had a really bad booger and didn't want to be caught with their own finger up their nose. Oddly Enough, this site is on NASA's webpage...   urlLink AdCritic  In case you don't know about it yet, AdCritic is a site that puts all the best commercials on the web. I watch the superbowl for the commercials, I have no interest whatsoever in all the football playing that surrounds them.  
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
        PIMPCHICKEN!   And now, another adventure of Pimpchicken, the Chicken who also happens to be a pimp. One day, Pimpchicken was out strolling the street, keeping tabs on his Hoechickens, when his arch-nemesis, Pimpfox, struts his way. Pimpfox was pimping his Hoefoxes on Pimpchicken's territory, and Pimpchicken was none too happy about that. "What do you think you doing pimping yo hoes on my turf, suckuh?", said Pimpchicken, with a scowl on his beak. To this, Pimpfox replied "I be pimping my Hoefoxes any damn where I want, chicken!". Now, Pimpchicken was enraged at this, and he was just about to whip out his pimp stick and lay the smack down on the ol' Pimpfox, when the farmer came out of the barn and shot Pimpfox with a big old shotgun. 2 days later, Pimpchicken was strolling the street again, keeping tabs on his Hoechickens, and the farmer came back. "Yo, you want one of my bitches, bitch?", said Pimpchicken, and with that, the farmer grabed Pimpchicken by the throat and snapped his neck. The farmer then threw Pimpchicken into the bed of his truck and drove out behind the barn to the burning pit. 2 days later, there was a new Pimpchicken. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
        I'm only partially here.   Man, being tired sucks. I could go to sleep and fix this problem, but I'm an idiot and addicted to the computer, so here I sit, blurry vision and all, typing some random non-thoughts into this post. I'll read this tomorrow and go "What the hell was I thinking?" and then I'll probably think "I need to sleep more." or possibly "Man, a twinkie would hit the spot right now." Speaking of twinkies - what the hell is wrong with Hostess, or whoever the hell it is that makes twinkies.... oompa loompas, probably. Anyway, twinkies were the same for millions of years, having evolved from the sea sponge. The common twinkie developed a defense mechanism - spooge - that ensured the survival of the species by rendering the twinkie inedible. Humans eventually evolved a resistance to this horrible poison, and began eating the otherwise tasty twinkies in vast quantities. The twinkie population was in danger of being wiped out by fat people, so they began to evolve toxins even more horrible than that white spooge crap in their body cavities. A few years ago, twinkies developed a chocolate coating. This chocolate coating was like toxic waste, plus it turned the flesh of the twinkie into a substance not unlike foam rubber. This variant of the twinkie apparently had some fatal flaw, because they vanished rather quickly. now, a new horror has arisen within the very flesh of the twinkie. I think they are called "tiger tail" or something, and they have what appears to be generic berry goo spiraling around the body of the twinkie. We humans will eventually develop a resistance to this as well, and the twinkie will be forced to develop something even more horrible. maybe a marshmallow and coconut coating. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
        I'm buying a bicycle.   The dagnabbed gol-durned price of gas has me all red in the face, like when I stuck my head in the fry-daddy. Now, way back in the way back, gas was like a dollar a gallon where I live. A buck sounds just about right. It works. Then out of nowhere, the price of gas had a spasm and suddenly it cost like a buck seventy to buy a damned gallon of gas. When I was just a young pyromaniac, before I had any bodily hair to accidentally burn off, a dollar would buy me a whole afternoon of fun, flames, and fumes. If gas did that knee-jerk price thing when I was a kid, I would have been so bummed out, I probably would have been forced to go to the pool or something else totally unfun. I have a friend with an econobox - one of those cars the size of a midget's athletic supporter. It gets like 700 miles to the gallon, which is good because it has a 10 gallon tank. I prefer the land yachts - cars that need 11 gallons to prime the carb. Anyway, this friend had to spend damn near twenty bucks to fill up his tank. This car is the size of a hamster skull, and it costs 20 bucks to fill it up. If I had a car (I'm usually a jobless bum), I'd probably have something that was 30 feet long and weighed 18 tons, and had a beeper thing for when I backed it up - not that I would ever back it up, because the back window is so far away that I can't see anyting thru it. I like these cars. These cars have time zones - they affect the tides. But if I had one of these cars, I'd be paying upwards of the total net worth of Oregon to fill up the gas tank. Now, the gas price hike isn;t really what pissed me off. What pissed me off is the fact that gas prices dropped, and then they leveled off around 1.20. Gas got up to like 2.50 in some places, and now it's down to like 1.20-1.50, and we are supposed to be thankful for gas prices being so low. I have news for you:  Gas prices are still high.  Remember before, when gas was a dollar? Now it is "back down" and it's still at least 1.20. Somebody is laughing their asses off over this, and it ain't the general populous. The general populous is scared shitless at the gas prices. Travelling salesman were paying so much for gas that they drew no profit. The United States Fucking Postal Service was going to drop Saturday deliveries because of gas prices. And young pyromaniacs everywhere have to shell out more money for their activities. Money they could be using for more productive things, like matches. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
        A few of my least favorite things.   I fucking hate the sun. And toothaches. And pretty much everything else when I'm sunburned with a toothache. And now, after coming in to work at 6 am for three days, I have to come in to work at 10 pm, so my internal clock is in chaos. Much like the rest of me. Fuck you, sun. piss off. I have to work outside. Outside under the unforgiving stare of the white hot sun. Sun, go fuck yourself. Eclipse already. So here I am working outside, in a legendary heat wave. it's been 100 and up for the last two weeks. got up to 106 today. While I was outside. Outside in a glass building in the middle of a parking lot. Everybody feel sorry for me. Because the sun is just laughing it up at my expense. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Apologies are in order.   A couple posts back I incorectly identified the United States Postal Fucking Service as the United States Fucking Postal Service. I apologize for any inconvenience this has caused, and I apologize to the United States Fucking Postal Service Pizzaria in Tampa, Florida for the extra mail and phone calls I have caused you.  And now, I would like to sing a little song for you:  Who lives in a pineapple under the sea? Spongebob Squarepants! Absorbent and yellow and porous is he. Spongebob Squarepants! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
        I am a joyful pomegranate.   My job is the most boring thing I've ever done, and I can stare at the ceiling fan for hours. I walk around and spray water on a parking lot. But my job is so much more than that. So many more things add to the utter boredom. I use a gas powered sprayer, so there is the constant mechanical drone, and that's all I hear. The only thing I see is concrete, since I have to watch where I am spraying. So I walk around looking at the nozzle on this sprayer, and all I can hear is an engine running. I do this for ~6 hours a night. As a result of being bored out of my mind all night every night, I have decided to go insane. I think I'll take a few months to descend into madness, to see if I like it. Then once I have myself to keep me company, I won't be bored anymore. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Deplane, boss, deplane!   Tattoo, how do you expect them to deplane when they're still in the air?   
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
        HACKED BY CHINESE!   uh, like, this post has been H4> \/\/00T!!! Damn, for some reason I just feel the need to rub my dick on the top of a person's head. I don't know why, but for like 3 days, every time I see a newscaster talking about really serious issues like heat related deaths and war in the middle east, I get this urge to be there, flopping my unit around on the top of their head. "In other news, (zip) kuzhijkbekhistan declared war on vuzhijkbekhistan (flop), citing religious differences (flop flop)." I bet I could do that to Dan Rather, and he'd maintain his composure. He'd be all deadpan, talking about how some housewife burst into flames going out to get her mail, and I'd be just whipping my trouser snake around on his toupee. That'd be fucking hilarious. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
        I'm a lot happier now.   So, if the price of prozac rises, does it bum out the people on it to the point where they need more prozac, which makes them more depressed, since they are spending more money? I have a truck. YAY! I have been without a vehicle of my own for a couple of years now. the last car I had ended up in the witness protection program. I was an abusive driver. I kicked the car, I drove it beyond what it was built to endure, I treated it like a 4X4 and it was an Ltd. The head cracked on it, so it would sort of stop running every once in a while, once it got hot. When the car stopped, I got upset and kicked it - a lot. poor car. fuckin' chunk of shit. Anyway, now I have a truck. a 1985 mitsubishi, actually, which I have named the Shitsubishi. I sense another abusive relationship coming. I bought it today, and it needs a starter. I have to push start it. yay. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Did you get me a pony?   It's my birthday today. I'm 25. Now you can all go track me down based on the information you have and steal my life just like in that one movie - "the net". Not like anybody would want my life. My life is a lot like a truck I used to have. I had a datsun truck, and the doors would decide to stop opening on occasion, and it had a problem with starting in the cold. So I would leave the door open with the truck running when I went in places. I bet theives just walked by it shaking their heads and looking for something worth the effort. My life is pretty much like that. I could staple my social security card to a tree in the front yard and nobody would even bother with stealing my life. Even if I somehow got ahold of some super secret spy data, they'd probably just come over and kill me before they bothered with stealing my life. I'm in a real happy place now, in case you didn't notice... 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
        "Vee have vays ov makink you talk." "What?"   So I wonder how small a post I could get away with... 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2001</date>
<post>

    
        I'll kill you all!!!!   Go to  urlLink My Normal Site.  I've been doing this weblog for upwards of a year, and I only just now built a whole page to wrap around it. actually, I built like 5 pages. I've gone and made a clearinghouse of all my random webpage ideas. every once in a while, I'll think up some random page, and build it. but I have no content to put up on these pages - I just think up the basic look and feel of it. So I went and made my page a starting point to go look at all my other pages. I also built a page called ++caffeine+based+life+form++, which is kind of a weblog, too. odd, huh? 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2001</date>
<post>

    
        Wanted   Wanted: One brave American willing to hijack a plane in afghanistan, while the plane is full of afghan people, and crash it into something important in afghanistan. the trouble will be finding in afghanistan worth crashing a plane into. I always wondered why we named our warm fluffy afghans after such a crappy hot worthless wasteland in the middle of nowhere. At least they don't keep attacking my ottoman. Stupid mongol hordes. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Wow, I must have died or something.    Seems it's been about, ohhh... (looks at watch) 6 months since I last posted. Well, I've been busy. Like, really really really busy. Doing  urlLink THIS   Yeah, Me and a friend of mine started up another site, so this one kinda fell by the wayside, whatever the hell the wayside is. Go there instead. 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Black Gold     So I never liked beer, but for some reason, I really like Stout. wait - I like STOUT. STOUT kinda kicks you in the mouth. tastes like burnt chocolate and nuts.   urlLink Guinness  makes the best and most popular STOUT, but this leads me to a question: What the hell is it with liquor/beer companies having webpages loaded with flash and music?  urlLink Stolichnaya ,  urlLink beefeater ,  urlLink Kahlua ,  urlLink Budweiser ... you get the picture. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Back From The Dead     Straight out tha casket - risen'  up  open up ya eyes - can't ya see me?  what the fuck is this madness?  pick up my bones  erase my name from off the tombstone  alive and kickin' - breathin' the air  call out my name punk and I'll be there  no question  my suggestion to the action  caught smack dab in the middle of the blastin  messin wit me - ya messin wit da best  BLAU! ya takin' two shots to ya chest.    Cuz' I'm back from the dead.             -"back from the dead" - house of pain.   
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Twinkies!   Ok, so I've only just now decided to revive this blogger. Yeah, I have  urlLink That Other Weblog Thing , but that has a more formal feel. I only post there if I really have something to say, or if I put up a new gallery or the like. This blogger was always for whatever was on my mind. Stupid random links, any random thought or idea I had, anything about monkeys... so I figure, if you want to see my creative-writing-class self, or my art and photography galleries, go to  urlLink Spauldonet . If you want to know what color my last shit was, or what I'm gonna do with all these ostriches, read this. On that note - it's RANDOM LINK TIME!!!!!! YAY!!!!!   urlLink Errorwear   Embrace your computer problems.They have t-shirts with various computer and web errors on them. They have THREE blue screen of death shirts. 3. not just the old skool win9x blue screen of cdr101 - but the nt debug screen (the *real* bsod - the one you only see when your shit ain't coming back.) and the win2000 "friendly" bsod. the one that says "all your base are belong to us. sorry, man.". I want a shirt with "the current drive is no longer valid" on it...   urlLink Dan's Data    I have become a daily reader of this site. This is a guy in Australia who reviews computer hardware, mostly, but he also has a few other hobbies, like remote controlled tanks and sparkler bombs... His writing style is hilarious, and he likes taking things apart to see what's in 'em. I used to do that, but my mom stopped letting me have pets.   urlLink peep Delta Airlines, beeyatch.   It's an airline commercial, in ebonics, with the ebonics done by a white ad-guy. funny shit. It's in flash, so if you can't view flash.... well, if you honestly can't view flash,  it's time to give up the ship. the internet holds no promise for you. Go read a book.  Well, that about clears it up. By the by, my last one was a rich chocolate brown, and kinda spongey. You know, those ones that are all sticky and take forever to clean up? Well, this was one of those. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2002</date>
<post>

    
        w00t!      I got some new hardware! yay! my poor old k6-2 500 recently got a massive hardware upgrade. I figured, I can't tell enough people, so I'll put it here. I had a 40 gig hard drive, and it was full (like, less than 100 megs free, with no games or anything installed) thanks to my gloriously fast cable internet. I bought an 80 gig drive to bring my total giggage up to 120, allowing me to pirate software with wild abandon (come get me, BSA biatches!). and I got a 16x dvd and a 32X12X48 cdrw and another 128 meg stick of ram (bringing me up to 320 megs). So my ide bus is full up, no room at the inn, standing room only... then my system sat for a while, with me hammering on the poor 80 gig, until a couple days ago. a couple days ago I got: a GeForce 4 MX 440, some (cheap) flat panel speakers with a subwoofer, and a compact flash card reader. I got the reader because I was tired of having to plug in my damned camera and drain the batteries while I waited umpteen minutes to get all my random pictures of spots on the ground on disk. This reader acts as a removeable drive (drive J:, in my case) and I can just pop in mr. flash card and drag the aforementioned pictures onto the disk. I also got another 64 meg compact flash card, so I can have twice as many pictures of spots on the ground. Next on the list is the cpu, but thsi will be a bit pricey, as I want to upgrade to an athlon xp, and I'll have to buy the cpu, motherboard, and some ddr ram before I can run it. but oh well, I have time.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Quck "before work" edition   So I went out and bought that sixer of honey weiss, and I also got a bottle of benedictine, because that was the first place I saw that carried it. benedictine is a sweet french herbal liqueuer, made from - well, that's just it - the recipe is secret. but it's pretty good. I only had a sip, because I have to be at work in like 20 minutes and this stuff is 80 proof, but I did have me a honey weiss... I also plan on buying a new bed when I get a day off. The queen size I sleep on now, well, I've slept on it for upwards of 7 years now, and my mom gave it to me when she bought a new one anyway, so it's getting kinda old and wore out. plus it's huge. I wanna go out and buy me a full, mostly because my roomates have a full size box spring I can use.  Well, with benedictine, that narrows my "liquor I gotta try" list down to advocat (dutch egg and cream liqueuer), aquavit (danish vodka flavored with carroway), and absinthe. well, not absinthe because it's illegal here, but maybe absente or something designed to taste like absinthe without having wormwood in it. In any case, I gotta go. Outtie like a belly button, G. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Drugs are good, mmkay?   So  urlLink Here's something.  It's a page on the white house site that shows the different slang terms for drugs. Hilarious. Even funnier, The boys at Brunching shuttlecocks have made  urlLink This page , which translatestext on a webpage to 'drug slang'. given the fairly large database, this makes for a lot of laughs.   On another note:  urlLink Go here , enter your (over 21) age, go to the "taproom" area, click on "honey weiss", and you'll be face to face with my new best friend. Leinenkugel's Honey Weiss is the most amazing beer. light and refreshing without tasting like all the other crap american beers. and it is a bit sweet, but just a bit. I found this at a local liquor store, bought a bottle just because honey in beer sounded cool, and I'm gonna go buy me a 6 pack tomorrow morning.  Of course, I still like stout, and  urlLink This one  is my favorite so far. Uh.. I don't have anything else to say, so like, bye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Now THIS is irritating.   See, I work a lot, and I planned to use my two days off to go out and take me some pictures. I had it all planned out: I had gatorade and water so I didn't dehydrate in the hot sun, I had my batteries charged up, I got my cam back from sar, along with his mutated telescope tripod, I was *ready*. and I wake up today - and it's raining. Even if it quits raining, it'll be all muddy out there, and it's going to be overcast all day, which will make all my pics look sad and crappy. Whee. In other news:  urlLink Check this out.  They don't sell a weather machine, tho, so screw 'em. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Freaky link   Like,  urlLink Yikes.  I don't know what the hell is going on there. I'm really weirded out. I bought a bed, tho... Turns out I don't have a queen. I have a full. So I go to the bed store, buy a full size mattress, get it home, realize it's the same size as my old bed, smack my forehead and say DOH! real loud, then go back to the mattress store and trade it in for a twin. then I go to walmart and use the difference to buy a sheet set and a new pillow. One thing: Bedclothes for twin beds are fucking cheap. I spent like 15 bucks on a sheet set and a pillow. the same stuff for a queen size would be 25-30... I'm starting to like this little bed. I don't have a box spring, tho, so I'll have to get that, and a frame, with my next paycheck. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2002</date>
<post>

    
        OHMYGODTHEYUPDATEDTHEPAGEANDIWASLIKEWHEEEE!!!!   So,  urlLink Threebrain  added some new 'rock videos' to their list of weird shit. they are the freaks behind the whole WHEEEEE!!! video. well, now they have a video that apple nipple monkey has this one apple nipple monkey line in the apple nipple monkey chorus that apple nipple monkey kinda gets into your apple nipple monkey brain and makes you all apple nipple monkey freaked out. I'll leave you to discover what apple nipple monkey line in the apple nipple monkey chorus I'm apple nipple monkey talking about. They also have their own take on the A-B-C thing, as in 'A is for AHHH!!!', which they present as a kid's video, because the other video has some apple nipple monkey cursewords in it. go lookee. And while you're there, spend the rest of your mortal life going thru the daily archives. I'll list a couple of my personal favorites here:  urlLink Ode to butter.   urlLink Stop it, kitty.   urlLink Valentine's day song, with hunger-induced psychosis.   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2002</date>
<post>

    
        IS THERE PORNOGRAPHY ON YOUR COMPUTER?    Yes. now leave me alone. I am really starting to despise these spams and popups telling me how  every  computer saves  every  picture from  every  website I visit. I can empty my own damn cache, and I can clear my own damned temp files. And besides, I  know  there is pornography on my computer, because I put it there. I explicitly searched out and saved hot sweaty teen anal asian britney spears lesbian alanis morrisette teen naked boob boobs breast sex teen lesbian buick sex teen files onto my computer, and I intend to keep them. On the same note, why do they only concentrate on porn? What if I was visiting sites detailing how to build a large explosive device with which I would assassinate my local authority figure? What if I was visiting sites about how to make the perfect souffle, and I didn't want my football playing roomate to see, lest he pound me into a pinkish paste? Eh. Eh, the official statement of the apathetic. That's me: A Shining Model of Apathy. I care a lot, I really really do. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Well now, THIS sucks.   Ok so, I went and upgraded my computer. Took the big step. Went from a k6-2 500 with 320 megs of lowly sdram to a anthlon xp 2000+ with 256 megs of asskicking ddr ram. this damned thing runs like a scalded dog. only problem is: it runs like a scalded dog on the freeway, meaning it dies a lot. I have no idea why, but this thing has been flakier than raisin bran since I put it together. it reboots whenever it feels the need, it gives me many wonderful and exciting blue screens of death. ("page fault in nonpaged area, wtf is that supposed to mean?"), and it isn't heat related, or stupid software related, or even voltage related. I run a little monitor program, and the thing can be running super cool with stable voltage, and I'll go to open a window or something and *poof* - reboot. to add insult to injury, when it does the castors-up macarena, I don't have mouse or keyboard when I get back into windows. no idea why. I just don't. although, resetting during post after a random reboot fixes it. I'm stumped. so, I'm going to dig up my old video card when I get a chance and see if it's my video card. It might be the video card. All, well, most of the lockups and reboots seem to hinge on me doing something that involves more video muscle than normal, and the video card has been flaky since day one, when it would sometimes power down the video for no reason at all.   Although.... daaaaaaaaamn gta3 runs good on this thing. until it reboots. and warcraft 3 runs smoov as silk with all the options on high. so I'm really happy with it when I don't want to chuck it out in the freeway... 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Ok, so this sucks worse.   So like, I upgraded, had a badass system, had bugs. OK. I can deal with this - I'll just figure out what the problem is and replace it. I thought it was the video card, so I swapped it for my old tnt2, and I still have bugs. not as many bugs, but still, the system is pretty much unusable. On top of this, I just smoked my second power supply. the one I had was about a year old, and it's a generic 300 watter, so I figure, Ok, it's dead - it happens. I do, afterall, have 2 optical drives and 2 hard drives on top of my power hungry cpu and video card. So I replace it, fine. Power supply is good, system is still buggy, and I'm suspecting the motherboard at this point. Last night, the thing rebootson me, and won't get past post. it keeps power cycling... Power supply number 2 down the drain. Now I have a badass system sitting in the garage until I can buy a new power supply and replace that damn  motherboard. I'm typing this, btw, on my roomate's computer. so, yeah, grrr. 
    
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Sucking, Not sucking,  Neon   Yeah, so I buy this new case. baaaaaaadass case. big blue antec badboy with a huge side window and an enermax power supply. ( urlLink This case,  with  urlLink This side window ) I also got a blue neo tube for it, so i could have a blue glow coming out of my blue case so I could showcase the dandruff swap meet (lots of flakes). Well, I'll be damned if the thing didn't turn into a rock solid asskicking number crunching godbox. not a sign of flakiness, no weird errors or blue screens or reboots. Schweet. So now it looks killer AND runs stable. and oh yeah, my bud  urlLink Sar  spent like 2 hours routing all the various cables around in the case so you can hardly see any, and that's a big deal in a case with 3 case fans and 4 ide devices and a neon tube and a power supply with like 40 feet of wire hanging off it. Plus the yellow wire ties glow real bright in under the neon, which makes me wanna go buy some uv-reactive paint from the store and do the whole inside of the case.  One problem, tho. I put my new video card (the geforce 4) back in, ran a couple things, and when I ran gta3 (strictly for testing purposes... *cough*) I went to shot a gangsta with my uzi (because gangs are just wrong) and got a bluescreen. One I know well. "KMODE_EXCEPTION_NOT_HANDLED" in ntdisp.dll hmm. this is disconcerting. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Hey   Somebody buy me  urlLink THIS.  I've decided I want to have an lcd monitor in portrait mode next to my main monitor. If you've never done portrait mode, you don't know what you're missing. I had three webpages *and* a chat window open, and I could use all three without resizing or shuffling windows. My (CRT) monitor doesn't like sitting on it's side, tho... Honestly, somebody buy me that. Send me mail at KILLS_SPAM_DEADeclipseATSYMBOLspauldonetPERIODcom, and I'll like, be your friend. I'll make you some graphics or like, wax your dog, or something. seriously. Also, you could buy me  urlLink THIS  fantastic webcam. It costs less than the monitor, even, so you can be my friend or get an honest opinion of your new haircut for less money. maaaaaaaan, go look at that webcam. It has pivot and tilt ability, controllable by the viewer, and it moves quick. Check out the live demo and look around the office. I set it to track and it followed this dude with a ponytail around his cubical. badass. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Holy Crapamoli   In 2 days, this blogger will be 2 years old. Jeez, I feel old now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
        It's the real thing   Coca-Cola comes in: 8 oz cans, 12 oz cans, 10 oz bottles, 12 oz bottles, 17.5 oz bottles, 20 oz bottles, 1 liter bottles, 2 liter bottles, and 3 liter bottles, with multipacks of 6, 12, 24, and 6 17.5 oz bottles. and I bet you can still get the 16 oz bottles... And don't forget the fountain. Man, they need to calm down. I just drank one of those 8 oz cans, and all I gotta say is "why?" It's nearly half of a 12 oz can, and costs more, due to the low volume nature of it. Nevermind, I'm too tired to make any sense. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Oops.   I keep forgetting to list the music I'm listening to. I wasn't actually listening to any music when I posted just now, but I fired up 'purity' by slipknot just now, so I guess that counts. Although, I will tel you what song just started playing in my cruel cruel internal jukebox...   current music in my head:   urlLink michael mcdonald 'I keep forgetting'  There, now it'll be in your head, too. Hahahahaha. By the way, the music from this song was used in a more recent song: 'regulators' by nate dogg and warren g. they managed to make it sound like some kind of tough guy music, rather than the lame crapfest it is now. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Quick link    urlLink THESE THINGS  kick ass. It's a radio controlled car, about the size of a standard hot-wheels. Seriously tiny. And it's full-function, meaning you can go foreward and backward, and turn left and right while going foreward or backward. it takes like 45 seconds for mine to charge, and I can run it for 5-10 minutes. I've driven mine around on a table at the booth in the restaurant I was at. I drove it on my desk, and I mean actually drove it around, like around obstacles and stuff. it's tiny, manuverable, and cheap (mine was less than 20 bucks), and oh yeah, you can mod the hell out of them. the link I gave you links to pages where people added a 2nd battery, custom wheels, new bodies, all kinds of things. Check it out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        What's a ute?    I've been playing a lot of Unreal Tournament 2003, since I recently built das uber computer,  urlLink Pictured here.  (and yes, the window makes it faster) I played the leaked playable alpha craptastic thing, and it pretty much sucked. Then i played the demo, and it was great, but y'know, I wanted more. So I bought it, and man, I'm impressed. Just like when the first Unreal Tournament came out, this game has awesome and diverse maps with great flow, great weapons, great music, and it's just all around great. And now it even has interesting characters. Mine's a demon, I think. He's a nasty fellow, always talking about eating souls and crushing the weak, but he's all spiky, and spiky means cool. uh, Anyway, go buy this game. It's like, great. I'd be a good game reviewer (This game is great! This game is crap!)    current music:  Some system of a down. it was "Chop Suey!" while typing most of this, and now it's "know", off their first album. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Hello?   The damned phone has rang like 77 times since I woke up. I don't answer it, or even bother looking at the caller id, because 99% of the calls we get here are for my roomate's business. he sells and repairs computers. so like, 76 of those calls are more than likely for him, and the other one isn't for me anyway. But this is slowly making me crazy. I can hear the phone, I know it's ringing, and I get that "go get the phone" urge we all get when a phone rings. But I've got no reason to answer it, and if i did, I'd wind up with a stack of messages to pass on, so to hell with that. It's just making me crazy, is all. CRAZY, I TELLS YA!    current music:  Uh, it's called "ping pong" and it's by spacetime continuum. Part of a mp3 downloading burst I had a while back where I got like, all the techno I could find. I'ma change it to some rock or something when this song's over, tho.  
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        cockbite   Also, I'd like to mention that this one guy who used to work with me now works at radio shack.  He was what you call actively lazy. He worked hard at avoiding work, often working  harder than he would have if he had just done what he was supposed to. man, that was confusing... Here, look at the monkey,  Look at the monkey! 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Radio Shack Belgium: You've got questions, We've got Antwerp.   So right now I'm using a blogger client. I've made every single everloving post to this thing using the web interface for blogger.com. Granted, that interface is neat, and it works quite well, but this program (blogBuddy, available  urlLink HERE ) is actually a window program that lets me just post whenever. It somehow manages to make blogger *more* convienient. This post is mostly just to check out the functionality of said program, and because that radio shack thing popped in my head. That makes like 3 or 4 I've had on here. Oh yeah, I also want to do something new. I saw how livejournal has a 'current music' thing, but you gotta pay for livejournal, or be invited to it, so fuck that. Besides, I've been at this for over 2 years now, I ain't moving.   current music:  Moby - "Honey", although my whole playlist is half moby and half daft punk, and I had slipknot's "(sic)" in between, which just scared me half to death after hearing a bunch of daft punk. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Good God, man, I just want the player!   So, I download a .rm file of some weird radio controlled car. The car has another, smaller car that can drive in and out of the ass end of the larger one. The site offers a video of this. So I download, and discover I have not yet installed a player for real media files. I bring up real.com, and that one vein in my forehead bulges out, and I start developing a headache, because I know I'm going to be here a while. See, real.com likes to rearrange their site every once in a while, and while they do offer a free player, they make absolutely  ZERO  mention of it  ANYWHERE  and their  ENTIRE FUCKING WEBSITE . You have to go pretend like you're going ot pay them 20 bucks for the plus player, and there, in a low-contrast colored button, about the size of an inch of pencil, is the button for the *shhhhh*..... (whispers)  free  player. Of course, clicking on the *shhhhh* (whispers again)  free  player leads you to a page showing you  how great the 20 dollar one is, and off to the right is this (much smaller) pane saying you can get this other player with a lot less features that isn't anywhere near as good as our other player but it's free so download that one if you want to be dissapointed by a crappy player. And of course, the download is managed by a stupid download manager that nobody uses, but you still have to use it at least to get the real player. Oh yeah, and the free player has big ads everywhere, and an "important announcement" bar that pops up once in a while, regardless of whether you told it to show or not, advertising the 20 dollar player....   You know what I want? I want to play that .rm file. that's it. I want to be able to play real media files. I don't want it to manage my mp3s or play my cds or burn cds or act as a browser or play any movie type besides real, and I don't want to create or edit real media files. I want to play them. period. Where's *that* player? Please, for the love of god, somebody write a  
    
    
</post>

<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        The Interna-....fuck it.   Yeah, so I called the truck guy about the international to see if I could work out a payment plan. somebody put a down payment on it today. so fuck. I don't really want to talk about it anymore. In any case, I know that if I ever start a band, i'm gonna call it The Failures. Although, as a quick search just turned up, there are already a couple bands named the Failures, as if I care.    Stuck In My Head:  Oh, man... I don't even know if I should put this one up. This is one of those songs that *WILL* get into your head, just by seeing the fucking title, and it will never leave, Ever. Ever.  urlLink "Iko Iko" by the Belle Stars.  Yeah, you know, from Rain Man... 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        The International Quest: Day Three    So, I got ahold of Mark, the truck guy, and he said the truck runs, sort of. The motor needs rewired, it had a fire or something under the hood. Speaking of the hood, he has it in his workshop. The truck was driven to belize and back 2 years ago (Belize being just north of fucking panama. we're talking driving to south fucking america... I wonder how much gas that used.) And he bought it a year ago. His plans were to fix it up and possibly show it, but he can't afford it with his house payments. So I'm in like Flynn, or so I thought, until I called my mom. She says No, she won't cosign for this $2500 truck, even tho she was going to cosign for a $5500 car, and already said she'd most likely cosign for this one. My only chance now is to hope the guy will let me pay it out with him. I might turn to other family members and see if they'll cosign. Jeebus, I hate this - You can't get good credit without already having it, it seems. I really hope I can get this truck. I'm so in love with it, I talk about it like it's my girlfriend, always telling people what it looks like, where it's been, how great it is, what a pretty shade of blue it's paint is... By The Way, the truck is supposed to look generally like  urlLink These do , but those are 1971s - 2 years younger than mine. She's aged gracefully. I never thought I'd love an older woman.    
    
    
</post>

<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        The International Quest, Day 2    I think calling it 'The International Quest' sounds better than 'Trying To Buy A Car', and it *is* an International... In any case, I called my financial backer (mother) and she's gonna cosign for the loan I'll need... But.... I couldn't get ahold of the guy to see what's up with the truck. His name is Mark. I know that much, 'cuz he said it on his voice mail.    Stuck In My Head:   This is a bad one -  urlLink 'Witch Doctor' by David Seville.  Yeah, you know, the one with the chipmunk voice singing ooo eee ooo aa aa ting tang walla walla bing bang.... 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        It was THIIIIIIIIIIIIS Big    So, I'm out taking pictures today, and I come across  urlLink This.  I want. it's a 1969 International Travelall 1200. Essntially, this behemoth is a Scout, with the Travelall package from a company that worked with International. The Travelall package is mostly body stuff, but Stageway coachbuilders took it and made it into a freakshow. It's for sale, for 2500 bucks, and tomorrow I'ma go try to get it. Yay. I'll post here either way. That thing, by the way, has 5 bench seats, with room enough in the back area for 2 more. It's a biggun. 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        HOT NEW FEATURE! NOW WITH PECANS!    yeah, so nevermind the title. I decided to add yet another new nifty thingy to my weblog posts: Stuck In My Head. I'll have the current music I'm listening to, and if some random song gets stuck in my head, I'll go download it and link to it here. Teeheehee. Yes, I am fully aware that this violates copyright laws, but I don't actually care. I looked around, I did, honestly, for my "caring about those worthless idiotic artist-denying record-company-fatcat-empowering cashcow copyright laws" gland, but it seems it's all withered up and dried out. Now, I'm not one of those people who has vowed to never ever buy another game or movie or cd again as some kind of protest - I've spent over a hundred bucks on stuff like that in the last couple weeks. but if I want the theme from 'I dream of Jeannie' I'm by god not going to go out and buy some tv themes cd. In any case, here ya go- I've already done it, but now it's official and stuff:   current music:  bile's cover of 'My Generation', which is highly recommended by like, me, and I'm the authority on me, so go get it.   Stuck In My Head:  It's  urlLink The theme from 'I dream of Jeannie' , and  urlLink 'Sunglasses at Night' by Corey Hart . Yeah, my internal jukebox is a sick fuck. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        I'M FULL OF TINIER MEN!    Serioiusly. I am.   current music:  Well, it was "hungry hungry hippos" by anal cunt, which is this fucking bizarre thrash cover of, you guessed it, the hungry hungry hippos song, but that song is 18 seconds long, and "Ccec" by autechre came on after that. Autechre (probably pronounced Aw-teck-er, but this is a subject of some debate) are fucking genius. "Ccec" is a strange song, lots of odd disjointed beats and samples, with the main instrument being a rapper's voice, chopped up into unrecognizable segments, and apparently randomized. they make some of the most cerebral techno I've heard. you can't just sit back and let autechre play in the background, you have to take it in, intently listen to it. You really oughta at least treat yourself to the mp3's of their "peel sessions" stuff. I bought both the peel sessions cd's. 
    
    
</post>

<date>30,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        My name is Legion, for we are many...   You know who I hate? I toss around that term a lot, but there are few that I truly and unabashedly hate - and among those few, fewer still warrant my hate forever and ever for all time with no saving roll, no 'get out of jail free' card. One group who holds a special place in my hate list, a placecard on the table of hatred, where my hatred is served in heaping piles, one group who has priority access to reserved parking spots in my parking garage of hatred - door-to-door preachers. there's no other way to describe them, really. Those people, generally mormons or witnesses, who feel the need to go door-to-door to tell people how great whatever religion they subscribe to is, and they always come at the most inopportune time, and they *always* take up a few minutes of your time, even if you don't have it to spare, and you'd rather boil them in oil and step on their puppies and piss on their mothers anyway. I hate these people. They beg my insolence. They dare to opine to me? To ask that I change my views and fundaments?  They hawk religion, and I will have none of it. They are deserving of nothing more than pure contempt, and they will get nothing but. Odious fools. One thing that should work, but doesn't, is telling them "We worship in our own way". That clearly tells them that No Sir, you will have none of what they are selling, and you already have plenty anyway, so please go away, preferably back to your own home, and stay there. I went to the store the other day, and there were young teens outside, running back and forth to people, telling them how cool god is. they came to me, and one girl asked if I personally had given any thought to accepting jesus christ as my personal savior and target of multiple blasphemous remarks when I stub my toe, and I told them "I am agnostic" and got that look you get from a a deer as you swerve to avoid turning it into deer jelly. This girl was attempting to sell me a vacuum without knowing what a broom was. I had to explain the precepts of  urlLink agnosticism  to someone who wanted me to convert to her religion. It took me some time to get her to understand that there is no converting someone who doesn't believe in religion. I don't know, I can't know, and I don't want to know. When I die, I'll find out what happens when you die - before then, I don't care.  As a side note, the title is a little gem from the bible. it's a quote from a man who is possessed by a legion of demons, and jesus asks the man his name, and that is his answer. The demons then beg jesus' mercy, and he allows them to go into a huge herd of pigs, which subsequently throw themselves into the ocean. I plan to use this line the next time somebody comes to my door asking if I know how cool god is. I wanna see if I can make them run. some blood and fire wouldn't hurt the effect, tho.    current music:  It was "albuquerque" by weird al yankovic, then "knfe prty" by deftones, then "the downward spiral" by nine inch nails, then "stolen holiday" from the sifl & olly show, which aired on mtv for 2 seasons, and starred sock puppets. it took a while to type this one. Btw, I spelled albuquerque from memory. HAHAHA! That's like the backflip of spelling; either you can do it, or you look stupid because you are too proud to admit you can't. I still checked to see if I got it right. I don't wanna look stupid.   
    
    
</post>

<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
        I wanna move to Iceland.    urlLink Purty.   I mean, yeah, sure, there are some problems with moving to Iceland. I don't speak icelandic, I can't pronounce any of the city names, I can't spell Reykjavik without looking for the name somewhere, and half the country lives there. It never really gets dark, as such, seeing as how Iceland is so close to the artic circle. Oh yeah, there's that little niggle: iceland is close to the artic circle. Let's see... I don't know much else about Iceland, I'm not keen on sheep, and oh yeah, I don't have enough money to even go visit there, much less move, and I have no way of making money once I do get there. I still wanna move to Iceland, tho.    current music:  "third eye" by tool. The live version from 'salival' prying open my third eye. prying open my third eye. prying open my third eye. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
        MAKE IT STOP!!!!!   Mr. Internal Jukebox has been on overdrive today. I'd like to explain something about my internal jukebox: For those of you who aren't cursed with one, an internal jukebox is your memory of every song you've ever heard. The mind, being a sick and perverse thing, pulls out songs you forgot about, with good reason, long ago, and plays them over and over. These songs aren't *always* songs you hate, or love, they seem to be pretty random, although mine can be triggered by various things. In any case, once a song gets going, it'll be with you for a while. There is no escape. Some people can avert it by listening to music. I am not so lucky. I need to hear the song itself, or sometimes I can wait it out. This is part of the reason why I started the "stuck in my head" thing. I also had a thought today - I can map out what my internal jukebox calls forth over time and see how it works. There has been a lot of 80's pop so far. Let's get on with it:  stuck in my head: Ok, so these songs all sorta started swirling around in my head today, all at once. And now you can have them, I don't want them anymore. First up to bat is  urlLink "Careless Whisper" by Wham!  So, Wham! isn't exactly my idea of a good band, or a band at all, and this sickly lost love ballad is sappy, even for the band who did "wake me up before you go-go" But it's here, nonetheless. Next up is  urlLink "Jeremiah Peabody's Polyunsaturated Quick Dissolving Fast Acting Pleasant Tasting Green and Purple Pills" (gasps for air) by Ray Stevens  I actually rather like this song, although the title is a tad much. Winner of the "First Stuck In My Head Song I Didn't Have To Go Download, Since I Already Had It" Award goes to  urlLink "Pick A Bale Of Cotton" by Leadbelly  Although I'm not sure why I had it to begin with. And somehow, *TWO* songs by Sade played in my head. First it was  urlLink "Smooth Operator" , Then that swapped out with  urlLink "Sweetest Taboo"  And I just abhor both songs, and Sade in general. As a side: I completely and totally refuse to pronounce Sade's name like she would have me. See, Sade wants people to pronounce it "Shar-day", and most of her fans do. I will never. If I became her greatest fan, and one day she came to my house offering me hot oily twisted kinky monkey love if only I would say "shar-day" once, I'd say, "No thanks, SADE" I'll pronounce it Like the marquis du sade, I'll say "saa-day" or "sayd" (Like "say" with a d on it) but If she wants me to pronounce it "shar-day, She had better put an R in there somewhere. An H wouldn't hurt, either. 
    
    
</post>

<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
        NOOOOOOOO!!!!!!!   Uh, this whole post is for the "stuck in my head" thing. I'll say something cool, tho, or something. um. Oh, hey! my computer (the one with the speed hole, pictured  urlLink HERE ) died. The motherboard, which has been the source of my problems from day one, keeled over and won't power up. good riddance. I now get to try to wrangle a new one out of the asian folks I bought it from. yay.   current music:  '(sic)' by slipknot. I listen to that one a lot, and so should you. well, if you are so inclined. Also "the song remains insane" by soulfly, which is AHAHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH CRAZZZZZYYY!!!!!!!!!! It starts off with a blazing fast cover of some song by a brazilian band, then a cover of a sepultura song (which the lead singer of soulfly used to be the lead singer of), then some hardcore thrash stuff. quite entertaining.   stuck in my head:  What you shouldn't listen to, more than likely, is  urlLink 'Goody Two Shoes' by Adam Ant  Don't drink, don't smoke, what do you do? I got this stuck in my head because my friend spauldo was talking about another friend, named adam, and said "Adam is adamant". I took this out of context and iwent "Adam is Adam Ant? Cool." Now, I see the error of my ways, as this fucking song keeps playing in my head. damnit. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
        HEY!   I built a new computer. See, I had the castoff parts of my old k6-2 500 from when I built the 2000+ (which has a dead motherboard), and I took those parts (case and stuff) and bought a new motherboard a cpu. Now I have a duron 1.2 with 256 megs of ram, and its own 8 gig hard drive, but I currently have the 40 and 80 giggers in there until I get vertex (the 2000+) built again. This new system, as well, has an ati all-in-wonder radeon 7500. the all in wonder series has always been some of the coolest video cards out there, and the new radeon ones add 3d gaming power to the lineup. this card does video capture, has a tv tuner, is clustered with all manner of inputs and outputs, and has an rf remote control. I watched tv all day today. on my pc. Tv on my PC! That's wild!   current music:  I'm getting the new stuff from Audioslave. Audioslave is rage against the machine, minus zach de la rocha, minus all the anger at the establishment, plus chris cornell, lather, rinse, repeat. Sounds very much like "the new soundgarden record" to me, but it's still cool. I just want zach de la rocha to get back to yelling about stuff. he's cool. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
        RANDOM LINK TIME!!!! WHEEEE!!!!   Yeah, so here's some links to stuff I've been looking at lately. Enjoy.   urlLink Video Rocketry   Some very cool footage from video camera (one of those x-10 wireless jobbers) mounted in the body of a model rocket. Badass.  urlLink Mindless Self Indulgence   An incredibly freaky band. A mixture of punk, hip-hop, techno, and anything else they can fit inside a 2 minute frenzy of a song full of violent time-shifts and vocals rapidly switching from growls to falsetto to rapping.  urlLink Artsy computer photography.   Like, pictures of old computers and the people operating them. neat stuff.  urlLink Penny Arcade   I'm surprised I didn't start reading this before now. An online comic about gaming. Also, it's hilarious.   current music:  "Scalped" by dick dale. Yes, the guy who plays that surfer music, and whos "misirlou" is the main theme of 'pulp fiction' I sorta randomly found "Misirlou" while looking for other stuff, and I ended up grabbing abunch of his stuff.   stuck in my head:  So, here's a thing: My internal jukebox went deep for this one, so deep that I can't find the song. It's "whatupwitu" by Eddie Murphy. Yes, he sings. Remember "Party all the time"? Eddie. Well, "whatsupwitu" has michael jackson in it, and it was made into a video, but it sucks so bad that nobody bothered to like, keep it around. I've only heard it like twice (Hell, Eddie's probably heard it less than a dozen times, and he sang the fucker.) But it's in my head, nonetheless. And it's been there for like 4 days, on and off, while I've been looking for it.   
    
    
</post>

<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
        Bacon Burger Dog   Guh. I just had 2 bacon burger dogs. I will now die.   (dies)  Ok, better now. A Bacon Burger Dog, or BBD - no, not BBD, because that makes me think of bel biv devoe... anyway, it's a hotdog, with cheese in it, wrapped in ground beef, then in bacon, then you grill it. sounds good, no?    current music:  Some electronica from deep in the genre. stuff you've never heard. stuff by groups you've never heard of formed from *other* groups you've never heard of. Specifically, I'm getting a lot of stuff by Photek, and trying to get some stuff by Mu-ziq (it's the little U symbol that means "Mu" in the greek alphabet, but I don't know how to make it and don't feel like looking), and "Expert Knob Twiddlers" by Mike and Rich, which is Muziq and the Aphex Twin (Mike Parradinas and Richard D James). It's mostly IDM (Intelligent dance music). I seem to be listening to a lot of IDM these days.   stuck in my head:  Well. I- I uh... It's just that - (sigh).... Well.... It's  urlLink The Theme From Popeye.  There, I've said it. I had the damn popeye song stuck in my head. I also have, for reasons unknown,  urlLink "The Neutron Dance" by The Pointer Sisters.  More 80's weirdness. Somebody kill me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
        movin on up. well, east, anyway.   So yes, I did get fired. I had worked there for like a year and a half. that really sucks. a lot.  but.  We're moving. To Illinois. Essentially, the only things keeping me here were my family and my job. I had a good stable job, it paid decent. my family and friends were all around here. Now, tho... I lost my job, my mother and step father are moving to phoenix, and most of my friends will live in Illinois as of monday... So I'm moving with them. Going to a little (still bigger than here) town outside of East St. Louis, which is across the mississippi from St. Louis proper. We're all (5 adults, 2 kids) going to be living in a 2 bedroom house for right now, until we get enough money rounded up to get moved into our own houses. My next post will most likely be made from the great state of Illinoise. I gotta bring my skull. I have this plastic skull with a canadian flag sticker on the forehead - upside down and burned. they'll love that in Illinois.   current music:   "Violent and Funky" by Infectious Grooves. It's.. Funk, Rock, god knows what else... Odd. and the bassline is badass. Infectious Grooves is a side project of a couple guys from Suicidal Tendencies, by the way. Like you know who any of these people are... 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
        the good, the bad, and the ugly. well, the bad and ugly, anyway.    So, news. I was at work friday night, finishing up my paperwork so I could go home, and a couple cops showed up. Seems I sold a 6 pack of beer to a minor. It was a sting, I got stung. I did stop a minor from buying beer that day, too. someone who used to work there came up trying to buy a 12 pack, and he's like 20. he was trying to fool this new girl. in any case, I got a ticket, and I'll probably get fired. My boss said I'm suspended until his boss gets back in town monday, and they'll pass judgement then. Of course, the Big Boss in charge of the company has it in for me, so I'll most likely get fired. I've had this job for a year and a half. I've never done anything for that long. The job market here is dismal, at best. I don't know what I'm going to do...  Other news. I bought a webcam and a 21" monitor. before I learned that I'd most likely be fired. the webcam was cheap cheap - 15 bucks cheap. the monitor not so much. I paid 249 bucks for a dell 21" trinitron-tubed monster. The monitor works great, and I've finally climbed up the tallest mountain and yelled to the heavens: " I own a monitor that can run at 2048X1536!! Suck it down!! " 2048x1536 is the resolution of the gods. to put it in perspective, set your (pathetic) monitor to 1024X768. now imagine 4 of those desktops, in a square, on one monitor. My monitor can do that. Yes, I've developed a superiority complex because of it, but c'mon - I mean, it's 21 inches!  Oh yeah, I mentioned the webcam, so  urlLink Go look.  I rn it the whole time I'm awake, but it just points to where I sit in front of the computer (with the monitor that's bigger than yours), so it isn't exactly tension-filled. I will end up doing weird things with it.. I mean, I always do that, it's kinda my thing.   current music:  The soundtrack for "requiem for a dream". I cannot describe the beauty of this album. it's a cello quartet and an electronic musician creating the soundtrack of a movie about heroin addiction. I was floored the first time I heard it. I still haven't bought the album, mostly because I can't find it where I shop for cd's. I do, however, have the mp3 (one mp3, the whole album. this album deserves to be listened to all at once) and I listen to it a lot. I highly recommend it. at least get the mp3 to experience it once. 
    
    
</post>

<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
        The news of my death has been pretty much spot on.   I am posting from the great state of Illinois. whee. I live in Spauldo's basement, which is cool. Not really a whole lot to say, really, except that I think you should go check out  urlLink Homestar Runner  Strong Bad is cool.     Current Music:  "House of the rising sun", only it's the live version by oysterhead. Oysterhead being les from primus and the guy from phish.   Stuck in my head:  "Jacking for beats" by Ice Cube, of all things... I remember liking the video, tho. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink THIS  is rad. qtvr panoramas done in macro. ever wonder what it would be like to live inside a flower or a box of screws? here's your answer. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       As if I didn't hate them enough -  urlLink HERE  is a link to a discussion on something I didn't even think of the last time I bitched about real.com's abomination: during the install of realplayer, you are prompted to opt-in for some truly useless spam about shit you don't care about and wouldn't read if you sought out a site that had that particular info on it, much less if it was bulkmailed to you. The problem comes when you realize there are *twelve* checkboxes, and you can only see the first 4 - but - the last 5 are checked. So those of you who didn't bother to scroll down will be bombarded by spam that you technically signed on for. Those worthless bastards. The next step, I predict, will be to make the free realplayer totally ad-served, meaning it will play an ad (loaded off some overloaded and slow server) every time you play a file, online or not. Man, I hate real networks more every day.   current music:  "Feuer Frei" by Rammstein, which explains the german topic. I don't understand a word these guys say, but I like it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       And even if ya down with my crew - I'll jack them too. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Lord Of The Rings :The Two Towers is a pretty freakin' good movie. But. The first one (which, when acronym-ized into LOTR:FOTR, looks silly) had one "joke" at Gimli, the dwarf's expense. It was when Mr. big strong full height man chucked his stubby ass across a chasm, Gimli got all huffy and said "never toss a dwarf.". yeah, haha, really funny, let's get back to the uruk-hai, shall we?  Anyway, that one dwarf joke excuses the dwarf "in" joke this time around, when Gimli asks Mr full height to toss him across another chasm so he can whup on the aformentioned uruk-hai. "toss me" says Gimli, regretting it before he even said it. That joke is fine, because it's a mildly funny reference to the mildly funny joke in the first movie. I'd let the movie have one more dwarf joke, that they're allowed. But no, there were something like FOUR HUNDRED more dwarf jokes. I might have missed some of the 'DWARVS ARR SHORT" grafiti scrawled on an orc's helmet or something, but there are still FAR TOO MANY DWARF JOKES IN THE NEW LORD OF THE RINGS MOVIE. At this rate, the next movie will be titled "Lord Of The Rings : Gimli Is A Short Dwarf  And He's Short Ha Ha" I mean, Come now. How many times can you be funny making fun of short people? Like 7 times, that's how many. beyond that, you risk getting sued by The Altitude-Challenged Americans Network or something. There is one dwarf joke that isn't about them being short. It's about how dwarf women (also short) have beards, and can't be distinguished from the males, and are really ugly, but you'll never see them anyway, because they are barefoot and pregnant in the kitchen, where all women, and especially short ones, belong. Seriously, I don't see how they avoided being sued over that crap. It's not even funny. I am, by the way, not a dwarf. I'm 5' 8". So I'm not like, lashing out or anything.   current music:   "Creepy Crawl" by Superjoint Ritual, which is one of like 40 side projects of Phil Anselmo, lead singer of Pantera. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so I needed to install realplayer. I hate realplayer, and real networks, and everything they love. But the website has morphed again, and I was able to download the free player within 2 clicks of the front page, and the links were fairly visible. Kudos to real. I still hate them, tho. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Yeah, you know how a couple days ago I mentioned that I used illegal methods to obtain music for free, even though that music had not officially been put on sale yet? I do that a lot. But I'm sorry. Truly. Except for metallica. Fuck those guys. I used to be a fan. I bought every album from the black album to the s&m thing they did with that orchestra. The black album was the first cd I ever owned. Now, I don't mean to hurt artists when I download music. I mostly use my downloads to see if i like the album, and I do buy a lot of cd's still. But metallica, on the other hand, won't be getting my money any time soon. They stopped being artists when they started trying to get their fans arrested for downloading their music. I'll never give them another cent. Oh, I'll still get their albums, mind you - I just won't pay any money for them. If I can't download the music, I'll fucking steal the cd. Fuck metallica.   current music:  "130 steps" by Badmarsh & Shri, which is this cool sort-of electronica duo. I say sort-of because Shri is an  instrumentalist , meaning he plays actual instruments, so the music ends up sounding very organic and natural, since it is for the most part. By the by, I really enjoy these people, and I never would have heard of them if I didn't see the "dancing drums" album in mp3 format on an ftp. So there. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I have a desk. 'tis a large desk, to be sure. It resembles  urlLink THIS.  It is the vessel on which my immortal soul will travel thru eternity, because it is the only thing that will last that long. It is also heavy. hernia-inducingly, mind-numbingly heavy. it forms a gravity well, and the moon will eventually crash into it. but it shall live on. and now it lives in the basement, with me.  My former roomates (who got a nifty apartment along with the computer business they are buying) went back to our former home and retrieved all my (and their) belongings, and ferried them 500 miles up here in a 26 foot u-haul. all my furniture and whatnot was in there, including the steel monster (as I am prone to call it lately). The desk and a large couch stayed in the garage, which is at-grade with the basement (the house is built into a hill). Normally it takes 2 people to move the desk, and 3 to carry it. I moved it into the basement, at great cost to my health. I fought it for a while, learned it wouldn't go thru the door upright, so I fought it onto it's back and fought it most of the way thru the door, until I realized that I needed to remove the door, since it was also too large to fit thru the door on it's back. So I removed the door (the only part of this ordeal that was easy) and proceeded to fight the desk back thru the door until I realized that it was * still * too wide for the space. so I pulled the leg off. See in that picture I linked to, how the leg is sort of a large square looking thing? well, it's a rectangle, and it is as deep as the desk, and the feet for that side are both attached to it. and it is attached to the desk via 4 nut-backed screws, 2 of which are very nearly impossible to get at, since they live deep within the bowels of the monster. but I prevailed, and re-attached everything, and now I'm sitting here in front of the old wooden desk, because I'm too tired to move the monster over here and transfer the computer to it, even though my 21" monitor is putting this particle board hutch thru unspeakable pain.   current music:  "26 mixes for cash" by aphex twin. It's an album of his remix work done over the last 10 or so years. It's not out yet, but I  PIRATIZED&COPY;  it. I found it on a warez channel I was hanging out in on irc. that and the new megadeth double live cd, and the rage against the machine rare and live cd, and the (7 disc!) soundtrack of gta:vice city. tee-hee! 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Slashdot  has a poll up: favorite meat. and I saw a couple funny funny funny lines in the comments.  ATTN: VEGETARIANS - CALM DOWN, THEY'RE JOKES.  "I love vegetarians. Some of my favorite foods are vegetarians." "Plants aren't food - food  eats  plants!"  Also, "Cows would have a much longer life expectancy if they weren't made out of beef and leather" I voted beef, but only because there wasn't an "all of the above" option.   current music:  the Primus cover of "have a cigar", which is one of my favorite ping floyd songs. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I mentioned the escape key. I had that last post half typed, hit the escape key for some reason, and all my text vanished. fuckers.  Anyway, the thing about the swarm mentality of the A.I. in RTS games is that is leaves them open for certain tactics. In generals, the chinese have a unit that can convert enemy buildings to your side, and is camoflauged unless doing something. I'll sneak in and convert a power plant or something, to get the swarm distracted blowing it up - then I convert the headquarters and build a worker. that worker, if you can get it back to your base, is the greatest fucking thing ever. It builds the buildings it would have built for the enemy - only they are yours. You can have that bulldozer (or rebel guy) build anything the enemy can. I've had the superweapons of all three sides built in a single game. I love that. I'll build a usa airbase and amass a swarm of helicopters, then I'll build a gla war factory and have toxin tractors spraying the area around my base with poison. Another thing about the computer: it's dumb. I've had one infantry unit survive an attack on the enemy base, and used that infantry unit to blow up the enemy headquarters. For some reason the AI will sometimes ignore a single unit unless it attacks an enemy unit. I just wish these game developers would come up with at least semi-realistic AI. Now, if you'll excuse me, my rocket buggies are done building. Time to rush those fuckers.   current music:  Wow. it was "People=Shit" by slipknot, which is a musical sledgehammer, followed by a song intended to aid meditation. it's all feng-shui and shit. That's random play for ya. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I just played a round of command and conquer: generals. Good game, but I have one gripe - the A.I. is fucking ruthless. I played a skirmish round with 3 computer controlled players, who  all  had assault teams rolling across my base before I had any way to defend myself -  before I had my fucking war factory built.  All I had was a handful of infantry, and a few builders constructing my base defenses. the builders, construction sites, and infantry were trampled upon and burned. My measly infantry units were no match for the mighty chinese flame tank, which then parked in front of my goddamned headquarters and crispy fried my new builders as they came out. I lost horribly. I got  stomped on.  in 5 minutes. So I decided to get on here and complain a bit, as I am wont to do. See, there is a technique called  rushing  in real-time strategy games like generals and warcraft and such. Rushing means to build a large army of cheap units early on, then use them to mow down your unprepared enemy, who might be able to stop a tank or 2, but is helpless against a swarm of humvees. The problem with this is: the computer rushes. constantly. every time it builds a new unit, that unit make a bee line for your base. and every unit that trickles down the road attacks the same building, over and over and over, until it breaks, then the stream flows in a new direction. The only way to combat this is to build defenses immediately, quickly building up an impenetrable wall of rocket towers or whatnot so you can actually build your base up without having to constantly rebuild key structures. But. the computer has certain advantages over you that I thought I might list here:  1) The computer can see the whole map, all the time, and it knows exactly what you are doing, and where - from the first second of gameplay. I've had super-weapons hit tank convoys that took the long way around, and never got within sight of any enemies. 2) The computer doesn't need to use a mouse or keyboard to issue commands, and thus issues them instantly to multiple units. The computer can have 45 units scattered to hell and gone and have every single one of them bear down on various key structures in your base - at exactly the same time. This allows the computer to organize vast multi-spearhead assaults that outflank your defenses and tear them down just in time for the bomber run that wouldn't have made it anywhere near the target otherwise. 3) The computer is 100% effecient. there is never an idle worker or any wasted resources. The computer knows the radius of attack of every unit and can position them in an exact grid to provide 100% coverage. 4) The computer instantly attacks the biggest threat when fighting you, then it moves on to the next biggest threat. If your flame tank is wiping out those infantry, the next missile will strike that flame tank. 5) All that "ruthless" A.I. that is supposedly using strategy and cunning to outmanuver you also allows it to amass hard-hitting assault teams at the base before they rush your base, giving them a greater chance to punch thru.  Picture this: you start a skirmish against a computer opponent. You start off with your one worker, who you tell to go build a supply center so you can collect resources to start building. then you queue up a couple more workers. The computer already has as many workers as it is going to need queued up - they were queued up instantly, in the same instant that the first worker went to build a supply center. You get your new workers, who you tell to go build a barracks and a war factory or maybe a base defense. The computer will be building tanks before you get done with the barracks. Then, as you go to work on your second defense turret, and you have a tank building, and maybe some infantry - the first wave comes. You will die quickly if you don't drive the computer away. Sucks to be you.   current music:  "kill you" by korn rad guys, korn. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So I just went to blogger.com to maybe post or something, since various parts of the net are being real slow for some reason, and I noticed they had the radio shack motto on the front page. Google (company motto: yeah, we misspelled googol, so sue us.) bought blogger, and there is a F.A.Q. explaining what it means to us, the end-users. The link to the F.A.Q. is "You've got questions, we've got answers.". I read this and went "Neat!" because I parody that all the time (Radio Smack: You've got questions, we've got a hot cup of shut the fuck up). Anyway, I just thought it was neat is all.   current music:  "Why does it hurt when I pee?" by Frank Zappa. Frank Zappa is (well, was) and odd motherfucker. And coming from me that means a lot. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Do you know how much it sucks to have a camera and an intense desire to explore a new environment while taking a plethora of pictures of stuff you've never seen before, only you don't have a car or money? I know.  Say, it seems the brunching shuttlecocks have gone and dynamically generated  urlLink the rest of my posts in blogger.    current music:  "spondee" by matmos. matmos made this one album where the music was created from like, medical sounds. libosuction and lasik eye surgery and such. but spondee is different. I assume the vocal track is from some tape dealing with hearing or something, but it's weird. imagine a basic hip-hop sort of beat, with a woman speaking the following in monotone: "sunshine. lunchbox. playground. raincoat. hot dog. oatmeal. railroad. ice cream. bathtub. pancake. eardrum." 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm nearly horizontal!  that is all.   current music:  Uh, "come to daddy" by aphex twin, which I think I've listed here before. lemme go check...hmm. seems not. Although I have mentioned the song before, because it is a fucking great song. I listened to this acoustic live version of "symphony of destruction" by megadeth before that. Acoustic megadeth - now there's some weird shit. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       How to tell if you have an exceptionally large vocabulary, part the second:  If you use the dictionary as a spellchecker, you more than likely have not only an exceptionally large vocabulary, but superb spelling abilities as well. I mean, you kinda need to be able to spell pretty well to crack open a dictionary to check yourself.  In other news, you better check yourself before you wreck yourself, fool.   current music:  well, "uviol" finished right after I made that last post (like 2 minutes ago), and since then, I've heard the original leadbelly version of "black betty", and now "duchess" from the video game alice is playing. the music in alice was done by chris vrenna, who is associated with nine inch nails. The music from alice is fairly disturbing. think victorian children's songs, if they were composed in a nightmare. the whole thing sounds like a music box forged in hell. Oh hey, now it's some band I've never heard of playing "(sic)" by slipknot - live, and poorly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       How to tell if you have an exceptionally large vocabulary, part the first:  If you use the term "pyrrhic victory" during normal conversation, and the conversation isn't actually about the term "pyrrhic victory", your vocabulary is exceptionally large, perhaps unnecessarily so.  here's a scenario where someone might use the term: (note that I will flex my mighty vocabulary muscle a bit here.)  Usage of the term "pyrrhic victory"  "So, I was playing warcraft 3 against a friend of mine, and he was obviously better than me, but my forces were holed up in a well-defended position, and I controlled most of the gold mines on the map. I decided to play it as a war of attrition, sending small parties of high-damage units to force him to waste the rest of his gold defending against me. Little did I know, he had amassed an army in a remote corner of the map, and he caught me unawares with a full assault. I still had adequate defenses to hold him off for a while, and I was able to generate a good number of defenders, so I fought him off pretty well until he managed to cripple my forces with a clever flanking maneuver. I still had enough fighters and defenses left to make it a hard fight, and although I knew I was sunk, I did my best to make sure his victory was a pyrrhic one."  Ok, kudos if you understood every word in there, double-kudos if you've actually said "pyrrhic victory" at some point, triple-kudos if you thought "hey, warcraft 3 doesn't allow large enough armies to build an effective flanking attack." and uber-kudos if you corrected my grammar as you read.   current music:  "Uviol" by autechre. man, those guys like giving songs names nobody can remember. 
    
    
</post>

<date>16,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so  urlLink These People  are goddamned weird. It's a circus, like a real travelling circus, and about half of them are a band. The band plays, well, circus music. Only not. It's kinda hard to describe, I mean, they play classic circus music, but with these bizarre lyrics and stuff, and I just don't know what else to say except go there. 
    
    
</post>

<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Ok, so a few things. One, I have been jobless since I moved up to the great state of illinois (best way to mispronounce it: "illinwah", like it was a french word), and I might be getting me a job stocking at the local wal-place, but they won't start interviewing for 2 weeks, and I kinda sorta really am entirely desperate to get a job right the fuck right now, if not sooner. So a friend of mine (Wanker) calls up and says "you want a job?" and yeah, I kinda do, as stated. So I'll probably start doing this other job in the next couple days. I'll be on a floor crew at a store. I'll be one of the guys working the various brooms and machinery at the store at 3 am. I used to be the other people in the store - the ones wandering around looking like some kind of seedy zombie who might shoplift or eat your brains if you blink. That job is only part time, tho. 3 hours a day, 5 days a week. feh. Work is money, and money is good money. Another thing - I played red faction 2.  it's really really really short. Like short. Like I feel like I played a fucking demo. Seriously. I downloaded it (yeah fuck you too), unzipped it, installed it, played it, and fucking beat it - inside of 24 hours. Actual playing time was like 8 hours, maybe 10. that makes me sad. Somebody expects me to pay 50 bucks for 2 cd's worth of 8-10 hours of gameplay. and it's a first-person shooter, so no replay value, really. Things like this just piss me off. I played the demo for thief 2, and it took me like 3 hours the first time thru. A 3 hour demo. And I kept replaying that demo, trying to do things differently, take different routes. I played the freelancer demo, and it was an average demo, but after the demo missions ended, you can play for a really long time in kind of a free mode, where you can trade goods or play random jobs (you play a freelance space pilot). People who make games take note: I'm not about to pay you 50 fucking dollars for a game I can finish in 8 hours. Most of my jobs, I don't make 50 bucks in an 8 hour shift. On a similar note: while Piratizing&copy; red faction 2, I saw metal gear solid 2 up for download. But No. Metal gear solid 2 comes on a dvd, so the download is *eighty* 50 meg files. for the small version that fits on 5.2 gig dvd-r media. Y'know, if I was to desire that game, I'd buy it. No way in hell am I going to download 5 gigs of one game.   current music:  Well, to begin with it was "astro" by the white stripes, which contains the topic as a lyric. but then it was "psycho drama" by ultraviolence, "my heat goes boom" by snoop dogg, "this means war" by busta rhymes with ozzy osbourne, "dope boy fresh" by T.I., and finally "blackout" by method man and redman. took me a while to type this one out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       Did you ever notice how there is just about *always* some major holiday around the corner? Not actually physically around an actual physical corner, mind you, but around an intangible corner, a few weeks away. I mean it was easter, now it's mother's day, then it'll be, shit, I don't know, yom kippur or some shit. I don't actually know when yom kippur is. But what I'm saying is that I think the marketing scum that rule the earth and keep us all under their greasy scaly thumbs have decided that certain holidays are more important so as to keep that "seasonal" isle full of the same overpriced garbage that the same people buy every year. I'm really disenchanted with the commercalization of the holidays. Easter has lost all it's original meaning to most people. Easter and christmas are deeply rooted in christianity, yet they center around a fucking rabbit and santa claus, rather than like, I don't know, jesus... I'm by no means a religious person, but I think that if you build a holiday around the death and subsequent ascension into heaven of the central figure of your religion, and 2000 years later people celebrate it by eating chocolate bunnies and buying lots of green fakey grass - something has gone wrong with your holiday. On another note, I've decided, only just now, to implement a new feature in this ever-increasingly bloated journal type thing of mine: the word of the moment.anytime I post, I'll come up with some random word I like and make that the word of the day, and link to it on dictionary.com or something. Let's start things off at the bottom and work our way up.   word of the moment:   urlLink Nadir . Nadir means the lowest point, it's exactly the opposite of zenith, and it's what I'd name my electronics company. And it sounds like a presidential candidate.   current music:  "drone" by autechre. It'd from their "peel session" album. I like it. so there.   
    
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I'm angry. pissed, even. I got this game, x2: wolverine's revenge. I saw it and went "hey, a game where you get to bust some heads as wolverine - cool!" and I got it. Now I hate it. I hate it mostly because of the fact that if you don't do something right, you fail and have to start the level over. I was in this underground base thing, turned on an elevator, and a whole fat gang of bad guys came in. well, I was in poor health, and I figured I'd just run thru them and straight into the elevator. And No. see, if you do that, you get treated a cutscene where this one guy, who you could turn into a sloppy joe in a coat, waltzez in and takes 5 seconds to shoot out a control panel. Game over. restart the level. Seems you *must* fight all these assholes before you go thru the door, because if the door opens before you shred everybody, you lose. So I exited. and I likely won't go back, because idiotic script setups like that irritate me to no end. anyway, Yeah, I'm done.   current music:  "slaughtered" by Pantera. Panfuckingtera, for when you are *really* pissed. 
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       I moved. I was living at Spauldo's place, in the basement. The basement was bliss. I loved the basement. Alas, Spauldo moved back to that black hole of a state, Oklahoma. So I moved. I moved to wanker's place, which is an efficiency. An efficiency is like, one room, generally L shaped. The kitchen is on one side of the L, and the rest of the place in in the other part, with the bathroom finishing out the square. It's tiny. Tiny like there is no place in the whole apartment where you could play darts without somebody saying you were cheating and standing too close. It's me, Wanker, Tara, and Wankers 4 year old son, Dyllan. Tight quarters, but it's all I could do until I get a full time job and can afford to get my own closet. Wanker is super cool for letting me crash here, tho. He saved me from having to go back to (shudder) Oklahoma.  
    
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

    
       So I have a new job, kinda. I work 3 hours a day, 5 days a week. Cleaning floors at a discount store place. Feh. I dustmop half the store while somebody else does the other half. Then one of us grabs the big battery-powered self propelled floor scrubber, and the other one follows him with the propane-powered noisy ass buffer. Oh, and somebody vacuums the shoe area. Feh, indeed. This brings me to the topic. The first day I was there, I heard 'security shoes' come over the PA system 12 times. 12 times in 3 hours. As if the Worst Hits Of The 80's radio station they play wasn't bad enough. Feh.   current music:  Nothing. I mention this because I only brought my computer over to this new place to help wanker get his cable modem working, and I have no speakers. 
    
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wonder what the virgin Mary's parents thought when she told them she was pregnant, but hadn't actually had sex with Joseph. And did they tell little jesus that Joe was his "uncle" or something? And did Mary and Joseph ever end up actually doing it? I bet her parents went "ohhh... that's wonderful" but were thinking something like "she's been whoring around with that pool boy again, I just bet you. Immaculate, indeed." And I always thought the whole immaculate comception was a little odd, considering that God has a real problem with people conceiving out of wedlock. I don't think God and Mary were married, and although he didn't actually lay her down and make sweet holy love to her down by the fire - he did still impregnate her. And violated one of his biggest rules in the process. Of course, religious folk will go "that's different." or something, but I don't care. I don't get a lot of things, tho. Like why is there a word for a gay woman, but not one for a gay man? If you are homosexual, you can be homosexual or gay, or various other nasty terms - but a gay woman can be more specific - she can be a lesbian. A gay guy can't distinguish his gender - he's just gay. So you have to say "gay man" when gender is required. I also wonder why there isn't a female version of misogynist. There are certainly man-hating women - why isn't there a word for them? Besides bitch or something, I mean. There also isn't a female equivalent of Effeminate, which means 'girly man', basically. Calling a woman 'butch' is asking for a hairy-knuckled fist in the teeth - some things can't be said, no matter how true they are. I have a thing for words, though, which is probably why I sit and wonder about these things when I really ought to be out mowing the lawn or something. I think I want to start a campaign to allow unusual plurals to flourish. I think that most words ending in 's' or 'sh' whould be given weird plurals. Examples: Danish should be Danishae, and Oasis should be Oasii. I'd call it the "Citizenry for odd pluralo" or something. Maybe not, because that would be pronounced "see-fop", and It's been my experience that acronyms containing words like Fop are a bad idea. Fop is one of those words that I don't actually think means anything, but it sounds weird, like it should mean something, and it should be unpleasant. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I wonder if they have a religion/political party/country for people like me. I have the general attitude of "you do your thing and stay the fuck out of mine." People should live right, and treat other people right, and shut the hell up and stop bothering everybody else because they aren't living the right kind of right. Just because I think guns are nifty or The Lord's real name is Jim, doesn't mean I'm doing it wrong. If I thought people with freckles were sent by satan and must die - well that's different. I see people following what I consider to be completely nutty and comically absurd ways of life - and I mean like "the original batman series" absurd - but I let them do their thing. As long as your thing doesn't interfere in other people's things, or hurt or kill other people - go ahead and have fun with it. My way of life has advantages - I don't get all fussy when I see somebody against something I'm for - because I don't care. Let them think the earth is flat - it just means I can laugh about it. Let them worship Buddha or wear tinfoil on their heads or vote for Nader or get naked and dance around a bonfire on the third tuesday of every october because - and this is the important part - I don't. I do my thing, and let everybody else do theirs. I think this should extend everywhere. Let radio and tv carry what people might find obscene. The old addage still stands - if you don't agree with it, don't take part. Don't listen or watch, and let people who want to listen and watch do so, and shut the fuck up about it, you whiny baby. Just because you don't think something should be the way it is doesn't mean everybody else does - or should. I personally practice no religion at all. This tends to upset religious folks, because at the root of it all - I'm doing it wrong. With politics it's easier - I don't vote, and nobody really cares. All the political ads are aimed at people just like me, but I don't watch them. I'm not an "undecided voter", because I've decided - to not vote. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I figured out long ago how I could make a stable living in a market that will never dry up: I could sell toilets. See, *everybody* needs a toilet, at some point. Every house has at least one, and barring some rapid evolution or invention of a new way to remove waste from the home - the toilet is here to stay. There are a very small number of people who don't use them, of course - people living in the mountains who think toilets have transmitters in them so the CIA will know what you eat, and people who, for medical reasons, go in a bag they carry around with them. I know selling toilets isn't glamorous, and I know that people don't just get up one day and go "hey - I think we oughta buy a toilet!", but I think toilets are just about the most stable market there is, short of maybe toilet paper. Of course, if I really wanted to make money, I could film porn on the side. Porn involving toilets. And hermaphrodites. I'm not sure why, but for some reason, a few years ago, the porn industry as a whole decided that girls peeing was sexy. I don't get it. I see nothing at all sexy about a girl taking a leak - not even the voyeur side of it - peeking in a window or something. I can't wrap my brain around what people would find appealing about watching other people urinate. Now, drinking pee, I can see. There's a real obvious dom/sub relationship when you tinkle in somebody's mouth. But just seeing somebody go... I don't get it. I think it was about the same time that the industry (I'm good friends with the porn industry, so I can just call it "the industry, like I'm in the know) decided that guys like women with penises. I think I get this one. I think the industry knows that a lot of guys have those dark urges to try out what their upbringing tells them is taboo: fucking another dude. So there have been ads for some time in the back of porn mags and stuff with pics of guys offering phone sex. These things were aimed, ostensibly, at gay and bi men, but the fact that they appeared in straight porn mages otherwise filled with pics of women taking dick means they obviously played at guys who wanted to try it, but didn't want to actually go find a guy. I think the chicks with dicks ads are the same thing: A guy sees a woman - guys are *supposed* to be having sex with women - that's fine. If "she" has a cock - that's not really technically a guy, right? I mean, just because this woman has a dong and you fuck her in the ass after she gives you a BJ doesn't make you gay, right? Truth is: those pics are either doctored, or the women were. See, there have been maybe 5 actual hermaphrodites in recorded history. An actual woman who just happens to have a dick doesn't exist. Those "women" are in fact guys, gay guys usually, who are taking estrogen and had boob jobs. Which means that were you to actually encounter one of these people in a sexual manner, you would in fact be having sex with a guy, with tits and a girl haircut. But apparently guys don't see it that way, since it seems 2 out of 10 phone sex ads in the back of those magazines has a tranny in the picture. So my toilet business would make extra money making films of tstv's pissing on guys on the toilet. And I suppose I could sell a clear acrylic one to the paranoid guy in the mountains. And maybe if I sold colostomy bags and diapers, I could cover 100% of all people. The complete service toilet store.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Pardon me boy, is that the chatanooga choo-choo? I ask, not because I actually think the frozen food aisle here in the grocery store is a train station, or that I think you, the stock boy, are the engineer or something - but I think it's a good way to start conversation. I mean, I ask you if that display of cap'n crunch is a train, you go "eh?" and then I can go off on a tangent, about how I read on this website about a bunch of people who want to get the cap'n promoted to admiral for some reason. I mean, I wouldn't promote him. I personally know the cap'n, and his place is on his big cartoon boat, not commanding some fleet of cereal-based warships, bound for milkitania, to overthrow the despot ruling it and to free the people, not, as some people think, to let the cartoon cereal mascots have easy access to that country's great stores of milk. I know we already conquered spoonland, and now spoons are cheap and plentiful here, and the new country, The United States Spoonland Federated Territories, is the geographical equivalent of a steaming pile of alpaca manure, only with less nutrients - but at least they are free from the terrible state-enforced free healthcare, education, and utilities. You know, while we're talking about cereal, don't you miss boo-berry crunch? I mean, it was the most godawful tasting bile of a cereal, but it turned your milk *blue*. Anything that makes milk blue without also making it poison is a gift from the gods. Also, I think stuff that makes milk blue *and* poison is a gift from the gods, but I probably worship the wrong gods. I invented my gods. I'm the only person who worships my gods, who mostly deal in turning things different colors. I think my religious system stems from the spiritual experience I had at the crayola factory. See, when I was young, My school went on a tour of the crayola crayon factory, and I got to see all the neat crayons and stuff, but then - They gave me a box of crayons! For free, without me doing anything spectacular or noteworthy. I mean, this guy just walked up and gave me a whole box of my very own crayons. I was so happy I went home and drew gods on the walls of my room with the crayons. Each color was a different god. I have 8. The blue god changes things into blue, but sometimes he also makes them poison. I think he's the bad one. Him and white. That white god hardly does anything, unless I leave like, pudding or something in my fridge for a couple months, then it turns white. But when the white god turns stuff white, it almost always smells real bad and tastes kinda funny. I can't usually remember what it tastes like, but I know the people in the hospital also wear white, which I think the white crayon god makes them do to freak me out. Oh, hey, so if you're the stock boy, and I wanted, say, shark fin, could you go out and catch a shark and defin it for me? Because I want my shark fin to be really really fresh. I make fermented shark fin soup from it. Hey, where are you going?  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, I see this diet coke with lime, and I wonder about things. Firstly, I wonder - does it taste like a cleaning product or something? diet coke with lemon tasted exactly and totally like somebody opened a diet coke and put an alka-seltzer cold'n'flu tablet in it, which is not quite as tasty as it sounds, which is bad because it doesn't sound very tasty at all. But I also wonder - did the coke folk make this because it was the next logical step, citrus-wise, in the fruit chain? Because I mean diet coke with grapefruit or orange sounds like it wouldn't sell very well. But if they didn't just do it because lime comes after lemon - did they do it because some bigwig at coca-cola  really digs cuba libres? I mean, the cuba libre is, after all, a rum and coke with some lime juice in it. This product cuts out the middleman, so to speak. That'd be cool if they started making club soda mixed with amaretto or creme de menthe, too. I don't know why you can't just buy a real honest-to-goodness boilermaker or dirty martini in a can. You can buy some rum'n'cola'n'natural'n'artificial flavors in a can, and you can get stuff like mudslides and white russians, but those are pussified 8% alchohol versions, not a bottle with real rum and coke or real kahlua and vodka. I should sell those. "Dr. Twilight's real mixed drinks in a can - for people too drunk to stir" You could use beer math on them, too. "man, I got shitfaced on a sixer of grasshoppers last night." I like how beer gives you one ability: you can multiply, divide, add, and subtract anything to or from the numbers 6, 12, 18, 24, and 30 - in your head, instantly, while half drunk. If there are 4 people drinking, and each is on their 3rd beer, you know instantly, without having to figure anything in your head, that the case is half gone, and that somebody oughta go get another one before you get past the excuse level. See, I think if a cop pulls you over and smells beer, and you go "I had three, I'm fine, dude." - he might just let you go. But if you just pounded back a sixer, you ain't going home tonight. You can't make an excuse for driving around with half a gallon of beer in you - 3 you can manage. "My damn wife is pregnant and I absolutely had to go buy rum raisin ice cream, right now." - to which the cop might say "Stay off the main roads - my wife always wanted pickles and dr. pepper." Even if your wife is barren, that one probably has a good chance of working with 3 beers. but if you've just finished 6 and say "I needsh to buy another cashe", well then, you're going to jail tonight. By the way, "barren" is a terrible way to say a woman can't have a kid for some reason. It makes her sound like an old dried out field or something.  
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm fixing to post my braindumps. These will follow a pattern. I write these things, then pick some odd line from them as a title. So any oddness in the title of each post in entirely intentional. Here we go. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How about that - almost exactly a year between posts! Keen. 
    
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, I was offline for a long time. And it sucked real real real bad. I mean like real bad. Like it sucked more than a prostitute at a vacuum cleaner store in a black hole. But I lived. I'm now back, and I intend to make a couple changes. Like for example: I ain't linking to the mp3 of songs that get stuck in my head anymore. When I was hosted on a friend's box, that was cool. Aloof hosting (my current host) doesn't allow them, so feh. Right now I'm actually kind of tired and don't feel like doing it, but at some point soon I'll flood this thing with the various stuff I wrote down during "The Dark Ages".   word of the moment:   urlLink resurrection  For obvious reasons. Just look at the date on the last post, for chrissake. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Said the ladies they love me - from the bleachers they screamin' all the ballers is bouncin' - they like the way I be leanin' all the rappers is hatin' off the track that I'm makin' but all the hustlers they love it just to see one of us make it.    word of the moment:   urlLink braggadocio  ...as the best rapper alive - nigga axe about me. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You know your car is too large when you bottom out on the curvature of the earth. You know you've had too much coffee when your urine comes out speaking Spanish. (spanish is spoken in Colombia.... think a while, it'll come to you.)   word of the moment:   urlLink onomatopoeia  It's words that sound like what they are. Buzz is a good onomatopoeia. So is whomp. 
    
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Yeah, right - when pigs fly. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    yes, we have no bananas. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Testing, testing, one two three... testing comments. whee. This is to test the comments, which I just now turned on. Please feel free to comment on any and all posts I make in here. I'd especially love it if you point out my spelling errors, grammatical mistakes, and false assumptions - that's what the internet is for, after all. Actually, I would really appreciate comments on any past post you find interesting, funny, offensive - whatever. I crave the attention. Of course, if you have mastery of time travel, feel free to comment on future posts as well. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       There, I said it. Not much else to discuss, I guess.   word of the moment:   urlLink schlock  - as in the elvis impersonation and james brown dance a certain orange cgi cat did in a certain worst movie ever to sully a movie screen.   current music:  It's "Garfield is the worst movie ever" by the catbeaters.  Good lord that movie sucks.  In other news -  urlLink I guess the banana worked.  
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Did I really just go on a "Kids These Days" diatribe - about video games? What a weird time to grow old. Sonny, back in my day, bikes didn't have suspension, candy bars cost 50 cents, and video games were goddamned hard! and heavily pixelated, too - we didn't have no 16X full screen adaptive anti-aliasing at 1600X1200@245fps. Our games were blocky, in 16 colors, and slow. And we were glad to have them! Mario Bros 3 was a technological wonder, damnit! (shakes cane) 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anybody remember MegaMan? I know they're up to megaman X9++ ultra, but do you remember MegaMan 1? Before he had all those friends and a robot dog and stuff? I saw this game with 10 classic MegaMan games, and went "Hey, that'd be cool! Oldschool MegaMan kicked ass!" But then I remembered - MegaMan was really fucking hard. I got my ass handed to me every time I played those games, even when I used a game genie. It's like "Make this damn-near impossible jump, but try not to land on the 42 spiky things that can leap halfway across the screen, and also avoid the flying things that will knock you into that bottomless pit there, and also you have to jump right now because the floor you're standing on is falling into the aforementioned pit." I just wanted to say that. MegaMan was really really hard. All these kids now don't know what hard is. They beat quake 3 and think they're badass. If games were dives, MegaMan would be the triple lindey, and quake 3 would be a cannonball. I'm just saying.   current music:  "Duality" by Slipknot. In the video, tons of angry teens tear this house to shit. I remember "There Goes The Neighborhood" by Body Count, where the band tore up an abandoned trailer, and the video got banned for being too violent. I like both videos.   word of the moment:   urlLink Juggernaut  A juggernaut is a terrible force that destroys all in its path, like democracy. It's also one of the representations of krishna in the hindu faith. And a supervillain. I hope Juggernaut winds up in X-men 3. He's a badass. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In reference to  urlLink yon post , I guess 3 participants doesn't actually constitute an orgy.   word of the moment:   urlLink menage a trois  - obviously. This is three people, fucking one another, in unison. The actual definiton differs somewhat from what every single living human being considers a menage a trois, but to hell with every single living human being - what do they know?   bonus word:   urlLink orgy  - which, of course, is much like the previous in that every single living human being that doesn't study ancient greece thinks it means "lots of people fucking in a big room", even though the original meaning is somewhat different. But like I said - to hell with every single living human being. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So, the Fucking Marketing Scum slithered out from under their rocks and decided that the world needs more ads. And they decided that the most ad-poor place - is your supermarket produce section. I've got bananas - with a sticker on them telling me to see Garfield, the movie. I am personally offended by this. This is worse than the FMS trying to get ads on a space shuttle, or tombstones - both of which have been attempted. Fucking Marketing Scum.   current music:  It's "God Hates Us All" - another upbeat work from those model citizens, Slayer. The album was released on sep 11, 2001, which is when some bad thing happened, I can't remember what. something about Iraq crashing our planes or something. If you're into angry thrashy heavy music with an anti-religious bent, I highly recommend it. Otherwise, you'll probably hate it, and come to hate me for mentioning it - and I'll be fine with that, because I already hate you, fucker.   word of the moment:  I couldn't find a suitable page with the definition, but this word of the moment is  lagnonector . A lagnonector is a person who kills in order to have sex with the corpse. Fun fun.  urlLink here's a page  with a bunch of sex and pregnancy terms starting with the letter L, including lagnonector. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A few posts back I said I didn't think "fop" meant anything. It does. I remembered, I own this really crappy dictionary, and it includes fop as part of a 3-way orgy of reciprocal definitions. A Fop is a dude or a dandy, a dude is a fop, and a dandy is a dude, or a fop. Clears that up. This is the same dictionary that had simile, but not metaphor. Yeah.   word of the moment:   urlLink fop  - I mean, what else would it be in this post? Dictionary.com does a hell of a lot better job at explaining what a fop is. And I was right - it is a bad thing. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink White   urlLink Green   urlLink Brown   urlLink Orange   urlLink Pink   urlLink Blue   urlLink Black   urlLink Also Black   urlLink Off-White   urlLink Red   urlLink Grey   urlLink Yellow  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       As a reference to this post, read  urlLink This Post  from way back in July of 2001. I was upset about the price of gas. Pissed, even. Gas was like 1.20 a gallon then. The national average is now dangerously close to 2.00 a gallon. My parents talk about when gas was 50 cents a gallon, waaaaaaaay back when they were kids, before I was born. Now I can tell teenagers "I remember when gas was HALF the price it is now." And they'll go "Yeah, me too. it was 4 years ago." Economists say that when you take inflation into account, gas is actually nowhere near record highs. Fuck economists. Economists should look at me. I was making 7.50 an hour in 1998 when gas was 1.00 a gallon. A month ago I was making 7.50 an hour - and gas was 1.97 a gallon. Inflation can go fuck itself. When my wages inflate to match everything else, I'll be ok with the price of gas. The heirs of all those prehistoric creatures who became the oil which became the gas we're paying so much for should sue somebody. It's the Amurican way.   current music:  "Satan Gave Me A Taco" by Beck. I love that song.  word of the moment:   urlLink inflation  - Including the quote "In inflation everything gets more valuable except money." I'll just let that one stand on it's own. 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Tried to get an 'old photo' look. Original can be found   urlLink here  
    
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So I got a job. I now work for... well, I won't mention the name - but let's just say it's the largest company in the world, headquarted in Bentonville, Arkansas and mascotted by a smiley face - and leave it at that. I'll be doing what I apparently love - floor maintenance. I am a Floor Maintenance Technician, or Mop Jockey for short. I do enjoy it. I mean, I'm in a company totally dedicated to customer service - but in a position where I'll never see any customers.   word of the moment:   urlLink salubrious  - one of those words that sounds dirty but isn't. I mean, just say it a couple times, slowly - Salubrious. Saluuuuuubrious. Nasty, ain't it? Know what salubrious means? Conducive to health. Eating your vegetables and sleeping are salubrious activities. A real downer of a word, if you ask me, which you wouldn't have.   current music:  "'A' Is For Apathy" by Powerman 5000. "Everybody's here but nobody showed up."  Yeah...  And I don't think "mascotted" is a real word. Lemme check... nope. I don't care tho. Now it is. I just invented it. I'm a rogue lexicographer, as of this moment. If I put some word that doesn't exist in here and it isn't just a typo - I did it on purpose and intend to spread that word into common usage through this medium. just remember that. And the opposite of "Mini" is "Wumbo", according to Patrick Star. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    I worry me sometimes. Well, alltimes. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I got a .torrent of every cd Rammstein has put out. I've been listening to german industrial metal all day, and it's been doing things to me. I'm different now. I want to grind things. I want to wear military gear and rubber pipes and sing in german. But I'll get over it. I also downloaded lots and lots of porn. Mostly pictures, so it's not like I have to go buy a 50pack of dvd-r media to hold it all - but it's still a lot of porn. I have an excuse for it now, tho. I got an idea for a weird picture involving lots of porn pictures. I'll post it when I make it.   current music:  Rammstein - all of it. Actually, my playlist has 82 Rammstein songs, and 1 Bloodhound Gang song - "You're Pretty When I'm Drunk." It's right after "Wollt Ihr Das Bett In Flammen"   Word Of The Moment:   urlLink Prurient , as in "In the prurient interest", which is how you determine if something is offensive and should be banned, or if it's sexxxxxayy, and should be masturbated to. Prurience is an inordinate interest in sex. So it's every human male between 13-18. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The past couple of posts have been made with a program called "hello", by picasa software, who I can't be bothered to go find and link to right now. Basically it's an instant messenger that allows you to upload pics to a server for purposes of blogging. It has other purposes, I'm sure - but I don't care.   word of the moment:   urlLink syzygy  - It's the first WOTM that I didn't know the meaning of to begin with. syzygy is when the sun, moon, and earth all line up. It's also the shortest word in the english language where Y appears 3 times. and It's a bot in Unreal Tournament 2003. The pronunciation key looks like  urlLink cuneiform , but you say "siss-i-gee" with the I being pronounced like in fish. 
    
    
</post>

<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Links to the 1600X1200 versions of my new porn-based images:  urlLink Porn - Light  is the first one I posted, with the whitewash over it.  urlLink Porn - Dark  is, obviously, a darker version of the first one.  urlLink Porn - Orgy  is the darker, redder version without the shadows and lines over the top.  urlLink Ass Orgy  has nothing to do with porn, but the name fits with the scheme, and it's a good way to throw you off after all that skin.   
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    The same image as before, without the shattered effect on it, and filtered to a darker, redder look. I'm using this one as my wallpaper. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Another image using porn as a source. This one less distorted, and no faces. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Here's that image I said I was working on - the one with all the porn. Click on it to get the 1600X1200 version. A quote from Spauldo: "Wow, that's like hell for pornstars." 
    
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       You thought it was a joke and so you laughed - you laughed when I had said that losing you would make me flip my lid, right?  You know you laughed, I heard you laugh. You laughed, you laughed and laughed and then you left but now you know I'm utterly mad!   current music:  "phone calls from the dead" by meat beat manifesto. I don't like it that much. If I wasn't so lazy, I'd bring winamp up and find something worthwhile. Ok, now it's "lovesong" by the cure. Much better. And much better than that cheesy reggae version 311 dropped recently, like so many steaming piles of alpaca manure.   link of the moment:   urlLink They're coming to take me away Ha-Haaa!    word of the moment:   urlLink Alpaca  It's my animal du jour, replacing ostriches, which replaced monkeys, which replaced  urlLink dimetrodons . I occasionally choose some semi-random animal I can apply to funny situations and keep it for a while. I was all over monkeys until it got all popular. being a trendsetter is only cool until the trend is set. I was kinda getting bored with ostriches, and besides - alpacas are just so...  obscure.    
    
    
</post>

<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Oh wait - that's just my ointment.  So I just watched spider-man 2. Well, I watched spiderman 2, but I'm still using the hyphen so fuck you. I had read that spider(hyphen)man 2 was a pretty good fucken movie, so I Piratized&copy; it - and yes, Spider(hyphen)Man 2 is a really good fucken movie. Especially the part where venom kills Mary Jane. Oops. Spoiler alert. You shouldn't have read that part if you haven't seen the movie yet. Since I'm on the subject of spoilers - You probably shouldn't go to  urlLink Moviepooper.com  if you haven't seen every movie ever made.   current music:  "more human that human (meet bambi in the king's harem mix)" by white zombie. It's a badass remix of a badass song, which makes me also a badass.   
    
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink This  is the funniest thing anyone has ever said in a movie. Ever. Nothing else to say, really.   Music Of The Moment:  "Love to Hate" by Slayer. Fun guys, Slayer.  Word Of The Moment:  Nothing. I couldn't think of anything. I think mostly because I'm tired and sick. And together we are: SICK&TIRED! 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So this post is about games. I know I have a lot of those, but I play a lot, so I feel justified.  &nbsp;  This is something I've noticted in games - most all of them.&nbsp; I hate how one shot to the head will kill somebody instantly - unless he knows you're shooting at him. Once alert, everybody gets some kind of internal kevlar helmet. They also get perfect night vision scopes once you've fired. If you fire one bullet into the back of some guy's head, everybody else - who was facing the other way, spins around and knows you've shifted over behind the car and adjust their "blind" aim to suit. They act like they can't see you, but when you move, so does the rain of bullets.&nbsp;And the bosses are&nbsp;"Just Tougher". I love those games, where the boss is just like anybody else, and there's no reason why you shouldn't be able to slay him with the same brutal effectiveness you dispatch everybody else with - but for some reason this guy can just take rockets to the forehead like nobody's business. I guess being evil or mean makes you more resistant to explosives and bullets and big fucking swords that cut everybody else clean the fuck in half. I can see the demon/giant spider/undead abomination/radioactive biomechanical mutant squirrel being hard to kill, but if the big boss is just this guy, and he's the mastermind behind all the evil, for some reason you can unload the ManKillerX4000 into his throat and he'll just run around the corner, or he'll whip out his Pistol That Hurts More Than Any Other Gun In The Game and fire away like you weren't putting 8 pounds of lead a second thru his larynx. And he's the most accurate shot in the world. He can be doing a flip thru an explosion and hit you, running behind a scaffolding 50 yards away, in the forehead, shooting from the hip, with a flintlock pistol, in a snowstorm. And he has an eyepatch.  &nbsp;   Music Of The Moment:  "crimson and clover" by Tommy James and The Shondells. Voted "best use of tremelo" for 1968.  &nbsp;   Link Of The Moment:   urlLink Turkish Delight   &nbsp;  Word Of The Moment:    urlLink Adjoining  which isn't really an obscure or hard word - but it's just such a great one. I mean - just say it: Adjoining. Ad-Joy-Ning. Isn't that just fantastic to say?  
    
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yeah, so it's been a while since I posted. It's not that I didn't have anything to say - it's that I didn't feel like posting.  I've begun a couple of new things. First up, Doom 3. Doom 3 will be my life, my all-consuming addiction - just as soon as I can get it to work. see, it crashes 10-15 seconds after loading. And by 'crashes' I mean 'hardlocks my goddamned computer.' I don't want to talk about it anymore. It makes me angry. You wouldn't like me when I'm angry. Y'know, cuz I can be a prick. The other new thing I'm doing, and only started doing this sunday: I'm playing dungeons and dragons. I'm a half-elf cleric of Kord, god of brawling, drinking, battle and athleticism. Mostly the drinkin' and fightin', tho. I've managed to get KO'd by a friggin' kobold with a wand that fires magic missle. yeah, I feel like a pussy. I'm supposed to be Mr. Big Bad Broadsword, and Mr. Rat Lizard With A Stick knocked me to negative hit points. Then later a goblin got a critical on me - for 4 points. I was so upset I had to chop his goblin ass in twain. I'm both the heavy fighter and the healer of our party. Probably not the best combination, considering I only picked up a bow in our last battle, which means I'll spend most of my time having sharp things land on me - and I'm the guy who's supposed to keep everybody alive.   Music Of The Moment:  "One Perfect Sunrise" by Orbital. It's ok techno, but I prefer "Bachelorette" by Bjork, which was on before. I love Bjork. I want her to have my children. I want us to marry and move to Reykjavik. I'll convert for her. Bjork is a member of Asatru, which is one of the elder, predating pretty much everything religions. I could go for worshipping Thor and Odin.   Link Of The Moment:   urlLink Asatru    Word Of The Moment:   urlLink Blah  but only because I'm amazed it's in there. I'll use it in a sentence: Britney Spears' new album is totally blah! Like, Drivel-icious! 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>