<Blog>

<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Every day should be a half day.  Took the afternoon off to hit the dentist, and while I was out I managed to get my oil changed, too.  Remember that business with my car dealership this winter?  Well, consider this the epilogue.  The friendly fellas at the Valvoline Instant Oil Change on Snelling were nice enough to notice that my dipstick was broken, and the metal piece was too far down in its little dipstick tube to pull out.  Looks like I'm going to need a magnet.   Damn you, Kline Nissan, daaaaaaammmnnn yooouuuu....   Today I let my boss know that I've submitted my Corps application.  The news has been greeted by everyone in the company with a level of enthusiasm that really floors me.     The back deck has finally been cleared off by the construction company working on the place.  This company, for anyone who's interested, consists mainly of one guy who spends his days cursing at his crew of Spanish-speaking laborers.  Construction of my deck began around the time Nixon was getting out of office.
    
</post>

<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Consider the ball rolling.  I've submitted my application and health review, and I've made myself available for assignment starting March 2005.
    
</post>

<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to be back in the office environment again starting Thursday.  Cry for me.  Oh well, I think hitting the submit button on my application tomorrow might actually make that return bearable.
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm still not making any headway with my family.  In fact, I think Mom has been rallying the troops (aka aunts and uncles) against me.  Meanwhile, my friends have been really supportive of the idea.  Thanks, all.  It's frustrating, you know?  Here, I want to get out into the world, have a pinch of adventure, and maybe help some people out in the process, and I'm earning the resentment of the entire freakin' family because of this.  I can only hope that, over time, cooler heads will prevail.  There's now a nationwide girlfriend hunt on for yours truly (hell, with Mom's Mexico ties, this shit could go international), because, obviously, the cure for all this foolishness is for me to get laid.  Oh, and I should buy myself something nice.  Problem solved.  Life is so sad.  Had a spot of Sunday night insomnia, fueled mostly by my discussions with the parents yesterday.  Thankfully, Jack Daniels helped me out with that.  Whoever is in charge of late night Sunday programming should be shot.  Sunday night insomnia is not an uncommon phenomenon, and TV needs to be there for people in their hour(s) of need!  Jerks.
    
</post>

<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two points for anyone who can identify that bit of dialogue (one of my favorite bits).  Hint: Director Steven Soderbergh insists that it's meaningless.  Back to  About Schmidt  for a moment.  I just love the name Schmidt.  Does anyone else feel the same way?  So many superfluous letters... that kooky "c"... that silent "d".  Along those same lines: it took Michael Moore to really help me memorize the spelling of "Fahrenheit".  Yes, I'm still adhering to my own rule that periods don't need to go inside quotation marks.  The parents are on their way out.  I'm going to try to think of something to cook, lest we end up at Axl's Bonfire Grill down the street.  Let me see... corn on the cob fresh from my grimy stove-top, or perhaps a nice walleye salad at Axl's?  Decisions, decisions.
    
</post>

<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       About Schmidt  this afternoon.  Pretty good.  A little vexed by the ending.  I think I'm getting too lazy to interpret ambiguity.  Finished up most of my application today, essay questions and all.  All that remains is to inform my references of their reference status... and that could very well mean letting my company know that I'm planning to leave in 6 mos. to a year.  I'm not sure how they'll react, but I'm not all that concerned, either.  Good people there, certainly, but I am giving them at least  six months  notice.  At this point, the only thing that gives me pause is Sydney.  I have to make sure she has a home for a few years, and I have to be sure that whoever gets her knows what they're getting into.  Sydney's a good cat in a lot of ways... very clean, very well mannered, sweet as all get out... and that tiny meow.  That said, she likes to scratch stuff, and I should probably get that in check before I expose her to furniture that isn't dorm-rated.
    
</post>

<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I spent a good hour last night paging through the application and making little notes about what to say for the longer, essay portions.  The questions being asked are standard job interview stuff, at least they were at the University.  Basically, how do you handle diversity, and why do you want to work here?  As for the short answers: I haven't decided whether I should be concerned by the fact that there's an entire page dedicated to previous volunteer experience... and, apart from a pledge that I'm going to be doing some tutoring work for the Minnesota Literacy Council, that page is going to be completely blank.  The job history page says to go back "at least 10 years."  Ten years ago, I was 16.  I was working at Best Buy, and I hated it.  I should note, though, that I saw my old manager working at Audio King (back when it was called Audio King), many months ago.  Then there was Media Play... then Hollywood Video... I can't believe that an international aid organization would find my ability to upsell Packard Bells, or say in what section  Femalien  resides, remotely interesting.  How I spent the remainder of my Thursday night: Watched  The Fog of War , an amazing Errol Morris doc about Robert McNamara.  Then, I went to sleep and had strange dreams involving Holly Hunter.
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's pretty obvious that I'm not a great learner of lessons, because here I am writing the umpteeth "first blog entry" of my life.  Someone, somewhere (probably pretty close to here, actually), is going to open up this domain expecting to see handsome video game Cratchit digging his way out of a sand trap, only to find I'm on the blogging track again.  Cue blood squib explosions and the first movement of Carmina Burana.  But, wait.  I'm a changed man, baby!  Things will be different this time, I swear!  Well, maybe not right away, but eventually, I hope.  I've been feeling more than a little anxious the past few months.  Life as a web developer has sort of burned me out, and I think I'd like to try something different... something that will get me closer the Great Life Goal I'm shooting for.  I'm not sure what the Goal is exactly, but I get the feeling I'll never get there on my current course.  Web development is great and all, but sometimes I get the impression that, in this field, I'm driven more by my perfectionism than by any genuine love of the work.  It's no secret to anyone that's spoken to me in the past few months that I'm about this (--) close to joining the Peace Corps.  In fact, the application is sitting on my coffee table right now.  There's a pen there, too.  Oh, and I've filled in a few blanks with that very same pen.  There are a few very big blanks that are going to demand more brainpower than I can muster after 8-something hours of mind-numbing development, but I promise you that I'm going to power through and get all 16+ pages of the form in the mail by the end of next week.  I'm sure even my fans in Chicago will be able to hear my mother's cries when she hears the news.  So, you see, this blog has a reason for existing.  I'm hitting the reset button on life, and you're all going to be here to see it.  Dramatic, right?  Anyway, here we go.
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My reference forms trickled in last week, and that left the weekend for me to buck up my cross-cultural adaptation essay, something I've been really struggling with.  What's a significant experience  you've  had with adapting to a different culture?  You'd think that a three month stint in Europe would make a question of this kind really easy to answer, but it doesn't... tourism, as it turns out, doesn't really lend itself to forcing you adapt to anything other than washing your clothes in a sink.  I wish I could say I've needed to wipe my butt with a leaf once in my life, but that's just not the case... hence, my application to the PC.    Back to the story, then.  I filled up the huge PC envelope last night and sent it on its way this morning.  There's an education addendum that I decided against filling out, only because it would have been a pretty pathetic-looking effort.  My IT addendum, on the other hand, was five pages long.  Huzzah!  I'd still rather not spend two years sitting in front of a computer in Whateverstan, but I don't want to limit my placement opportunities, either.    So that's that.  Now I wait for a nomination.    On the 'rents:  This weekend, I told them that I've submitted my application and met with a recruiter.  Their heads didn't explode.  They didn't key my car or light my hair on fire.  Still, Dad says that I'm making a mistake, and Mom said she wouldn't be able to sleep.  I stressed the importance of optimism, as opposed to--well, you know--flipped-out, irrational fatalism.    DNC:  Politics.  Feh.  Here's my take on politics:   Dear Republicans:  George W. Bush...  This is the best you've got?  Are you fucking serious?  Dear Democrats:  John Kerry...  This is the best you've got?  Are you fucking serious?     That is all.  You may return to your regular business.    
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, I gave you guys a little vacation.  Hope you enjoyed it.    Met with my Peace Corps recruiter Friday afternoon at the PC office above Kieran's. Answered a bunch of those types of questions you get at job interviewsm, and was fingerprinted for my soon-to-be-generated FBI file. There goes my backup plan of becoming a jewel thief.    Managed to skirt around conversation relating to this on Sunday, when I visited the parents. Actually, I haven't yet told them that I've actually started the application process, only that I've been thinking seriously about it.    I probably would have gotten into it, but Mom called me on Thursday afternoon, loaded up with a bunch of anecdotes from the "Casualties of Peace" series of articles that ran in the Dayton Daily News last year. Arguing with your mother is a good way to ruin your lunch break, and many of the hours thereafter.    But I really should be going. Hoping to get the rest of my paperwork in this week. After that, I'll ready myself for a series of invasive medical check-ups. Joy! 
    
</post>

<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My parents have the week off work... so when the weekends just aren't enough time to argue about my decisions, now I can do that on Thursday mornings, too!  Something about social circles, I guess: my parents insist that everyone they talk to about my future excursion rolls their eyes at the idea, throws their hands up in the air and cries "Why?!"  Perhaps they exaggerate.  My mother is a veritable encyclopedia of horror stories about international travel.  "Didn't you hear about those people in Honduras two years ago that were tortured and killed?"  "Didn't you hear about that couple in Mexico that they put in jail and wanted $10,000 from?  And the wife had appendicitis.  And then Satan bit their arms off, and smuggled them over the border... stuffed with cocaine!"  "You don't want to go to Africa!  They have apartheid, and they like to kill white people!"  [rolls eyes]
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A recruiter called today, and I'm all set up to interview/be fingerprinted next Friday afternoon.  The recruiter also wants to flesh out one of my essay responses.  I wasn't altogether happy with my essays.  Like I've said before, my capacity for churning out long form answers that are semi-coherent has been damaged by one too many English classes over the years.  More often than not, I come off sounding like a damn moron... or maybe I always sounded that way, and all of those English classes just helped me to recognize my own moronitude.  Setback: I called today to register for ESL pre-training classes, but it turns out they were completely full for the month.  OK.  August, then.  Now I won't be able to sit down and actually tutor anyone until sometime in September.  Too many do-gooders in this world, I tell you.  This weekend: Friday, I did very little.  Saturday, I tried to see the Grand Excursion, but the boats were late, and it started to rain.  Plus, I didn't care.  Jer and I hooked up PSX controllers to the computer and played some old arcade games via MAME.  You know MAME, right?  Of course you do.  Everyone comes back to MAME once a year to remember just how bad most of the games were they drooled over years ago.  Remember "Narc" and "Bad Dudes"?  Terrible, terrible games ( "I'm bad!" ).  "Final Fight" still seems decent, and thankfully shows that not  all  of those precious quarters were wasted.  Ahh, to be back in the K-mart arcade playing "Altered Beast" and "Time Warriors"...  Sunday, I sat around some more.  While everyone else was watching fireworks, I was sitting through "Fahrenheit 9-11".  In a nutshell: I loved the first ten minutes, including the minimalist title sequence, and the eerie handling of 9-11.  Moore's naked contempt for G.W. is palatable when it's merely being insinuated.  It's less so when he refers to G.H.W. Bush as G.W.'s "daddy"... but then I guess that's what political discourse has become in this country.  As with "Bowling for Columbine", Moore's film is most effective when read at arm's length.  Many of his facts are incorrect, and the things he infers can be completely unfair, but some of the broader strokes (such as our cozy relationship with Saudi Arabia, or the increased fear-mongering of the media in the past few years) invite discussion, which is probably a good thing.  Wild man Dan Nordquist has invited me to post on his new  urlLink video game blog .  See you there.
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got a big pack of PC forms in the mail yesterday, including a few for my fingerprints.  With luck, I'll get an interview scheduled this week or next.  How are you doing?  I'm so happy to hear that!  Not feeling terribly motivated to get outside for some fireworks this evening.  I've been dead tired all day, to tell you the truth.  Spent some time out at my parents' place today, but Peace Corps didn't make the meeting agenda, so the Big News will have to wait a week.  Signed up for Google News Alerts about the Peace Corps today, just to keep my eye on things.  Bleh, I can't seem to eat anything that agrees with me these past few weeks.  I wonder if I have a parasite.
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I received a short E-mail from the local PC recruiter this morning.  They've received my application, so I guess the online form works.  More forms on the way.  Sent a mail to the MLC last night to get signed up for their programs.  ESL tutor pre-training starts next Tuesday.  Marlon Brando died today.
    
</post>



</Blog>