<Blog>

<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever wondered what a  urlLink Bad head, or a head crash  on a hard drive might sound like well wonder no more.  Hitachi has your back, on their support page they have a variety of sounds of HDs crashing and burning so to speak.  Check it out, I'm so going to use this when i'm doing tech support.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seems the wonderful corporate artists at etoy has started an  urlLink etoy.DAY-CARE , it's goals are: etoy.DAY-CARE was established in 2001 to reach the following corporate goals: -to recruit and train outstanding individuals for long term etoy.OPERATIONS                                                          -to research identity issues, group behavior patterns and the creativity potential of children in digital environments                                                          to integrate children into the production of art instead of teaching them about art                                                          -to study future markets and to give etoy a competitive edge                                                          -to test and improve etoy.ART in a playful and innocent environment Why can't i be 10 again!  Seems very cool i'd totally forgottten about etoy.  Reminded me i've also lost track of  urlLink RTMark , i wonder how they are holding up.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A gentleman spends the better part of his life documenting his life, how much does it cost him to make the video $218 roughly, yet when he investigates the cost of the music that he wants to license in the video the price sky rockets to  urlLink $400,000 .  Though i must admit when i read stories like this i have to ask where did he get his camera and tape from?  Also how did he edit this masterpiece?  Last time i checked even a cheap Camera ran about $200 for an extremely low end.  You easily run into the $500 range without batting an eye. And tape even in bulk isn't cheap.  What ticks me off is the ratio, not the exact amounts.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For me i don't have as much free time as i would like to.  I don't have time to create like i used to.  I haven't yet purchased from  urlLink these guys , there price is sorta steep, starting at $299 for a set, or $99 for a clip.  Their samples look quite beautiful, especially as an alpha channel overlay would add character to just about any video i think.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a better way to christen Media Wh0re.  Then to link to a mpeg of a  urlLink Tornado sucks up entire house .  Interesting side note is tapes and pictures of storms and tornadoes were what got me into media, both still and motion.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just getting started.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quite and interesting article,  urlLink VJ Culture: From Loop Industry To Real Time Scenarios .  Makes me wonder if VJing is becoming mainstream will people finally understand what i'm talking about when i say i VJ.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Segways in a hip hop video?   Need i say more.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wish this was a higher quality and that you could actually see him get hit.  But i guess you live with what you get.  Still a decent video of  urlLink a sheriff getting Tasered  to show his support for the weapon
     
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh the joys of  urlLink Crappy Wartime meets Blair Witch Footage  to market a movie or show of some sort.  I love how it's supposed to be "Americans."  First off they look more like journalists more then military.  And what proper self respecting American uses an AK-47?!?  I mean i would use an AK-47 but i don't consider myself a decent American.  Bleh. I guess it's worth watching once, it's free unlike blair witch project was ;).
     
    
</post>

<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is an awesome video of an experiment showing  urlLink sand acting as a liquid 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Some really powerful photos of gang lives take by  urlLink Robert Yager. 
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Canon Announces the XL2  Need we say more.  I've been craving an XL since the first XL1.  Now the XL2, though I still want a  urlLink Panasonic AG-DVX100A .  Guess I just want it all
     
    
</post>


<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Test post.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've seen this before, i mean it's a must it's a freaking DREAMCAST, they stopped making those in like 1998 before they even knew they were making them, in any case my fetish  urlLink grows. 
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Isamu Sawada is an amazing designer.  I wonder if he does design as a profession or simply in his spare time.  I must say i only have mixed feelings about his  urlLink PowerfulBook R6 concept.  Still more amazing then anything i could do.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I always wondered why i didn't make more friends over the telephone now i  urlLink know. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I love aerial photography.  I think it just reveals so much about our cultures and what we find central and how we organize our living environments as a whole around each other.  I guess that's why it's a definite that i'm picking up  urlLink this book. 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My addictiong to  urlLink Hello, Kitty  branded computing merchandise continues to grow.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow if  urlLink this is true.   I maybe almost required to get one.  I truly think it's a dumb idea, i mean come on a game phone.  But i do give them props for certain things like bluetooth wireless gaming.  I mean that seems like such a simple no brainer to me.  Oh well, granted even if i got one it's not like i'd have anyone to play wireless with.
     
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is a decent  urlLink Headset Roundup Review (MobileBurn) , though for some reason i was under the impression that it was every current bluetooth headset out there.  Still quite nice, as i keep searching for the bluetooth headset that i'm gonna get next...after i get a bluetooth phone that is.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A great article on the evolution of the Mac OS  urlLink help system.  
     
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Perfect description  urlLink William Gibson 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok.  So maybe i'm not enough a programmer/developer to understand this, but i have to rant.  WHY OH WHY, do vendors make "simulators" for their hardware products in Java, only to have them only run in windows?!?  They go on and on and on how it's java based and the silulator is written in java as well, shouldn't that mean it can be recompiled for Linux, Mac, etc?!  Argh  
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I must say i truly love my sidekick.  The software is well integrated and the device is a decent size.  The problem is i've been unhappy with the way  urlLink T-Mobile  has been handling the device and it's service specific to it.  There has been a decent amount of hub-bub around  urlLink Danger's  newest incarnation of the device, but no really good pics of it, until  urlLink now  at least.  Though i must say i'm noot sure what i'll do when it's time to replace my sidekick, if i'll upgrade to the newest hiptop, or something else.  I do know one thing, i am not a fan of the  urlLink Treo 600 , like everyone else seems to be.  Perhaps i'll look into a  urlLink blackberry  and get a separate cell phone for voice.  I'd been considering that with my Hiptop for quite sometime now, just can't justify it since i rarely use the phone aspect of it.  Anyone have any suggestions i'd love to hear them.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I thought i was a fanatic for notebooks and pens.  I carry 2-3 pens with me and a pencil and erase with me at all times.  Not to mention 2-3 notebooks for various ideas and categories of notes.  I must say though my pens have slowly been dying out since graduation i've been putting off getting knew pens till  urlLink now .  With that article i know what pens i should get and fill my bag and draw up again.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Following closely on the heals of WiFiFoFum, which allowed a user to see relative position of base stations on a "radar screen" of a WiFi equipped PocketPC.  Now comes  urlLink Open Source Virtual GPS for Wi-Fi. 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Continuing in the veign of cool gadgets, gizmos and Hello Kitty Merchandise.  I present to you:  urlLink FJ!!'s Pink Hello Kitty Laptop 
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I'm certainly behind on the news.  Apparently  urlLink SubEthaEdit  V2.0 was release a couple days ago, I didn't even realize it.  Also looks like they added all the improvements i wanted into it: code completion, line numbering always on, and new window size setting.  In case you don't know the coolest feature of SubEthaEdit is the fact that it allows writers(code, document, etc) to collaborate together using rendezvous.  I'm very much stoked.  So rush out and get it.  Oh best part is it's free.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't have a PocketPC but i keep getting twinges to buy one simply from my gadget addiction kicking in.  That and the fact i don't have one and never used one for extended ammount of time so i can't realize i'd use it as much as my half a dozen Palm Pilots i have laying about.  Then i discover apps like,  urlLink WiFiFoFum , which kicks my gadget addiction, specifically the PocketPC vein into high gear.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hopefully the craziness over the iPod Mini will finally subside with news of  urlLink this  coming out.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I meant to post this a day or two ago but totally forgot oops.  This is the kind of stuff that really pisses me off about big business, specifically the RIAA and MPAA:  urlLink Slashdot | RIAA Loss Report Contradicts Nielsen Sales Record 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Women in Gaming  is a great insight into why "gaming for women" fails.  As i've been saying for years, if you want to understand why it's failing -- asking women will usually generate the proper response.  Unfortunately business and gaming companies usually end up with  urlLink this.   Oh and a side note(being a complete chauvinistic pig to boot) the author is amazingly hot, Stevie Case at least, i can't state how Alice looks as there is only a sketch 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's projects like  urlLink this origami folding robot , that make me realize, i don't have as much of a head for 3D and robotics as i think i do.  It's just amazing stuff, all the different concepts that need to be mastered in order to make such a device.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This  urlLink blog entry  is a perfect example of why i blog and why i feel blogging is important.  It's not about "stating" something as fact.  It's about posting commentary on the world around us and quite often asking for feedback from the community.  I know in past blogs i've ran i've asked questions as many times as i've posted pure commentary.  I think it's just a new idea in media, and it will take time for people to understand exactly WHY it's different the past forms.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I must say, as a gamer and gadget freak, i'm very saddened by the lack of "cool stuff" that America has compared to all the amazingly cool (and mostly useless) stuff Japan has.  I mean i can finally get  urlLink a Hello Kitty memory card for the PS2 ,  urlLink Metal Gear Gamecube Bundle Pack .  It's all only via import.  Come on guys get with it and bring us cool limited editions.  Americans are RIPE for the what seems like the Japanese tradition of owning multiple copies of consoles.  I mean if they brought that gamecube to the US i'd definitely buy a second one.  I'd soo buy a  urlLink FFXI  special edition PS2.  Oh well i just have to be patient and vote w/ my money when i can.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Stilettos and Starbucks  Man why didn't i call my blog THAT.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I wonder if i could fit this in my new apartment,  urlLink Petabox: a 1,000 terabyte array  &  i thought i was being hardcore with my dream rack of XServe RAIDs.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I just found 2 words that probably could be used to describe me.  The first i guess is a good connotation to it.  The second seems like it could be used in both good and bad connotations:  urlLink The Word Spy - technosexual   urlLink The Word Spy - geekerati 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh gawd, now we're going to have PC users saying no wonder Macs suck look how slow they run on my emulator. urlLink Mac Rumors: PearPC - PowerPC/Mac OS X Emulation on a PC 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Neural.it: English content.   Ahh the days of an EMAC student rush through my memory while at this site.  Makes me remember why i hated the program and refuse to become an "artist".
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The new version of playfair,  urlLink hymn -- Hear Your Music aNywhere  which cracks the DRM on tunes purchased from iTunes, but doesn't strip your Unique ID from the file.  I feel this is the best anti DRM software yet.  DRM is a touchy subject and it's still in the process of finding the "right path".  So having tools like this is handy in case said DRM style becomes antiquated.  Though in the end you are still breaking the licensing agreement/law.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink  Fresh Air: Bill O'Reilly Interview .  He doesn't want us to here parts of this interview so of course i need to blog about it and let everyone know to listen to the interview and pass on the fact that he doesn't want people to hear it.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow the new Blogger is really quite sexy.  I must say i didn't think that Blogger could get much better, but this is definitely much better.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i need to get  urlLink Anthony Hamilton's  music.  His music has a real nice sound.  To bad i can't find the link i've used to make iTMS links.  Oh well, you will know how to find the album i'm sure.  EDIT: Oops forgot  urlLink Los Lonely Boys   EDIT: Oops forgot to publish haha but as you can see i re-found the link to format iTMS links again.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Much like cars, some people just shouldn't be allowed to use computers.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Continuing in my pirate radio vein:  urlLink iPod pirate radio bumper stickers .  Not sure how much the FCC would like these but eh, stick it to the man.  Sorry that was horrible but i couldn't help it.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So it looks like my post yesterday about needing being able to make a pocket size radio station has been answered with a  urlLink DIY iTrip Amplifier .  I mean yea we could just broadcast with an iTrip but that's only like 20-30 feet if lucky.  So this is a welcome addition to the collection.
     
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink How-To Tuesday: Make your own Pirate Radio Station with an iPod  Reminds me of my frosh year at RPI when we made a pirate radio stationg that blanketed freshman hill.  The fact there is a possibility to make a pocket size pirate radio station is awesome.  I'm very much for low power pirate radio stations, ahh the good ol' days.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't want one, I NEED  urlLink one .  No seriously, please i'm a sucker for old school film tech.  I have an old school 8MM and i'd have probably half a dozen or more if i still went to yard sales and flea markets like i used to when i was a kid.  The fact i can actually have the look and feel of old film tech and digital internals just makes me more excited then is reasonably expected.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok this is quite old but supposedly people have  urlLink the real dirt on Apple’s Cinema Displays?   While the sizes seem about right as well as the resolutions there are a couple of things that common sense just state don't work.  First of all, switching from the ADC(Apple Display Connector) to DVI.  I think Apple really likes be slick and having as few wires as possible.  With dropping ADC you lose Video, Power and USB all in one cable.  So you would go from 1 cable to 3 cables.  Which brings me to my next point, they state there will be 2 firewire ports on it.  How is this possible since ADC doesn't carry firewire signal and if they do go with DVI there would be neither USB or Firewire.  So now that's 4 wires coming out of this display.  Bleh i wouldn't mind many of these features but just don't see it happening.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sadly right before my switch over, i as well suffered from the delussion that I could  urlLink turn my PC into a Mac .  As the expression goes the interface is just skin deep.  You don't get the true OS X experience.  Well perhaps you can now, as when i did this it was 3 years ago, and the software on the market to do these things was new and buggy.  Still interesting to see, i wonder what the psychological aspects of all this are.  Perhaps there aren't any haha.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have dreams about having an army of robotic artist minions to do my bidding as an artist.  For i seem to think on a more conceptual level and not really good at that whole "creating" bit.  I can think of cool idea but horrible at making content.  Just all about remixing and re-manifesting previous art into my new pieces and now i almost can have my dream with,  urlLink Project K .  So just need more machines making abstract automatic art, preferably which changes over time so that i can incorporate them into my video. Mmmmm robotic artists...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's days like today that i'm still amazed by Apple Computers.  There is all this press about a few pictures of a "new"/"upgraded" g5 that have been leaked, or photoshoped.  Whatever the case may be.  Then they release the  urlLink AirPort Express .  I think several times more amazing then an upgraded G5 will ever be.  I mean i'm looking forward to a bump since i'm in the market for a  urlLink mid range g5  and  urlLink mid range screen .  The fact that they made a complete base station alittle larger then there current powerbricks AND added  urlLink features  to it, just blows me away.  Keep it up Apple and keep me amazed.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So it looks like the web-utility i use to make the beautiful  urlLink Amazon Links  is offline, hopefully it will be back up soon, but just for record i'm now read  urlLink Angels & Demons  and still playing Rainbow Six, though i did pick up  urlLink Full Spectrum Warrior  i haven't had much free time to play it.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh by the way, show you how busy i was yestarday.  I TOTALLY missed my favorite  urlLink OSes  b-day.  Yestarday marked  urlLink Ten Years of BeOS (coverage via slashdot).
     
    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So i was just thinking about sharing tunes via  urlLink rendezvous and wireless networks .  When i realized well i only carry my tunes via my iPod making it useless in this system, then i was like why can't i hook it up to the USB port on the Pocket PC.  Nope, USB is a Master/Slave relationship not Peer-to-Peer like Firewire.  Luckily  urlLink a USB host Compact Flash card  is soon to be released.  Then i realized between USB 1.1 speed, the speed of wireless, and PocketPC speed, this would be gawd awful slow, i still think it would be worthwhile to tinker around with.  I guess i'll still look forward to a company to actually incorporate this sort of sharing into the Mp3 Player of choice for me.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thank you,  urlLink Engadget  for making my day with this choice quote: "Most people still have absolutely no idea what in the hell we’re talking about when we bring up Voice over IP (which is why we’ve long since abandoned it as a pickup line)."  It's the simple things in life right?
     
    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ahhh one of my ultimate favorite trends of the 80's(and continuing on i may add) was the breakdance trend.  I could watch hours and hours of this stuff.  Luckily there appears to be  urlLink Renaissance of Breakin' .
     
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Obligitory  urlLink Hello Kitty Robot  Post.  Just following tradition. ;-).
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Obligitory  urlLink Hello Kitty Robot  Post.  Just following tradition. ;-).
     
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Some really beautifully designed audio hardware being  urlLink Bootlegged into digital Objects 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This set of designer  urlLink Radiators , is to be filed under "tobuy when I'm a millionaire" category @  urlLink del.icio.us .
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hhmmm perhaps i should get these,  urlLink notvanilla braille t-shirts and wearable art; provocative, touchable and interactive , for Cass to wear.  To bad about the flip out description.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      To make up for my lack of posts, here is a really cool, different PDA in fact it's not calling itself a PDA.  It has dubbed itself the TDA(Tactile Digital Assistant.)  Without further ado their web site:  urlLink Welcome to the Jackito-TDA community website 
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok so I'm finally getting settled into my new place which means two things: Me blogging again and a gallery of pics of my new place woohoo.  Though i'll probably post rough pics of what it looks like with what little stuff i have in my apartment then a "finalized" version in about a month when i get the last of my furniture ordered and arrived.  Moving into my first apartment alone you realize how many "holes" you have in personal possessions as roommates seem to offset the need for owning everything.  But i'm excited as i get to order my sofa and bed this week.  Left to get: 2 Desks and Dining Room chairs.  This is a pretty boring post but just an update why i haven't posted anything in SOOO long.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Oh and happy 4th of july by the way.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I need more time in the day where i can just sit and blog all the crap that i come in contact with.  Hopefully when my job application for Millionaire goes through that will be a side job i can pick up.
     
    
</post>

<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok i haven't posted in a while.  I haven't fled the country or locked up or anything bad, just settling into my new apartment and working hard.  So no time to dork out, plus no really comfy spots in my house yet as i don't have a real bed or couches yet, to dork out in.  So not to worry i'll be back soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I sooo need one of  urlLink THESE  it's not even funny and it's only $229 to boot.  Not to mention it comes with Toast 6 Titanium which is a $99 in and of itself!!  Ahh i need more money.  Wonder if Apple will make the leap and make dual layer media.  Here's to hoping.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>