<Blog>

<date>22,May,2002</date>
<post>


       
      This is my new blog, in which I will deliver opinions, ideas, and advice to a grateful world. Hold on to your teacups.
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>


       
           The very first issue of  Gamut , a monthly magazine covering Memphis arts and culture, is on the stands now. I wrote a piece entitled "Saving Soulsville," about the new Stax Music Academy.  urlLink Read  it,  urlLink comment  on it, and then  urlLink subscribe  to  Gamut  so I can keep writing for them.     
     

    
</post>

<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>


       
       PBS didn't run " urlLink The Legendary Liberace " for any high-minded purpose. They threw it in during pledge week a few months ago to squeeze the 55-and-older demographic for cash. Still, it was a hoot.  As a pianist and entertainer, Liberace was pure old-school vaudeville, a hardworking entertainer who did whatever it took to knock 'em dead. From the 1940s to the 1980s he entertained audiences with an act that was more cocktail party than concert. The patter and the occasional songs were just an excuse to show off costumes that leave one  urlLink speechless . Calling his costumes gaudy is just inadequate; it's like calling the ocean wet.  Liberace may be an entertainment footnote today, but in the 1950s the man was  huge . He was the first Vegas superstar -- he opened there in the late '40s when the town had exactly two hotels, and his style is still imprinted in the town's DNA. When the fledgling television networks blew him off, he syndicated himself and ran on more TV stations than "I Love Lucy."  Time hasn't been kind to Liberace's shtick. The jokes fall flat and the music is Welkian dreck. Yet the costumes and staging are so over the top, so beyond any fashion or style, that they never age.  Even more fascinating is Liberace's rapport with his fans. Judging from the video clips, his TV and stage shows attracted a mostly female audience of a certain age, all of whom looked like  urlLink Auntie Em  or  urlLink Dame Edna . It's no mystery why those stolid '50s middle-American matrons went gaga over a borderline drag queen. After all, their stolid '50s middle-American husbands ate red meat at every meal, raised sexual harassment to an art form, and saw a Commie pinko under every rock. Who wouldn't want an alternative?  The  urlLink Liberace Foundation  claims to be the Official Liberace Web site. The  urlLink Estate of Liberace  does too. The  urlLink Liberace Museum  is the Official Animated Twinkling Candelabra site.  The Liberace Museum site carefully avoids any mention of the man's personal life or the cause of his death (complications from AIDS, 1987). The Liberace Estate mentions only his "heart disease and emphysema." At least they said the word "AIDS" on the PBS show.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Poolside at the Sahara. Sky: Caribbean blue. The 14,000-foot wall of Sierra Nevada granite to our west casts a rain shadow that keeps the Las Vegas sky flawless. Of course it also means that Vegas must resort to extreme measures to fill all those pools, water slides, dancing fountains, and hotel showers for more than 30 million visitors each year, not to mention supplying the million-plus people who live here fulltime.  How long can Vegas ignore the fact that it sits in the middle of a bone-dry desert? Probably many decades, given human ingenuity. Eventually Vegas probably will go the way of the Hohokam (an ancient Southwestern Native American civilization that apparently outgrew its water supply), but until then we'll have a great time poolside.  Last night we enjoyed excellent slabs of dead cow at  urlLink Drai's , a high-end joint in the basement of the Barbary Coast Hotel. Good service, nice merlot, and fabulous chocolate fondant. Afterwards, David spent a few tense minutes stuck between floors in a balky and overloaded elevator before it finally lurched back down to the basement level. We then took the stairs.  After that repast, we walked through Caesar's Palace and marveled at the Neronian architecture and the cheesy but fun "living statues" show. Then we made a brief stop at the Mirage, the vaguely Polynesian casino that features Siegfried and Roy, a huge indoor jungle atrium, a dolphin habitat, and a giant volcano fountain which flames higher than Siegfried and Roy put together.  There's great people-watching on the Strip, indoors and out. Vegas is very democratic in some ways. Anyone can wander into a casino, admire the surroundings, use the nice restrooms, watch the spectacles, and not spend a dime. The high rollers might get preferential treatment, but they also get taken to the cleaners to the tune of a few hundred thou a night. We prefer the cheap seats.
     

    
</post>

<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The Spanish had a name for the trail across the desert to what is now Las Vegas. It was "Jornado de Muerta": Journey of Death. Nobody died on our trip from LA to Las Vegas, but after driving Interstate 15 we certainly understood where the Spaniards were coming from.  We departed Santa Monica after enjoying brunch and a walk along Venice Beach with Greg's friend Marie. From that point near the ocean, it took us two hours and 70 miles to get out of Los Angeles and its suburbs. Seventy miles of housing developments, office parks, and strip malls as far as the eye could see. (Okay, the eye couldn't see very far because of the smog, but you get the idea.)  We then climbed a few thousand feet into the high desert of the Mojave. It was brown with patches of beige and an occasional madcap splash of ochre. The Mojave is beautiful in a pitiless and austere way, but not quite the grand empty space you might imagine. Tens of thousands of cars ply I-15 every day between LA and Vegas, so it's far from a lonesome desert trek. It's more like city driving without the city.  Still, we were awed by the Mojave's sheer scale. One valley in particular sticks in our minds: Greg and I topped a hill and saw the interstate stretching away before us. Six lanes of asphalt and endless traffic dwindled to a mere scratch across the sand on the far horizon, where it disappeared over a hill. We used the trip odometer to determine how many miles stood between our initial view of the valley and that final hill. The result: just over 10 miles in one breathtaking glance.  (Note: we got out of LA without posting our impressions of that fair city. We'll catch up asap.)
     

    
</post>

<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Greg and I are about to leave on our  urlLink Great American Road Trip . We had planned to drive all the way back to Memphis from Los Angeles, but Hertz told Greg he could only use his points on round trips. (Thanks Hertz; can you say Avis?) We didn't feel like spending a thousand bucks on a car rental so we quickly redrew our route as a big counterclockwise  urlLink round trip .   We'll spend the first weekend in Los Angeles. We'll stay  urlLink here  and play at  urlLink Universal Studios . We'll also do some sightseeing and visit Greg's friend Marie in Santa Monica.   Then we'll spend about three days in Las Vegas at the fabulous  urlLink Sahara . We want to see as much over-the-top kitsch as possible, so of course we'll hit the  urlLink Liberace Museum . We'll also make our religious pilgrimage to  urlLink Star Trek the Experience .   From there we'll drive on a stretch of old Route 66 and then veer north to the  urlLink Grand Canyon . From there we'll go to  urlLink Sedona  for awhile. After that we're mostly playing it by ear, but the rough itinerary is:     urlLink Meteor Crater    urlLink Painted Desert & Petrified Forest    urlLink Mesa Verde    urlLink Arches, Canyonlands, Capitol Reef, and Zion national parks  in southern Utah  The  urlLink Extraterrestrial Highway  in the Nevada desert, with obligatory stop at the  urlLink Little A'Le'Inn  in Rachel  Across the Sierras through  urlLink Yosemite  assuming Tioga Pass is open. If not, we'll do one of these:    A northerly route through Sonora Pass on 108 or on I-80; or  A southerly route down the gorgeous desert highway 391    Thence across the amazingly Delta-like Central Valley as quickly as possible  Down the Pacific coast on  urlLink Highway 1  back to Los Angeles    Will we be snowed in on a mountain pass and forced to eat human flesh or, worse, Taco Bell? Will we bliss out in an energy vortex at Sedona and move into a teepee? Will the aliens join us in Nevada or maybe LA? Stay tuned. 
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Today was a perfect March day: sunny, warm, and windy as hell. Our friend Charlie invited us to join him at Overton Park for an afternoon of kite-flying with his son Justin.  I took the new camera phone and recorded the hijinks.  urlLink View the slideshow .
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After four and a half years, Greg and I are certain that we're stuck with each other for the duration. Who else would put up with our unique collection of neuroses?  With commitment comes a long-term perspective. You know whose face you're going to see first thing every morning. That face isn't going anywhere, come hell or high water or another Republican president. It's a big load off, that kind of reassurance. It frees up a lot of time and energy. It lets one wrap one's mind around big long-term commitments, like a 30-year mortgage. And marriage. And parenthood.    Mortgage? Done that.  I bought a little place just before I met Greg, but it was too small for two fully equipped geeks and all their gear. It also wasn't in Midtown, as Greg reminded me every few minutes while we lived there. So two and a half years ago we bought a bigger place. The neighborhood is quiet and the neighbors are delightful. Most importantly, it is Inside The Parkways. (You can  hear  the capital letters when dedicated Midtowners say those words - see "Midtown 101" below.)   Marriage? We’re trying.  We’ve been talking about it off and on about it for years, but San Francisco’s big open-hearted invitation to come and get married got us off our butts. We made an appointment for 1:30pm Thursday, April 8, at San Francisco City Hall, but the California Supreme Court canceled it for us. We’re still going to do a proper wedding here in Memphis this summer; stay tuned for details.   Adoption? We’re jumping in.  I’d never really given adoption a lot of conscious thought, but I put the whole parenthood question on “simmer” a long time ago. My decision-making tends to be long and drawn-out, with oceans of self-doubt, mountains of anxiety, and tar pits of depression. It’s a big old mess, so I tend to keep it all to myself where it won’t bother anyone else. Sometimes I keep the debate so tightly bottled up I don’t even know much about it myself. Then one day I’ll wake up with my decision and announce it to myself and whatever part of the world is interested.  In this case the announcement – to myself and the interested part of the world, in this case Greg – came at  urlLink Melange , where we spend way too much of our spare time and money. We were talking about something, I mentioned kids, and Greg asked something like “So you want to adopt a kid?” And I nearly boo-hooed and said, “Yeah. I do.”  Since that night we’ve been researching our options: Domestic or international adoption? Open or closed? Baby or older kid? Boy or girl? We currently lean toward a domestic open adoption of a baby boy. If it came down to it we’d be just as thrilled with a little girl, but we feel we’d understand a boy better. Girls seem pretty understandable until they hit that bizarre horse-fixation stage, and then it’s all downhill.  The Tibetans talk about “tulpas,” thought-creations so vividly imagined that they take on physical form. Our little tulpa’s name is Junior. We talk about fixing up a room for Junior, changing Junior’s diapers, picking a school for Junior, taking Junior on trips. At times we can almost hear Junior running around the house. Here’s hoping our tulpa becomes a real boy soon.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
         For you non-Memphians, here's a quick tour of the most fabulous part of Memphis:  Midtown is a collection of leafy bungalowed neighborhoods and busy commercial streets located between downtown Memphis and the vast postwar suburbs. ( urlLink Here's a map .)  Midtown developed mostly in the 1910s and '20s as a streetcar suburb. A few neighborhoods like our own Lenox began even earlier, growing up around scattered train stations in the late 19th century when Memphis was still far to the west. Lenox boasts a pre-Civil War farmhouse and a handsome little 1880s Italianate among the early 20th-century bungalows and late 20th-century townhouse condos.  Midtown gained its traditional boundaries in 1902, when the parkway system was created. North Parkway runs east-west between the river and Midtown's Overton Park. East Parkway runs north-south between Overton Park and a point just south of the Mid-South Fairgrounds. There it meets South Parkway, which runs east-west between the fairgrounds area and Martin Luther King Jr. Riverside Park.  The Parkways are grand residential boulevards in the New Orleans tradition. Traffic runs on either side of broad, wooded medians. The parkways pass through a fine representative sample of Midtown's neighborhoods, from shotguns to bungalows to mansions.  Freeways and factories have claimed a few small stretches, but the modern parkways are astonishingly close to the original beaux-arts vision.  Midtown occupies most of the space inside the parkways. Orthodox Midtowners draw the boundary at the parkways to the north, east, and south, and I-240 to the west. Reform Midtowners admit the Vollentine-Evergreen neighborhood just beyond North Parkway and maybe Chickasaw Gardens to the east. A few crazed radicals draw the line as far east as Highland Street.  No matter where the precise boundaries fall, most Midtown neighborhoods share a few key characteristics: big old trees, older homes of all sizes, shops and bars and restaurants clustered around long-gone streetcar stops, more big old trees, 1920s Spanish Colonial apartment buildings with tile roofs and broad porches, handsome churches, rich folks and poor folks, gay and straight, white and black and Vietnamese and Hispanic, and did I mention big old trees.  There are other lovely and livable neighborhoods in Memphis, but for those of us Inside the Parkways - or slightly past the parkways, or even out to Highland - Midtown is it.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Today Greg and I took a guided hike through Overton Park's old-growth forest, a few hundred acres of never-logged, rarely disturbed forest right in the middle of Midtown. The hike was sponsored by Park Friends, Inc., a group of volunteers who work to preserve the forest from the predations of kudzu, bureaucrats, and other invasive species.  This is  my  idea of getting in touch with nature: strolling through a hushed cathedral-like forest five minutes from our front door and two minutes from a charming apres-hike lunch on the terrace at Bosco's.  Take your own hike through the woods:  urlLink view the slideshow  now.
     

    
</post>


</Blog>