<Blog>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yet another TV Channel. This time it's called Zoom and comes from the Times group (Publishers of Times of India, Economic Times, Indiatimes, Femina and so on.    This channel will most probably be launched at the end of the month 28th August being a tentative date.  Professed to be aimed at the urban young, hip and happening is supposed to appeal to the consuming public.  Some of the programs to come  Page 3 (If it is from the house of Page 3, then how can there not be a program called Page 3) Not Just Page 3 ( The opposite of Page 3) Item Number Girl hunt (After the hunt for pop stars, film stars and what not, a hunt which is finally interesting... The hunt for Item number girls)  I'll be getting to see some of the pilots next week. so full reviews of them then...
    
</post>


<date>31,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm looking for the mp3 of the Gary Barlow song Open Road. If anybody has links to it pls email  urlLink me 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      my new email address  urlLink chirag@chiragpatnaik.com 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Kota is the place of the day, this city has the unique distinction in India to be the host for different kinds of power plants namely, Thermal, Hydroelectric and Nuclear power plants. Your's truly has visited them all. This city is also in the western state of Rajasthan. It is very hot here in the Summer and almost nobody uses an Air Conditioner. This place afforded the only stability for any length of time. As I did my Class 10th 11th and 12th here. Had a generally fun time, as everybody does in the final years of school. We visited a lot of places in Rajasthan from here. Jaipur, Jodhpur, Bikaner, Bharatpur(the bird sanctuary), Mathura and had almost decided to go to Delhi in the same trip but wiser counsel prevailed.   I will want to go to this place, just to revive the memories of the good old days of school and the like.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>30,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Domains domains and more domains, I want more
     

 
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
       My posts to the blog will still be daily though erratic. This is because of me going underground to prepare for the upcoming interview in Calcutta, so I need to get in Shape and real fast that too. Anybody who has a magic bullet for weight loss may please contact  urlLink me . That's all for today folks.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      The next city in the current series is Allahabad. This city lies on the confluence of the three rivers the Ganges, the Yamuna and the Saraswati. However, if you pick up the Atlas, you'll see that there are only two rivers. What about the  third  river? Well! it is mythological. Yes that's right it's Mythological. it is reputed that the river Saraswati flowed there and due to some event (I don't remember what) it went underground out of shame. The rivers in India have been personified, that's how the shame factor comes into the picture.   Anyway back to the city, A nice city to live in. I did my class sixth and seventh here in different schools, namely the St Joseph's College and The Kendriya Vidyalaya, Manauri. After this city I've always studied in Kendriya Vidyalayas(Central Schools in Hindi). Amazingly there is nothing very remarkable about this city as far as modern times go. But this city is steeped in Indian Mythology. Lord Ram is said to have been here during his 14 years of forced exile. Another feature of this place, the roots of a Banyan tree which gives of leaves(you've got to see it to believe it), the very same Banyan tree is said to be several Millenia old and the British even tried to set it afire (out of plain old Malice)so that we'd lose this part of our heritage, but this tree survived and is said to be one of the largest trees in India.  There is also a tunnel which is said to go all the way from Allahabad to Delhi. People have tried to follow this tunnel but it ends due to a rockfall some distance inside. I was here during the infamous Babri Masjid (Mosque) Demolition. That was one shameful aspect of India's modern history, when a bunch of Hooligans decided to break down the Mosque. There was a lot of tension because of the demolition and the Army had to do Flag Marches and the like in certain localities to calm things down a bit. I was also here during the infamous Anti Mandal Commision riots. The riots took place because of the provision for reservation for the Backward classes in the Government jobs and other government owned and operated institutions. A lot of heartburn took place in this country because of that one man who was responsible for this. The amazing part is that man is alive and hopes to enter active politics again. (To dispel any confusion it was not Mr Mandal, But Prime Minister VP singh who actually implemented the commision report and is thus reviled for the reason).  I probably will never want to come back here again, simply because there is nothing to come back to. 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>29,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      And the Indian TimeZone in Blogger still does not work.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm registering domain by the dozen, u'r right I've nothing better to do.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      hI've made  a new graphic for u ppl to link to.   urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm sick of looking for travel quotes for a round trip to the US. I was looking for the cheapest one available, but no luck so far. I'm playing rinra-ringa-roses and they send me from one place to another. Why am i looking for a round trip ticket to the US? Cause my Mum has to go towards June this year. and what about me? not for another 10 years at least.  PS If anybody can help me, please email  urlLink me . with quotes of flights, to New York from Bombay (or Mumbai) on the first sunday of June and returning around the the second week of August (yah, a very long time).
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Today's city is Srinagar, to those who haven't heard of Srinagar, it is the Summer Capital of Jammu and Kashmir, with Jammu being the Winter Capital. It is not a very hospitable place now, due to the activity of Pakistani Terrorists in the Valley. It is now a non family station for people like My father meaning families of Defence Personnel and the like are not allowed there. Srinagar is famous for its Gardens by the Mughal Emperors of India in the Medeival ages, and also the Houseboats on the Dal Lake. House Boats are just that Houses on Boats, and are now used as tourist hotels. Correction,  were  used as tourist hotels, due to the activity of Pakistani Terrorists, no tourists. Not only bad for tourism but also for the local people, as tourism is the mainstay of the local economy.   There will be sometime before normalcy returns, but it is unlikely as the Pakistani Government survives on Pure Hate. If India vanishes tommorow the whole country of Pakistan will collapse. or maybe not they already have America to hate and Russia and...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      the city of the day coming up in a couple of hours
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I rated 75 out of 100 on the  urlLink suave-o-meter .  It says:  You are quite the Casanova! You know how to play the dating game, and you're damn good at it! Most likely, you are a woman magnet and you are never without an admirer. It appears that you have an incredible amount of charm, and your attentive and sensitive demeanor makes you irresistible. You have definitely been taught well. You know how to treat a woman, and you make sure that she feels special and appreciated by yours truly. You have a knack for expressing yourself and showing your interest, without looking too eager. That is a difficult balancing act, and you deserve a pat on the back for perfecting it. At the rate you're going, you won't be dating much longer before you score your dream girl!   I don't have a girlfriend, and with my looks never will too.  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I decided to add a few blogs on my page, then I realised that my blog would come (if at all) on other peoples blogs way down in the bottom, so I've decided to change the name of my blog to  A Blog Formerly Known As My Ramblings and Rants . hahahah I'm  Invincible . I may not be original, but I'm invincible.   urlLink Tracy  dropped a line saying I'm a lazy bum (not quite) haha. she actually asked which blogs were abusive. I say all of them heeheehee.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      logging fr the day. 2morrow is a brand new day
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      The more I use it the more it convinces me Netscape  sux  period
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Netscape sux, I installed netscape to see how my pages look in Netscape. totally unreadable. Hence the conclusion, Netscape sux
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I/m bored i think I'll go drown myself in a bag full of chips
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      for a list of all the places I've been to got to  urlLink places.chiragpatnaik.com 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Today's place is called Naugam, this place is so far from civilisation that the nearest School is 35 Kms away, cool eh? You might also be interested to know that this place lies in the Kashmir Valley is right on the LoC with Pakistan. So sensitive is this place that one is not allowed to use crackers for  Diwali . A nice place to visit for a while but horrible place to stay. a lot of picnic spots next to mountain streams and brooks, and also a lot of hiking trails, camping out is really fun here. There is no animal threat of anykind except for the occasional Leopard and the like.  Last Words: Nice place wish I could visit every Year, Unfortunately can't because of Pakistani Terrorists which makes this a non family station. Maybe in a century hence it'll be peaceful again, till then sigh
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      today's town will have to wait for another couple of hours.  For those who cam ein late, I'm doing a series of writeups on the towns and cities I've visited over the past fifteen years. You can the read about the ones before in the blog or the archives
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I think I'll take a break now. for lunch that is  I'll be back 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      damn thing still don't work, the timezone that is
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm registering domain names by the dozen, get on to the band wagon to at  urlLink namezero . you could visit  urlLink my site  too for more details.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Yesssssss! I've done it, I've my own domain at  urlLink www.chiragpatnaik.com . Long live free enterprise long live the free net. hurrrah
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I think I'll sign off fr today I've had enuff. Our team needs help some serious help
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      why doesn't the Indian timezone work in  urlLink blogger . They gotta fix it
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Fight buggers fight we gotta win this one. In case u'r wondering what I'm talking about go  urlLink here  for a live scoreboard and match details
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      India is losing, damn damn damn, we ought to stop playing cricket for a year or two maybe even a decade or two
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      You really should try  urlLink Human click , Lets u keep in touch with u'r visitors
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm having a generally a fun day today have been online for quite some time now and will be for some time to come, hope the day never ends. if anybody is a Caesar 3 freak like pls contact  urlLink me . 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My url isn't yet active, will be in  24 hrs and then a couple days for me to put up something on it
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I have a new url, www.chiragpatnaik.com, for free. Get u'r URL at  urlLink NameZero 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      By the way, when prez Clinton left India for Pakistan he had to use a decoy plane, The secret service feared the plane would be shot down by stinger missiles in Pakistan. Stinger missiles in Pakistan? well they were supplied with gay abandon to the Afgani's during the Afganistan war. and now are in the hands of the Pakistani terrorists.  The best part is yet to come. The CIA tried to buy back the Stingers, then they said they'd pay for photographs of the broken stingers. yes ppl it's all true, it's all happening here, the most happening place on this planet.  The  Nuclear flashpoint in this world.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Todays town is Nasirabad. this town is in the Western state of Rajasthan, this place is extremely hot in the summers and has a perenial water shortage. Nearby places of interest include Ajmer which has the Dargah(shrine) of someone famous (forgot who it was). it is rumoured the emperor Akbar himself had come here and had had his prayers fulfilled. I did class 2 and 3 here, in Battle Axe Montessori and the St. Anslem's School. Last words Okay place, absolutely no crime and I don't wanna go there again, ever..
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      new look to my site and blog, hope u like it. The old look was ripped of  urlLink Tarsh's  Blog. The New look is mine, sorry to Tarsh and thanks to  urlLink Doug Miller 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm Back frm B'bay. Had a great exam, hope for an interview call. funny thing was there were a few errors in the exam paper. will post details in 12 hrs time, also will continue on my continuing series on the places I've visited.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm leaving for Bombay in an hour so see y'all after two days sunday eveneing or monday morning my time
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      have added the  urlLink webloggers  code 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Blogger is now on the IRC on DalNet type /join #blogger in u'r irc client to join the channel
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'll be going to b'bay again tommorow, so there'll be no post tommorow or day after, why am I going to B'bay so often? you ask. Well! I'm looking for a place to study. I'll be also going to calcutta in the Second week of April. Why? this time for a job. (I call it a paid holiday)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      The next place I'm writing about is Wellington, no it is not the Wellington you're thinking of. This Wellington is in the Southern Indian state of Tamil nadu, My father was here for his Staff College Course at the Defence Services Staff College. This place too served as a jump of point visit several Southern Indian cities like Mysore, Chennai (Madras) and the like. The hill station Oooty is just a stones throw away from here. There are two ways to get to Wellington. One is to take a bus from the nearest Railhead Coimbatore, and the other is to take the toy train, just joking, it's actually a metre gauge train which has a third rail in between the two tracks to provide traction while climbing the steep hill sides. again a very Picturesque location. I did Class 1 and half of Class 2 here, we had stayed here for only 1 year. I studied in a school called the Holy Angels. The year of stay 1985.   Last words: A very sleepy town, absolutely no crime, ideal retirement home, I could live here, in 50 years time
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Did you people hear, Windows (primitive version) source code has been leaked, I'm looking for it, if nebody knows where, please mail me. I want it, I want it. Why? you ask. Obviously so that I can be the next Bill gates, hehehehe
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      The first place I'm writing about is a place called Yol Camp, This town is based on a hillside in the Kangra district in the state of Himachal Pradesh. This place is near Dhramsala, which more famous due to the the Tibetan Government in exile. I've lived in this town twice, the first time when Iwas doing kindergarten, and then more recently in class 8th and 9th. I remember a few things from my first stay. I used to go to a school called the Sacred Heart School, which is about 8 KM away from Yol. And the other time I studied in Kendriya Vidalaya (Central School).   This place has a lot of temples around it. This place also served as a jump of point to visit other cities and towns in North India, like Pathankot, Jammu, Vaishno Devi(a very big pilgrimage spot). A very picturesque locale. As the whole town is based on the hillside, and the roads up the hill are inclined at a 70 degree angle, and is wont to happen, a lot of accidents take place.   Last words: A very Sleepy Town, absolutely no crime, ideal retirement home (let me otta here)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I will be puting up daily reviews of the places I've visited over the last 15 years, since I don't remember anything previous to that(I'm 20). I'll be posting to the blog first and the same will be availablke thru links on my website. It'll give some continuity to the blog and something for me to post everyday.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Sylloge is holding a 5k contest. The idea is to be creative with the 5k page size limit, this includes the images, scripts, etc, etc. for more details visit  urlLink the 5k Award 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Hello ppl, This is a brand new day (when isn't it), not very original I admit(Whoopie Goldberg in Sister Act 2), but a brand new day anyhow.   If you've heard about the recent Massacare in Kashmir my Pakistani terrorists, and feel outraged, please drop a line to your respective head of state, please also feel free to drop me a line at  webmaster@india.4mg.com  Personally I think we should retaliate in kind, 10 for every one of ours is fair enough. If that does not stop 100 for one is even fairer. If I have some smart alec who says an eye for an eye will make the world go blind, I don't mean an eye for an eye, I mean  two  eyes for an eye, we are already half blind, lets blind them altogether.  A full fledged Pentium capable PC can be made under $200, using a netappliance called i-opener by  netpliance corp . This device originally runs a  Real Time OS called  QNX . Those who don't know what a real time OS is, please visit the QNX website and see their demo at  www.qnx.com .  Just how do u do this amazing thing, go to  www.linux-hacker.net/iopener/  for more details. Don't worry the machine does not run exclusively Linux as the website indicates. It runs others too (Windows, BeOS). By the way if anybody has a recent BeOS CD (The one I have is way too old) lying about and could take the time and expense to send it to me, I'd be very grateful. Email me for more details at  cpatnaik@email.com .   If you are the anti establishment kind, you may want to visit  www.2600.com/news/1999/1112.html  for lowdown on DeCSS. 2600.com is looking for mirrors for deCSS, (yep that's the DVD ripper). Though I fail to see, how encryption would have prevented piracy, one needs only to copy the disc.  In other news a Billionaire wants to start a net Univ for free read all about it on  wired   A long entry, as you'd have guessed this was done offline. What to do? Web is very expensive in this part of the world. ;) Cheerio, I really am hoping that they'd devise a way to update by email, and while they're at it also an offline client (I know know, totally contrary to the spirit of a blog, but no harm wishing it)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>21,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I finally decide to add the webring code for the webring by  urlLink  jish  will add another soon.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Am not able to put in my bit regularly, the web is expensive here, hope these guys will figure out how to update the blog by email. I encourage you to send me some email, so that I update this more often. Am quite busy these days with interviews and exams for both jobs and education. either way I'll be able to be online longer sio i can post more such thotless thots
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      sorry ppl, had gone to B'bay for an interview, will be more regular from now on send me mail if you get the opportunity
     

 
    
</post>

<date>10,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      There is this cool contest on the latest issue of PCQuest  urlLink www.pcquest.com  on e-speak and apllications ( urlLink www.e-speak.net ). e-speak is being promoted by HP ( urlLink www.hp.com ).   There's this cool new service called blogger at  urlLink www.blogger.com  allows you to keep a blog (weblog. try it out, it's cool and it's the next big thing to hit the web after hotmail  urlLink www.hotmail.com .  Am applying to PC Quest for a job, yup they've done it again and called for recruitment.  Cheerio
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Hi ppl, my navigation system for india.4mg.com is in place click  urlLink here   to see it. then rigth click on the page to see the menu.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>08,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My first post to my blog,  Those Paki's (Pakistanis)ought to be fried in hot oil, maybe even roasted in the warm glow of Nuclear radiation.   In brief the rant is as follows: Pakistan (a country with delusions of grandeur) claims that Kashmir is a part of their country, when actually it is part of mine. Their (The Pakis) country has been a breeding ground for terrorists like a piece of rotten wood is a breeding ground for Fungus. I believe that the Western media has still not emerged from their cold war mindset, is shown by the fact that whatever India does is a Human rights violation and whatever the terrorists do are legitimate acts towards freedom. Also seen in their attitude in Chechnya. When the Russians bombed that place to oblivion, it was a gross violation of Human rights, when Americans and the rest did the same in Yugoslavia it was a fight for the good of mankind (certainly not that of the Yugoslavians)  Do hungry people a favour click on this link  urlLink The Hunger Site     Have decided to implement a new navigation system for my website which is located at  urlLink http://india.4mg.com . Free traffic is welcome anytime.   Will be posting once a day from now on, all my Ramblings and Rants are copyright me i.e Chirag Patnaik
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,March,2000</date>
<post>


       
      This is the first post, with many more to come, stay tooned
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      i found another free phone call to the US service  urlLink here .
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      bye again, this time for some days
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm 21 today.  What a glorious day
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My posts are going to be more and more erratic till I get back from Calcutta and Bhubaneswar grand tour, from my interview and holiday, so please bear with me. You'll also note the change in writing style, which has now become staid and stilted, I dunno what's come over me and all that, perhaps the tension of the upcoming results and interview.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My posts are going to be more and more erratic till I get back from Calcutta and Bhubaneswar grand tour, from my interview and holiday, so please bear with me. You'll also note the change in writing style, which has now become staid and stilted, I dunno what's come over me and all that, perhaps the tension of the upcoming results and interview.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My posts are going to be more and more erratic till I get back from Calcutta and Bhubaneswar grand tour, from my interview and holiday, so please bear with me. You'll also note the change in writing style, which has now become staid and stilted, I dunno what's come over me and all that, perhaps the tension of the upcoming results and interview.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My posts are going to be more and more erratic till I get back from Calcutta and Bhubaneswar grand tour, from my interview and holiday, so please bear with me. You'll also note the change in writing style, which has now become staid and stilted, I dunno what's come over me and all that, perhaps the tension of the upcoming results and interview.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My favourite place of the lot is Pune. This maybe so because I did my graduation here and lived here foir two years in a hostel.I visit this place once in a couple of months, the fact that this place is only 4 hrs away also helps. A very very nice place to live in, I'd like to live here, if I I get a job or something like that. This place is a 4 hour train ride from Bombay, and a retirement city so to speak. though it is changing for the better now. It is more and more becoming a young persons city, somewhat like Bangalore.  God I love this city, wish I could stay here for ever.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      The city of the day coming up in two hours
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      That's all folks for today
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,April,2000</date>
<post>


       
      From the West of the Country I went all the way to the North East. The next city I lived in was Guahati. This city is the largest in the entire North Eastern Part of India. It has a very famous temple called the Kamakhya which has been filthly maintained. Also famous in this region is the Assam Silk Saree, which was exported by my Mother to all her relatives all over the country and abroad. We went to several places in Assam and the neighbouring states. Some of the places we went to were Cherapunji(Highest Rainfall in the world). We also went to the Kaziranga National park, famous for the One Horned Rhino. Generally an okay city if you can put up with the people who cannot speak English or Hindi properly and not to mention the fact, that they invariably mispronounce your name. An interesting superstition is that  you cannot leave Assam unless you have crossed the Bramhaputra at least seven times. If you do leave before you have done so, you are destined to come back. I don't think I want to go back to this place again simply because there is nothing to go back to or for.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2000</date>
<post>


       
      My net connection expired so no blogging. Am not very regular these days, will try and be so from now on.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Will get back to regular blogging frm tommorow. goodnight
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2000</date>
<post>


       
      And I'm bad 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2000</date>
<post>


       
      I'm back 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2000</date>
<post>


       
      guess so anyway i'm off for a couple of days got an interview for the Times School of Marketing wish me luck
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2000</date>
<post>


       
      Is blogger finally working 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I wonder if anybody in India reads newsgroups                my new timepass, newsgroups     
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      dunno for how long though
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,January,2001</date>
<post>


       
      oh well i'm back
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I wonder when will blogger fix that time glitch. India timezone still doesn't show :(
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      another day begins, wonder what this has in store. I downloaded the new  urlLink Internet Explorer  Beta here, with smart tags et al. Must say the Outlook splash screen looks mind blowing. It seems to be more stable than the earlier preview release. The smart tags are neat, but I wonder as to how useful they might prove in the course of ordinary browsing??
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Bah that Tom Clancy book Line of Control sucks, no sense of reality or perspective
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I think I shall call it a day today too many mp3's today  will try out that morpheus bit tomorrow 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I wish I were out selling space instead better than sitting here doing nothing
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I hope my job is like my internship all play little work :)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      and how
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      with a bang
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,July,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm back
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      Today is the Brand Equity Quiz. The  largest  Quiz show in Asia. Pity I can't take part... Why? Cause My Company is hosting it... boo hoo.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      ok I'm going back to work now. I have to do a research presentation on The Times of India in the city of Delhi. Times of India for those who don't know is the world's  largest  English Broadsheet publication... and is part of the Bennet Coleman and Co Ltd. India's  largest  Media house bar none :)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I just realised that the line was pretty lame and I have used it before... bah!
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I'm back and like how. I finally have net access at the office...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2001</date>
<post>


       
      I really really must update this blog more often...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      After two weeks of long days and nights I think I'lll be able to leave office at a decent time from tomorrow.  I was preparing a  media manual for Nokia... lots of time spent... I hope the effort was worth it... I guess I come to know when I present it to the client  But that is tomorrow, today I got to get back to work...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>19,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      BTW, Martin Sorrell bought over a sister (our host) agency Bates. Which means our host will probably cease to exist ina  few months time... which makes me wonder as to what happens to my agency? 25% of which is now owned by WPP, and the rest is owned by WPP's arch (and bigger) rival Publicis... the word that comes to mind is B...... :|  that the agency parentages are somewhat complicated is an understatement...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I now have to check all the billing figures over the past 4 months to see how much more money is left for spending on TV... boring is not even beginning to say it...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm pretty pleased with myself... I learnt how to make a channel recommendation all by myself... and all in one night... :D
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      it is 4:45 AM and I'm still at work... there is a lesson in this for everyone...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Monsoon seems to have finally hit delhi... to celebrate I drove through driving rain (on my scooter) from home to office (about 10Km's)... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm bored... I think I'll drown myself in a bag of chips and a large cheese and pepperoni pizza...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      from today I'm the sole media planner on the Nokia account :)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Nehru's policies  urlLink evil? 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have  commenting system  in the blog now... so if you feel like yapping back at me or commenting at particular post, feel free...  I'm also testing various counters... so the page hit counters you see on the side will keep on changing from time to time... some times you may find two or more... :)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      More on Cellular data in India,   No. of Cellular Subscribers by   urlLink Circle   & by   urlLink Providers  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Have been doing some work on  cellular service providers  in the country (India), Click  urlLink here  to have a look at the various brands available in the various circles...  More stuff coming up on this...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It is said that if Newton had not discovered the principles of Gravity, somebody else surely would have. This has been proved time and again, Ramanujam reputedly singlehandedly calculated all the mathematical principles that the world had done in the for the past 100 years or so, because nobody told him that someone had already done so...  Why am I talking about this?  I thought it might be neat idea to use WiFi as a third standard for 3rd gen mobile telephony (apart from GSM, CDMA), by piggybacking VoIP on WiFi. simpe isn't it.   It turns out that half the world is already working on it... Not only working on it but a search for  urlLink it  tells that it is talking about it like crazy. And not only working on it & talking about it, but also taking steps to counter/co-opt it, as last month's (sorry can't lcoate it online) issue of wired reports...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I may not get to see preview release of The Matrix Reloaded today, and that makes me very sad... Why? I have to take over the Nokia account, and the handing over takes place today and will take the whole of evening... :((((((((
     

 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I thought mega retail outlets were not making money, apparently they are, because  urlLink RPG  is spending a lot of moeny...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Dettol  urlLink is not  an antiseptic soap... gosh!! I would have never known... I remember my branding prof back in college saying "Dettol means *protection*"... Hee Hee :D
     

 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm a marketeers delight, I'm also on the market for an mp3 player, this  urlLink SlimX 550  is one of the ones that made the shortlist. A  urlLink review  of the same.   More models that were considered...  urlLink SlimX 400 ,   urlLink SlimX 350   Though I'm tending towards a Hard Drive Player...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Super Fast Computer  for ten facts about the internet...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      So you thought economics was a nutty subject... In   urlLink What's the difference between working for money and playing for money?   Kottke comments on virtual economies interacting with the one in the real world...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm going to be buying a bike soon... A  urlLink Pulsar  is what I have finally settled on. the specs on the Bajaj site are totally out of date. Rumours have it that Pulsar is going to be out with a 250cc variant. Will wait for that.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink More  on CAS Chaos, this time the research focuses on consumers rather than the commercial interests.   It's a research report, so one can't comment, but one guesses that far more people will go in for the boxes than the research suggests, even at the higher prices mentioned. TV is too much of a basic necessity for families to ignore. What will they do in spare time? go and take a walk in the park or hit the football field, like the old days? not bloody likely.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Found  urlLink this  awesome piece of code  urlLink here . which allows you to convert any summary sheet/table into a database list!!! cool... eases work so much. aahhh...  There is a slight error in the code, but if you are familiar with Excel VBA, you should be able to fix it in a snap... :)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Nice quote for the day...  "There's a warder who's fond of me. I don't ask why, I've learnt to take what's there without questioning the source. When he sees me on all fours scrabbling at the earth in a random-looking way that is quite scientific, he gets upset and hurries over with the spade and offers to help me. Especially, he wants me to use the spade. He doesn't understand I want the freedom to make my own mistakes."   ~from "The Passion", by Jeannette Winterson
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Matrix Reloaded here I come... I get to see the preview release this Thursday... :D
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I went  urlLink ego surfing  today...   A search for  urlLink Chirag Patnaik  on Google, throws back one of yours truly's websites which I mentioned  urlLink yesterday .   A Search for Chirag on the other hand shows nothing... :(
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
        Does advertising have variations across the year?   was a question asked.  Of course. and it varies differently for different categories. As a broad and general statement for print, advertising peaks in October, with an immediate fall in November. For the rest of the year it is more or less at a stable level, except for a slight dip in Feb, April and July.   Of course there is also the fact that there will be individual variations for different categories... woollens, cars, computers for obvious reasons.  Then there are special events like the world cup, which would bring about huge swells in spends. This last world cup showed a monitored swell of 50% on print... amazing is the only word I can think of
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink INDIAN LINKS  was one of my earlier efforts at websites. The attempt was to test stuff like Javascript, seeding search engines for better rankings and general stuff like that.   The search engine rankings worked (for sometime at least), I was number ONE on Altavista for some time... and once I even did a story on manipulating search engine rankings for  urlLink Education Times   Had never heard of software like Frontpage, so did everything, believe it or not in Windows Notepad.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink In Indian context FTV is truly an ADULT channel!  From the looks of it... this gent is watching a lot of it... ;)  elsewhere someone mentions that there is no advertising on FTV except for Sienna.  not true,  We bought tons of FTV for Nokia...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CAS  (Conditional Access System) was supposed to be a boon for the viewer, with the promise of cheaper cable. Option of choosing only the pay channels one wants to watch. More accountability of the cable operator towards the braodcaster.  Instead it has brought uncertainity... worst case being talked about is that the four cities just drop of the Satellite TV map of the country on July 14th (the date of implementation in the four metros). Bah!   Thank God I never bought a TV...  More on CAS from  urlLink agencyfaqs.com 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink exchange4media  reports that there might be a shift of ad revenues from TV to print due to CAS (Condional Access System)...  Nonsense.   I think (like the other Media Planners quoted in the story) nothing of the sort is going to happen. Silly to assume, that post CAS viewership and readership patterns will change... In fact if the promise of cheaper cable comes through. one might have more people opting for a cable connection.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My most favourite quote for today...  In between goals there is something called life, which has to be lived and enjoyed...   :)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It's Monday morning and I'm blue...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Drew's Blog  comments on something I've been looking for, for quite some time... He mentions Radio. I've heard of Radio... Expensive... sigh!
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Saturday Morning! Work... Bah!
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink ETC Punjabi  is throwing a party on their 3rd Anniversary today at  urlLink The Ashok ... yay. I'm off straight to the party from Office...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Some people commented that this was a new thing and they had read about it in the magazines...  Not True!  Look up my  urlLink archives , they date back to 2000. (I just kinda dropped out of the scene.) and there were people blogging  years  before I was...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For the people who are visiting this place and have no idea about what is a blog... here is a brief intro...  A Blog is short for WebLog. It is nothing but a personal online journal. In my case as the description on the side says, it is "The Ramblings and Rants of somebody in particular about everything in general..." :).  If you need pointers on how to get one for yourself, do drop  urlLink me  a mail...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The Website of my college,  urlLink The Times School of Marketing .   I Did it :)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My Favourite Quote for Today...  "To laugh often and much; to win the respect of intelligent people and the affection of children, to earn the appreciation of honest critics and endure the betrayal of false friends; to appreciate beauty, to find the best in others; to leave the world a bit better...to know even one life has breathes easier because you have lived. This is to have succeeded" - Ralph Waldo Emerson
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have to sit and enter the readership and circulation data for all the publications in India over the past 5 years... this is slowwww and painfull... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I think I may have finally figured how to get this working again...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      apparently blogger can send posts by mail ad well... am trying to figure out a way to use it...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      American shores beckon a batchmate of mine, Rohan from  urlLink Times School of Marketing . He is going to  urlLink University of Michigan . Best of Luck Rohan!!!
     

 
    
</post>

<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've settled on buying the Hero Honda Karizma. Costs about 85K (ouch...) my dad (and other poeple) suggests a car at that kind of outlay...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have a community online that I've been trying to do somehting contsructive with @  urlLink http://tsm.indiatimes.com/community/  it'd appear that nothing seems to be working... it is deader than a fish out of water.  more time, more time... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Tux is the nickname for the mascot for Linux...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It was an interesting time on linux...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A person I thought was a good friend lied to me, on something that I feel is fairly trivial...   why did he do that is what has been troubling me the whole of this weekend...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I was mucking around with my hard drives partition and guess what... no operating system... it seems the the boot loader has been corrupted :(.   so I picked up  one of the free linux cd's lying around, installed it and downloaded a msn messenger version for linux and now I'm good to go... :D
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Some months ago, when I was with BCCL, (the publisher of The Times of India and he Economic Times), I had a conversation with CTO of the group Internet company, Times Internet Limited. Who asked me to put down some thoughts on how I see things on the internet shaping up. While I did put down those thoughts, I never actually sent it to him, the file was lying around till I came across it a couple of days back.  Here is a rewrite of what I initially penned down (typed up?).   A lot of rambling about nothing in particular.    The positioning of a product or service is more and more targeted to more and more specific audiences? Case in point are the BMW and Mercedes, both are from fine German engineering pedigree, both are premium luxury cars. However the buyers of the two will probably as different as two people can be. The former will be bought by a person who will drive the car himself and the latter probably by someone who has a chauffer (Yes, I know Mercedes also makes sports cars… this is the general perception that I expressed here). Such a huge differentiation in mindset is what branding is all about. This trend is seen in media as well. The rise of niche publications in developed economies such as the US and UK is illustrative of this.   Any media would broadly undergo the distinct phases of consolidation in the growth phase and then  fragmentation once the medium matures. The internet is perhaps one medium which fragmented even before it matured. This is perhaps explained by the global reach of the media and the fact that ideas can be easily replicated across geographical & political boundaries; i.e. something that works in America, will almost certainly not work in India, simply because the maturity of the American market is of a different order of magnitude. To illustrate this point further the existence and flourishing of sites like epinions.com (in the American context) and the apparent non-starter of the Indian equivalent mouthshut.com which are sources of information.  Or price comparison sites like mySimon.com which as far as I know has no comparable Indian site.   With this brief background, it would be instrumental to see the whole internet game in a different perspective . The internet tends to promote the formation of groups of people with very specific interests. A sort of mother of all niche publications, which you can talk back to and what’s more it talks back to you and allows you to communicate with your peer group.   While the Bennet philosophy has been to be an aggregator of audiences by subsidizing the price the audience pays to retrieve content and then retrieving profit from the purchasing those audiences. This can prove counter productive as far as the Internet goes, as the internet has people who are used to getting content for free and are likely to freeload. On the other hand the audience which does pay to retrieve the content would then be most prized and wanted by an advertiser, if nothing to prove non frivolousness of their transaction with us. The idea would be to convince the mass populace that information is of value. The easiest way to ensure that is to look for focused verticals in the information segment. The first one that comes to mind is economictimes.com or more accurately perhaps the work of ETIG.   The biggest problem that one can make out is how will people pay for it online. Multimodal payment mechansims are already in use by the Indiatimes family of websites. Virtual currency of some kind can perhaps be also created for this purpose.   What about the business we are in?    Content can take several forms, one of the forms could be that of blogs (such as the one you are reading right now). Blogs are the latest rage in America, now spreading to other parts of the world. Blogs are nothing but a personal running commentary on the world in general and sometimes specific to a topic.   Another form could be in the form of reviews. Reviews can be on any topic, from the palces to party & eat out in Delhi to where to find the best shoes in Chandini Chowk. Ineractivity which needs to be the cornerstone of such an offering. Such content may well be in the form of a blog.   Traditional content in the form of newspapers, TV, Radio will definitely migrate in one form or the other to the web. Evolution of devices like the Microsoft Tablet PC or the Handspring Treo are definitely a step in that direction.   In that respect standardisation under one name a la indiatimes.com is probably the biggest single mistake being undertaken by us and many others across the world. This conclusion is based on our initial premise that internet promotes the formation of specific focus groups. By definition these focus groups would be unlikey to turn to a general interest portal to get their kicks so to speak. The creation of multiple brands would be a better branding and strategic idea, having a ghoomnahai.com rather than having something like Indiatimes Travel. This gives an identity to the content and makes it more valued by its consumers.   The above, when seen in the overall context of evolution of media, is a perfectly logical sequence of events. Growing media consolidates, and then fragments. During the growth phase it is perfectly acceptable to have a single brand name, but the moment the medium matures (maybe in the context of the limited audience it gathers in the Indian scenario)   Show me the money!!!   Whether people will pay to read (& someday in the future see) such content is debatable. The likes of Al Ries would have us believe that advertising will never work on the internet (which is something I disagree with strongly). So what will happen? Will the internet become a subversive medium which will undermine modern society as we know it. A sort of a no man’s land where no content will be paid for? products and services being the only ones able to draw any sort of revenue?   “The Truth” as the immortal words form ‘X Files’ go “is out there..”.  My personal suspicion is that heavily prized content a la NYT or WSJ will not only be paid for, but will also attract significant advertising revenues. For the rest, creation of strong niches will allow them to do the same…   PS: Don't hesitate to comment...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I got a job offer today... ad sales... hmmm... I wonder...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      had an accident last night... totalled one side of my scooter... and got hit on the knee real bad... I think I'm out of comission for the next few days...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      two of my batchmates have founded an agency called... "Late Nights and Crazy Weekends". True agency wallahs both of them. Best of luck to them... if you want to give them some biz... call Rohan @ 9811649393
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      no  urlLink says  NDTV too
     

 
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Will monsoon hit delhi today? no  urlLink says  weather.com
     

 
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       [Gizmodo]  AgileMobile says it has a new software application for cellphones that can detect when the person you're talking to on the phone is lying. Supposedly it can measure the stress that shows up when someone is being less than truthful. We're sure it works perfectly.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm moving on from by job at  urlLink Zenithmedia  to my previous employer Bennett, Coleman and Co. Ltd. who publish  urlLink The Times of India  and  urlLink The Economic Times 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink What is a Weblog? 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      He who will not reason, is a bigot, he who cannot, is a fool; and he who dares not; a slave. - Byron
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink MIT Everyware  MIT is giving away their course ware to everyone for FREE... you can be sure come people   will sign up...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      GP, PGP, PGP-13: Sound familiar? actually not... For every Physics grad (like yours truly) who ever went to a Movie... Any Movie.  urlLink Intuitor Insultingly Stupid Movie Physics 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sony's F-828 can  urlLink shoot in the dark 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Incase you thought Diamonds were expensive... Check this piece out in Wired on  urlLink The New Diamond Age . Diamonds are cheap it says... $5 a karat to be exact... :D... Not to mention DeBeers is not amused...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For those with a need for speed, coming soon Diamond semiconductors, NTT   urlLink did a demo  which ran at 81 GHz. For a refernece. Intel's current consumer chips run at about 2.x GHz
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Michael Gartenberg says   urlLink PowerPoint is NOT Evil . This of course in response to a recent Wired story that is doing the rounds of th weblog community
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Dropload  a neat thing to transfer files all over... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       [Wired]  Toyota plans to release a car that parks itself. Automotive journalists test-drove it and say it works like a charm.   I Want One 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       CD Freaks  CDR's may only last 2 years ... Damn I have to make back ups of my back ups now...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Decentralisation in the real world  urlLink The Distributed Library Project 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Boston Globe  The Net: an uber medium?
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HT  urlLink to go to Bombay . Best of luck to them. It's gonna be an interesting time in The Times. Almost makes me want to go back to my previous company.  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have been looking for Edward Tufte's Book,  urlLink The Visual Display of Quantitative Information  and  urlLink Envisioning Information . He keeps on Raving and Ranting about Powerpoint... So much so wired did a   urlLink piece  on this...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  ship I gotta have...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The  urlLink Matrix  Revolutions trailer is out... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink We Love Arnold  from the people who brought you  urlLink http://www.WeLoveTheIraqiInformationMinister.com/ 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I barely said Good Morning today, and my mailbox is flooded with virus laden mails... pah!
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today is  urlLink Janmasthami  Holiday...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Wired:  A new worm circulating on the Internet is designed to kill MSBlaster, the worm that wreaked havoc on computers last week. 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Texting blamed for summer movie flops .. Text Messaging! .. got faster .. using  SMS ... consumers  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Coca Cola Index ... Economist is also threatening a French Fry Index
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Big Mac Index  mmm....
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Map  of the world's currencies... I think you may need an economist subscription for this...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey this is yet another oppurtunity for India... to set up back end data warehousing and backup operations.. far far away from your site of operations...   New York Times : Many companies that had their own disaster recovery plans found on Aug. 14 that their backup site was within the blackout area.  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Russia  urlLink plans  Mars nuclear station... Another giant leap for man, and a gianter leap for mankind.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink New Scientist  reports a DNA powered computer playing tic tac toe, and apparently, it can never be beaten...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Buckminster Fuller believed tieing all the world's continents into the  same electrical grid ... connecting power grids across the world... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Wired report , The Internet still functions after Saturday midnight -- so far. The Blaster worm failed to bring down a Microsoft's site and network, and cause other mischief as planned. Microsoft says 'no problem,' but warns individual computers remain vulnerable if not patched.   When my comp was having fits last monday I was wondering what the hell was happening...  It was this blaster worm of course, fortunately for me I had another OS installed, I got on to the web, downloaded the patch and was back up and running in no time flat :D. 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Next time you run out of a calci Use  urlLink Google's ... Just type the equation in the search window, hit search and ta dah back comes the answer
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Long weekend last week... Independence Day, Sat, Sun... This should happen again and again...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My director has been posted to  urlLink Zenithmedia  Vietnam
     

 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Suddenly and quite of the blue I'm on this audiophile kick... I have this unexplainable urge to buy a Home theatre system, DVD/CD 5.1 Surround et al... Onkyo is uspposedly good... so is Bose, but that is very expensive. Research, research adn research.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Though Technology is supposed to be a business driver, sometimes it seems technology is adopted for the sake of technology rather than for achieving something concrete.  In my previous company (a publishing house, which generates pages and pages of content everyday) , whenever one spoke of content management , the discussion usually involved tech professionals, on what to use how to use. Very rarely would a discussion be around as to how does it help business  urlLink This piece  looks at it from a managerial perspective, as a business driver.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Kottke  is asking whether the iPod he bought is his or Apple's?
     

 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Michael Fischler  comments on GM's campaign to tackle the negative quality perception.  The ad as described (I've not seen it) is marketing suicide... which is the thought the author has articulated as well.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink iRATE radio  is something one needs to watch... along with the  urlLink Grapevine  Project...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This piece  attracted quite a bit of offline comment from my people in my previous company BCCL which publishes  urlLink The Times of India  and  urlLink The Economic Times ...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Robert Heinlein  "An artist can look at a pretty girl and see the old woman she will become. A better artist can look at an old woman and see the pretty girl she used to be. A great artist can look at an old woman, portray her exactly as she is, and force the viewer to se the pretty girl she used to be, more than that, he can make anyone with the sensitivity of an armadillo see that this lovely young girl is still alive, prisoned inside her ruined body. He can make you feel the quiet endless tragedy that there was never a girl born who ever grew older than eighteen in her heart."
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Times of India  Delhi Today published a screen shot that I gave them of Google going Local (i.e. India edition). If you look closely at the Google screenshot on the  urlLink business page  (free registration required), in the taskbar there is one tab which says Chirag... That's  ME ... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Lycos critical of MSN chat room closure  Microsoft may say otherwise, but the reason for closure is most obviously Financial.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      All Media reporting seems to concentrating on the fact that a  single  yahoo group has been banned. but the fact of the matter is. It is the  entire Yahoo Groups sub-domain    urlLink groups.yahoo.com  that has been banned...   The ultimate irony is tht everyone know knows of this yahoo group... and atleast worldwide (if not india) people can read what the dissidents have to say... and this censorship has made them more famous, rather than consign them oblivion which was the intention...  The  urlLink IT ACT 2000  says it allos for  balanced flow of information ... which is bullshit. It is censorship plain and simple. What is most pissing is that hey don't even know how to do it properly. 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CNET Story  on the blocking of Yahoo Groups
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Bill aims to curb Net censorship ... They better finish it very quickly... How soon before the Indian Government start banning emails...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Another  urlLink story  on censorship of Yahoo Groups by the Indian Government.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I was looking for coverage of the blocking of Yahoo Groups by the Indian Government and I stumbled onto  urlLink Google News Alerts .. Neat...   I can already see possibilities here... I can set an alert for "Chirag Patnaik" be the first to know when I get famous...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Times of India article  on the Yahoo Groups censorship
     

 
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Wikipedia entry  on censorship in china... it is pretty comprehensive, in terms of what the Chinese government has been doing, plus what the world has been doing to circumvent it... How long before we have a similar entry for India?
     

 
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is the first major censorship attempt by the Govenment of India.   My alumni group runs on yahoogroups... I'm really really pissed. Apart from  urlLink anonymizer.com , there is  urlLink Guardster.com ,  urlLink the-cloak.com  and the dmoz/google  urlLink directory  of free anonymising proxies...  this is al very fine.. but I can't login to see the mesages on the group... The Cloak is supposed to allow it, but it doesn't seem to work... suggestions welcome
     

 
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Govt. of India  urlLink blocks  Yahoogroups access from India. Why? because it did not like what was going on two of the groups there...   Ths is the most asinine thing I've ever heard... I don't know why we even believe we live in a democracy...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Whatever will they think of next??  urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink  Dgital Blasphemy  has some neat computer generated pics...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've shifted to BCCL The Publishers of  urlLink    on the 1st... and am currently looking for a place to shift to in South Delhi. My roomie of the past one and a half years has more or less kicked me out (or is going to)... that's coz he's gotten married... :D
     

 
    
</post>

<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Economist Emerging markets data  shows India's GDP Growth to be 5.7 WHich is more that the Hindu Rate of Grwoth Theory, which hypothesises that's India's growth will never be more than 5%
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  is a good read...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink CNet  has this story of hwo VIA's mini-ITC boards are being used to create fully functional PC's in the strangest of cases and place like Lampshades and Bread Boxes
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Railroad Tycoon 3  is out.. Can't wait to get my hands on it... I hope it runs on my (almost) acient comp...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink NYT  reports that from next month, subscribers will be able to switch services without having to change numbers... One wonders when this will happen in India, I'm just about sick of the service and am going to switch.   Number moblity would be so cool...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Forune has an intersting  urlLink story  on Piracy. While Most blog commentary has been decidely anti-RIAA, This one takes a more balanced view to the whole issue.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Frst it was the  urlLink death of email ...   now  urlLink death of the PDA  (Economist Link. No Premium mebership required)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Lore Brand Comics: Sex Lies of the Future 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      No Comment on the life and works and other controversies surrounding the Mother, just rah rah on the beatification... read the  urlLink Wiki on The Mother , if you have more time read the book  urlLink Final VerDict . The full text is available online without pictures...   The Book looks at the other side of the personality
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The World's most common Operating System is...  urlLink not Windows , but something called ITRON which runs on an approximate 3 billlion microprocessors
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Comics by RSS ... Cool... I'm deleting my comic subscriptions right now...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There is some talk in the blogosphere on the death of email, saving email, rss replacing email, new email projects like  urlLink Internet Mail 2000 ... what I'm trying to do here is to piece together the various points of views and solutions..   The premise: E-mail is dying. Why? because of the amounts of spam flowing into peoples mail boxes and the attack of viruses like SoBig.    We will explore what Michael Fraase has to say  urlLink now  and  urlLink then . At some point one will begin to wonder whether RSS will  urlLink kill "email" or "email publishing" ... huge difference between the two. When one figures this out, one will realise that there are people on the other side of the debate too. i.e. feel email will  urlLink live  and of course someone  urlLink countered  this as well and a  urlLink response  to that and of course there will be people like  urlLink me  who will be bystanders attempting to make sense  urlLink in the chaos that exists 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The Festival of Lights  This is one of the oldest Hindu festivals occuring in the month of Kartik, which commemorates the return of Rama to Ayodhya after an exile of 14 years. It also marks the beginning of the new year and is celebrated with the lighting of lamps. Diwali or Deepawali, literally 'an array of lamps', is the festival of lights and is celebrated on the darkest night of Kartik. It is perhaps the most important festival in India. Originally a Hindu festival, it has now crossed the bounds of religion and is celebrated by all in India with fervor and gaiety. This day is a public holiday all over India.  Twinkling oil lamps or diyas light up every home and firework displays are common all across the country. The goddess Lakshmi (consort of Vishnu), who is the symbol of wealth and prosperity, is also worshipped on this day. This festive occasion also marks the beginning of the Hindu new year and Lord Ganesha, the elephant-headed god, the symbol of auspiciousness and wisdom, is also worshipped in most Hindu homes on this day.  Another view is that Deepawali is meant to celebrate the destruction of the arrogant tyrant Bali at the hands of Vishnu when the latter appeared in his Vamana (dwarf) avatar. The occasion of Deepawali sees the spring-cleaning and white-washing of houses; decorative designs or rangolis are painted on floors and walls. New clothes are bought and family members and relatives gather together to offer prayers, distribute sweets and to light up their homes.   Diwali is also perhaps the oldest festival still celebrated today and is mentioned in the Ramayana. The celebrations include the lighting of lamps and candles, and the bursting of crackers (fireworks). Friends and neighbours exchange special sweets. People buy new clothes and in fact, in certain communities, it is absolutely essential to wear new clothes on this day.  Diwali in India is equivalent to Christmas in the West. Therefore it is also the time when people get the festival bonus to their salaries. It marks the beginning of the new year for a large majority of Hindus, especially the trader community.  Preparations for the festival begin many days prior to Diwali. It is time for a thorough cleaning of the house, for the belief is that Lakshmi will enter clean and nicely decorated houses. The scientific reason is that the monsoon is a time for insects and fungus to breed.With the end of the monsoon, homes need to be cleaned and painted, and belongings aired and dried before the onset of winter. The festival itself extends over about a week even though the most important day is the new moonday.  In east Bihar and northern India, two days before Diwali is celebrated as Dhanteras in honour of Dhanvantari, the physician of the gods. He is believed to have emerged with a pot of amrita during the samudra manthan. People bathe early in the morning and observe a fast, which is broken only after sunset with sweetmeats, puri and other delicacies. On Dhanteras, new kitchen utensils are bought and kept at the place of worship. The buying of utensils, according to one theory, relates to the myth of Dhanvantari emerging from the ocean with a pot in his hand. Since he is also the physician of the gods, cleanliness and hygiene are essential to this festival. The day before Diwali is celebratedas Choti Diwali or 'small Diwali'. It is Diwali on a smaller scale, with fewer lights lit and fewer crackers burst.  The morning after Choti Diwali, the women of the house make beautiful, coloured rangoli in the doorway and courtyard. Tiny footprints made out of rice paste are a special feature of the rangolis made for Diwali. They signify the footprints of Lakshmi, as she enters the house. In Hindu homes, Diwali celebrations involve a ritual puja to Lakshmi and also to Rama in the evening. Songs in honour of the gods are sung and arati is performed. Oil or ghee diyas are also lit. The gods are offered kheel, batashe and khilone and various sweetmeats. After the puja, the diyas are placed in and around the house: in the doorway, near the Tulasi plant, the backyard, every room and the back and front gates. After this, crackers are burst, and people meet friends and neighbours to exchange good wishes and sweets. Since Diwali falls on the new moon night, lamps are lit to brighten this moonless night. According to a myth, Lakshmi will not enter a dark house. The lamps also welcome home the spirits of dead ancestors, who are believed to visit on this auspicious night. In addition, the light frightens away any evil spirit that might be wandering about near the house on this night. In Orissa, lamps are lit to light up the dark path that the spirits of ancestors take back to heaven. In modern times, ghee diyas have been replaced by wax candles and coloured electric bulbs. In many areas, there is a competition of sorts among neighbours as everyone tries to have the brightest lights. The origin of Diwali can be traced back to ancient India, when it was probably an important harvesting season. It was thus extremely important to the largely pastoral Vaishya community. Their granaries were full, and the weather was good, at the end of the long monsoon and before the arduous winter. It was therefore a good time to celebrate. The Vaishya community began their new year with this happy occassion, after paying their debts and clearing their ledgers. As the religion developed, various mythological stories and explanations were attributedto this festival to give it religious sanction.  However today, this historical explanation is all but lost among the many stories and folklore linked with the origin of the festival. According to the most popular one, Diwali is celebrated in honour of Rama, his consort Sita and brother Lakshmana, returning to their kingdom Ayodhya after a 14-year exile.To celebrate this event, people at Ayodhya are believed to have lit up their houses with lamps. The illuminations also symbolise the removal of spiritual darkness and the onset of happiness and prosperity.    According to another belief, it is on this day that Lakshmi emerged from the ocean during the samudra manthan .Lakshmi Puja commemorates her birth and therefore forms a major part of Diwali celebrations. Being associated with the goddess of wealth and fortune, Diwali is specially important to the Vaishya   community. Most tradesmen close their old ledgers and dealings and start afresh with new ledgers after Diwali. This day, with its emphasis on money, is also considered lucky for gambling. Giving social sanction to a vice, a popular saying states that one who does not gamble on this day will beborn a donkey in his next birth. Casinos and local gambling houses do brisk business during the Diwali week. In most homes, people invite their friends and relatives over to play cards.   Another reason for the celebration of Diwali is that it marks the killing of the evil Narkasura at the hands of Krishna Naraka is believed to have abducted 16,000 women. Krishna killed him and rescued these women whom he later married. Naraka is the personification of hell and is believed to be the monsoon during which all activities come to a standstill.   Though Diwali is equally important in the south and the north, the celebrations are markedly different. In South India, the story widely associated with Diwali is that of Narasimha, the man-lion incarnation of Vishnu. According to a legend, Hiranyakshipu was an evil demon king. He was unjust and cruel to his people. However, he was almost invincible, having extracted a boon from Brahma that he would be killed neither by beast nor man, neither inside nor outside, neither during the day nor at night. When his atrocities became unbearable, the gods sought Vishnu's help. Assuming his fifth incarnation of Narasimha, the man-lion,Vishnu killed Hiranyakshipu with his claws in the courtyard just before day break, hence steering clear of the boundaries of the boon. For this reason in the south, people light diyas in their houses on the day preceding Diwali. The next day begins early. First is the ritual bath, which begins with an oil massage of the hair and body. This is absolutely essential on this day. Its importance probably refers to cleaning oneself thoroughly after the monsoon months. After bathing, people receive new clothes and gifts from their elders, which they are expected to wear. The family then prays to Vishnu for its well-being and prosperity. After the prayers start the main celebrations which, as in the north, consist of bursting crackers and lighting candles.At day break, all celebrations end.People then visit friends and relatives and exchange sweets.   References to the word 'atishbaji' or'crackers' are found even in ancient literature. The bursting of crackers is today the most important and eagerly-awaited part of the Diwali celebrations. According to one belief, the sound that resounds throughout the universe makes all aware of the great homecoming of Rama. Another belief is that the crackers are an indication ofthe joy of the people living on the earth, making the gods aware of their plentiful state. Still another possible reason has a more scientific basis: the fumes produced by the crackers kill a lot of insects, found in plenty after the rains. The use of high-tech bomb crackers is fairly recent. At times, Diwali celebrations get ugly, especially in the metropolitan cities. In New Delhi, people start bursting crackers in the evening and this continues till the early hours ofthe morning. As a result, the city is engulfed in toxic fumes and smoke for almost 10 hours. Another problem with crackers is that their manufacture is usually unregulated. As a result, the manufacturing units are unsafe and the material used is inflammable and toxic.Every year, many units are destroyed inaccidental fires, resulting in the death of those employed there.   Kerala is probably the only state in India where even Hindus do not celebrate Diwali. The major festival there is Onam. In West Bengal, Kali Puja is performed on Diwali as it is believed that on this day Kali killed the wicked Raktavija. Being one of the main festivals of the trader community, markets are gaily decorated and lit up. Many safety measures and precautions are telecast on television and radio, especially for children. The fire departments are kept on the alert, and the municipal corporations of bigger cities also organise buckets and tankers of water at strategic locations. The second day after Diwali is celebrated as Bhai Duja when sisters apply tilak to their brothers and pray for their long and happy life. In all likelihood, this ritual was originally intended only for married women. Since they celebrated Diwali with their in-laws, this festival allowed them to come to their parents' home during this auspicious time. They got some time to meet the family and to rest after the hectic activity of the preceding week.And it gave their parents an opportunity to give them gifts, an opportunity they did not often get. Nowadays however, among many communities Bhai Duja is observed by both married and unmarried sisters.   urlLink http://webonautics.com/ethnicindia/festivals/diwali.html 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I have been running  urlLink Google Compute  for some weeks now... It is a distributed computing project like  urlLink SETI@Home . SETI@Home is itself going to migrate into an open distributed computin platform which is due to start soon
     

 
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A new release of  urlLink Mozilla Firebird  0.7 to be exact. I wonder if it has changed enough to match the IE feature set.. 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The Observer's  urlLink 100 greatest novels of all time . I've read 22 of them and have heard of another 10...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      One of the advantages of working with a newspaper is that you meet all sorts of people, techies, editors, business people, Lawyers. A few things that I have been talking to people about recently in the company  Preseidential Blogs Death of Email / Email Vs RSS Marketing the 3650 by blogs Social Sofware Comment Spam  If I find the time to follow the incredible number of cross links and discussion threads expect more on these...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Lore Brand Comics  Most awesome sense of humour
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Commodore 64  on a Nokia... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Digital Media Manifesto 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Meta Filter.  urlLink Oh, it's nothing...    I quite  liked the deifinition on notingness...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink SENT  is the first Cameraphone Artshow...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      In a Scientific American  urlLink interview  Michio Kaku is grilled on the possiblity of Time Travel
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This edition still in Beta, presents the daily paper online, not in classic internet format, but regular broadsheet format. With one being able to click and read the section one desires. This is similar to the Orange Country Register Digitl version.  Though one is not privy to the software being used, but the underlying technology, navigation and presentation clearly points to Olive Software, which has also powered the Orange County Register digital edition.    urlLink http://digital.guardian.co.uk/ 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Electric Shaver Museum 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      For all those people hungry for  urlLink data on media 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink The Money Map  is a neatresource on where the Presidential candidates are getting their funds from...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This Wired  urlLink story  on a space mission being put up on eBay has to be the most ridiculous thing I've heard so far...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This had to happen sooner than later... Dell was the first to start commodotisation, Walmart will take this further...  urlLink Wal-Mart to write own name on notebooks  
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Scoble Comments     Last night in the airport I was reading a copy of Fast Company magazine. It's really weird to see quotes from webloggers in the pages of magazines. Joi Ito had a quote featured there.   In Wired, the smiling faces of Ben and Mena Trott stared out of the pages at me.   It's a strange world we've all entered. Three years ago I barely knew what a blog was.    
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Playboy has  urlLink reportedly  offered Britney & figure amoount to pose nude... Ha
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink NYT  talks about  urlLink The Hollywood Stock Exchange , which is apparently something the Hollywood studios have begun to take really seriously...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  is like the largest PVP/MP3 player...  I want one... 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      There is  urlLink speculation , that Microsoft may abandon the Pocket PC platform... Between the Phone Platform and the Tablet PC, there is little reason to continue with that platform anyway...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      After  urlLink months  of procastination (deliberation?), I finally bought a  urlLink Pulsar ...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wired reports  urlLink Move Over DVD, Here Comes the EVD . Analysts qouted in the story say that the evd will not suceed, considering that hollywood studios may not support the same... I think otherwise, The Asian markets are still new to DVD's and Asian producers may switch to this. Also like most consumer electronics, DVD/EVD players will be manufactured in Asia (China, Taiwan et al). They just might suppport it...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      In a Wired Story  urlLink Fast Track for Science Data , what has been termed as Internet2 for quite some time has finally gone online...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The Top 10 Internet Fads   urlLink kuro5hin 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       This is neat. You can link to the middle of a realmedia stream... Presidential debate has been discussed, but I can use it as a marker in between a movie...   urlLink Read more  via  [Boing Boing Blog]  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Some more links of AdAsia Coverage   The Times of India   urlLink Advertising industry enters a new era   urlLink Advertising industry enters a new era    The Economic Times   urlLink Ad Asia ends with kudos to creativity of Asians    AgencyFaqs   urlLink Santosh Desai lambasts marketers for their narrow view of society   urlLink &lsquo;Don&rsquo;t emulate western ideas,&rsquo; is the creative consensus   urlLink Money is compensation for not living your life the way you want to: Charles Handy   urlLink Are marketers missing the grey boom, asks expert on ageing   urlLink Don&rsquo;t break the wrong rules: Jack Trout    Financial Express   urlLink Curtains On Grand Advertising Meet   urlLink Advertising Highs: Lessons From Jaipur   urlLink Reflections From Thought Leaders  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'll be changing the RSS feed URL, in a few days. I've to rely on Feedster, as blogger is still not providing rss feeds...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Om Mallik comments... This was the whole point I was making, that technology is no longer something you can talk about when you are marketing a product when I posted  urlLink this    According to the Chinese Ministry of Information, world # 1 and #2 wireless handset makers are not doing that well in China. From January to September 2003, Chinese makers produced 129 million handsets.  Ningbo  held the top spot at 15%.  Motorola  slips to #2 at 14%, followed closely by   TCL   at 12%. Rounding out the top four,  Nokia  held a 10% share. Wanna bet that next year one of these two chinese handset makers will be selling phones in  US  for $50 a pop - and they will include camera, some bluetooth and good knows what.   [GigaOm]  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My host was not working the whole of today... I guess that's the price for doing this without spending a single rupee
     

 
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Awesome...   The file-swapping company, which is locked in a legal battle with Hollywood studios, has struck a deal to digitally distribute a full-length feature film made in India's Bollywood.  CNET News   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      It'd seem Ricardo Semler's talk at AdAsia is having an impact as  urlLink Hind Lever freezes market research budgets  :D
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Boing Boing Blog  comments on VoIP an dall the chaos surrounding the VoIP providers.. The fun will start when some does VoIP over WiFi.  While this is new as a commercial service, the technology is not really new... Dial Pad, Buddy Phone et al. from 4 odd years back... and not to forget corporate WAN's. my company, The Times has been using it fo quite some time...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      One of the things the blogosphere is talking about  urlLink Skype . Skype is peer to Peer voice application on the web...  From the Skype webite     What is Skype   Skype is the next phenomenon from the people who brought you KaZaA. Just like KaZaA, Skype uses P2P (peer-to-peer) technology to connect you to other users &#8211; not to share files this time, but to talk and chat with your friends.  The technology is extremely advanced - but super simple to use... You&rsquo;ll be making free phone calls to your friends in no time!    Features    Free unlimited worldwide phone calls to other Skype users  Superior sound quality - better than your regular phone  Works with all firewall, NAT and routers &#8211; nothing to configure!  Friends list shows you when your Skype friends are online and ready to talk or chat  Super-simple and easy to use  Your calls are encrypted &#8220;end-to-end&#8221; for superior privacy     Telcos beware 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink New Pen-Based Nokia 3108 phone ... Finally is all I can say. The competitors like Sony Ericsson and Treo are already into their second (P-900) or third (Treo 600) editions of their Stylus phones.
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      As a member of the Nokia planning team, I was party to the market Insight, that the device is becoming secondary to the whole process of communication... While this is worrying to Nokia Nokia is itself digging it's own grave...  How?   For years, Nokia phones were known for their simplicity and ease of use, and admittedly by the top execs of hte company that the proprietary interface on their hones had a lot to do with it... Howver the newer Nokias are using the Symbian Series 60 based OS. Which means that the interface is no longer the key distinguishing factor between the different brands of phones.  This coupled with the earlier insight would mean an ever weaking technological position which has been Nokia's marketing pitch in the past. The oft repeated statement in any marketing course as to Technology no longer being a differentiator, but a leveller, will be true for Nokia.   This  Wired  story on cracking of the Nokia N-Gage Games to be run on other Series 60 OS phones (Siemens), illustrates the point above.. It doesn't matter who you buy your phones from, modern applications will run on all of them  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Some more coverage of the AdAsia conference in Jaipur...   The Economic Times   urlLink microsite  on AdAsia   The Times of India   urlLink India's moment has arrived : Ambani    Exchange4Media   urlLink microsite  on AdAsia   Indian Express   urlLink Batey Bets On Top Ten Global Indian Brands   urlLink Brand India    Business Standard   urlLink Ambani, Kumar Birla pitch for Brand India  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Crooked Timber: Sex selection banned in the UK  India went a step further than this when it banned Sex determination per se.   This is ofcourse, because of the society feeling that the girl child is unwanted and a bureden on the family.
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      My Boss and other bigwigs fron the The Times are away at the AdAsia conference at Jaipur...  A poor substitute to being there is to read about it... So read on...   The Economic Times   urlLink microsite  on AdAsia   The Times of India   urlLink Ad Asia mantra: Break rules to break even   urlLink Ad industry maturing in Pak    Business Standard   urlLink Admen salute consumer, the king   urlLink Asian admen get royal welcome    agencyfaqs.com   urlLink Brand India will succeed: Mukesh Ambani   urlLink Great brands play the role of protagonists: Scott Bedbury   urlLink Cult Branding: The Harley Davidson experience   urlLink Over time media will become more targetable: Irwin Gotlieb   urlLink "Advertisers have lost focus of the key purpose of advertising" &#8211; Sergio Zyman   urlLink I have never broken any rules; perhaps none of us have: Amitabh Bachchan   urlLink Product variety is not the same as experience variety: CK Prahalad   urlLink Engaging the consumer of tomorrow: MS Banga   urlLink "Industry-wide emulation" is the problem, says Ricardo Semler   urlLink Anticipation unbound    The Telegraph   urlLink Salary fixing is based on basically three parameters for the corporation: what the competition pays, what the company pays for the same job, and the level of anticipated profits in the year ahead: Ricardo Semler   via   urlLink Mediaah!   urlLink Bachchan shatters marketing myth on norms    Indian Express   urlLink Breaking Rules & Bringing A Pot Of Gold     Financial Express   urlLink Advertising Is More Than Just Commercials: Zyman   urlLink Retail Revolution Has Begun In India: Banga    Business Line   urlLink Big B beckons admen to keep finger on common man's pulse     The Guardian   urlLink Ad men try to keep eastern promise    The Statesman   urlLink Big B owes Zanjeer success to Emergency 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ross Mayfield Comments on Many to Many:  The rise of social networking gives greater credence to the saying "It's not what you know, but who you know." This inherently undemocratic notion concerns some, and, indeed, the Network is the Market. Within a power-law distribution, preferential attachment implies...  Full Article  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Some Newspaper Blogs that I cam across, there are many more ofcourse   urlLink http://www.spokesmanreview.com/blogs/   urlLink http://www.guardian.co.uk/weblog/   urlLink http://www.journaltimes.com/weblogs/ 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I wonder how I can get myself one of  urlLink the 10 most overpaid jobs in the U.S. 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Should you turn of your cellphone or remove the battery if you don't want to be contacted?  urlLink This comment on Smart Mobs  says that mobile phones can be tracked even when they are turned off... I found this worrying and somewhat unbelievable... till one reads the comments...   Where someone comments that a signal is sent out by the phone, when it is being turned off... This  gyan  explains the different operator messages one gets when one removes the phone battery without turning the phone off... vs. just turning the phone off...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Microsoft  is allegedly going to enter the Blogging/Social Software scene...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Srinagar has WiFI 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Reading  urlLink Why Indian media is so self obsessive , makes me wonder whether Om Maliks definition of a blog, is to be news and anaysis and can't be on the lighter side of things... Also read the comment that I left attached to the post... PM have you read this...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>07,November,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Define Your World  with the Urban Dictonary... Pretty Cool...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Delhi Metro NRS 03	results  Average Issue Readership in 000s The Times Of India	1432 Navbharat Times	1431 Hindustan Times	1327 Punjab Kesari	1119 Hindustan	894 Grihshobha	612 Dainik Jagran	552 Meri Saheli	346 India Today - Eng	340 India Today - Hindi	310 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      TOI is the new leader in Delhi as per the NRS 2003, beating HT
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      In celebration of 10 years of Doom  urlLink The Doom Comic 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The  urlLink NRS  results are out.   The Times of India featres as the only English paper in the top 10 daily newspapers in the country.  Coverage on  urlLink Mediaah   urlLink Exchange4media    There has been a lot of litigation on the release of the NRS. 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I couldn't resist and went ego surfing yet again...  I'm the  urlLink 3rd   urlLink Chirag  on the list. Just a  urlLink week  ago I was number 5. I must be doing something right...  But what?
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is a really significant precedent. First there was the intersection of commerce on the edge, with scores of E:Bay auctions selling stuff in the make beleive worlds, then it was legitimised, with the game companies selling the stuff themselves. And now a judge in the real world rules on property in a vistual world. The intersection of the virtual and real worlds is complete   http://www.reuters.com/newsArticle.jhtml?type=internetNews&storyID=4022155   Online Gamer in China Sues, Wins Over Virtual Theft  Fri December 19, 2003 08:30 AM ET   BEIJING (Reuters) - A Chinese court has ordered an online video game company to return hard-won virtual property, including a make-believe stockpile of bio-chemical weapons, to a player whose game account was looted by a hacker. 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Did you know that the postal department can also be  urlLink termed  as broadband... 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Blockbuster Chief  urlLink asks  for scrapping of Region encoded DVD's. About bloody time...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I thought this was a brilliant idea. Apparently the Google bar doesn't have the IE Control+Enter shortcut, and it trips up on urls like http://bloglines.com/myblogs, or part urls like download.com,  which are handled by the address bar.  So if someone at google fixes this, then one can be rid of the address bar and save some screen height in the Web Browser...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      In search of more browser screen space, I was trying to minimise the space consumed by the toolbars, when it struck me to replace the address bar with the google bar... like so   urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Sony DSC-F828  is what I'm going to be buying next year...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      More  urlLink hmmm... 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink hmmm... 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Smite on...    urlLink God Considers Smiting Bible Pirates   Vatican City - God did not rule out smiting as a final measure against those who share his most famous work, the Bible, on the Internet. This marks the first time a deity has spoken on IT-related questions since Steve Jobs was temporarily Enlightened when touching the One True iMac some years ago.  Authorized Version? Citing misuse of His word, misquotation, and putting hardworking Bible printers out of work, God said he would now start hunting Bible pirating around the globe. 'I have to defend both my world-famous brand - the Bible and its distinctive likenesses - and the livelihood of those who create and distribute legal copies of it. Sure, they live not by bread alone, but website hits - someone else's website mind you - don't pay the bills for these folks.' Since large portions of the Bible are many centuries old, many people believe the work to be in the public domain. Not so, said God. 'Look, most copyright laws are based on something like the author's lifetime plus, let's say, 15 years. News flash: I'm still here.' ' I am a jealous God,' He said, 'but I am by no means unreasonable. If the person will stop distributing My copyrighted materials, there will be no further consequences. Like I've said before: hate pirating, love the pirate.'  
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I've finally renamed the blog today... It is now no longer called "A Blog Formerly known as My Ramblings and Rants", instead it is now called  urlLink Marlinspike . This is a sailors needle and can most simply explained as Knot Untangler. Though it is aso used to Tie knots :D.  Why Marlinspike?   I really don't know...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Marlinspike is a knot untangler... it is used by sailors to... Untangle Knots and also to tie them.   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Decided to go  urlLink ego surfing  today. The term Chirag  urlLink throws back  this blog as the number 5 result. Not bad considering a  urlLink few months ago  I wouldn't even feature in the top ten.  A search for  urlLink Chirag Patnaik  now throws back this blog as the first one... Earlier it used to throw back one of the sites I'd done.  I also decided to have a look at who was  urlLink linking  to me... Pitifully few of course. And all of them from Comments I made somewhere or as part of some blog directory. I found    urlLink Recently Updated Indian Weblogs   He lists my Blog as...  urlLink Chirag   This is of course because of the long and unwieldy name of my blog. I'd realised this  urlLink earlier  of course. This just proves that I have to rebrand the blog.
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      As much as I dislike indulging in a flame war, but this  urlLink poor loser  seems to  urlLink have  a fan following...  Further the  urlLink poor loser  claims  urlLink     I admire and respect people who can argue logically, without getting petty or personal. I also admire people who can admit defeat graciously when they lose an argument fair and square. I admire people who hear out other arguments before stating their own, instead of blindly sticking to a stand. I hope to be such a person myself.     HAH!  He doesn't like the fact he can be google bombed too :D  In retrospect, the term  urlLink poor loser  seems  to have been very apt since he is most definitely a  urlLink poor loser .   Okay Okay, I'm repeating myself... 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      New Scientist  urlLink reports  the Freezing of Light
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I want a  urlLink Private Island 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Hindi Movabletype 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Suggestions are welcome for a new name for this blog... use the comment link to leave a suggestion.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm considering a change of name...  Not my name.. the name of this blog...   Why?  It's a long story...  It goes back to my training as a marketeer... The Name "A Blog Formerly Known as My Ramblings and Rants" is far too long and from a branding perspectiv too complicated for anyone to refer. Not that anyone is refering to me... But, if someone were to refer to me, then that would be a real problem... A Branding nightmare... In fact I can hardly think of any popular blog which has such a long name.   So one needs a snappy one or two words for the blog...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Sony  urlLink has announced a 360 degree camera lens .  This has to be the most cool thing in photography since photography itself... :D
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is so awesome...  urlLink The Helloworld Project 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I  urlLink commented  on an  urlLink item  on this  urlLink poor loser 's blog:    How juvenile...  It's like spitting on a Mercedees Benz whizzing by, while sitting in a bus...    To figure out the context visit this  urlLink Poor Loser 's Blog
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      The  urlLink Toyota Prius  claims a fuel efficiency of 55 miles to the gallon...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>09,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Self assembling Nanobots: here they come...    urlLink IBM claims 'self assembly' chip breakthrough 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Hmmm... 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      If Microsoft  urlLink buys  AMD...  This is pure speculation of course...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Wonders of modern techonlogy alow this man to  urlLink get out of trouble     urlLink via gizmodo   
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Economist.com  urlLink has  this analysis on the Indian Railways. If it were privatised. God only knows how it would run. If it were not there. God only knows how this country would run...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  is a curious article on Mid-Day. It talks of a meteoric rise of the MiDay Stock in response to speculative trading. This is all the more curoius because other media stocks are flat.  Of Course rumours of buyout of MidDay means that speculators are at play. and some talk of my company as being one of the suitors. That seems to be unlikely as there is some internal movement my company launching an Afternoon paper in Mumbai. 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Roland Piquepaille in  urlLink Can You Pay U.S. Programmers at Overseas Salaries?     While cMarket has solved its immediate challenge, the implications of Jon's approach are potentially mind-bending. What if other companies begin taking the same approach -- offering Indian-style wages to American workers? On the positive side, we could begin to solve our job-creation problems. But on the negative side, America's standard of living would inevitably decline. There's only one way to find out for sure how it all might shake out, and that is for other executives to replicate Jon's experiment. The results could be quite interesting.    What is irritating about this is that America waves the flag of globalisation and when globalisation hits it, it goes screaming like a baby...   This is similar to the Visa regimes instituted by the West post World War II, trying to stop the influx of immigrants to maintain a better standard of living. When people world over figured that manufacturring in poorer countries is cheaper and businesses started moving manufacturing... America started screaming like a baby again about labor standards et al.   Conclusion of this Rant: If you want globalisation, allow free flo of labour. oops, you can't do that... otherwise Indians will take over your tech jobs... :D
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  wired story comments on natural monopolies. While commenting on the economics, gives the instance of Burlingon.
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink DNA assembles nanotube transistor 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Phone cum camera cum MP3 Player or only a camera?   urlLink Camera phones set to prompt price cuts on digital still cameras ... They better fal somewhat quickly as I'm looking for a nice high quality Digicam for sometime...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This image is part of a  urlLink Gigapixel Image    
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>02,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Last night I started reading  urlLink For God, Country, and Coca-Cola  by Mark Pendergrast...   It traces the history of Coca-Cola from the early days of being a patent (quack) medicine as a rip off by pemberton, of something that was then sold as Vin Marini... the buying out my Asa candler, the early blanket marketing by Robinson... The rumours of Cocaine content, and the subsequent removal fo Cocaine from the formula. Earlly advertising, the journey from being a medicine, to a Cocaine laced soft drink to a Simply refreshing Cold Drink. The book reads like a thriller. I've reached a point where Robert Woodruff has just taken over the company...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      First I lost the posts then I got them back... what gives?
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I'm reposting the hotmail post without the text...   urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      I seem to have lost todays posts...   that's Wired's list of must have toys and the new hotmail interface...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Looks different and nice, has a drop down menu bar on top which makes it easier to use. Junk mail and filing options are different. Seems to be yet another facelift...  urlLink    
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      BBC reports  urlLink No volunteers for orgasm implant ... ;)
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Wired has  some cool must buys... The Sony DSC-F828 and the Skrail suspension are my favorites...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Ok A little mor investigation reveals that.. the coffee warmer being discussed, is not the one being talked about earlier... I wonder if this one works...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Further investigation  reveals... that the much aclaimed USB coffeee warmer is a piece of crap...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      A  urlLink USB coffee warmer . This I got to have...    urlLink  Via Boing Boing 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Today was election day in  urlLink Delhi , and the streets were empty. I rocketed through on the way to work... 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink New Scientist  reports on Smart Cell phone Antennas, which have Autonomous software agents which can talk to neighbouring antennas and do load balancing... This is goign into to testing during the Athens Olympics
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Pickled dragon mystery 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Missile Art 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Talk about the unbelievable...   urlLink Headbanging Blind Mole Rat uses sonar to find its way 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In an Economist feature  urlLink The World In 2004  A story on the Smart Dust revolution.  Alun Andersen, the Editor in Chief comments that for decades we have considered progress to be packing of more and more transistors on less and less silicon... Progress he argues is, things like the coming smart dust revolution. Smart dust or more accurately networked intelligenece to do  hazaar  things like do remote surveliiance for the military. or the use of RFID in supermarkets... enabling tracking of merchandise and a  fully automated staff less  supermakret...    For almost 40 years we have all been subscribing to a simple dogma about the growth of the information age: progress means making more and more computing power available at lower and lower prices. Back in 1965 Gordon Moore laid out his famous law that the number of components that could be squeezed on to a silicon chip would double every year or two. Now everybody can buy a laptop computer with the computing power that entire nations were aspiring to in the 1970s.  Moore’s law still has a long future. But in 2004 the belief that progress means packing in ever more computing power will be seen as far too narrow. Just arriving is another kind of information revolution, driven by the ability to manufacture billions of tiny, intelligent communicating sensors. Capable of organising themselves into networks, intelligent sensors will make up for their small brains by their immense numbers.  
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Don't want to register for to read or use a website visit  urlLink bugmenot.com  via  urlLink Digital Deliverance 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Talk about crazy inventions... Matsushita has developed an  urlLink Intelligent screwdriver . It can be pre-programmed. As one readerd somments on the quoted post. it is more a luxury item than a practical tool...  an even better quote...   My Sears el-cheapo 14V screwdriver is a fair bit damn more intelligent than that one, I'd bet...   ... It's powered by my finger, which has a pretty straight pipe to my brain.  Beat that, Matsushita.  :)  
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      After th ePorn weblog, we now have porn search engine  urlLink Booble.com  
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think this  urlLink Magnetic Cup Holder  is worth having...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>06,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Subterrane - How to build an H-Bomb 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>05,January,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink eBay item 2976980274  is selling a presidential election vote... So Much for democracy...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Moving using  urlLink nothing  at all.
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Harvard is  urlLink starting  a student porn magazine called H - Bomb. India has a long long way to go... it'd seem...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Patent Number Two was invented by Patent Number One!   Whatever will they think of next... 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hired an air conditioner for the season... that leaves the tv, cable gas connection and a fridge
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I Moved houses today. Happiness! My own place finally...   Now all I need is an air conditioner, tv, cable and a fridge...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm moving Homes yet again... From South Delhi, I'm back to East Delhi. In Karkardooma to be precise.  This will be the 5th place in 8 months... Not bad if you ask me.   Hopefully I'll stick around this place for at least six months or so.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm House hunting yet again... East Delhi or NOIDA perhaps
     

 
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      test
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I dropped out of sight again...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Fujifilm FinePix S7000  is yet another alternative. Only this is 150 dollars more.. thought there is a 100 dollar rebate going with this. picture quality is said to be supect.. so I'm wary of this one...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Panasonic Lumix DMC-FZ10S  is another alternative camera that can be considered... only problem is the 100 dollar plus on the price tag...   definitely not affordable
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm going to be buying a digital camera soon... I've finally settled on the  urlLink Canon Powershot S1 IS . Mainly selected because of the huge Zoom (10X) and the image stabilisation system on the camera... Am Also buying a  urlLink Sandisk 256 Mb Compact flash Card .  and a couple of sets of  urlLink 2200 NiMH PowerEx batteries and a Maha Charger  to power the entire rig...  
     

 
    
</post>

<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I got an invite for  urlLink Game Never Ending . I'd signed up for this months ago. Now to see what it can do...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I was thinking of starting a blog with a theme. TV Program reviews perhaps, English Channels. I can't bear to watch the Star Plus crap anyway...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Google Ad Sense wrote back to my crib, saying we apologise blah blah and here is your account to make billions and billions of dollars, oops rupees. Mua hahaha.   Anyway the ads are not running as of now. maybe in 48 hours as claimed by the  urlLink faq 
     

 
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The reason I commented on the lack of ads on Blogspot, was because Google denied an adsense account, reason given was that this URL was duplicate submisssion. Considering that I only created the url a few days back, it is somewhat absurd...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As you can see, when you look at the top of  urlLink Marlinspike - Knot Untangler  There are no ads on this blogspot page. I know some people who registered only a couple of months ago, who do have ads on the blogspot pages...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been telling my guys at office for months now, but they didn't think it was a big thing. This  urlLink Blogging from Boston  article explores legitimacy accorded to bloggers at the Democratic nation Convention happeing in the US currently...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      :((( We were to have a class reunion. and yahoo groups was the preferred communication medium... oh welll I guess it is back to cell phones :) &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Self Pic, was trying to play around with the picin Photo Studio... Still some time to go before I master this&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My bike after extensive repairs... all the body panels were changed from black to blue.&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A  urlLink Google Search on  chirag  reveals that my blog is the fourth on the list. the only problem is that I've changed the URL to blogspot. So one wonders as to how the google algorithm will place me now.
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now that the camera is out of the way, I was thinking of getting myself a new hard disk mp3 player. This is a dream device  iRiver PMP 120  &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink     Or this  iRiver H 320   urlLink     urlLink     They have the advantage of being able to interface with my camera and download pics directly. Can Play MP3 (duh!), Ogg, WMA, Show pictures stored and the first one also plays video.
     

 
    
</post>

<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It's been a week since I started driving a bike again... I don't think I can get the bike to scream down the streets of Delhi at 100+ Kph for a few months to come :(  The Bike is now blue (Pics tomorrow), it was black before.   Black is not lucky (auspicious?) for me (or so an astrologer told my parents)
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Some More pictures here . This time of the house&nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is a stitched panorama of the view outside my dad's house in dehradoon. it spans a full 270 degrees... &nbsp; urlLink     urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have a new Feed URL at  urlLink http://chiragpatnaik.blospot.com/atom.xml 
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Am looking for a physiotherapist close to my place in Delhi... no luck so far :(
     

 
    
</post>

<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Have been trying to migrate from my previous host to Blogspot... A lot of bother... :(
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The url of my Blog has changed to   urlLink http://chiragpatnaik.blogspot.com/   See you there...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Not very flattering I agree...   The lighting was bad. I haven't shaved in a few days. The mushtache has to go. I was in hospital for a month.   u get the idea ... ;)     urlLink     urlLink   
     

 
    
</post>

<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I Put up some more pictures  urlLink here ... they aren't labeled yet.
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink This  is the first pic that I'm uploading from my brand new Canon S1. Many more on the way once I get to Delhi. Bandwidth in Doon is so darned expensive...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Gmail may still be in beta, but  urlLink Hacks   for it are already up and running...  Viva Gmail. The best thing since email itself... :)
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Neowin  forums has a story that hotmail is to upgrade space. 250 MB for free users and 2 GB for paid users. Of course I would still not use it because of the tons of spam that pours into hotmail accounts
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Friends, Pakistanis and Wellwishers, lend me your ears. (actually eyeballs) :).  After weeks of what can only be termed as medieval torture i.e. pricks, boiling water, melted wax, electrocution, fingers bent thisway and that, I've recovered to a state which can be termed as normal as far as civilised humans go. I was finally able ride a bike (Yes the very same one, that was smashed in my unfortunate close acquaintance with a truck on the picturesque route to Mussorie) as of yesterday. It was limited to a an agonisingly short 10 minutes, but till more strength returns that will have to do. Physiotherapy will continue for the next few months, but if all goes well, I should be back in Delhi on the first of August and rejoin on the 2nd. Of course I have to hunt for a physiotherapist that suits my timings, but that is a small matter...  Before you say that should be the last joyride across the country, I'm thinking of driving back to Delhi on the bike... still have to convince a few people though... :)  Cheerio  Chirag
     

 
    
</post>

<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have yet another invite for The Game never Ending... Hmmm Now to get rid of it...
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My company has declared a 5 day week from today. So now I get two days to kill on on the weekend... hmmm. I think I should plan to buy the DVD player as soon as possible. I have one on my laptop, but the screen size is no fun.  I'll maybe pick up a cheap sony two speaker DVD/Tuner combo. but Sony stuff in India is damned expensive...
     

 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      What the...  urlLink You are Blogging my view...   The first time i heard the term “Blogging”, the first thing that came to mind was two men in Kerela on a Gogonet tree and one saying to the other, “You are blogging my view”. However, now this means something totally different to me. Blogging my view, now means that after reading your blog, my views are changing. How many of us are actually willing to let go of our opinions and accept new ones as we just read or heard something different from the views we so strongly believed in all this while. This is like writing a personal diary for everyone to read. I always thought about those who write a diary. I thought those were the people so desperate that someone  picks up their diary and reads it and saves them. It was a cry for help for those poor recluses and introverts. And then they made this rule, thou shall not read a personal diary. This obviously attracted more people to their diaries. So am i turning into a hopeless recluse?? I hope not. I do tend to drift away, but i think it gives you a chance to increase the scope of your discussion. Anyways...  
     

  urlLink Link 
    
</post>

<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm back in Delhi. Yay! and I brought the rains... double yay!
     

 
    
</post>


</Blog>