<Blog>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Lstening to the radio this morning as they discussed the killing of Damilola Taylor and the social issues that create children who don't care about anything. The talk swung around to the attitude of children today and the issue of punishment. As usual as far as the media is concerned there are only two sides, those who advocate physical punishments and those who are against this. The sides always seem to have the 'beat them - it never did me any harm' and opposing them the do-gooders 'there are other ways to punish them'. I find it slightly amusing that the do-gooders never seem to actually give details of these 'other ways'. I've worked with youth for 17 years now and I have found that the attitudes of the boys I've worked with has changed over the years. When I started boys were eager to get on with whatever activity was going on. They were respectful to their elders and obeyed instruction without any problem. Now, they don't want to do anything, are cheeky and only do what is asked of them under severe protest. This is not all boys, but a vast majority.  The attitude is not helped by parents who in the past attended events, provided transport and generally encouraged their youngsters. Now some, not all, are uninterested, they give no encouragement, we never see them. There is a distinct lack of commitment from the youngsters that is sponsered by the 'he didn't want to' attitude of parents. Discpline has been eroded in this country. The attitude of 'you can't make me' gives every boy a powerfull weapon to disrupt whenever and whatever he wants. I think it's about time the media showed there are more than two sides to this discussion. And the alternatives to physical punishment should be discussed not hinted at
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Pigs might fly 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The crowd round a workmates desk wasn't for some problem he was having with work. They were all playing 'Who want's to be a millionaire'. Unfortunately they seemed to stall long before reaching the magic million.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm currently attemping to read a specification for changes to the software project I manage. Somehow, forgetting to use a style for presentation can be overlooked when the content seems to be the random thoughts about the changes, written as they occurred to the writer with no attempt to organise or even remove duplicate thoughts. Venting my thoughts this way means that I don't have to have an argument with the writer (again) and then have him spend the next couple of months stabbing me in the back whenever he gets the chance. (Ha Ha - management seems to be onto him)  So far this blog has just been me pointing to the odd/interesting pages I've seen on the web but I'm finding that when reading other blogs the more interesting bits are the daily life and thoughts of the writers. The idea of writing about everyday life somehow seems daunting, after all who would want to read about my life. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Why doesn't Gore admit defeat.  In his  urlLink TV address  he says that "And many thousands of votes that were cast on Election Day have not yet been counted at all, not once.". How does he know?  Surely the count could have been done a lot sooner, discarding those votes that were not valid.  This is so odd, in other countries, if something like this happened, observers from other countries (ie USA) would have been sent to decide if the voting is to be accepted or not.  Time for the USA to sort itself out? I think so. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Cool Guy  - All the reports eg  urlLink BBC  show David entering wearing only a hat, light trousers and boots but the webcast shows him with a jumper. He is also reported as 'unable to move' but he seems to have quite a bit of freedom. I think the guy's just plain nuts.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink America finds new way to invade Canada 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Who's off to the travel agents?  urlLink Porn pictures turn up in holiday brochure 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Nice to see that blogger is back up to speed. I was contemplating having to write something to generate my pages. The weekly archive is still causing me problems though. I've switched to monthly and it seems ok. Number of days posts on the main screen has problems
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Happy Birthday to John.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ABC News reports that "ATTRACTIVE PIGS Clinton and Chelsea visited the home of 31-year-old farmer's wife Le Thi Luong, who has renovated her tiny house with money made from her tofu-making machine and chickens."  urlLink Hillary Lauds Vietnam Village-Women Entrepreneurs  When the major news sites can't write HTML what chance for the rest of us. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink ICANN   urlLink report on new domain names  published. This is summarised by the  urlLink BBC 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Now all Bush has to do is repeat this on the Floridians.  urlLink Bush Executes 253 New Mexico Democrats: Retakes State's Five Electoral Votes  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The New Yorker article on  urlLink weblogging . thanks to  urlLink linkmachinego  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Talk about getting  urlLink loaded  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Cheap unmetered internet access is now close to becoming a reality for the UK, after industry regulator Oftel set out tough new guidelines for British Telecom.  urlLink BBC News  reports that we could soon enjoy unmetered internet access for as little as £10 a month. This has got to be a great boost to internet use in Britain. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The time some people have for creating things like this  urlLink Bush - Gore Dance  could I'm sure be used more constructively. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The new Netscape browser was supposed to conform to the standards more closely than any previous browser. But in this  urlLink report  doubt is cast on it's compliance with standards.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Privacy worries by mobile phone users seems to be spreading as  urlLink Sprint’s plan to use chips to track cell phones stirs privacy concerns . Before you think of throwing your phone away, take a moment to consider how many people have mobile phones, nobody is going to be keeping track of everyone. And if someone wants to keep track of YOU then phone or no phone they will. Dont forget just because you're paranoid doesn't mean they aren't after you. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Perhaps this should have been how the  urlLink ballot paper  should have been printed for Presidential Elections in Florida. How anybody with a modicum of comman sense could misinterpret the paper is beyond me. Even worse is to publically announce your stupidity by saying I couldn't understand the paper, well you get what you deserve. Perhaps the Democrats will be arguing that the  ballot paper  looked like this to the Republican Voters 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The world is full of guilable people. This example of how to fool some of the people some of the time is a cracker.  urlLink Pirate Software Scanner  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The  urlLink Patron Saint  of Spammers.  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      BBC lowest friday ratings for years  urlLink Minister criticises BBC1  I haven't rated the BBC on Friday night in a long time. There is never anything on. I wonder when the last time they had good ratings was. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Some people don't seem to have any common sense. In a report about  urlLink giving alms  this bloke seems to have taken things to far. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      An insight into American Presedential Elections - re the electoral colleges from George Will  urlLink Why  the Electoral College is still a good idea?  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      As  Jakob Nielsen  says  urlLink Flash: 99% Bad . I couldn't agree more. There can be no greater crime on the web today than those websites who force you to watch the designers idea of entertainment. Give me a quick loading page of information any day, thats why I went to the site in the first place. The only thing that compares is the splash screen. Who wants to look at a page that says 'click to enter'. When I type the URL I want the site not an extra page to download. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This is my last post till either I get a new monitor or I return to work on my birthday (2 Jan). So to those reading this  Have a Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      hey we're back on
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Vizzavi upgrade a mess . If you think Blog*spot has problems Vizzavi has upgraded and it's a shambles. They sent out new passwords that don't work, neither do the old ones. The service won't allow new logins. You cant migrate your email/calendar from the old service o the new. The only plus is its a lot faster.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Flash news, blog*spot back down
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Finally, we have connection. Now that blog*spot is back I've published the last two days muses. On the monitor situation, my wife doesn't like the monitor I've aquired and says we need to buy a new one. She says only 15" as there isn't room for anything bigger.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Only 5 days to go. The presents are all wrapped, the cards sent, just a small matter of the groceries for the festivities. Cant stand shopping so I'm not looking forward to the trip to the supermarket. A place that will be packed to the rafter with people hauling trolleys that are loaded to capacity. Christmas cheer, there'll be none of that, everybody will be wanting to get in and get out. Ah well only 5 days to go.  Blog*spots still not working but I've managed to aquire a monitor so I should be able to log on in the next couple of days  Fed up with having to redo other peoples work.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been using the new 'Blog This!' bookmarklet and so far I've posted to the wrong Blog every time. I'm going to have to keep my eyes open. With the Blog*Spot backbone lost, I dont know how soon these posts are going to reach publication but I'm going to continue. Unfortunately I can't surf at home as my monitor blew up the other night. Got to get it replaced ASAP. It was a shock hearing about the  urlLink death of Kirsty MacColl . I'm sure that may tributes will pour in for the singer.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Tesco smuggles in 2,500 PlayStation 2 consoles   Whats the world comming to. When a supermarket has to get it's supplies from the 'grey market'  urlLink Missing  A half ton statue is 'only noticeable by its absence' 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      On 6 January we could say, with Othello: "Chaos is come again."  urlLink An embarrassing relic of authoritarianism   US defence experts believe Saddam Hussein may be building a weapons supercomputer from Sony PlayStation 2s  urlLink Saddam grabbing PlayStation 2s for weapons 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Got a nice surprise, found I had a runner up price of a bottle of vodka and a Stollen cake in a Quiz. As the quiz organiser was a Church I was very surprised at the Vodka.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Beer aids clear vision  Good News, mines a pint.   urlLink Jobsworth Award  A council in County Durham has told a local taxi driver that he can't wear a Santa hat and beard because it doesn't match his identity photo.   urlLink Man rescues snowman from swordmen  A good citizen has come to the aid of a snowman when it was attacked by two sword-wielding teenagers.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Facemail  Do we realy need this. Surely text email is enough   urlLink ZDNet: News: Microsoft warns of Q2 profit shortfall  Is this realy a problem, $6.4 billion to $6.5 billion, profit for the quarter and people are complaining.  The whole Bush/Gore saga is now over I'm glad to hear. For those of us non-Americans this means that the news isn't filled with todays latest from the massed lawers of the two political parties squabbling over the slightest issue. But with this  urlLink Presidential Curse  maybe Gore is going to be better off.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink NASA: Satellite Odds of Hitting Someone 250-1  Maybe at these odds its a good job that the Pentagon has stepped in. Good buisness by Motorola in saying they were about to nudge the 560-kg satellites into decaying orbits.   urlLink Scientists create 3D floating hologram    urlLink It's 100 And Out for Uncle Bob 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Big Brother wants to listen to you 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Christmas is coming  Now December is here its time for the Christmas decorations to go up. Alison (my wife) and Joshua (my 5year old) both looked as excited as each other on Friday night as we got the tree and all its trimmings out. The lights worked, the baubles were intact and the garlands had survived. At the office however we fall into two camps, those who participate in decorating their section of the office and the 'Bah, Humbug' rest. This year more people have joined in. The decorations start in my teams corner. Tinsel, tree, lights, and the dodgy decorations hung from the ceiling - the ones that everybody had at home ten years ago and rather than throwing away have taken to work. The amount of decorations decreases as you move away from our corner until you come to some sections that are as bare as the rest of the year.  So get your decorations out 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Internet 'may be a passing fad' 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wired.com reports on a  urlLink Light saber . This sounds more like the stun setting on a phaser. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      How can a firm that keeps losing money stay in buisiness.  urlLink Amazon loses £60million . Just who is funding the massive losses this comapany is making, more than £180 million over the last two years. Somebody, somewhere has very deep pockets.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Bomb goes off at charity shop . And the animal rights groups claim they don't do this sort of thing. Terrorism is terrorism. On the day the Lockerbie suspect is found guilty isn't it about time that these extremists were found, convicted and jailed.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The following is from Second Wind by Dick Francis  There are lonely concrete launch pads there, deep set in dusty grass, They are circles scarcely fire-marked, barely twenty five feet accross, Rockets stood there, waiting, men inside with trusting courage, For the lift-off to the stars.  Now shuttles roar routinely to a station up in orbit,  Soon they'll print a cosmic schedule, issue a boarding pass, And who will spare a memory or even a passing thank you, To those circles in the grass?  Many a windy year will blow accross the Cape abandoned. Ghosts of fear and bumpy hearts wil thin and fade and pass. Woods green the concrete circles. Its from a launch pad out in orbit That men have gone to Mars.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tried  urlLink Opera  tonight, installed from a magazine disc. It seems ok but can't blog from it, I needed to load IE to write this
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Problems at work today with servers going down and then the power cutting off. Hopefully we havent lost any of the work my team is doing.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Dropped the news feed, it wasn't worth the slowdown in load times
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My daughter, Autumn has started walking, jus a few steps a couple of weeks ago has turned into walking almost the whole time, just reverting to crawling when speed is required. So this Saturday turned into a shopping expedition as she 'needed' new shoes, this then blossomed into 'we might as well get these, for the holiday' .. we're not going till the end of June. Ah well it's only money. The satisfaction as everyone admires you offspring and says she looks beautiful makes all those shopping trips worth it. Doesn't it. Sunday started with a phone call, Alison's (my wife) Auntie had died that morning. Although we had been expecting it, it's still a shock. Alison's mother was distraught on the phone so we spent a few hours with her. The rest of the day seemed to disapear, leaving us no time for cooking, so we ordered an Indian takeaway, very tasty.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink George W. Bush or Chimpanzee? 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Pain relief.  I think not.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Spent the last week with boiler problems, some mornings no heat and no hot water, arrangements to be made for people to come in and wait for the engineer. All seems to be sorted now but I had to take a half day holiday to wait for an engineer for a morning appointment, he arrived at 11:59am just as I was picking up the phone to ring and find out why the appointment had been missed. What a waste of time.  My Dad is now at home following his heart bypass operation. He's doing fine, following all his instructions. Thanks to those who have wished him well.  We're currently doing all the last minute development work for a major release of the software product I'm in charge of. The team is loving cramming all those last minute 'wouldn't it be nice ...' features in.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Microsoft down  also reported by  urlLink ZDnet .
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Pentaguard  urlLink Mass hack takes out govt sites 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Freedom of speech , not at Hotmail! Microsoft's Hotmail has been discarding e-mail sent to and from sites hosted by controversial Internet service providers.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink She's back  Melissa virus alert
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Dad is doing well although felt a bit grotty all day yesterday. He is now off all monitors and drips etc and being encouraged to walk. I'll keep you posted   urlLink Postal Experiments 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Got to visit my Dad in hospital tonight, he had a triple heart bypass monday and already is off the monitors and being encouraged to walk. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink AltaVista decide they own the patents on search engine technology.  In an attempt like BT claiming it has the right to hyperlinks AltaVista has patents on spidering and indexing which means it believes that virtually everyone out there who indexes the Web is in violation of at least several of those key patents. The whole idea of patenting the idea's and logical processes behind software of this sort is insane. Note they are not the only ones Amazon.com patented the patent for its affiliate programs ie If an affiliate puts a link to Amazon on its Web site, and someone follows that link to buy something from Amazon, the affiliate gets a cut. Is that an original idea? The Patent Office says it is. The also took out a patent on one-click ordering and promptly took Barnesandnoble.com to court to stop offering that service. A Seattle judge later issued a preliminary order against B&N. Maybe this sums up the whole  urlLink issue 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Talk about the  urlLink blind leading the blind 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Whoops!! 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink BT suggests using phonebox  rather than mobile.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink 'Metric martyr' faces £5,000 fine . I can't see what his problem is. British schools have been teaching metric for over 25 years. The whole metric/imperial measurement issue should be long sorted.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink The ultimate computer productivity tool  Thanks to  urlLink Greybo 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Official  urlLink Lord of the Rings   site goes live today
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Vizzavi upgrade still not fixed 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Nader Wants Internet Control 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Woman sues McDonald's firm after car coffee spill . Some people need an injection of common sense, and the American legal system needs reviewing if anybody thinks the defendants in this case have a case to answer. Surely the ownus is on the Woman to check if the cup holder is safe before using it to hold coffee, which is supposed to be HOT!!
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink You got fired   urlLink Judge compares Bill Gates to Napoleon   urlLink British prime minister hit by tomato   urlLink Revamped Broncos To Test Saints   urlLink Faster fast food  McDonalds Tests Wireless Payment Technology Finally, a decent  urlLink hands free cellular headset  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Listening to the radio this morning I as they discussed the idea of the workplace being more representative of the community. (ie posative discrimination) The idea of a company employing somebody to fulfill quotas/targets rather than employing purely on merit is PC gone mad.  Posative discrimination means that someone will be discriminated against (and thats illegal if its race or sex thats the discriminating factor).  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink The Public 8 Ball 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Woman bit off testicle . Wjat amazes me is that he did not immediately notice he had lost his testicle, which was later found under a picture frame by police.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Finally got a monitor so I'm back in buisness, although downloading email took forever last night.  urlLink Streakers  are now available for the table-top football game Subbuteo 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Polar bear penis bone up for sale . Who would want this, and why
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Credit Card Clones , this may worry some of you  urlLink The Internet Villain Awards   I reported that  urlLink Sadam buys Playstation2s  an update says his agents  urlLink couldn't find any 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Mysterious monolith appears in Seattle park 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Did You make a New Years Resolution, I didn't though Alison did on my behalf (looks like I'm on a diet). Are you finding it difficult to comply with your own resolutions? Have you broken them already?  I never make them, they are too hard to keep.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've added a news feed to the right hand site. I've yet to decide if it's going to work ok. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Happy birthday to Me  Well I'm back at work after an exhausting (family) Christmas & New Year, but still no monitor. Maybe this week I'll get some time to buy/aquire one
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink It's not only Windoze that people hate 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Health news:  Dad is getting better all the time, although he's realising that he needs to rest more after excercise than he has been doing. My slipped disc/trapped nerve is still giving me some trouble but I'm coping.  Tried  urlLink LiveJournal  as a general exercise on blogging. Still on hold as the desktop client wont log in.  BLOGGER Rules. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Microsoft's strange advertising . Should they be saying we were crap but now we're better? Well of course they should but in an advert to try and make you buy their products?????
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Here's one to cheer you up 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Penguin thrown to the lions . There's some sad bastards about.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was wondering why I hadn't had any visitors to my site, checking my counters stats there didn't seem to be any hits for quite a while, then I realised on changing the style I had left out the counter code. Duh!
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      "We've had three major generations of computing: mainframes, client-server and Internet computing, there will be no new architecture for computing for the next 1,000 years." so says Larry Ellison chief executive of Oracle. This guy mist have some serious predictive software or one giant crystal ball.  urlLink Full story 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Be carefull with your  urlLink e-mails 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink BillyConnolly wins web name battle . Well yes he may have done but the  urlLink site  is still showing Rougemar Billyconnolly Available now for stud duty.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wasted a morning waiting for the Gas Board to come and fix my boiler. Ther say we'll be there between 8&12 but what they mean is we'll be there sometime (probably about 12). When I rang them to say it was 12:05 and nobody had arrived and I hadn't had a call to tell me they were going to be late all I got was he's on his way now, and its only 5 minutes.  They couldn't take on board that I had wasted a whole morning, and used a up a half day holiday from work. It's about time the service industries got their act together, surely its not that hard to give an approximate time, within a couple of hours would be a start.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      blogspot now ok says blogger, I'll give it a try
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Added my imood and cant get the site published
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Slight reorganisation, me on left, links on right. Hopefully this gives more on initial view
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      An update on my slipped disc, the pain killers are working ( a little ) but as they reduced the inflamation my leg started to hurt also, turns out I've got a trapped nerve also. The leg hurts more than the back at the moment and I've got more pain killers for that. I'm starting to rattle.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Got an email from  urlLink Mo  who said 'It's all gone quiet at Peex. don't tell me you've given up...'. No Mo I've not given up but my back is causing me to spend less time sat at the computer and more time laid on the floor.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tried  urlLink Blogfinder  with my sites name and came up with just my own sites plus a couple of others, one of which didn't load (unable to access) NB it now loads. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Kournikova virus hits computers . When are people going to learn
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The Governments plans for  urlLink Comprehensives to be overhauled  seems to be a recipe for disaster. Specialist schools, selective schools, schools managed by religions (who's going to decide which religions can manage schools) and business (what's in it for them). I dread to think where it's all leading
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Finally went to the Doctors yesterday, I've had a bad back for a while now but last Wednesday's ten-pin bowling seemed to be the onset of a great deal of pain. The Doctor tells me I've slipped a disc, so I'm on painkillers and hoping the disc will slip back in soon
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      "Instead of just trucking the nuclear waste off into the distance ... the waste should be kept close to the scientists who claim they have the technology to look after it." — Lucy Brown, a spokesperson for  urlLink Irati Wanti , a website started by Aboriginal women opposed to nuclear dumping in the Australian Outback.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Have you ever watched kids On a merry-go-round Or listened to the rain lapping on the ground? Ever followed a butterfly's erratic flight Or gazed at the sun into the fading night? You better slow down Don't dance so fast Time is short The music won't last.  Do you run through each day on the fly? When you ask "How are you?" Do you hear the reply? When the day is done, Do you lie in your bed With the next hundred chores Running through your head? You'd better slow down Don't dance so fast Time is short The music won't last.  Ever told your child,  We'll do it tomorrow And in your haste, not see his sorrow? Ever lost touch, Let a good friendship die 'Cause you never had time To call and say "Hi"? You'd better slow down Don't dance so fast Time is short The music won't last.  When you run so fast to get somewhere You miss half the fun of getting there. When you worry and hurry through your day, It is like an unopened gift.... Thrown away... Life is not a race. Do take it slower Hear the music Before the song is over. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Spent the last few days suffering without computer at work as the 'Technical Department' were reinstalling my machine as dual boot NT4/W2K. What a cock up, first nothing under NT worked as SR1 was missed on office2000 and the reboot after each product installation was deferred. Secondly once I got my machine back it had W2K Server rather than Professional and as it was for testing we needed the client version. Next time I'm going to do it myself.  My dad is doing well, he's doing his daily walks, further each day without getting any pains or problems with his breathing. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wish I could write error messages like  urlLink this 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Rugby finger-fiend banned for 12 weeks . Mr Jones said: "It wasn't a wedgie. That's when your pants are pulled up your arse. I think I know the difference between a wedgie and someone sticking their finger up my bum."
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Stormy waters ahead for portals . This is hardly news. The consolidation of portals due to their falling ability to generate revenue has been under discussion for at least a year if not more.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink AOL UK bans time 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've just spent a fortnight off work due to my slipped disc, various visits to the osteopath and the physio have got me back to work although the back is still painful at times. Alison has spent this weekend decorating our bedroom. This has seemed to necessitate trip to the DIY shops plus getting new bedding, curtains, and ornaments. I'd just have slapped on a new coat of paint and left it at that.  Work seems to have managed without me - although I've got a pile of things to do - Ah well, nose back to the grindstone.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Not posted for a while as I've been very busy both at home and at work.  urlLink LiveJournal  is still a problem on Win2000, but Win95 seems to work fine. I'll try to post some more this week as workload allows. And now back to the grind
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Work has been a little slow following the latest release of our software package. It seems we've tested it way beyond the usual, and this has resulted in only a couple of faults reported in the last two weeks.  On the home front tomorrow I'm travelling down to Coventry for my brother Stephen's wedding. He's the only member of the family to live outside our local area, both my other two brothers live within 5 minutes of our parents house. It's not like we haven't been around. I attended Coventry Polytechnic some 13 years ago, David was in the army and lived all over but we've both ended up back in our home town. Simon on the other hand has always lived here.  The kids seem to grow up fast, Autumn is now starting to talk a little and associating words with things - at the moment its nose, nose, nose.....  Joshua's reading is coming on great, I don;t know how he compares with others in his class but he has come on in leaps and bounds in the last six months.  I've been thinking about trying instant messageing but what with  urlLink ICQ ,  urlLink MSN ,  urlLink Yahoo!  there seems to be an abundance of the things. I think I'll try  urlLink Jabber  this has a gateway to the others except AOL's IM. only thing remaining is I don't know anyone who currently uses IM.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Microsoft promises it won't meddle with digital TV market , and we can all trust them eh!! I don't think so.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Racy gun photos earn prison time 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Release Day. We made it, the release is finished and ready for delivery.   At home Joshua settled for trip to McDonalds rather than getting soaked for a walk to the fair. We'll probably be goingin tonight. I can't see him going on anything so it'll be just a walk with lots of noise and flashing lights.  The whole family seems to have come down with a cold, so the tissue box is emptying at an alarming rate.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Release Day -1. Work is now in the frenzy of getting the software release ready. With final bug fix's still going in and a datebase change added today, we might be a little late. Well another day won't matter. Will it?  The fairground hit our town this week and even though it's bucketting down, I've prommised Joshua (my 5 year old) that I'll take him tonight. So I'm in for a drenching.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The back is much better. I'm mobile again.  My son had his friend round for tea this Saturday. It's amazing how much noise and mess two five year olds can create when left to their own devices. Games involving lots of plastic action figures (power ranger zords, batmen, action men and others) seemed to involve them both shouting at the top of their voices about how they were pretending that this or that figure kicked/puched/shot/etc the other. Ah wish I was five all over again.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Cool  Server
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've added a couple of counter to evaluate their performance and to give me some better idea of my sites usage. I'll keep them both on for a while as I monitor them to determine which gives me the best data.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Let's see if I understand how it works lately . . .  If a woman burns her thighs on the hot coffee she was holding in her lap while driving, she blames the restaurant. If your teen-age son kills himself, you blame the rock 'n' roll music or musician he liked. If you smoke three packs a day for 40 years and die of lung cancer, your family blames the tobacco company. If your daughter gets pregnant by the football captain you blame the school for poor sex education. If your neighbor crashes into a tree while driving home drunk, you blame the bartender. If your cousin gets AIDS because the needle he used to shoot up with heroin was dirty, you blame the government for not providing clean ones. If your grandchildren are rude brats without manners, you blame television. If your friend is shot by a deranged madman, you blame the gun manufacturer. And if a crazed person breaks into the cockpit and tries to kill the pilots at 35,000 feet, and the passengers kill him instead, the mother of the deceased blames the airline. I must have lived too long to understand the world as it is anymore.  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Its not just governments that are spying on you   urlLink It's not the phones that are the problem it's the drivers 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Took the kids to Gulivers World yesterday. A great day out for younger kids, plenty for them to do, with wnough for older kids and younger adults to keep everyone entertained.  urlLink Tourists face new 'sun tax' on Spanish islands , good job I've already booked a fortnight in Salau on the Costa Dorada for next year. This year we're going to Teneriffe - only 5 weeks to go   urlLink E-mail users warned over spy network . How often do you use any encryption, and even if you already have something like  urlLink pgp  how many of the people you email do you have some sort of encryption key for?
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just been offerd a great deal on a holiday for next year. 2 bed appartment for a forghtnight in Salau for 4 people (ie me and alison and our two kids) for £378. An "offer I couldn't refuse"
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Due to problems with then blogger servers and their T1 connection the Discuss feature is currently out-of-action
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink A painful affair of the Internet heart . This details the webblog of Kaycee Nicole a 19 year old with leukaemia who never existed. People are saying it's outrageous that this hoax was perpetrated. Unless the weblog actually asked for money or gifts then there is no hoax it was just a story, a work of fiction. The only hoax was the one these people have inflicted on themselves.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Police to sms-bombard stolen phones 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well it's been anual performance and salary reviews this week. I got a glowing performance review, and the note that as we expand I'm in line for promotion - my boss is already thinking of me as his right hand man. I was pleased with my salary increase although you always want more.  I'm now starting to look forward to the summer holiday - a fortnight in Tenereffe. We're going with the same friends we went to Cornwall with last summer, where we had a great time despite the weather. Hopefully the weather will be better and we'll come back tanned and relaxed - although with a five yearold and two toddlers I don't know about the relaxed.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink 3 year investigation - wanking is immoral 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Looks like I was on the ball with jabber as  urlLink France Telecom backs Jabber IM . Although I haven't yet had time to use it, I've downloaded it ready for instalation
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Surfer mistook great white shark attack for friend fooling around . Duh!
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Friday night update: Wigan gave Wakefield a thrashing 50-6 and to top the night off Leeds beat StHelens 74-16. Bank holiday weekend. Saturday took the kids swimming with some friends. 5 adults and 4 kids.Sunday not very busy. Monday afternoon in the park with my two kids. Joshua and I kicked a ball around whilst Autumn (16mths) toddled around on the grass. She has go used to walking on the different surface but after she falls down she just sits there as to get up she would have to put her hand on the grass. Can't wait for her reaction to the beach.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Work has been hectic. I'm training staff to use the new quoting system my team has written along with keeping our customer happy with bug fixes for the major release of the software we've spent the last eight months writing. On top of that I'm interviewing for new people to strengthen the development teams to deal with the incoming work - at least two major deals signed in the last fortnight.  I'm off to the match tonight - Rugby League - Wigan v Wakefield  - hopefully the Warriers will stuff the Wildcats.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tomorrow is the start of two weeks offline. I'll be on holiday with family and friends in Tenerife. So my intermittent blogging will be resume mid July. We seem to have been packed for ages – Alison packed our cases Sunday and since then I’ve been moving them or falling over them every time I go into our bedroom. The only part I’m not looking forward to is the flight. I’m not worried about flying I’m worried about keeping a five year old and a mischievous 18 month old occupied for 4 hours when they have to remain in the seat – or in Autumn’s case on my knee. The worse part of taking any time off work is getting everything set up so that you know everybody has enough to do, knows who to report to, and that everybody is aware of who is dealing with any issues that come up. And you know that as soon as you get back there will be hundreds of emails, requests and things that have piled up in your absence that anybody could have dealt with but everybody assumed somebody would deal with it and nobody did.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Spent Wednesday to Friday confined to bed/sofa with tonsillitis. Felt awful, couldn't eat couldn't drink wanted to sleep all the time. I'm back to work now and I find that our company is in the process of implementing its 'INTERNET ACCEPTANCE USE POLICY (AUP)'. I think I'll need to review it thoroughly to see if I can continue posing from work or if this site becomes an evening process. If it goes to evening then I'll be posting less often as I don't seem to get on the computer all that regularly, must be something to do with the wife and the two kids.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Autumn (17 months) last night decided that a half hours nap in the car was quite enough. When we put her to bed she decided that it would be rather amusing if she waited till we were at the bottom of the stairs and then get out of bed and remove things (noisily) from drawers and shelves till we went back to replace her in her bed. By 10pm she tired of this and decided to go to sleep, I don't know who was more tired her or us.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Blogvoices removed for time being
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Triumph of the Weblogs  by Kevin Werbach. An interesting piece that explains some of why we do this. reference by  urlLink Blogger 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink US smoker wins billions in damages . For anybody to claim he was unaware of the dangers is ridiculous, for a jury to award this sort of amount does 'holds the  American judicial system up to world-wide ridicule ' and is a further example of the  urlLink if you didn't tell me in BIG letters that something is stupid I'll sue you .
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      By 2005, an estimated 35 billion e-mail messages will be sent daily -- six daily messages for each person on the planet. There will be a billion e-mail accounts by that time, [an] IDC study said.   urlLink RCFoC Quote of the Week.  Thats each person sending 6 messages and each inbox receiving 35. - Mismatch of numbers or does this suggest that less than 1/6th of the population will be online?
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sunday was Joshua's birthday party. We held it a couple of weeks early so that his school friends could attend before they all went away for the summer holidays. The 15 kids enjoyed 2 hours of madness at a Wacky Warehouse. I'm glad I don't work with young kids either for a job or a volunteer post - my head was ringing by the time the parents arrived to collect their offspring.  Amber (daughter of the friends we went on holiday with) has got the chicken pox (as predicted by the doctors in Spain after her fathers hospitalisation with shingles). She's covered with spots - poor thing. Hopefully Autumn will not get it - but then again perhaps she will.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well I'm back. Two weeks in the sun, and I'm feeling refreshed and raring to go - NAH. Two weeks with my two kids and the daughter of the friends who went with us was not that relaxing. I got a tan, not from lying in the sun unfortunately but from walking the pram round trying to get Autumn to sleep and from playing in the pool with the kids. Andy spent 5 days in hospital with shingles, with his wife Wendy rushing back and forward from hotel to hospital and us Looking after their two year old Amber.  Back to work and the problems they had last week meant I was better off in the sun by the pool. Its going to take a few days to get everything back on an even keel.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       the saga ends?  driving home last night a text message on my old phone from the old company invite me to take up thier one time offer
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Mobile phone saga continues  Just got a call from the termination desk, trying one final time to interest me in a deal. Hopefully that's the end of that.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Mobile phone saga part 3 & 4  Since the last message on this subject I've received a text message from the old company asking me to ring (0800 number) and on ringing asked me if they could do anything to retain my business. Then I got yet a call from them today asking if they could do anything to retain my business. They apparently think they are going to wear me down or maybe it's just that they are not recording my details each time they speak to me. The last caller also asked if I would tell them who I'd moved my business to. You can guess my reply to that one. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
        urlLink Google  increases search rate  Both  urlLink Davenet  and  urlLink Doc Searl  suggest that frequently updated sites are being re-cached more frequently. I've checked this site and the cache is from between July 24 and Aug 5. I apparently don’t update the site often enough for  urlLink Google  to have added me to its frequent updated sites list.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Favourite kids tv programs  Can't say I agree with the possition some of these programs came in the top 100 but what a walk down memory lane this was.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Archives  Having problems with my archives, I can't seem to get them to republish. And I seem to have got errors on some of the months, even though I had no problems at the time of the postings
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       What a weekend!  Friday evening we went out for a meal with Andy & Wendy, part way through the meal I got a text message from my brother, his wife had gone into labour (1 week early). A quick phone call later, I hate people who use mobiles in inappropriate places don't you, I found out she'd been at the hospital since 11am that morning. Waited all night and all day Saturday with infrequent messages saying 'No news yet'. Sunday at 4:45 she gave birth to a daughter 'Jessica Maya' 6lb 6oz. Mother and baby doing fine, father knackered, relations exhausted with waiting for news.  Monday we took the kids out, Joshua is learning to ride his bike without stabilisers. He's almost there, but pedalling, balancing and steering seem to be just one more thing than he can concentrate on.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Wow I'm a catfish according to  urlLink this quiz      Make no mistake, this cat's a cool customer. Your laid-back nature makes you the perfect choice for swimming around with. No need to compete with the other big fish; you're comfortable in your "fins" and love to laugh. You don't have time for fish fights -- you're too busy lending a fin. You're a hard worker and can be counted on to get the job done. If anybody teases you about being a bottom-dweller, remind them that you're simply more resourceful than the average fish.   Ref from  urlLink Meg 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       continuing saga  Further to my mobile phone saga. The old company rag to confirm my letter of cancellation, and asked whether I had got a new contract elsewhere. When I told them I had they asked why I hadn't gone to them to see if they could match it. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       The saga starts  I came to the end of my contract with my mobile phone provider. So I rang them up and asked about upgrade options for signing another 12-month contract.  I was amazed at the response -  No Deals .  They couldn't even discount phones that they were giving away  FREE  to new customers as detailed on an advert in that days paper. They even tried to say that the advert wasn't them but it was a separate company that ran the shops and then contracted with them for airtime. As all the local shops for the company are now relocated I decided it was time to check the local shops and find a new provider. I eventually settled with the same network through their own shop. I got the phone I wanted at half the advertised price with a credit to my account of double the price I paid for the phone.  So I'm now passing the new number round (better deal for new number than retaining old number) and flashing my new phone wherever I go.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Reading the stats for this site I have realised that although I didn't set out to make it UKcentric, the site is read mainly by people in the UK. I've been wondering how to get the site more widely read, perhaps by adding some US content (non-derogatory).
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Heard a devoted Man United fan admit his sides defence is crap this morning on the radio. Geoff Boycott (a 40 year supporter of the club) was saying teams with a good quick attack will cause them problems as their defence is awful, something every non ManU fan has known for years (how the Nevilles get into the team baffles me, I couldn't see them making the grade at many other Premiership teams). Hopefully this might mean that other teams apart from  Liverpool  will get at least one win against them this season, and hopefully  Liverpool  will do the double on them again.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Found a reference to  urlLink blogBuddy  on  urlLink evhead  and thought I'd give it a try. Worked straight out of the box, after entering blogger username and password and entering the proxy server id it found my blogs and Here I go posting. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This weekend saw the start of the local Boys' Brigade companies annual camp (not really annual as it hasn't been run for about 7 years). I am unable to stay all week but I did my bit by driving the van with all the gear to the site on Saturday morning (and I'll be picking it up again next weekend). The rain appeared at intermittant times giving us a chance of getting the tents erected in the breaks and we managed to stay almost dry. We had most of the tentage up including the marquee by the time it absolutely poured down for the best part of an hour.   I returned home Sunday morning after a night with little sleep to take the kids to a Birthday Party. Amber (the daughter of the friends we went on holiday with) was two and her cousin Fergus was one. Parties for two year olds can be so tiring (or is that boring) for those who are not directly involved.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Some people will go to any lengths fo a bit of money - including ruining a childs life.  urlLink Child's name offered to highest bidder 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Boring, boring, boring  Yesterday I had to drive up to Hull for a buisness meetimg. Total 4 hours drive for a 3 hour meetimg that mainly consisted of people saying yes we understand that the XML schemas we've defind are the standard  but  we'll need to have some fudges when dealing with certain parties. I thought the whole idea for a standard was that everybody adhered to it. Needles to say I left with a headache and when reporting back today found my notes contained only comments for me to check certain information to ensure we are uptodate.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
        urlLink Lessons on how to fight terror   A message from the United Kingdom: Don't torture. Don't shoot boys who throw stones. And don't imagine for a moment that there is any guarantee of success.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Nasty virus  Work today was halted as we were infected by  urlLink Nimda . Our technical team due to holidays is down to one person and he was dashing about like a blue assed fly, as people all over the building were asking for the  anti-virus software disc or just the latest update. As all the machines on the network had files deposited on their shared drives by an infexted machine we were all in need of a fix.  Hopefully as we are all now running the av software we'll all be moderately safe from now on.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       In Perspective   urlLink Pale Blue Dot : A Vision of the Human Future in Space by Carl Sagan
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I haven't posted for a couple of days as nothing going on in my life had any real relevance in light of the atrocities committed on Tuesday. I find myself starting to write some comment on the aftermath, something to express how I and others are feeling but on reading what I have written I find myself deleting the words as they either don't fully express what I'm trying to say or they are too sanctimonious and critical. I grieve for people I don't know and my prayers go out to all who have any connection with this tragic incident.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Joshua went back to school yesterday. It doesn't seem like two minutes since I took him for a couple of hours during the last term before he started and now he's in Year 2. He seems to have grown loads in the summer, even so I bet he's still one of the smallest in his class. We got the usual report from him about what he'd done during the day - 'Work and PE'. He was excited about bringing home some spelling to learn as  homework  as well as the usual reading book. I can't imagine he's going to keep the excitement for homework for too long.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Archive  After amending my template slightly and republishing all my archives they seem to be all ok. I'm not sure what was causing the errors but it seems to be ok now.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Went to visit my brother at the weekend to see the new addition to the family.  The baby - Jessica Maya - is as good as gold, wakes for a feed and then straight back to sleep afterwards, with just two feeds during the night. Joshua loves babies and was constantly asking to hold her. Autumn who is only 20 months was constantly looking for the baby saying 'Baby - shhh'. She wasn't bothered by Alison holding Jessica as she sees Alison holding babies at nursery, but she got quite jealous when I held Jessica.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The houses we visited were ok. But neither had much space outside and one had the brightest   orange   hall stairs and landing . So we continue to look
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yet another example of America's preposterous litigation society.  urlLink U.S. seeks recall of 7.5 million BB guns . I don't approve of guns, but to say a company should recall its product because somebody might get shot is ridiculous. Who points a gun at someone else?  You're just asking for this kind of thing to happen.  While it may assuage their guilt to blame others, the ultimate responsibility lies with individuals. It should not be the responsibility of the state or manufacturers to say "don't do this, its stupid". One of the greatest delusions in the world is the hope that the evils in this world are to be cured by legislation.  -- Thomas B. Reed (1886) 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Went to try some contact lenses this lunchtime. Apparently I have an astigmatism, something to do with rugby balls not footballs duh? My left eye was fine but the right eye wasn't focused so they are going to have to order some lenses from a different supplier.  On the house front, we are aranging to see a couple of houses tomorrow night.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Took the kids swimming Saturday, considering how much I enjoy the water the kids must take after Alison as niether of them are confidant. We're just going to have to go more often.  Alison was going out Saturday night, one of the girls at work's leaving do. She thought it would be an idea if I defrosted the freezer as I would have plenty of spare time. She must have forgotten how long the freezer takes as I waited till Autumn was in bed and Alison had gone to get ready, when she came down ready to go I was sat watching the telly all finished.  We really need to start looking for a new house. Alisons mother and father are buying ours, they put thier house up for sale last Thursday, the first viewer (Friday evening) put in an offer Saturday morning. Fortunately for us it was rejected as too low, but we need to satrt looking.  An odd thing about buying houses. If you go into a shop to buy something you tend to accept that the price on the goods is what you have to pay. With houses the buyer always seems to think that they can offer a figure substantially below that and the seller has to take that. Why? Surely if a house is valued at a price then thats what the seller bases his calculations for his move on. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Blogger occasionally looses my archives, so I have to republish. Unfortunately this means they get published with my current template. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been using blogbuddy since  urlLink Aug17  and just upgraded to 0.4.0. All previous versions worked out of the box, but this time I got an error. I've reverted to 0.3.1 till I see its fixed.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      MSN Messenger, seems like a good idea but you need to know people with hotmail accounts. Mines pdbibby at hotmail.com
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Columbine victims' families sue maker of anti-depressant  Another case of the absurd legal system in the USA where if something happens to you and yours, you sue everybody concerned, knowing that there are lawyers who will pursue your ridiculous claims and judges and juries that will award you money.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Friday night Andy & I went into town for a couple of drinks with friends, this ended in us gatecrashing a 21st Party. We finished the night eating chineese take-away at his house waking his wife - he shouted up the stairs as we got in 'Are you awake love'. Anyway she came down and ate half his supper - serves him right.  Saturday, hairdresser rang early to inform us that Julia who cuts the whole family's hair  had rung in sick so we're going to have to arrange a new appointment. Slightly later the optician rang to cancel my appointment to have contact lenses fitted, apparently he didn't have the ones needed for me and will ring bake to re-arrange when the order is delivered.  Saturday evening, a dinner party at Andy & Wendy's. The evening went great. We were still at the table talking and drinking untill somebody checked their watch and realised it was almost midnight  Sunday turned into a lazy day, the kids didn't wake us till going up to 10 and we had nothing planned for the whole day.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Crap day at work yesterday, a number of meetings where I was the lone dissenting voice on the proposed plans. Also the proposed plans all seemed to be more work and in particular more for me
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      No posts, been off work for the last week and didn't go anywhere neear the computer at home. We spent the week shopping, or so it seemed. We have now bought all the kids Christmas presents (and wrapped them). It's not me who is so organised, it's Alison. On returning to work colleagues are saying there should be some sort of law regarding being so prepared.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Social Life  Joshua seems to have a better social life than I do. He's off again to another birthday party, so I'm leaving work early today to get him there on time. I seem to spend my time taking Alison and the kids here and there, Saturday afternoon was an exception.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Sunday  Visited  urlLink Eureka  this afternoon. Joshua loved it, running from exhibit to exhibit, all hands on. Somewhere to visit for those with kids between 6-13, loads for them to see and do.  Saturday  Time for a beer. Joshua was visiting a friend, Alison and Wendy took Autumn and Amber to  urlLink  C  l  o  w  n  -  A  -  R  o  u  n  d   so Andy and I got time to go into town and down a few beers. 2 hours, 4 pints and 8 games of pool later we weaved our way home to have a couple of cans watching the football results.  We were amazed at Spurs being 3-0 up, but knew ManU would come back to win. They always do, must be some sort of fix going on, the wives and girls arrived to loud booing as ManU went into the lead. All in all everybody had a good and for Andy and I an intoxicating afternoon.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Our fianancial advisor saved us a trip to the bank tomorrow by checking out the deals for mortgages and finding one that fits our situation. He also filled in the forms and sent them off. So the mortgage application is under way. We're taking the kids to see the new house tomorrow. I hope they like it, but it's tough if they don't.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well we found a house this weekend. This morning I've contacted a solicitor and now all we need is a mortgage and we're up and running.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      We really need to find a house soon, Alisons parents havea a firm offer on their house, they are buying ours. So were checking the estate agents for houses that are available, and driving round looking at various area to see if we would like to live there. It's time consuming and we seem to be getting nowhere.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Took the kids to the christmas lights switch on in town.  The lights are not that impressive but there was a fireworks display that Joshua enjoyed. Autumn is suffering with a cold so she went to sleep.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I went back to the opticians yesterday and returned the contact lenses. I could see ok whilst outside, distance was no problem. Inside was another matter. Nothing close up was quite in focus. I also felt that the right eye was being irritated all the time. So I'm back to glasses
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Sunday  Remembrance Parade in the morning, it's sad to see the numbers of old ex-service men dwindle as the years go on. The afternoon was spent watching the Lions outperform the Kangaroos and our Rugby League guys finish off a good weekend for British Rugby.  Saturday  Watched the footy, England still have a ways to go to be good enough to win the World Cup. The Rugby Union guys did well defeating the Aussies. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Picked up some contact lenses yesterday. I had some 12 years ago and thought I'd try them again.  Had them in fo a couple of hours last night and all this morning. Can't get used to them yet! I've got till next Wednesday lunchtime to try them before making any decisions.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Problems with the archive, they all work except October.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The last week seems to have all been regarding the Boys' Brigade. I run a local company (2nd Accrington) and over the last few days I seem to have done nothing else Monday night - rehersal for annual display Tuesday night - final check that I have all awards and my annual report is ok Wednesday night - display night Thursday 8am - Speak to local paper regarding display Thursday 4pm - Speak to another local paper Sunday afternoon - Founders day service and activities day This Wednesday we meet for our normal weekly meeting and Sunday morning will be the local Rememberance Day Parade to attend. Can't wait for the Christmas break
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Fireworks  Saturday night we went to the local cricket club for their bonfire and fireworks. The kids enjoyed the event although Autumn fell asleep immediately after the final firework. Joshua was his usual nervous self, 'were to near the fire, it's burning me', 'the fireworks are too loud' but he gets over it when we ignore his complaints. Last night we lit some fireworks in the yard. Joshua loved them, through the patio doors, Autumn wasn't interested.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink School seeks right to smack.  More power to them. It's about time sombody stood up for the majority, rather than letting the minority (with loud voices) rule us.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I hate month ends. Each month admin ring up with problems with the interface between the quote and ledger systems. First its invoices that are dated first of the month that need altering to end of the previous month, then its the interface file that needs deleting and the data setting so the two periods can be imported seperately. It goes on and on.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      We had a pleasant weekend courtesy of Alison's employers but Monday morning Alison did her back in again so we were unable to attend my works do on Wednesday evening.  I spent Wednesday delivering cards presents and picking up Joshua's Christmas present. He's bound to have me running up and down the street holding on to the back of his new bike as he learns to balance and steer at the same time, no matter the weather on Christmas Day. Final day at work today before my Christmas break, and I can't see me doing much blogging till I return on my birthday Jan2. So a happy Christmas to anybody reading this.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Keep a lookout for colleagues with one of  urlLink these 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I see that the 3 most used links recently on  urlLink blogdex  are links to 'tests'. Why on earth do people fill these in, I know I have in the past and probably will in the future, so I'm not imune to them, but Why?
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      We went to Alison's works Christmas Do on Saturday night. Not a bad night, especially as Alison was presented with a weekend away for two as part of the tenth year celebration of her employers. Alison has worked there for nine of the ten years the company has been going with only one employee with more service. So this coming weekend we are off sans kids for a bit of R&R.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Getting some hassle about the house. Apparently the people 3 down the chain are pressing for a 14th Dec completions date. There's no chance of us being ready, although our in-laws maybe (they are buying our house). The survey on our new house is being carried out tomorrow, so we should hear about our mortgage soon.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Phone systems, I hate them, ours at work is OLD and trying to pass calls on is a pain. I also hate auto answering services, 'press 1 to do this, press 2 to do that' by the time they've all gone past you've forgotten which you had to press as none quite matched what you wanted 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Christmas is comming so the decorations have started to come out at work. Our small area decorates over a few days, so we go from a bare to an over decorated area of the office during the week.  I've put up my little tree and a bit of tinsel, the lights round the desk will come later. Others have started with small desk decorations and will progress to tinsel and finally to decorations hanging from the ceiling.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The kids liked the new house. Joshua was impressed with his room, no longer sharing with his sister. Although he seemed more impressed that there was a telly in his room, it took us a while to explain that the telly wasn't staying when the people who currently live there move out. They both loved the swings and slide just across from the house and we had to go and look, even though it seemed like 10 below with the wind blowing across the fields. It will feel very strange being able to see sheep and horses in the fields just a stones throw away.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Jish asked me to say HI! to my  urlLink webloggers webring  neighbours. &#0171;  to the left of me:   urlLink Ponderous Ponderings . &#0187;  to the right of me:   urlLink the Clearly Blurry 4.0 - Space Oddity? .  Thought I'd also say HI! to my  urlLink blogphiles webring  neighbours. &#0171;  to the left of me:   urlLink Faded Ink Dot Com . &#0187;  to the right of me:   urlLink jeanhank.com: the blog . 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Moving went OK, apart from the 2 hour wait after loading the van whilst the solicitors were on lunch. Once we got in it wasn't too bad.  Saturday was spent unloading boxes as was Sunday. Monday and Tuesday were spent painting the dining room, buying curtains and a table and chairs, and putting up pictures. The only problem so far is its either rained or been very very windy.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Gott have one of these 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Picked up the keys today so we can do some cleaning prior to moving on Friday. Now just 3 days to go
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      We have been informed by the solicitor that the contracts on the houses have been exchanged so packing is progressing at a furious rate.  We went round to the house yesterday afternoon for a rundown of stoptaps, keys, swithces and the operation of boiler and fire. The brickwork that needs doing has been estimated at £65 so it's not worth him going through his insurance, so he's instructed the builder to do the work at our convenience and bill him direct.  Alison has already started deciding on colours and saying we could paint the living room this coming monday & tuesday. I was planning on at least a month or three before starting any decorating.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      We signed the contracts for the new house this morning, so its all systems go.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've started informing the multitude of companies and services that need to know of our address change. This looks like a long and tedius job.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      After receiving a letter from the solicitor asking for an enormous amount of money we have contacted a removal firm and are now pushing ahead with the 25th as our moving date. We are signing contracts on Wednesday and then there is no going back. The builder came an said it was straight forward (as we thought). My call to the NHBC took out the option of claiming it through them so it's a good job the current occupier says his solicitor has advised him to get it done through his insurance, and she's going to push the insurance company.  This blog has in recent weeks revolved mainly around moving house, exactly like my life. The house is littered with boxes and there are bare and empty area all over the house. I seem to spend my time either packing, deciding what to pack, informing people of the move or deciding who to inform next.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Somehow I had to do it.  urlLink the blogger code . It seems I'm B5 d- t- k+ s+ u f i o+ e- l- c++
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A call from our soliciter confirms that we are looking at the 25th of Jan as our moving date. Two weeks to go, it seems like no time at all, everything seems to have gathered pace, till it's rushing along with no control. We're starting to pack up into boxes the last nine years, it somehow seems longer.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Latest news on the house. The people at the end of the chain are now pushing for a completion date as soon as possible. Apparently their mortgage offer is coming to the end of its time frame, if its not taken up soon they will have to reapply, and they need to leave their current rented accommodation this month. So as far as we are aware at the moment we are looking at a moving date around the 25th of Jan. The builder is coming on Saturday morning to have a look at the house and give us an estimate for replacing the bricks but we are being given advice from a couple of sources that this may be covered under the NHBC 10-year guarantee.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It was Autumn's 2nd birthday yesterday and it was a delight to see her face as she opened her presents especially the main one of a play kitchen. Unfortunately we can't get her away from it now.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The people we are buying the house from contacted us via the estate agent to let us know that a couple of bricks had frost damage. This gave Alison major worries, she's given me grief about it all weekend. So on Saturday we went round to have a look, about 10 bricks have had a bit of the front face flaked off and need replacing. The current houseowner says he'll knock the price a builder estimates off the price of the house so we can get it fixed when the weather is better. This still didn't calm Alison down, it wasn't till her dad had a word with a builder he knows who says it's common and not a problem that she stopped worrying.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm now back at work - for a rest. The news from the last 12 days. Christmas this year seemed to alternate between mad busy and very quiet. We had Alisons parents round for Christmas followed by us visiting them for Boxing Day, also Alison's Dad's birthday. The kids got loads of presents and we've spent the days since trying to play with them all and trying not to fall over them. We also started to potty train Autumn over the Christmas break, she's doing very well. My birthday went off quietly, work during the day (yesterday) and then a quiet evening at home. The house purchase is progressing but as you can imagine we have heard nothing over the last week as everybody has been on hols including the people we need to get on with the searchs, contracts etc.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Is a  urlLink Home Storage Network  going to be the answer to our digital life. ref from  eric norlin 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Google loves Blogs , or How Weblogs Influence A Billion Google Searches A Week.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Are personal digital recorders the  urlLink death  of TV as we know it (ps what happens when we always skip through the adverts).
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Despite its announcement that prices are dropping for broadband access  urlLink BT's own site  still shows prices from £39.99.   Although  urlLink elsewhere  on the site its announcing "openworld will launch Plug & Go on the 5th March 2002, with a free activation offer, waiving the £65.00 activation charge for orders received up to 31st May 2002, making broadband prices even lower. Plug & Go monthly rental will be £29.99 and there will be a one off equipment charge of £85.00".  On checking whether I would be able to get the new service I get the message " Your postcode may just be on the edge of your telephone exchange's range for Extended Reach broadband   Broadband (ADSL) is distance dependent, so this range will need to be checked.  Because there's a good chance you will be able to get BTopenworld broadband, you can order now online. For information on how to order by phone, click here "  Why would I order till I get assurance it will work?  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Another  urlLink comment  on blogging, and yet  urlLink another .
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink A Blogger Manifesto  Why online weblogs are one future for journalism. This is a clearly written argument for blogging by professional writers, but there is still room for us amateurs.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Trying to plan a 5-a-side competition for the local BB companies is a nightmare. We have a date, a site but getting teams to play is driving me nuts. We have 12 local companies, 3 of which havent responded at all, 2 cant make the date, 2 havent got teams. The ones that are saying will come, fall neatly into 2 teams for each age group and 1 team that I'm not sure which age group they are going to be in. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink "Never-ending" ski slope planned for Wales   
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink The Register is baffled by ICQ "hack" . Was it hacked or wasn't it? You be the judge.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
        Happy Valentines day to my wife, Alison.     Health:  Well after a week of feeling sick courtesy of the antibiotics I'm finally back to myself again. I cant recommend enough that feeling of nausea for losing weight - you just don't want to eat as you know it makes you feel worse.   Home:  One set of the curtains were too long, we asked for them to be 83" and they came back 84.5". When returned the response was 'Oh did they have to be exactly that length?'. They are for the patio doors, of course they have to be the exact length we measured. Ah well, they will be ready this coming Saturday.  The table and chairs we ordered are coming tomorrow so we can start eating sat at the table from tomorrow night rather than eating in front of the television. I'm hoping it will improve the kids manners and will help with getting Joshua to eat the varied food we eat, rather than the same food each day.  We are having my niece to stay overnight Saturday as my brother Stephen and his wife Helen are coming up from Nuneaton to go out for the evening with friends. it will be the first time we have had her stay and Alison is looking forward to looking after a baby again, even if it's only for one night.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The flu is subsiding and the antibiotics are helping with the throat infection. Hopefully another couple of days and I'll be back to  normal . It's been a strange week as at times I've been a little disconnected from reality. People talk to me and I've asked them to stop and start again as I've drifted away and haven't the foggiest what they are talking about   Work:  Even in my debilitated state the release got done at work. I'm hoping for a little praise, but I'm expecting the usual amount - none.   Home:  The curtains for the living room and dining room are being altered (shouldn't the house buliders/window manufacturers and the curtain makers get together and produce a set of standard sizes that they all use - we can get a width that's ok but they are all far too long) and should be ready tomorrow, so that should finalise the changes being made downstairs.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm suffering from flu/cold/cough or something and would rather be at home than here at work where I need to prepare the latest release. The weekend saw us decorating the lounge, so downstairs is as done as it's going to be for a while. A 'pale coral' lounge and a 'warm yellow' dining room leaves the living areas a lot brighter and warmer looking than the lilac/pink combination of the previous occupiers.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Do you care?  You should
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well another week has gone by and more decorating done. The stairs and landing is now complete, walls painted, banister varnished and banister posts glossed. I'm glad that Alison likes painting, she says she finds it theraputic, I find it boring.  We took the kids swimming yesterday. Autumn wasn't keen to start with but settles down quite quickly. Joshua like splashing in the kiddies pool, but take him to chest deep at the end of the pool and he goes off swimming big time. But by the time we're out of the water and in McDonalds you would think he had a great time and was a champion swimmer.  This week will see the front of the house having a new door and windows. This should see an end to worrying that we're going to have a wet carpet when it rains. It always seems to rain directly on the front of the house and the wind sweeping across the fields as nothing to break it up so we get the rain driven straight through the slightly misfitting door. No more, the new door should keep us nice and dry, only thing to worry about is damp patches from Autumn's potty training accidents.  Next week should finally see the arrival of the new seatees, we ordered them on 28th Jan and due to a slight case of phone tig and the fortnightly delivery to our area we are due to receive them on the 3/4 April. Can't wait, we got rid of our old seatees a couple of weeks ago and I'm fed up of sitting on the floor or on a stright chair from the dining room.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink A nice idea .
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Listening to the radio on the way in to work this morning, the debate was whether 'Banning fox hunting' was of national importance, i.e. should Parliament be discussing it yet again when there are so many other topics. Of course the topic is only of importance to the two minorities at either side of the argument, the problem being that they are very vocal minorities. Representatives from both sides tried to hijack the topic to force their views down the throats of the listeners, but thanks to the efforts of the presenter this was largely unsuccessful. The argument for the majority of the UK is not relevant, they are not going to either demonstrate for or against the issue, they just wish the politicians and the media would spend their time on more pressing issues,  issues that affect all of us .
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yesterday I was out on a customers site training them in our database design so they can use SQL to report on their data, thus saving them money by not needing us to write them reports. My day was rather longer than normal, leaving home at 6:30am and not getting in till 7pm, I know others do these hours regularly but when you usually leave at 8:15 and are home by 6pm then this is a significant increase to your day. It also meant I missed seeing the kids in the morning and we had to arrange alternative transport for getting Joshua to school.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Not posted for a while, work has been hectic. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This weekend we got the first major downpour since we had the new windows fitted - and the lounge window leaked. I've rung Safastyle and they will get a service engineer to ring within 48 hours. Windows that let water in are apparently not a major concern for them. I'll give them 24 hours to ring and then I'll get back on to them.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Poor Bill 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well we got the code out on time and are currently involved in a major testing phase on the whole product, not just those areas changed. Enough to keep the whole team busy for a while. Homewise, I fitted a carpet in the downstairs cloakroom, the first carpet I've fitted, and it turned out ok. Joshua had a big beaming smile for me this morning when I told him we'd ordered the new England Football quilt cover, curtains and rug for his room. The smile more than made up for the cost £70.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink The Blogging Revolution .
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A  urlLink ">Six-Figure Speeding Ticket . Now that was an expensive journey.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      After a day off, a day out doing customer training and a day sick I return to work to find the shit has hit the fan. We now have one week to complete all the code for the next release, and more than one weeks worth of work to do, four of the specs were only signed this lunchtime. I've been saying for months that this would happen and been regularly reassured it wouldn't, well it has. I could now do with some more time off as I've been running round all day trying to ensure that we can come as close to completion as possible. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Dion's new CD crashing party for some users . "New Day" was released in the United States on Tuesday. Industry watchers expect it to sell more than 500,000 copies by the end of its first week. Well I for one won't be buying it. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well the sofas were delivered today from  urlLink sofasofa , they look ok, and are very comfy. Unfortunately the delivery men have trailed dog shit all over the carpet and I spent quite a while cleaning the carpet after they left. I am pushing the sofa company to stump up for a professional carpet cleaning.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Just trying  urlLink Blogbuddy 0.5 . It seems to be ok, the edit posts is a feature I can see myself using as I regularly post to the wrong blog.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Joshua is now getting the hang of riding his bike. He's alright on the flat in a straight line but cornering is another matter. We are only allowed to go and practice when there is nobody about (his friends play on the swings and slide across from our house), he obviously at six doesn't want anybody to see his Dad running behind the bike attempting to keep him upright. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Saturday, we went to  urlLink Chester Zoo  with Andy, Wendy and Amber. The kids loved it, particularly the elephants and the chimpanzees. We were slightly aprehensive about Joshua before we went as the last time we took him to a zoo he was terrified of everything, he wouldn't even get close to the cages. A previous visit when he was two where he started to chase some birds on the grass and the birds decided to chase him instead had obviously affected him more than we thought.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Friday, the new windows and door were fitted in an amazingly short space of time. The fitters were polite and tidy, even polishing the glass and giving the plastic a good cleaning after they had finished. Couldn't fault them. Unfortunately I can fault  urlLink Safestyle UK  for their after sales sales push. Monday I got a call from a telesales person who just wouldnt take no for an answer, I had to put the phone down in the end. He then rang back to see if I could recomend anybody to them who wanted windows - fat chance.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Google Search Ranking Technology  urlLink explained  
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Judicial Common Sense  in the UK
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It was the funeral of a long time family friend this morning. Alan lived next door but one to me when I was growing up and his daughter was my friend from us being old enough to walk (she was 10 days older than me). They introduced me to the church I still attend 27 years later and it was that church that was full this morning with people who had fond memories of a man who said little but who was a great observer and encourager, with a dry wit. He will be remembered fondly by many as a faithful servant of God, and an East Lancashire character.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Well after the  urlLink panic  regarding when we had to finish coding the release of the software happened on time, just. The final compile and build was prepared at 8:40pm last night. We now have two version of both the major products I'm in charge of out on site, they all get monthly upgrades, one of the four wasn't tested by the testing team so the shit will hit the fan later today, somebody will need to explain why we aren't able to send the monthly update the customers are expecting.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Autumn's spots are now going. She didn't really understand what was wrong with her, she asked us a few times to get the spots off her face. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Thursday afternoon the engineer from Safestyle came round and fixed the windows, apparently the drainage holes can get blocked accidently when putting in the windows - sound like a common fault they should address. He also fixed the door which he said was far to stiff, it now opens and shuts a lot easier.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This morning, Autumn was very whiney and it wasn't till I started getting her ready that we found out why. She's got some spots. Alison who's a nursery nurse, straight away called into work saying she won't be in the rest of the week as Autumn has chicken pox.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Monday evening when I arrived home I found that another window had let water in. So I called the salesman, who happens to be the area manager. He suggested I ring the service centre the next morning and tell them I want a date for someone to fix the windows whilst I was on the phone or I was to tell them I was ringing the bank to stop payments on the finance deal. He also called the sales guy who rang 3 days after installation a knobhead.  Tuesday morning I got a call from the service centre, I think they must have already been called by the area manager because they are coming round tomorrow. They also asked whether we had had an inspection - so I think we may also get an inspector.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      just added a reference to this site on  urlLink friendsreunited  to this site and also to my family site  urlLink Bibby.org.uk , although I should have pointed out that I havent updated the family site for a while and its currently just a front sheet with a couple of links - must do some updates soon.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It only takes a couple of days off sick to make returning to work a daunting thing. It's that email inbox, 2 days off 63 items to read, digest and reply to.  On top of that is all the normal paperwork, holiday forms, tasks completed, source code to move to testing the list goes on.  After a couple of days off you soon feel the need for a break, cant wait for my next holiday.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm currently having problems with my works email system. It keeps bouncing my home email address. I'm going to have to give our technical dept a visit to get to the bottom of this.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Privacy, what Privacy? 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Alison has really got the decorating bug. Autumn's bedroom was painted over the weekend, bright pink, sot of Barbie pink on steroids. This cant go on as we've only two rooms left to do. of course the painting didn’t quite go to plan.  As I painted the ceiling Alison had to direct me to where to paint as I couldn't see the difference between painted and not painted. The previous owners of the house had the room a dark purple, which was a sod to cover, it took three coats of a paint described as 'one coat'. Well after the first coat, the room looked sort of half and half, the second left it looking pink with purple speckles and finally the third left it PINK!!!!!.  Finally moving the furniture back in, the bed just fits between two walls and of course I knocked the paint off getting the bed back into the room, I blame it on Alison who was holding one end of the bed as I manovered it through the doorway and up in the air to get it in the correct place. So I had to repaint, twice, one section of wall that had several patches of purple showing. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Drive carefully 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      DIY reared its head again. Joshua's room has now been painted and the rooms we've already done have had all the marks (of a couple of months) patched up. Apparently I've agreed to paint Autumn's bedroom this weekend (I don't remember agreeing), which will leave the shower room and our bedroom, after which I may get a rest before it all needs doing again.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The football on Sunday morning didn't live up to expectations, England should have used their early dominance to put the game out of reach for the Swedes. We've got to hope that Fridays game against the Argies will be better.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Yet another example of the  urlLink madness  of the American legal system. What does this say about Americans in general that they allow crap like this to happen? This lawsuit should be laughed out of court and the lawyer should be disbarred for trivialising the legal system.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Spent the last few days at work dealing with a customers data problems. Hopfully I've fixed it now and he's not going to have any more problems.   It's Alison's birthday again.   Happy Birthday love 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      An email from a list I subscribe to. I may not agree with all the points but some of this should make us all think about the society in which we live. We want to be tollerant of others viewpoints and religions but morality and knowing right from wrong should not be something we let go of.  Billy Graham's daughter was interviewed on the Early Show and Jane Clayson asked her "How could God let something like this happen?" ( regarding the attacks on Sept. 11 ).  Anne Graham gave an extremely profound and insightful response. She said "I believe God is deeply saddened by this, just as we are, but for years we've been telling God to get out of our schools, to get out of our government and to get out of our lives. And being the gentleman He is, I believe He has calmly backed out. How can we expect God to give us His blessing and His protection if we demand He leave us alone?"  In light of recent events...terrorists attack, school shootings, etc. I think it started when Madeleine Murray O'Hare (she was murdered, her body found recently) complained she didn't want prayer in our schools, and we said OK.  Then someone said you better not read the Bible in school ... the Bible says Thou Shalt not kill, Thou Shalt not steal, and love your neighbor as yourself. And we said OK.  Then Dr. Benjamin Spock said we shouldn't spank our children when they misbehave because their little personalities would be warped and we might damage their self-esteem (Dr. Spock's son committed suicide). We said an expert should know what he's talking about. And we said OK.  Then someone said teachers and principals better not discipline our children when they misbehave. The school administrators said no faculty member in this school better touch a student when they misbehave because we don't want any bad publicity, and we surely don't want to be sued (there's a big difference between disciplining, touching, beating, smacking, humiliating, kicking, etc.). And we said OK.  Then someone said, let's let our daughters have abortions if they want, and they won't even have to tell their parents. And we said OK.  Then some wise school board member said, since boys will be boys and they're going to do it anyway, let's give our sons all the condoms they want so they can have all the fun they desire, and we won't have to tell their parents they got them at school. And we said OK.  Then some of our top elected officials said it doesn't matter what we do in private as long as we do our jobs. Agreeing with them, we said it doesn't matter to me what anyone, including the President, does in private as long as I have a job and the economy is good.  Then someone said let's print magazines with pictures of nude women and call it wholesome, down-to-earth appreciation for the beauty of the female body. And we said OK.  And then someone else took that appreciation a step further and published pictures of nude children and then further again by making them available on the Internet. And we said OK, they're entitled to free speech.  Then the entertainment industry said, let's make TV shows and movies that promote profanity, violence, and illicit sex. Let's record music that encourages rape, drugs, murder, suicide, and satanic themes. And we said it's just entertainment, it has no adverse effect, nobody takes it seriously anyway, so go right ahead.  Now we're asking ourselves why our children have no conscience, why they don't know right from wrong, and why it doesn't bother them to kill strangers, their classmates, and themselves. Probably, if we think about it long and hard enough, we can figure it out. I think it has a great deal to do with "WE REAP WHAT WE SOW."  Funny how simple it is for people to trash God and then wonder why the world's going to hell. Funny how we believe what the newspapers say, but question what the Bible says.  Funny how you can send 'jokes' through e-mail and they spread like wildfire, but when you start sending messages regarding the Lord, people think twice about sharing.  Funny how lewd, crude, vulgar and obscene articles pass freely through cyberspace, but public discussion of God is suppressed in the school workplace and sometimes the home.  Are you laughing?  Funny how when you forward this message, you will not send it to many on your address list because you're not sure what they believe, or what they WILL think of you for sending it. Funny how we can be more worried about what other people think of us than what God thinks of us.  Pass it on if you think it has merit. If not then just discard it ... no one will know you did. But, if you discard this thought process, don't sit back and complain about what bad shape the world is in!
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Back to the docs this morning, he tells me that the infection is reducing but not quite gone, I'm on more antibiotics for a while but an op to remove the cyst is looking more likely
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sunday, took the kids to a (almost) local park along with friends. We then followed up with a few hours in the back garden relaxing. We were going to go out for a meal but after a quick discussion it was down to the chippy for everyone.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Spent Saturday painting fences again, they have all got two coats now. We also picked up some more plants from the garden centre, which I have artfully planted to give a colourful display rather than the bare ground (except for our little tree, which is now doing well) the front garden had become.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I had to take Alison back to the doctors this morning, her back is no better and the tablets were doing nothing. The doctor told her it could be 2-6 weeks before she's better. Whilst I was there I had the doc take a look at the bottom of my spine, I have what appears to be a slight lump there, which has become sore over the last week. The doc tells me I have a cyst that’s infected, so I'm back on the antibiotics and if they don't do the job then he'll be booking me into hospital to have it removed.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sunday, back ache from the gardening yesterday, I think some of it was psychosomatic as I knew I still had an afternoon of gardening to do.  Saturday night was party night. Well a family party. My Aunt and Uncle were both 60 in the past fortnight. So a family gathering was held, a meal and a bit of music for the kids to dance or run around to whilst the rest of us imbibed a few glasses of falling down water.  I spent most of Saturday afternoon in the garden. A little bit of weeding and trimming, and a lot of fence painting. I've discovered a quicker way of painting the fence, rather than using a brush, my neighbour advised me that it was easier using a sponge. It was easier and quicker, but I'm still not quick at painting.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Alison is currently off work; she's had a reoccurrence of her slipped disc. So she's spending time at home and taking the tablets - I've got plenty of sympathy as I can see (and have experience of) the pain.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      This week is Camp week for the local Boys' Brigade companies. 1st & 2nd Accrington and 1st Rishton companies packed their bags and on Saturday morning set off for Robin Hoods Bay nr Scarborough. I set off a couple of hours earlier with Joshua and took all the tents, equipment, food, and most of the lads’ personal bags in a van and set off on the trip. The van struggled to reach 50mph and with any uphill gradient a quick drop through the gears was necessary to ensure we continued to go forwards. As we left Lancashire for Yorkshire the skies threatened to open but for a while it was only a threat. A small amount of rain followed by the mists descending as we went over the moors past RAF Fylingdales meant that were unable to see the early warning station. This despite the fact that it's a great big building two to three hundred yards from the road that under normal conditions can be seen for miles. Descending from the hills we passed through Ruswarp where the river was close to flooding. As we crossed on the bridge the river raced by under us rather than at its leisurely pace. Back up the hills for the final descent to Fylingthorpe and the weather looked to be clearing. A couple of hours later as we were putting up tents on an already soggy field, the rain stopped threatening and treated us to a bit of a wetting. The constant milling of lads round the tents churned the soggy ground to give us mud patches that almost rivalled Glastonbury, so a trench was dug to divert the water on the field creating a little stream that flowed at the rear of the site for a number of hours after the rain stopped.  Sunday morning, the farmer was roused to pull the minibus off the field with his tractor, this was after a couple of attempts to spray mud over everyone - sorry to drive off the field. Shortly after, Joshua and I got back into the van for our trip home. The trip home at just under 4 hours was a lot better that the just over 5 hours it took to get there.  The camp will hopefully go alright and I'm going back with the van on Friday evening so that Saturday morning we can pack everything up for the journey home when everybody can start telling stories about how bad the week was and whether it compared to 'that year at Cricieth' or to 'the year Angelsy flooded'.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Penis amputated 'by accident' . Some accident
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Obituary of Mr. Common Sense Today we mourn the passing of an old friend Common Sense. Common Sense lived a long life but died recently in the United States. No one really knows how old he was, since his birth records were long ago lost in bureaucratic red tape. He selflessly devoted his life to service in schools, hospitals, homes, and factories helping folks get jobs done without fanfare and foolishness. For decades, petty rules, silly laws, and frivolous lawsuits held no power over Common Sense. He was credited with cultivating such valued lessons as to know when to come in out of the rain, why the early bird gets the worm, and that life isn't always fair.  Common Sense lived by simple, sound financial policies (don't spend more than you earn), reliable parenting strategies (the adults are in charge, not the kids), and it's okay to come in second. A veteran of the Industrial Revolution, the Great Depression, and the Technological Revolution, Common Sense survived cultural and educational trends including body piercing, whole language, and "new math." But his health declined when he became infected with the "If-it-only-helps-one-person-it's-worth-it" virus. In recent decades his waning strength proved no match for the ravages of well intentioned but overbearing regulations. He watched in pain as good people became ruled by self-seeking lawyers. His health rapidly deteriorated when schools endlessly implemented zero tolerance policies. Reports of a six-year-old boy charged with sexual harassment for kissing a classmate, a teen suspended for taking a swig of mouthwash after lunch, and a teacher fired for reprimanding an unruly student only worsened his condition. It declined even further when schools had to get parental consent to administer aspirin to a student but could not inform the parent when a female student was pregnant or wanted an abortion. Finally, Common Sense lost his will to live as the Ten Commandments became contraband, churches became businesses, criminals received better treatment than victims, and federal judges stuck their noses in everything from the Boy Scouts to professional sports. Finally, when people, too stupid to realize that a steaming cup of coffee was hot, were awarded a huge settlement, Common Sense threw in the towel. As the end neared, Common Sense drifted in and out of logic but was kept informed of developments regarding questionable regulations such as those for low flow toilets, rocking chairs, and stepladders. Common Sense was preceded in death by his parents, Truth and Trust; his wife, Discretion; his daughter, Responsibility; and his son, Reason. He is survived by two stepbrothers: My Rights, and Ima Whiner. Not many attended his funeral because so few realized he was gone. "Illigitimi Non Carborundum" 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My quote and recenlty read books are not being updated at the moment as blogger seems to have lost the template
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Last night I took my son to another BB company - 1st Oswaldtwistle, after we shut the company at our church last week - 2nd Accrington. He was quite nervous at the start as his Grandma wasn't going to be there (she ran the juniors and anchor boys at our church's company). But when I picked him up, he had enjoyed the evening and was looking forward to next week. I was offered the chance of joining the company as an officer (my second offer plus 1 hint) but I'm still going to give myself some time to think about whether I want to get involved with another company.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Last week we had to close the Boys' Brigade company I ran due to a lack of boys wanting to attend. Recruitment drives didn't have any response. We can only assume either that the boys in the area or their parents do not want to be involved with achristian, uniformed organisation. The company has run for 24 years and I have been involved for all of them from a boy through to being an officer to being the Captain in charge of it.  The meeting to close the company was quite sad, and even though we knew that we as officers were not at fault there still was a feeling of guilt and failure.  For myself this was lifted a little when talking to a couple of the boys last night, I was trying to encourage them to continue in the Brigade with another company and was about to let them know the details about other comapnies (when, where, how many boys etc) when I was told that they both really wanted to continue with the Brigade. For myself I am left with coming to terms with the closure of something that has been part of my life for 24 years and have now to make some decisions whether I want to get involved with another Brigade company or whether I am going to find something else to occupy my time. I have had some great times with the BB and hope anyone who's thinking of joining or thinking of sending their sons to the BB do so, I'm sure they will get as much out of it as I have.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink In Greece, use a Game Boy, go to jail 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Whether  urlLink copy protection on CDs is 'worthless'   or not, I won't buy copy protected CD's and I would urge you not to either
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Comments I have none
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I seem to have resurected my book postings, as you may notice it's a bit behind
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I haven't blogged for a while for no real reason
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It's about time, an Americal  urlLink legal judgement  that makes sense
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I've been a bit busy recently, work has gone from a 37.5 hour week to 53 hour week, which for some poeple is not much but an increase of 41% and the loss of 1 day of the weekend makes it significant to me. We're now in the final week (supposedly) of development to be followed by a beta testing phase when we get to fix all the bugs reported in the alpha tests. (these started a month ago, and should really start after development finishes).  Having to work Saturdays has meant that a number of things are not getting done, visits to the library, haircuts, etc and the weekend of 8/9 March will find me trying to catch up on 7 missed free Saturdays. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Why Did Google Want Blogger?  the conspiricy continues. with the BBC   urlLink commenting 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       urlLink Now it's official: most Americans are idiots 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Got a new pc at home this week. The speed makes the old machine seem like it was from the dark ages. Work is still at the busy pace it's been all year so far, but the weekends working is due to stop after next weekend. The customer is due to go live with the software on the 15th.
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      After a hiatus of a year I finally returned to blogger to  find it changed. I've republished my site with a standard template and will  probably give a few of them a go over the next few weeks/months. I'm also using  the email-to-blog option to see if that gives me some extra  usability. Not  a lot has changed over the year, still doing the same job etc. etc.  I  found little time over the last year for non essentials so blogging was one of  the first to go, although it didn't save me much time writing, it probably saved  me hours each week trolling through sites that had little or no new information,  and little entertainment. Whether I'll publish daily, weekly or monthly from now  will depend on what I see in my new net regime, one where I look at only a few  sites regularly but view a few other sites for specific articles or just because  someone recommends something that site is saying. 
     

        
</post>

<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      With the recent aquisutions by  urlLink Google  and  urlLink Microsoft , I've given both  urlLink Picasa  and  urlLink Lookout  a go.    Lookout  (searching tool for Microsoft Outlook), this is amazingly fast and very useable. The ability to search over multiple pst files and also into documents on your hard drive make this a must have for outlook users.   Picasa  (digital image archive) unfortunately this whilst doing an ok job is lacking in some areas, it doesn't pick up the information you have added to the files properties, and only lets you add keywords to its info on a picture.  I'll continue to use both but unless Picasa makes some improvements I'll be looking for something else longterm. 
     

        
</post>


</Blog>