<Blog>



<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well my first day probably won't start officially till tomorrow seems i think i have well and truly blown it this weekend :) but i did have a chicken salad for lunch if that counts.   Exercise wise, i am mainly going to use the gym downstairs i've been using it off and on and there is a pool as well but i'm not really comfortable swimming just yet and there is the small problem that i need new swimmers so maybe once thats resolved i'll start swimming as well. I've also started a food plan, and might start an exercise plan as well, as maybe i will stick to it more if i set it out and i think as long as i exercise more and eat less i should be doing ok.  Seems i don't really want to list my weight for the whole world to see just at the moment :) i'll just say my goal weight for the moment is 70 kilos (165.5 pounds) and i'll reasess from there, but i remember i was that when i was in Israel and i was pretty happy with how i looked so...Good Luck to me and Leslie and Aleta and anyone else that joins! 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today I begin....well sorta....I am sitting here getting ready to actually plan a menu for this next week. I want to buy the book, Eat Right 4 Your Blood Type, but at the new store its pretty expensive. I did find the website though, and it looks like there are some support forums, so that will be nice. I also need to come up with some sort of exercise program. I love swimming, but there's a little issue of finding a pool that I can use. I like walking, so I may decide to walk during my lunch break at work...which means I have to plan and make sure I have a lunch with me each day instead of running to Walmart to get something at the last moment. 
     

    
</post>

<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A while ago when i started talking about going on a diet for the wedding, Andrew said as my reward if i could lose 10kilos by June 3rd he would give me a day at a spa: facials, massages the works :) so that is what my reward is to myself and also one of my earlier goals... I have lots of goals i guess but some seem to intermingle with the others: Goal 1 would be to try and lose a kilo a week which seems to be what most people recommend Goal 2 is to get down 10 kilos so i can have my reward :) Goal 3 is to be 70 kilos, and with that my main goal of all is to not be a fat bride! I have just over a year to reach that goal so i should be ok as long as i have the restraint from food and the motivation to exercise.  So next sunday i'll be able to blog if i lost weight or put on weight or stayed the same!  This week was a bit up and down i exercised which was good but food wasn't consistant, have to stop getting these secret shopper jobs that involve pizza *G*  I have started craving soups lately though for some odd reason so bought some of them and i'm starting the total wellbeing diet next week so we'll just see how it goes.  Hope everyone has a good "healthy" week :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I recently started a diet and excercise plan (about a month ago).  However, it's turned into excerciseless diet.  It was easier for me to stick to a healthier eating plan because I gave up my detrimentally cherished vices with serious committment to encourage my mother in her efforts to quit smoking.  Soo-o-oo-o, I enjoyed some initial weight loss. But, when the excercising came to a complete halt and I wasn't as strict with my eating..my weight loss also came to a screeching halt.  In fact, I even put back on three of the lost pounds.  Of course, its encouraging to know this weight loss plan works for me, but it is also frustrating to know my body is so resistant to weight loss that I could gain when I'm still eating better than before.  In order for me get past this obstacle, I think I will have to do more than put down my stress elixer, Dr. Pepper(a super sweet soda).   I need to again eat smarter and EXERCISE REGULARY.  Here we go!  Thanks everyone for an accountability outlet.
     

    
</post>

<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have to 'fess up -- now -- that I won't actually start this until the beginning of April.  I absolutely HAVE to get my neck / shoulder / arm thing fixed before I can even begin to think about regular exercise or planning or anything.  Devoting three nights to PT plus one night and maybe one weekend morning to massage therapy, plus work, just leaves no pain-free space.  And I am not going to wander Europe saying "Gee, maybe I shouldn't eat that pastry!"  However, I am SO glad that Grey decided to start this and that we can keep it going.  I have, upon reflection, realized that I need to set action goals, not result goals.  That is, my goal can't be "lose X pounds" or "lose X inches" or "wear size X."  It has to more like "Go to gym X times" or "Cook healthy meals X times" or "Bring in lunch X times."  But I like the idea of rewards for goals.  The problem is that I pretty much buy myself what I want, when I want it.  Which isn't good fiscal discipline, come to think of it.  So I'm going to be thinking about actions, action goals, and rewards.  I'll get back to you! 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so   some  of us have talked about our goals...but what about our rewards? What is your reward for yourself? Is it a trip? An afternoon off?  After much thought (ok not really), it finally dawned on me what a great reward would be. a).Clothes wouldn't be that great of a reward because they can get to be expensive and I already have a ton to pilfer through. Besides, by the time I meet my goal I will _have_ to buy new clothes anyway. b).food just seems to be on the wrong scale of things. c). can't really do a day trip in the car I have d). So I am sitting down reading Saratoga when it dawns on me: I am still missing 6 lower number Trixies (meaning  not  books 35-39. And it dawned on me! That will be my reward! :)   And since I am a believer in rewarding one's self every 10 pounds or so, its perfect! For each 10 pounds (about every 6 weeks, if I do this safely)....I can attempt to find one of the one's I am missing!  Sounds like a plan to me.  So what's your plan?
     

    
</post>

<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I woke up sick this morning, to the point of not being able to go to work...so I did great in the food department! LOL....ate about one meal's worth of food today....no exercise though...so that's bad.  Oh, and as for goals...I want to lose about 50-55 pounds. And be more healthy too :)  As a side note: I am so glad that I found the Eat Right 4 Your Blood Type webpage...I had read another book (not the ER4YBT) and in it, it said I should stay away from wheat based products (avoid)...the "real" book, just says its a Nuetral....which better than an Avoid...that makes it alot easier on me in creating a menu...hmm...wonder about chocolate :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I wanted to add two of the "diets" that I've considered.  The first is based on the book  urlLink Volumetrics .  I own the  urlLink original , but that one looks good too.  It has some very good ideas and good recipes and it was rated as very healthy by Self magazine (one of my favorites).  You can read more about it  urlLink here .  The other diet / lifestyle plan is the one my brother Daniel, a physical therapist and certified athletic trainer, gave to me.  I used it to lose about 40 pounds twelve years ago and as a result was very healthy and fit.  It's pretty easy to follow. 1) Eat no more than 30 grams of fat per day (you may need to up this to 35 or 40, depending). 2) Drink lots of water, or other sodium-free and sugar/sweetener-free and caffeine-free beverage.  I used lemon-lime seltzer. 3) Get enough rest - and rest is NOT sitting on your butt watching TV, or reading, or talking on the phone. It is RESTING your body and mind. 4) Try to avoid caffeine.  If you can't avoid it, consume it on a regular schedule (i.e. one cup of coffee in the am, every am, but no other time). 5) MOVE!  A regular exercise plan is good.  Anything is better than nothing. 6) STRETCH at every opportunity.  Flex your feet and legs while you watch TV.  Do lunges when you pick stuff off the floor. 7) Don't go hungry.  Eat often and eat to a comfortable level of fullness.  (NOTE: If you follow #1 and #7, you'll definitely lose weight.  Your body won't think you're starving it, and you'll have to eat fruits / vegetables / grains because you're limiting fat but not food).  I think I'll be trying a combination of these plans.  Also, here are some links Leslie might want to add to the sideboard:  urlLink FitDay  - The Online Diet and Fitness Journal.  This one is REALLY good - you can enter what you eat and do and get customized reports.  You can also make it public, if you want, to link to.  urlLink The Self Magazine Challenge   urlLink The Shape Magazine Recipe Finder   urlLink The Shape Magazine Find a Workout    
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm still running around trying to get ready for my trip (see my blog for the gory details), but I figured Aleta and Misty had a good idea with the stating goals bit, so here are mine:  I'm hovering around 16/18/20 depending on the item, and weigh between 215 and 220. Since I stopped growing taller, the smallest I've ever been is size 10/150 pounds, and that was when I was running high school track. I'd like to get back down to that weight, which means I've got about 70 pounds to go. More importantly, I'd like to get back into consistently running. I'm doing pretty well with walking three to four days a week, even amid the current work chaos. I'm hoping to start running parts of those daily walks in a couple of weeks (once work's March madness settles down) and would like to be able to run two loops through the park (2.6 miles) by April 19 (Patriot's Day). That's a weird Massachusetts holiday (commemerating the battles of Lexington and Concord) and Marathon Monday. I would like to run Boston some day, but this year I'll settle for a tenth of a marathon. :) I also want to incorporate some yoga into my daily routine to help build flexibility and keep me more centered during the crazy weeks at work.   I've made a few changes since January to get to these goals: * Walking in the park. 2.6 miles three to four days a week, so far. * Bringing dinner from home. Instead of running down to the Mexican place around the corner, I've been bringing soup most nights.  * Switching (most) snack food for vegetables. I'm still slipping up on this, especially since the Girl Scouts are everywhere with their cookies, but I'm much more likely to grave a plum or some carrots than cookies or crackers now.  * Using whole-grain bread instead of white.   In the next month, I want to: * Add fish 2-3 times a week * Add running into my daily walks and go out 4-5 times a week * Incorporate yoga into my evening routine * Limit munchies to fruits and vegetables 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      You know, maybe I should "officially" start next week.  I spent most of yesterday in extreme neck/shoulder/arm pain, which resulted in yogurt for lunch and peanut butter toast for dinner.  See, sore neck = nausea = eat only those things which can, er, be easily returned.  TMI, I know.  But reading about your efforts is helping, and I know we're all in this for the long term.  This isn't a one-week or two-week deal.  So, rather than blog about what I'm NOT doing, I'm going to put my goals out in front, like Misty did:  Weight / Clothing Size:  I am currently a 16 / 18, depending on the cut, and weigh around 185 lbs.  I want to return my healthiest ever, which was size 6 / 121 lbs.  But, I will happy if I can get to a size 10 and 135 lbs. I am 5'6" and medium-boned.  Physical strength: I want to be able to climb more than one flight of stairs without huffing / puffing / yawning for air and having my heart thudding.  I want to be able to do more than 5 sit-ups / crunches without feeling nauseous.  I want to be able to carry heavy things.  I want to be able to run and to stay on an elliptical machine for more than 10 minutes.    General well-being: I want to "fix" the issues with my neck, and my knee, and the toes I cut last year.  This may require some surgical intervention, but in the meantime I want to strengthen the related muscles to help myself.  Lifestyle: I want to eat regular, healthy meals.  Cook more, or get better take-out.  Go to bed and get up at reasonable times.  Not use sleep to "self-medicate".  Focus on hobbies and interests.  Get outside more.  Find balance and reduce stress.  Whew.  NOW I'm tired.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is a fabulous idea, Leslie!!  Ralph and I were just talking about how I am an externally motived person while he's more internally motivated.  Hopefully this will help me keep doing what I need to be doing and I'll be able to help others just as much.  I have a few things coming up that are helping to motivate me.  First, my ten year class reunion is in July and I have a goal of losing 45 pounds by then.  Second, Ralph and I are going to the USVI in December and I really want to not embarrass myself on the beach, so I'm trying to lose 90 pounds (my ultimate goal) by early December.  :)  Last, we've talked about it some lately and we've decided we want to start getting serious about having kids, going as far as fertility treatments if we need to.  However, I've always been told that if you are able to get your weight to a more healthy range, your ability to conceive is increased, so I'd like to try that method first.     Food Today:   Today I had for lunch pot roast, brocolli/rice casserole and baby carrots, along with two wheat rolls and unsweetened tea.  For dinner, we had chicken salad on crackers and spinich salad with walnuts, dried cranberries and maple/vinegar/oil dressing and apple juice.  So far, so good.   Exercise Today:   Uh, I didn't exercise today.  *Hangs head in shame*  With working on the Jixaversary this past weekend, I didn't have time to study for my midterm tomorrow, so I ditched the gym in favor of studying.  I'm going to try to get up and go in the morning before work, but I'm NOT a morning person and that just doesn't usually work out very well.    More tomorrow!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well to clarify...I haven't actually started the diet...just investigating what I need to do to get started...haven't been able to go grocery shopping yet....looking forward to it...especially since I found out oatmeal is ok after all :)  And a big thank you to Irish, Misty, and Angie for joining!!! I can't wait to see all of ours progress!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Exercise Wise:  Well i went and worked out this morning, did half an hour on the treadmill on one of the programs it has so up hill then down hill, whilst watching Ricki Lake :) felt good once i was done, its just very, very hard to get the motivation to actually get off my butt and go down there. But am aiming at a minimum of 3 times a week and the plan i have set for myself to start with is 10 minute bike warm up, 30minutes walking program and then 2 sets of 15 repeats on the weights they have. I'm hoping that will be enough to kick start the fat removal. :)  Food Wise:  So far today i've only eaten a bowl of porridge (rolled oats) and a pork salad sandwich, so doing good foodwise, i did some searching this morning and found this menu/diet that i am going to try and do and keep to. Its the  urlLink Total Wellbeing Diet  it looks pretty good, gives food plans which is something i need and the food mostly sounds pretty yummy so i'll let you know how it goes :) Will start that next Monday! I weighed myself today properly *G* not good at all lol...but at least now i know if i lose any. Anyways thats all from me.
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is a really great idea! Since my work week runs Monday to Sunday, Mondays are the first day in my week. :) Today's not been all that great. Between running around trying to get everything done before I head to a conference Wednesday and trying to use up leftovers that would otherwise spoil while I'm gone, I've been doing not so hot on exercise and eating.  But I packed oatmeal to eat for breakfast while I'm gone rather than the cholesterol specials I'd otherwise eat on the road. I also held myself to one cookie after lunch, even though Samoas are my favorite and I had a whole box sitting there.  I'll be somewhat at the mercy of the road most of this week, but I'm bringing my sneakers and such and plan to walk mornings before the panels start. The hotel's even connected to the rest of downtown by covered walkways, so rain shouldn't deter me. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Aleta and Sarah! :) I think we are all off to a pretty good start!  We can do it! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think I'll make my first day yesterday - because my calendar starts weeks then.  Not a great start - Breakfast was mini-wheats and skim milk, chai tea with skim milk.  Lunch was a delightful fried-fish platter at Long John Silver's!  Dinner was at the Chinese buffet - but I had sushi, oysters, crab legs (no butter), and a small helping of mongolian bbq (mostly veggies).  Then a slice of birthday cake - but a small one.  Not so good on exercise - I managed to trip on Saturday and bump my foot in such a way that I really messed up my left knee.  At least, when walking up stairs, I can't seem to haul my weight on my left leg.  So I had to go right-left; right-left; right-left.  On the other hand, the massage therapist is helping and I have hopes of healing my arm / neck /shoulder issues.  And, of course, I leave in 2.5 weeks for Germany and the Czech Republic, where I will do LOTS of walking.  So, I hope today is better. 
     

    
</post>

<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Aleta...thank you for the Calorie King site! I love it! Its just like what ediets  used  to be like! It even does meal plans :) Thanks for sharing! 
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      There are now comments on this blog. I know I had told at least two of you that I wasn't going to add comments....one, because I get tired of how much enotation is always messed up, but also because I didn't want outside people adding "bad comments" However I was looking at a blog today and saw that they used a different program than enotation and supposedly this one will let me do ISP banning if necessary....so we shall see :)
     

    
</post>

<date>17,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Calorie King  lets you look up the calorie count for lots of different foods, if calorie counting is your thing.  It has lots on fast food, too.  It never rains but it pours.  This morning I threw my back out -- picking up the newspaper, no less -- so I have yet another "reason" why I cannot (1) exercise and (2) shop for healthy foods.
     

    
</post>

<date>16,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well i checked the scales this morning when i was spose to wait till Sunday but i've lost a kilo already since starting the diet Monday...not that that means much *G* it will be up and down for a while yet but i always get excited when i see the figure going down not up!!! The food is actually pretty good with the meal plans although some of the amounts seem a little in excess...i'll figure it out though.  I think the meal menu idea is a great idea,  should make it a lot easier for you and you know that there is something to go home to thats yumm and not take away!  And i'll just chime in my agreeance with everyone else Misty, last year i was going to the gym and working out doing weights etc and i was hardly loosing anything but i was getting more toned, i even had muscles *g* although its pretty dissapointing the scales won't go down you'll see the results in clothes definately. I'm really impressed with your exercise plan, wish i had the motivation to do something more like that :)   Oh and that soup sounds yumm Aleta i'm going to make me some of that next week.  Ok well I'm off to have lunch: chicken salad and ryvita for lunch day 3 and a diet coke cos its on the "free" item list :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      1) The shit ALWAYS hits the fan at work between 11:30 am and 1:30 pm.  This means that my ability to get lunch (from the cafeteria in the basement or outside at a restaurant) is often limited and never predictable.  2) If I don't bring food with me, I end up...oh, say, eating Coney Island potato chips at my desk at 2:00 pm.  Since I'll be starting changes when I get back, I think a good thing for me do during the next week is to make menus, like Jennie talked about. What can I cook on the weekend and pack that I won't get tired of during the week?  Plan for lunch AND dinner.  Plan healthy.  For a long time, I used to bring a "vat o' gazpacho" to work every Monday.  Then, each day, I'd also bring in yogurt or string cheese (for dairy & protein) and pre-sectioned oranges or pre-washed grapes (for fruit and fiber).  The gazpacho was spicy and filling, too.  Here's the (tweakable) recipe, for anyone who might like it.  Since I used to share it with my then-office mate, who had cilantro issues, I left that out.   Soup base  1½  bunches green onions, chopped, tops included ½ seedless cucumber, chopped ¼ green pepper, chopped 1 can (12.5 oz) diced tomatoes  Combine in blender; puree.  Empty into glass bowl    Mix into base  1½  bunches green onions, chopped, tops included ½ seedless cucumber, chopped ¼ green pepper, chopped 1½ cups frozen corn, thawed 1 can canneloni beans, drained    Stir into combination  1 cup tomato or V8 juice ¼ cup olive oil Minced garlic to taste Salt/pepper/other spices to taste  Refrigerate until chilled.  May garnish with additional green onion tops. 
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Did pretty well on the exercise thing yesterday, but not so good on the eating.     Food:   Had a cup of lowfat yogurt for breakfast (1.5 grams of fat) with a bottle of water.  For lunch, had a chopped sirloin steak with a sweet potato (there's that meat craving!) and then chicken salad on low sodium Ritz crackers for dinner.  Had a midafternoon "snack" of a Dr. Pepper.   Exercise:   Bicycled for 30 minutes because all the treadmills and eliptical machines were in use.  Worked legs for an hour after that.  (Calves, hamstrings, quads, hips, thighs and butt)  Weekly Exercise Plan: Tuesday: burn ourselves out on cardio - probably eliptical machines for an hour and then do crunches (because I forgot last night!)   Wednesday:  I play with the big boys in the weight room.  (I work out with Ralph and his friend doing everything for the arms/back/shoulders/chest you can think of!) Thursday:  Light cardio and legs again Friday:  Heavy cardio and abs
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Found  urlLink this article  this morning and thought it might be of interest to some.  It's about healthy "briefcase breakfasts" - foods that are easy and healthy that you can take with you in the morning for breakfast.  
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Misty, I'm going to echo what Aleta said. Muscle does weigh way more than fat. When I was running track and throwing the shotput, people always underestimated my weight because so much of it was muscle. Plus, muscle burns more calories at rest than fat does, so the more you have, the better off you are, weight-loss-wise. I walked 2.6 miles today (two loops around the park) and kept up a pretty brisk pace. I'm planning to start running either Sunday or Monday, so my big goal this week is to get out every day but Wednesday and walk.  I did better eating today, though I've figured that instead of breakfast lunch and dinner, I eat before work (usually abour 11), at work (usually about 7) and after work (lately, about midnight). Usually all I do after work is eat dinner, then read for a while and go to bed. I think I'm going to try cutting that meal down to some steamed or raw veggies and tea or water and see how that works.  Oh, and I have another tip that I've found works really well. On Sundays (most weeks), I try and plan out my at-work meals for the week. Sometimes I'll make a big pot of soup and put it in tupperware containers, or grill chicken. Monday and Tuesday's meals go in the fridge, the rest go in the freezer, and I don't even have to think in the morning. It helps me stay away from the restaurants and sandwich places downtown on my dinner break, plus I can keep the amounts fairly small. This was a great idea, guys. I'm a lot less likely to skip a workout or scarf down cookies when I know I'm "reporting" to somebody. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks, Aleta.  I tried very hard to not be disappointed tonight when I went to the gym and had gained half a pound!  LOL!  Ralph says it's not a big deal, that he can tell I've lost fat, so to quit stressing out about it.  So that's what I'm going to do.  And if you could see the marks on my shoulders from the squat machine and the calve press, you'd probably rethink your desire to have a Marine helping you train.  They're so ugly!  (uh, the marks are ugly.  Not the Marines.  The Marines are adorable!  Like puppies!)  LOL!  Leslie, do you go to a gym and workout or do you do it at home?    If you go to a gym, you might consider packing your clothes and shoes and things you'll need in the car with you, then you won't have any need to go home first.  If I have to try and make it to the gym on my own (without Ralph), that's why I do.  I just have a bag that's packed with things I use and need like TUMS, ponytail holders, hair clips, a book, a couple CDs and a walkman.  I just leave it in the trunk of my car and use a small canvas bag for clothes that can be replenished each evening.  It takes some of the temptation out of just going home and vegging for the rest of the evening.  (I'm with you.  I'm just NOT a morning person.  I've tried it a few times and it makes me so miserable by about 2 in the afternoon that I don't usually bother trying the mornings.)  If you stay home, maybe if you have everything set up before you leave the house in the morning, it'll be easier to get it done when you get home.  Like have your clothes laying out and your exercise tape or apparatus that you use already in front of the TV or in the VCR ready for you as soon as you walk into the door.  I go so far as to even have a bottle of water in the refrigerator waiting for me.  I know that the less I have to do to prepare, the more likely I am to follow through with my plans.    Jennie, good on you for taking advantage of some of your opportunities!  I think it's more difficult to do when you're away from your home, your schedule and the things you're comfortable with.  Keep up the good work!!  Even if you just improve a little at a time, it'll make a big difference in the end!  Sarah,  your reward sounds fabulous!  *g*  I tried to get Ralph to help me think of rewards for 10 lbs, 20 lbs, etc and he just gave me a blank look.  "You'll be 10 lbs lighter.  Isn't that enough reward?"  *sigh*  Men.  Sounds like you have a good support system and a good start, though!  I know you'll do fabulous!!  Angie,  you know, I gave up the chance to have a huge slice of cake in exchange for a Dr. Pepper earlier today.  I LOVE the stuff.  I know it's bad for you, but I just can't help it sometimes!  Maybe you can implement that into your motivation?  Once you accumulate 3 hours of cardio exercise you can have a can of Dr. Pepper?  Or something similar?  I'm sure you'll think of something fabulous and congrats on the weight you lost initially!  Try not to be frustrated with the three pounds.  You did it once, I'm sure you'll be able to do it again!!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, so I didn't do so hot this week...but I did excercise once! :) Awhile back I had gotten ahold of the New York Ballet's Workout Video Part 2.....Its kinda fun cause it incorporates ballet into a regular type work out...something that I like because I always wanted to learn ballet. Foodwise...I haven't eaten as much this past week in but I probably ate as much calories, if that makes sense.... in other words I didn't eat as much snacks but I probably ate more at meal times....not sure which is better.... oh well....I am taking the slow and easy method cause I know me...if I try to change overnight it won't happen. Right now my main concern is finding a time to work out....I am starting to think that right when I get home from work will be the best time (I can't seem to get myself up in the mornings, no matter what time I went to bed the night before).  Glad to see you blogging away....I know its tough, but we can all do it!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Misty, definitely go by clothes and not the scale.  For one thing, muscle weighs more than fat.  You could lose 5 lbs of fat, gain 10 lbs of muscle, and wear a smaller size of clothing.  Check body measurements and use that as a guide.  Second, red meat is not necessarily a BAD thing to be craving while you are doing weightlifting!  You could try eating other protein sources, or indulge in lower-fat red meat cuts in small amounts.  From my own experience, denying a craving makes you eat much more than you would if you let yourself have a little bit.  Can I borrow Ralph?  I could use an ex-Marine to kick my butt!
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, here's my first problems.  Maybe someone has some suggestions.  I'm not only doing cardio, but weightlifting with a former Marine.  (yeah, that's REAL fun.  uh huh.  *snicker*)  So, I'm getting some nice muscle tone underneath the layers of fat, but it makes me CRAVE really bad food.  Things that are high in fat, particularly red meat.  Seriously.  So, I'm doing well with the workouts and have that pleasant soreness you get when your muscles are tearing and rebuilding, but I'm eating like a horse!!   I've not lost any weight, but my clothes are a little looser, and my rings are starting to spin on my fingers again, so I'm going to not let myself get discouraged by the stupid numbers on the scale.  Still trying to work out a reward system for myself, too.
     

    
</post>

<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, my conference is over and I'm back in the real world again.  The weekend was kind of so-so for me. (In terms of this. The panels etc. were terrific.) One morning I had oatmeal for breakfast, and another I had an overpriced pumpernickel bagel and apple. I also had oatmeal one night for dinner. But the other two were cholesterol specials. *sigh*  Friday I had very little lunch, mostly because they ran out of plates by the time the second wave of us arrived. I was limited to a small (dinner roll) ham sandwich and turkey sandwich, plus a can of Sprite. No chips or potato salad (which I don't eat anyway).  Saturday I went to an Italian place and got chicken Marsala (yes, I know, it was Lent, but I'd already forgotten twice that day). There were two chicken breats on the plate, and I only had one.  I got out Thursday morning and walked, but didn't have time the other days. They had a gym in the hotel, which I didn't know when I packed. I wish I had brought workout clothes - then I could have gone down there at night when I had time.  Basically, I did a few good things, but missed a lot of opportunities to eat better and excercise while I was gone. Now I'm off to the park to do today's walking.
     

    
</post>

<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I haven't forgotten that I signed up for this. Let's just say my attention was diverted this week and I have some catch-up to do.  I promise to join in very soon~!
     

    
</post>

<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I haven't really done all that well this week....though I have been taking vitamins and I have drank more water than I usually do (but not the 20 oz that I was hoping for). I haven't excercised at all this week, but I have a *very* good excuse. Last Saturday I woke up with what I thought was allergies (allergy season is well upon us). Well I got worse as the day went on, and I finally thought..."hmm" So I took my tempature....yep, I was running a fever. Continued to run one on Sunday as well. And of course once I have a head cold it travels into my lungs.... When that happens, I don't dare try to exercise because I start coughing like crazy, and start feeling really sick. At least this time, it doesn't seem to have hit my lungs too hard....I still remember one time when I got really sick, was out of work for a week, and then tried to excersice about 3 weeks later and still got sick again! ACK! I think that time it took 2 months before I could truly excerise again....I think tomorrow morning I am going to try to do some stretching type excercises, so that I am doing something, but that its not too much for my body.  
     

    
</post>

<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I will be walking the streets of European cities and sucking down pastries.  So that's half-positive (lots of walking and fresh air) and half-negative (the chocolate banana, the nougat ring, the crepes, the strudel, the ...).  I'll back around April 8th.  Good luck to all of you in the meantime!
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Something that I have been thinking is that we should try to have actual challenges. So this is my idea:   The Rules: This week I will introduce a challenge. Those who are going to do it will post (either in a post or comment stating that they will participate) The first person to post after 7pm CST on Monday the 29th, who has accomplished his/her goal for the week, gets to assign the next challenge.  The same person can't assign a challenge more than once a month. When you make a challenge, it can be anything that is _sane_....such as everyone works out at least 5 times that week....or everyone drinks at least 64 oz of water a day that week....or everyone stays away from chocolate. I hope you get the idea.  You can offer a reward if you so wish, however each person that accomplishes his/her goal for the week will get a nifty icon next to his/her name (if I can figure out how to do it) I reserve the right to deem a challenge as unhealthy or unreasonable :) You do not have to participate in these challenges.    Make sense?   So this week, I say "goals" (Mine would be to drink at least 20 oz of water a day, and excerise 3 times in the next week).  Whatever your goal is, it should be  attainable  but one that you will still need to stretch yourself to accomplish--and not something that you are already doing on a regular basis.  My reward to you: Its not much, but for those who reach their goals for this week can have a character named after them (or choose a character's name-nothing crude!-)in one of my 3 universes. (Note: this is not a promise that the story(ies) will be written really quickly though! ;)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have company for the next week.  My thin, curvy sister and her lanky fiance are staying with my thin, muscular husband and myself.  *sigh*  I'm determined to still get into the gym a few times, but it's going to be sketchy while they're here.  The past two days, my eating habits have gone to hell.     Exercise:   Spent three hours in the gym last Wednesday.  Spent Thursday being very, very sore.  Friday did the "Flight of the BumbleBee" cleaning exercise, which includes me running up and down my stairs cursing violently at how messy Ralph and I are.  It WAS aerobic, though.  Saturday was spent wandering around Sea World for 7 hours.  I'm hoping I managed to get enough exercise that I at least made up for not going to the gym yesterday or today.     Eating:   Very, very badly.  I'm consuming a lot of junk that's just not good for me because the kids have brought it into our home and I am weak.  :(  This week will be better.  I hope.  Still ignoring the numbers and trying to keep an eye on how my clothes are fitting and how I'm feeling.   
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome to Susi, soon to be our newest member! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys, I am going to create a page that lists our goals and progress....make it a little bit more tangible, maybe? Anyway let me know if you don't want to be on the page.
     

    
</post>

<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well i had a great week food wise, i'm really enjoying the food plan setup where i can just follow it, and for the first time in my life i'm really following it measuring everything etc but i didn't do any exercise at all this week, have had bad cramping and felt horrible so decided to just eat right this week and get into the exercise next week but i still had a pretty good week and i'm happy with myself.  Highs:  Highs for the week for me are that i lost 2.5kilos (5.50pounds) :) Yay!!!  Lows:  No exercise and Andrew came home with a chocolate for me (so sweet and obviously i couldn't hurt his feelings by not eating it *G*)  Aims:  Mum is coming down for a week on Thursday so my aim is to stick to the food plan while she is here and not eat out to much and also to still exercise.  Thats about it for me, have to decide what to do for Easter cos i want my eggs :) which is ok but when we drive home (8 hour drive) we always have junkfood to eat, and because i'm so bored i constantly eat in the car...have to find something a little more healthy but still yumm!  Hope everyone elses weeks have been good, i like the comment option now to Leslie by the way and hope your back is feeling better Aleta, more so for your trip :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well mum has just left so i finally have time to sit and blog but my report this week is pretty bad *G* I have luckily maintained my weight from last week but considering the foods we ate this week thats pretty damn good. I am restarting the meal plan when we get back from going home at Easter so i won't be around for a week or so but i have been good and i haven't been snacking in between meals which i'm pretty proud of but my exercise is non existant :)  Have decided my goal for the week is that i will take the dogs for a walk at home at least 3 times next week and that i will drink a litre of water a day, i really need to drink more water!  Hope everyone else is going good...:)
     

    
</post>

<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Last week was more than only a trifle hectic, so all my goals vanished into thin air. Let's try again!  Today, my SIL and I will go to our first Weight Watcher meeting. I hope it helps. There's no time for any exercise today, but my goal is to do half a hour of bycicling on Wednesdays and Thursdays. That's more than I'll have done within the last five years!   On the long run I'll have to lose about 20 kg of weight. My health is beginning to suffer from my overweight. My left hip aches for weeks, and whenever I have to climb a stair I'm catching for breath.   And I'm trying not to worry so much anymore (about my job, about the possibility to lose my job, about hub's job, about him losing his job, about everything ... I guess you've got the picture!)  Wish me luck!
     

    
</post>

<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok, a day late, but here is my goal for the week.  1) I'm going to make it to the gym and cardio at least 2 hours this week. 2) I'm going to lift weights 2 times, working every muscle group at least once. 3) I'm going to yoga on Saturday morning. 4) I'm not going to drink any soda this week.    Wish me luck! 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm back from my trip.  The good news?  I lost five pounds while I was on vacation!  I'm sure a lot of it was all the walking and stair climbing that I did.  The bad news? I got sick, picking up a cold, a sinus infection, and bronchitis.    So, I won't be jumping into my new and improved lifestyle now that I'm home.  But I am starting from a better place than when I left.
     

    
</post>

<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went out running Monday (Brrrr!) morning and out of 1.5 miles, ran about 3/4 mile. I didn't go quite as far as I would have liked, mostly because we dipped back down to freezing weather. On the plus side, when I started walking (I walk about half a mile to warm up), I thought running was going to be painful and unpleasant - it just didn't feel good even walking. I was pleasantly surprised to find that it actually felt really good...and not just because it helped keep me warm. :)  I didn't go walking yesterday, but I'll be taking advanatge of my days off the rest of the week to run in the afternoon when it's warmed up a bit. I also found a Web site called www.connectingconnectors.com that's for overweight women who are running or walking to lose weight. They have state chapters as well and membership is free, so I signed up for that. Hopefully that will help me keep on track with running.  Eating's gone better as well, though I did succumb when one of the copy editors brought in a bag of cheetos. We have entirely too much food at work. Other than that, I've stayed on track and kept my foods healthy and portions reasonable. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      No, I haven't forgotten about this - life's just been really hectic. Among other things, my boss needs to have knee surgery in 10 days. They want her to have it sooner, but her boss is off all week and she told them they couldn't put her out of commission for a week with him gone. *sighs with relief*  Anyway, I invested in a new pair of running shoes yesterday, then christened them with three loops around the park (mostly walking). That's just a hair under four miles, and I ran about a mile of it in two spurts. My goal is to be able to run two full loops (2.6 miles) by Marathon Monday (two weeks from tomorrow). The new sneakers are wonderful - like running on air. I hadn't realized just how broken down the old ones were until I headed out in the new ones. Fortunately, my legs held up pretty well - my wind was the problem. I'm hoping warmer weather and some regular training will solve that problem pretty quickly.  I'm been doing not so great with the eating - 14-hour days at work tend to have that effect - but I started to get back on track with dinner tonight and I'm hoping it will carry over through the week. I have three meals already packed in the fridge and freeezer, and I'll pick up a few cans of soup tomorrow. I've also started drinking more water, mostly because the almost-full bottle of lemon juice in the fridge was nearing the end of its useful life. So I've been making water with a twist all week in my 32-oz water bottle.   This week's goals:  Run MWF, working up to running two miles out of 5.2 (four loops) by Friday.  Walk 3.9 (three loops) miles on the days I don't run Bring my dinner to work this week and avoid the snack machine. Eat at least half the veggies in my freezer. 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This first week went better than I thought. My SIL and I didn't find the Weight Watchers meeting on Tuesday, though the group was supposed to meet in the kindergarten. So, I decided to go back to my good old "count fat" method. Its a method that teaches you not to eat too much fat, not a diet. I've done pretty good this week and kept the fat-level that's supposed to be healthy. And I had some workout, so I even lost weight!   My goal for next week is to keep the fat-level, do as much workout as this week, and drink at least one litre a day. The last one is difficult, because I don't like to drink a lot.   BTW, if you wondered: this is Susi. Blogger wouldn't accept me as Susi. 
     

    
</post>

<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I did so-so la-la last week. Though I kept my fat level, the drinking was really a problem. I didn't come near one litre, which is bad. But I'm now drinking herb tea instead of coffee at the office, that's at least a start.   Instead of 2 x half a hour walking I did 3 x one hour and 1 x half a hour! I'm so proud! My hubs is really supportive, since he's afraid that I might get a heart attack, and so he comes with me walking. Yesterday was really funny. The forest begins about 5 minutes from our door, and since there are really nice paths, we decided to walk there. On our way back we took a wrong turn, and what started as a pleasant walk ended as a kind of military-through-the-bushes-trip. Wow, was I k.o. when we came home!   Although I ate sensible and did some walking, I didn't lose any weight this week. But I'm not concerned about this. It's "this time" of the month again, when my body stores water. Believe me, I feel like a marshmellow-man! But since my weight didn't increase, either, this means that I must actually have lost weight. Does this make sense?   My aims for the next week: - Keeping my fat-level - at least one hour of walking - doing some gymnastics - drink one litre a day  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If I dare say so, I did really fine last week! I kept all my goals, that is, if you count doing gymnastics once as "some gymnastics"! *g*  At last I managed to drink enough, though I now think about asking my superior to move my desk to the ladies restroom. *g* Though, walking all across the office a couple of times a day gives me a lot of extra exercise, LOL!   Because I was such a nice girl and worked so hard on my health last week, I thought it was time to reward myself. I bought some new, beautiful smelling body lotion and self-tanning lotion.   So, here is my question: What do you do to reward yourself each time you kept your goals? Or do you think that you deserve nothing for the hard discipline you're keeping?  My goals for the next week:  - keeping my fat-level - drink a litre a day - do shopping by feet as often as possible - stand up when I telephone or dictate - 4 x gymnastics - one hour walking
     

    
</post>

<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well i have to admit i fell of the healthy food and exercise wagon *Hanging head in shame* :) It was so hard over Easter to eat healthy when i had immediate access to chocolate and all that good stuff, i did little to no exercise unless walking around the shops counts?? :) But i am determined to climb back up, its less than a year now till the wedding so if i want to be seious about it i really need to find the motivation and keep it.  I did make a massive batch of pumpkin soup yesteday and froze it so that should keep me going for a while, other than that i'm getting back into exercising at the gym and trying to eat more healthy. I'll see how i go next week when i report in.  Cheers 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've finally been released from Physical Therapy.  Of course, this means I have to make appointments with myself to do my exercises (as well as new ones to tone up all over).  And I want to start eating right.  The first step was getting a small refrigerator for my office.  I did that last week, then on Sunday hauled up groceries (carrots, seltzer, caffeine-free diet coke, yogurt) and a big batch of homemade gazpacho and some hard-boiled eggs for lunch.  Other than yesterday (when the call of the hot dog wagon was too strong to resist), I'm doing okay.  When I feel bored or frustrated, I grab the bag of carrots and start crunching.  Since I clench my jaws a lot, it's a good idea.  Hopefully, things will continue to get better.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ok!?!?! First off when did Blogger change so dramatically? And second, where on earth have I been? Yikes!   Part of it is because I am on limited internet access now. I am back to dialup, so I don't get to spend as much online as I would like to....but oh well :/  My diet and excerise plans are really, really off right now! Trying to get back in the game.....
     

    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Things have been a little crazy around here as I pack to move, but I've been managing to get out walking most days. I did an extra lap today at the park (4 miles total), but only ran a little bit - not even a quarter mile. One good thing about the move is I'm close enough to the park that it would be silly not to walk, which should add in at least an extra mile every day. :) There's also a (small) pool in the complex, so I plan to add some swimming in after my walks/runs.  My goal this week is to break my habit of waking up around 6:30/7 a.m. and rolling over for more sleep. I figure I can always nap after I go walking/running, but it's so much cooler at seven than at nine that I really need to take advantage of it.  I'm doing so-so on eating, but I had a huge salad at a local place downtown yesterday (big enough that most of it went home for dinner later) that was really good, so I think I'm going to try my own version for lunches this week. 
     

    
</post>

<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well we have heard from some of you :) Hoping to hear back from the rest of you.   As for me, I am not doing so great, but I am going to join CalorieKing next week. When I was a member of eDiets (before the changed everything so dramatically), I really lost a lot of weight and I was eating healthier. CalorieKing is so much like what eDiets used to be like, I can't wait to try it again
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Claire (aurie)! Glad to see you made it! 
     

    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've been doing so-so lately. I've been getting out to walk/run three or four days a week, but my eating's been not so great. Part of that's because I'm moving in two weeks so I'm trying to use what I have now rather than shop for stuff I just will have to move in a few days. Part of it is because I've just been busy between packing and moving and haven't taken the time.  My new apartment has a pool and is within walking distance of the park, so that should help. Right now, I'm trying to eat reasonably well, keep my existing exercise level and plan to dive back in once I get moved, since I'll have to tweak my routine then anyway. 
     

    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm still around, eating terribly but exercising a little :) have exams starting on Monday so i'll check back in once its all over with :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And I've slacked off horribly too.  So, a new beginning for me as well?
     

    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I doubt people know this, but I am not big into completely cutting out sweets and snack type foods. I just don't think this is feasible. I really like what one of my roommates does. She buys the snack foods, but she keeps them in the highest shelf in the house, and not in the typical pantry area. That way: a). they aren't the first thing she sees when she opens the pantry to get herself something to eat. b). She has to go through a bit of work to get them down when she wants them (so if she doesn't really want them, she won't put through the extra effort.   I think its a great idea, and thought I would share.  And as for why I didn't start my diet today after all please see my regular blog :)
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I suck so hard.  School got in the way (as it always does).  Worked out last Wednesday and spent several hours walking around downtown Dallas on Sunday, but other than that, I'm a big loser.  :)  I'm sick right now and all my energy is being channeled towards making sure my head doesn't explode in a shower of snot.  But I'll be back real soon with some real goals for myself (maybe).
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Since Leslie threatened in her last post to come over us if we don't post, I think I'd better get in gear! ;)  Maybe you read my post about this topic at the jix message board. About one month ago I got serious back problems. It hurt so bad that I had to see an orthopaedist. Thankfully, it's not what I was afraid of (arthrosis), only cramped muscles and a lack of muscles in my back and tummy. The doctor said I had to build up more muscles, so I finally gave in and signed up with a fitness center, though I hate to go to the Mucki-Bude (muscle-hut), as we call it here. Ever since then I've been a very diligent girl. I do my workout three times a week (otherwise my back will drive me crazy).   About two month ago I made the solution to improve my health and change my lifestyle. Of course it had a lot to do with the fact that I needed to lose about 23 kg ... So far, I lost about 4 kg, +/- 500g, it changes from day to day. There has been no significant weight loss since I joined the fitness center, but I seemed to have turned fat into muscles. When I started, I had 42 % fat on my bones, now it's only 39,5%.   This week, I'm doing really poor with my new eating habits. I am supposed to have a week of vacation, but in fact I'm back to the office at least once a day for 2-5 hours (long story!). I'm so frustrated about that that I eat whatever I can lay my hands on. I hope I'll be back on schedule when I start working again next week. Unfortunately, all my good solutions are gone as soon as I am under pressure. Does anyone know what to do about pressure-eating-attacks? 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thank you for the welcome, Leslie and I love the new look. I've decided that next Monday is going to be my offical day one. This week has been awfully busy and I've been eating out heaps. I'm going to be basing my eating on Weight Watchers since that's what I'm familiar with, although I won't officially be attending the meetings. I also aim to exercise more, though now being in winter that is certainly going to be a challenge in itself! Maybe I'd better find the legs to my rebounder. The mat is tucked between the computer desk and the wall and keeps looking at me reproachfully! So next Monday will be it! 
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am starting my diet over! I am bound and determined this time :) As most of you know, my birthday was on Sunday. I want to be healthy again and buying brand new clothes by my next birthday!  I was going to try today with working out, but after my bit of insomnia last night there was no way I was getting up early to workout.   I still need to create a menu for food. I really like Calorie King's website so I think after my next payday I will subscribe to it. It creates menus for its users :)  
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome Jayne!  I'd say "Settle on in" but that would be an antithesis of what we are trying to accomplish :)  We may also have two more members soon.   This makes me wonder just how many contributers we can have in one of these blogs :) We may end up finding out.
     

    
</post>

<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I hope everyone likes the new look. I noticed that Blogger now has its own comments (shouts of joy!). I'm sorry but our old comments got lost.  Claire, you should have email.   If I missed anyone else please either email me ( greyfort AT gmail.com ) or leave a blog comment here!  Please note: at the the bottom of where you type in your entry there is a little section that says "More post options" If you click on it, it will allow you to turn comments off for your entry (only) and/or change the date/time of your post.  Now for a bit of housekeeping.  I am guilty too! We have slacked off tremedously people. I don't know if we are slacking off our health goals or if its because we have gotten to busy to post.   That being said: If you don't post here by June 7th to let us know how you are doing, then you _will_ be hearing from me! :)
     

    
</post>

<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      First the bad news - we had pizza at work tonight because all the schools had graduation and everybody was working, and I had four slices. (Two Hawaiian, two Philly cheesesteak)  But this morning, I got up at 7:30 and went running in the park. With my 200/30 run/walk ratio, I made it 2.5 MILES! Even better, I covered more ground in the first few sets than I had in the same number of counts yesterday AND my legs feel great. :) So for the rest of the month, I plan to work my way up to four miles (three loops) at the 200/30 ratio. Then I can spend July increasing the run/walk ratio until I'm running the whole thing by the end of July. :D (That would be about 20 miles a week.) My long-range running goal is a marathon in a nearby city held in mid-April. I figure I need to be running about 35 miles a week for about a month by the end of the year so I have the base to start training for the marathon in January. That would be three days running either three or four miles, two days running eight miles and one running 10 miles.  *pause to work out schedule* Actually, barring injury, I should be able to have two months of training at that level (November and December) before I need to start building up for the marathon. So that's my next big goal. And if I eat reasonably well, which I'll need to do to have the fuel to handle the running, I figure my weight will take care of itself. (The less you weigh, the faster you run. The faster you run, the more calories you burn both while running and at rest. It's all good. *G*)
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tonight is check in for me. We shall see how it goes :) 
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      As you all saw last week I mentioned that everyone should post by the 7th. For those who did, they are grandfathered from some new rules that I have been meaning to set into place, but hadn't.   Since we are trying to help each other with healthier lifestyles, I think it is imperative that we post our progress. Therefore I feel that we should be posting at least once every two weeks. So from now on, for those who don't post at least once every two weeks will be placed on a passive list. If after a month that member hasn't posted, then they will be removed. S/he is of course elgible for membership again. I do this not to discourage anyone, but to encourage each of us.   Exceptions can and will be made on a case by case basis.  For those who posted by June 7th, as requested, there is a grandfather clause for you. You are not bound by these rules, however if you stop posting, for say 6 months, then I may have to talk to you :)  Any questions, ask me!  
     

    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My eating is still a mess, sigh! My body is craving for moutains of chocolate (and getting it). So I haven't lost any more weight. But at least I'm still doing my training as scheduled. Actually, I've changed another 0,5% fat into muscles. So, I'm making little progress, but it's still a progress. 
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm about midweek and doing okay. I'm managing to stay within my points allocations for each day and have had some treats. Getting exercise when I can - mainly walking to and from the bus stop but that's okay. I do need to drink more water, I've been a bit slack on that. But otherwise I'm happy!
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, this whole running/walking idea is working better than I thought. Today, I tried running 200 counts, walking 30 and repeating. I ended up running 700 counts and walking 120, and covered about 1.5 miles, which is three times as far as I can run if I just start and go until I have to stop. :) My next goal is to be able to make two loops around the park (2.6 miles) at the 200/30 ratio. Once I can do that, I'll probably switch to 300/30 and keep adjusting until I can run the whole thing. My goal right now is to be able to run 4 miles without walking by Trixie Camp. With roughly six weeks to go, I figure I'm in good shape.  Eating's still kind of up and down, mostly because I'm trying to use up odds and ends of food so I don't have to move it. But I'm being good about avoiding the snack machine at work and trying to keep things balanced.  Oh, and the paper's sponsoring a co-ed softball team this summer for the county league, and I signed up for that. Games start July 8, and I volunteered to be catcher. I did the same thing three summers ago and my legs got a great workout, since I basically spent 30 to 45 minutes a night doing deep knee bends once a week. :) This league plays two games a week, which will be good. No clue what it will do to my running, though. We shall see...
     

    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I showed a couple of my co-workers my lunch both yesterday and today, and like me, they are shocked. I just can't get over how much food I _can_ eat. I really like Calorieking, especially after I found where they hid all the rest of the foods known to man, so I am able to change out what I actually eat for what they say I should eat (there is no way I am eating fat free plain yogurt....can you even find that stuff???) So then I mix the numbers up, and voila! My own menu. I _love_ it.  Course yesterday I ate a bit more than I was supposed to, but that's because I am in those couple of days per month where nothing I eat fills me up and I am hungry again after only an hour or so. Thankfully that only lasts a little while. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thanks to a tidbit I picked up in Runner's World, I was able to run twice as far today. Basically I ran my usual - a half mile - than walked for 30 counts, then started running again, this time counting. Since I made it 200 counts the second time, I let myself walk for 60 counts, then started running again. That time it was only 100 counts and I was petering out pretty quickly, so that was the end. But it got me another half mile around the park, so I figure it was a success, especially since it's high 80s today. :)  I also resisted the temptation of the snack machine at work last night and stuck with munching on the pistachios I'd brought.  I'm also trying to juggle writing and working out into my regular schedule since in the past I've always ended up picking between the two. We shall see. I think getting up closer to seven than 8:30 will help - cooler for running and more time before work - but we'll see. 
     

    
</post>

<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      In about 2 hours it will be midnight and the start of my healthy eating/get more exercise plan. I'm on night shift starting tomorrow night, so it's easier for me to think of each day from midnight rather than when I wake up. At about 8am I'll weigh myself - eeeek!!  My goals are really just to stick within my points allocation for each day. I don't expect to get much exercise this week but I'm okay with that. I tend not to exercise much on nightshift. I'll just have to go for lots of walks around the ward!
     

    
</post>

<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      3 is the magic number!  Of pounds that I have lost this week, that is :)  Happy Dance, Happy Dance :) :) :)
     

    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My pants feel slightly loser today. I think its my imagination though.   My checkin is in the morning-so that I can report my progress tomorrow at lunch :)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Okay, I definitely have to get my sleep schedule on track. I went out running about quarter of nine this morning and it was already in the 90s. Since I didn't have much to drink last night or this morning, I stopped after 1.25 miles. I need to stop rolling over when I first wake up around 6:30 a.m. and just get up and go running.  I start moving tomorrow, so it's going to be kind of a crazy weekend. But with all the books I have to move, my arms will get a great workout. :) I'll be internetless from tonight until Monday morning, so don't expect to hear from me until then. :)
     

    
</post>

<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well i had a bit of a freak out last night well not freak out but i realised i have to do something about my weight instead of ignoring it so i weighed myself, went through my cupboards and took out all the clothes i have that don't fit me (2 garbage bags full) at 11pm at night this is *G* i made signs and put them around the house and had a cry :)  This morning we got up at 6am and went for a walk which i'm going to start doing everyday, took us about 30-40mins, i'm really cutting back on the food and i'm going to eat some of those pre packaged dinners for a month or so. I do feel loads better having exercised and am really going to stick to this seeing all my nice clothes in the garbage bag that don't fit me was so sad...i'm going to make them fit me again!!! I have some extra motivation at the moment as i have found a wedding dress i want and its cheaper if you can fit into a certain size or $60 something more if you can't i want to save money so i have to fit into the smaller one :) This may sound weird but i'm getting Andrew and my dad to sponsor me *G* Andrew will put $20 in a bank for every kilo i loose and when i reach my first goal (which is a little ways off) i get the money to go and buy some clothes or something, if i put on a kilo he takes 20 out, Dad i'm just going to get him to give $10 per kilo and when i reach the goal weight he will give me the total...i really needed to do something because if i keep telling myself its ok for me to be larger i will never lose any!!!   
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well I didn't lose anything, but that was to be expected since I didn't exercise at all last week...just ate healthier....I have decreased my caloric intake a bit since what I was on was just _too_ much food. But I did start excersicing on Saturday..... so very happy right now :)
     

    
</post>

<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've had a good week. I've lost weight, and I do feel better. Does anyone find that as soon as you start dieting (hate that word but it describes things better)and exercising you already feel slimmer? I do, even on day 1 :) I'm happy with my first week, but it's always the first couple of weeks I find the easiest. I do have a short term goal to lose 10kg by the middle of August as I want to fit into a particular outfit. I have over 30kgs to lose in total but I'm looking at smaller chunks at the moment. I have to try and keep myself from standing on the scales every day because I know that weight fluctuates, but I can't help peeking! *g*  Goals for this week:  1) Stick to points 2) Go for at least one 20min walk  
     

    
</post>

<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, I didn't do any running this weekend, but with all the lifting and carrying inherent in moving, I got a decent workout. Aleta and I also went swimming Saturday to cool off. I didn't do anything today - first the cable guy came, and then I got called into work early - but if the pool's not filled with small children this evening, I might go in for a while.  Eating should improve now that I'm moved and can restock my shelves.  
     

    
</post>

<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've weighed myself this morning and have lost 2kgs so I'm happy. :) I did keep within my points though some days I didn't eat enough. Being on afternoon shift I'd sleep late and not have breakfast. Have a little lunch then have dinner and nothing else. I'll try to correct that this week. I'll have to think of a reward for myself next week if I lose about 500g as that will make it 5kg. I know what I'll do for when I lose 10kg - buy some Lush products. I love their bath ballistics and bubble bars. Just wish we had a shop in Dunedin!   I've been able to keep out of the snack box at work. To be honest, I haven't even been tempted yet. I had to buy dinner a couple of nights this week so I just bought Weight Watcher meal rather than buying from the cafeteria. I even had lemon meringue pie two nights - quite low in points for a dessert. I made popcorn for watching the rugby instead of buying potato chips. I have a popcorn maker so it was totally fat free. I think popcorn might end up being one of my 'safety' foods.  Kind of cheated for my walk, I counted it by walking from church into work. I was going to do it anyway, but it's still a walk. I'm aiming to go for a walk today. It's probably warmer outside that in at present.   Goals for this week are the same as last week: stick to points and go for at least one walk.
     

    
</post>

<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm starting over again.&nbsp; School is almost over.&nbsp; I'm a research paper and a business plan away from completion, so I think I can manage to add a little to my schedule. &nbsp; Also, I went ahead and joined weight watchers about a week ago.&nbsp; *sigh*&nbsp; It feels like failure, but I know it isn't.&nbsp; I'm getting used to eating less crap and more vegis, which is a good thing.&nbsp; Ralph tried to talk me into ice cream last night, but I resisted.&nbsp; (I swear that boy is nothing but trouble!&nbsp; *g*)&nbsp; &nbsp; Exercise: We took the dog for a walk last Wednesday.&nbsp; At noon.&nbsp; In Texas.&nbsp; I've never sweated so much in my life.&nbsp; We also went for a walk last night and I think we might add walking to our evenings a few times a week.&nbsp; We also got up this morning and went to the gym.&nbsp; I spent 30 agaonizing minutes on the elliptical, but feel pretty good so far today.&nbsp; Tonight is yoga, then home for a quick dinner by myself.&nbsp; Tomorrow is my weighing day, so I'll let you guys know how I do! &nbsp; 
     

    
</post>


</Blog>