<Blog>


<date>30,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Folx the good news is that I am most probably going back to college to finish my final year (Bachelor of Design) and it will be alot of Multimedia, the bad news Is... dekonstrukted is kinda dead right now and our hosting support if dropping. What I will do now, that I have finished my Client work and get set to go to UNI is work on some concepts and Ideas for a New "design" website, The reason it is hard is because there alot of cliche's going around the web designers communities right now, so something original is all we need, nothing wrong with following a trend, it's just my kookie attitude thats all. we will see what happens, but please stay tuned to this news box... ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Scene360  is a rockin zine, you go there and just love the content I would buy this zine if it where printed !
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink H73  is up and NEW ! all I can say it Finally a decent design zine layout. Speaking of layouts, even though this site has only been up for less than a week I think it's time for a re-design !
     
    
</post>

<date>29,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Want to know whats the hell happend to dekonstrukted?  urlLink here is my explanation , and also here are my things to do today: TA client website, Phone card design, call up UNI, help dad sand the the floor, drink some Jamican rum and call up girl that none of you know ;) hehe I will try and get this small amount of tasks by tonight.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      The sections are pretty much up, and ready to roll, and also I updated my  urlLink resume  a little and HTMLised it so all you hungry employers can peek at it and hire me now, because as you may or may not know I am loking for full time work at the moment. The Index page will now have POTD (pic of the day) witch may not be updated weekly, just whenever I choose a new pic to show, so now the site officialy open, crack open your bottles of chanpagne and get pissed.
     
    
</post>

<date>27,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      ok all the thumbnails, sections and links to sites and sfiles will be up within 2 days... now that i finaly got hte dam site working :)))) like th enoo shit?
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       Finaly got the site working if your reading htis post then your probably just testing cause i wouldnt let anyone see this shit ;)))))))))))))
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Jesus F*&)9%$n christ! if I see another Pixelated cartoon im quite literaly going to puke all over my keyboard, now before you curse me for using the lord's name in vein
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Lets just say we are a a bunch of lost souls..with depression in our minds, haunting us like ghosts.... the string of hope lies on hour hands and all we do is hope for it to fall...
     
    
</post>

<date>26,January,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Gawd...what a year this has been so far, looking for work and not getting it, I spent so many years training myself in graphic design and now it seems I will never get anything because I dont have enough commercial experience according to the Suits, well I will keep going nonetheless, I know for a fact that I can do better design and graphics than most of the yuppies out there in Sydney in the so called CBD, but for some reason they are afraid to take someone on without a huge list of previous work for other companies, now I kept my mouth shut all year, I tried being a "normal" jobseeker but its getting on my god damm nerves, NOT even working for free. Hey I get some clients for freelance webdesign so There I do work, but all I want is to get a job in a nice design company to put my print skills to work. So since this is my post and my blog I can scream my thoughts around, here is one email I got as a reply from an internet job placement site:  "From the details you have supplied it appears that you do not unfortunately,have quite enough experience at this time for us to actively seek suitable employment for you. Current demand and client expectation in the marketplace requires our candidates to have at least one year of industry-based computer experience for permanent work and two years industry-based experience for temporary work.".   Ok if 4 to 5 years using Adobe Photoshop and whatever crap they ask for, including Hands on design and art history is not enough for them what is? for crying out loud you gotta give someone an opening dont you? I will try as hard as I can everyday to get the job I want but if the design companies keep up this snobbish attitude then I just think I might take up the job offerings as an Illustrator reprographic in the Australian Army. And then they are never accurate, when they ask for designers what they really want is programmers, and vice versa, Well I hope for the future this system goes close to the right way. 
     
    
</post>

<date>22,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink PhreaKam  MY little attempt to join the webcam community, why do I feel I will regret this.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink New Lifestyle  a new wallpaper for yo desktop from me (grins) Its a new brighter, happy  one rahter than the usual hate shit.
     
    
</post>

<date>18,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink OShock2 , Optical Shock is back and gaw dam I love his new attitude, It was what I went through for about half a year and I didnt realise it, if you dont know what Im on about about read the ABOUT section on his site, and while your at it be in awe of his art, I still think the older stuff should be up but anyhow its up to him.
     
    
</post>

<date>17,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      And we thought there was only one  urlLink Seire.org,   urlLink Koalesce.org  is yet another attempt at making another Seire, Now before you accuse be of bagging them out let me just say that there is only ONE of everything !
     
    
</post>

<date>15,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Woohoo After the bad day I had something good to come home to  urlLink Australian INfront  Not only Am I featured there, we can now update our profiles on it, I expect this site to be huge for new media in Australia.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      well fellas It's decided dekon is back up and its diffrent but this time Im the boss and if you dont like it you can go, Im sick of making non-profit sites where it becomes all about the guest rather than it's members. I hope I dont need to make the link, I have not enought time right now just go to dekonstrukted.com, bo bHi
     
    
</post>

<date>07,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Kaliber 10,000   finnaly has a kick ass issue, I always thought the last few issues were a little dull  but the brazilian guys have produced an amazing peice of motion design in quicktime, I still cant belive my eyes after seeying it 4 times, this is why Im smiling about doing multimedia and audio visual this year :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      OK I have blown off a little steam the last few weeks, but things are getting better, although im still holding my breath. now for some reason people dont seem to understand that this site is a personal site, If I want your involvement I will ask for it, please dont email me asking me about dekonstrukted, I dont care how pissed off you may be about it It is just not going to happen right now so I want you all to forget about dekon for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Opticalshock.com : buddy I could not agree more with your words !, you made me feel glad that I closed dekonstrukted
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink WOW, WOW, WOW, WOW...did I mention...WOW 
     
    
</post>

<date>01,February,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know what the fuck has been going on, but whatever has been going around about dekon is not all from my mouth, because if you read  urlLink RTT  news then you finnaly see most of the truth is there, one of the many reasons i closed dekon was because of this shit, people taking it too far, seriously and above all not respecting people, and then trying to make me take sides, now I have had enough of it. I am a string of hair away, from stoping all of this webdesign bullshit, theres just too many fucking webdesign sites, to many wannabee's too many concepts that are just useless and too much going into this ---of a community, if you want to learn design go to a fucking graphic design school and learn some god damm typography dont make a pathetic so called "web-design-site" All I want is for people to stop this shit, YES I am angry, The steam thats been building up is just about ready to come out, now if you even think about telling me off for my decisions or words, think again,, why dont you all just leave me the fuck alone and I will do the same, I have gone through this shitty depression thing and ignoring the doctors, for too long and Now I am trying to get my life straight if you cant understand thats fine.. because you shouldnt waste your friggin time on pathetic websites that mean nothing exept for the people on the other side of the world. 
     
    
</post>

<date>21,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Should I fear you "THE VISITOR" for opening my mind, showing you my dreams, my random acts of... I dont know make up a word for me.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      She said Can you be my boyfriend, I said I can be your friend, she said I hate you, I said I dont, she said she loves me, I said I didnt, do we ever stop, now Time has happend and we are here nor there but up in friggin clouds, I was a survivor, but I need my saviour, soon enough.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont get how many times I have to tell you I love you before realising your not there? how many times does it take me to realise you are thin air, I need to breathe the air you breathe, you left me nothing but imagination, I dont want this, I hate maybe's, come with me, let me call you, dont play games, Give me my heart back.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      so here we go again are you ready for it?
     
    
</post>

<date>05,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Something just occured to me, the so Called BLOGGING generation is just a continium of the current "Real Life Show" trends... thats all I had to add, I am in a rush Im tipsy, and Im going out to a few drinks and chat...LOL daim, I am part of this Real Life Show shiznat, kool...way to look at diffrent perspective Luis ;))), gawd I need to get mah brain straight, Well fellars It seems I am getting a few hits from k10k.com and more sites at the mo, So I better start trying to make more sence, hehe this is just a babble, drink and talk box, and the beautiful white box on the left is the clean Straight news posts, so keep coming back 200 times a day for em, k bye peoplz ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Well I got that outta the way
     
    
</post>

<date>04,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      If you thought this page is just text based and looks booring you are are probably right, and I dont want to get into the Content Vs Design issue but relax, because I have done the Hundreth or so website design that should be cool enough for a few days, hehe and I will add my Photograhy section, and Blah blah, just wait , it should be up by tomorrow. Oh and yes I have remooved my bad pics from the site, this Voyerism has got to Stop ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>03,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Wah hoo man sometimes i can work fast I done half my assigments in one night, now its time for some playing around ;)))) I cleaned up the layout a bit today.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      On another note, I have over 40 digital artworks and about 50 drawings to add and so on, because most of the stuff here is starting to get old, either that or me ! so I will update either tonight or tomorrow. And I am leaving for Uni [College] right now, it will probably be another shit day.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah I dont think I have explained the reason for this site, as you may or [may not] know dekonstrukted has kind of closed its doors, nobody's fault, it's just that there is not time at the moment to run it, so I cant guarantee that It will be back and if it will it will be done properly with a full group. But now you can enjoy my personal ramblings news, events and mainly poetic words from a manic depressant of whatever you want to call it. Last year was a little shit for me and this year is becoming nothing diffrent, im going to be 21 at the end of the year, I had so many dreams and visions to reach at this time, and still nothing, so I am a little bitter, but now I am realising that there are people I know that actually give a rats arse so I better start making a bigger effort, anyone online or on my icq that has gone through late nights whilst I was drinking away, or anyone that has put up with my meaningless words in community sites, I apologize, and if you enjoyed, try drinking yourself to sleep regularly, I am sick of misconceptions people get and as of today the world will be a better place !... ok wel this page at least... for me :), ooh and did I forget to mention I am posting with less spelling mistakes?!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I let my guard down, it's an emotional battle and a fight for who cares the most, I almost went down again, but rise I shall.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      No not you I didnt mean you, please dont cry, my dignity tells me I was wrong, but My heart tells me im right, I dont understand you, and you dnt understand me is that it? can we leave it there or do we have to push it?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I just dont know what happened, one day I realised that everything was out of control and out of range, to put things into perspective something had to be done, I did not know what that was, I did know what I was doing, I still dont, but I knew that something had to be done and after reminding myself not to follow my instinct anymore, Thats exactly what I did. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      my back is filled with scars of knife wounds, and when i look in the mirror i see a clean back but I have the memories of the pain in my head, and it block all my emotion from one to the other
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      You all suck, but why should I say I love you tomorrow? out of pity or fear you might disown me, fuck you all and your social games.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,April,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Why did I stay home today, locked in my room, did you think I cried? did you think I planned my stabbing of your back? I didn't I drank myself to sleep, I woke up I cleaned myself up I went downstairs and Felt regretful, This is not for you, it is not for them but for me, the world "I" is not there but here, so dont think of telling me you are my friend nor foe you are just a pin in the pin basket like I am a peice of cut grass in a field of grass
     
    
</post>

<date>24,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I haven't posted anything for a few days, been busy running around doing stuff for my major project, spending time with Carly and friends and whatever else I could fit into a day, I feel like shit right now, unfortunately I always feel like shit when I update my diary, come to think of it, that's pretty much the only reason I decided to have this diary, to show the visitors of this site, what's goes through my head, and to vent a little bit, I'm sweating a bit, dehydrated and lacking, and I mean lacking sleep, I haven't had a good night's sleep for a long freaking time, I only have tomorrow and Tuesday at college then I have 4 and half weeks off, fuck that will be great, I'm finding it so hard to finish this work all I have to do tonight Is finish my Kiosk touch screen in Director 8 =/ and prepare everything for Mounting..ooh and I forgot about he 1500 word essay !, Geez I'll save that for tomorrow When I am at least more awake, enough of this college shit !  As for other stuff, everything is very ..urm in between ok and shit, I am not as busy as I make it it sound sometimes, because I don't work that hard on my projects these days, but I'm just so mentally exhausted, I cant seem to do much anymore, I'm fed up...well not to say fed up...but maybe just a frustrated with people around me, people I love, people I care about.... It's not that they did anything, I guess I just need a break away, somewhere by myself, away from family, friends and everyone else around me, I devote so much time and effort into satisfying everyone..that in the end it does the opposite, and makes everyone uncomfortable, I want my independence, I want a steady regular sleeping pattern, I want to be able to wake up at 6am everyday and feel great, like I used to when I was 17, I want to be inspired again, I used to hate sleeping and I used to wake up early and start drawing and going swimming and so on, and now its odd, that I have or am on my way to getting the things I always wanted so badly, I feel the exact opposite =/ I don't get it, no amount of coffee or guarana energy drinks is gona heal my tiredness now.....a break, that's all, Not having to think about anything for at least a week, but then Id have a limit to that ! heh... I don't know I'm loosing my chain of thought now..
     
    
</post>

<date>18,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      after resting and working on college stuff...that leaves next week as the last week,, the one where everything is due, so tonight I should have be at least up to 90% done on my work, this is the list,  - Website layout - Kiosk design and production (a touch screen,information booth) - 8 page broshure - Identity and logo...(should be first before anything) - a 10 metre wall for exhibition space - and essay describing my racionale for doing this whole thing..blah blah... and so forth - a 30 to 40 second short film/multimedia project..for Sound Studies...basicly jsut gota make and produce a little story with sound as the main medium - a Log book for multimedia..showing that I have been recording all the research.. - and last but not least 6 A2 sized boards with the big major project witch invloved most of the above things....  now all this has to be done by next week, sorry carly, im dying to see you but I'm not too sure that going to happen, she went away for a few days, I will miss her again but hey, bring more coffe on...i must finish this shit load of work, you know that only good thing that will come out of this with be the 4 weeks holidays I will get after that, I feel so bad, like total shit, all I want is to be curled up in bed with my girlfriend..and wake up in the morning and go to Bondi beach and play some  urlLink capoeira  on a sunny afternoon and go for a swim, then come home and finnaly make some art I have been hanging to mke...after that I would then go out and drink all my money away...*poof* I just woke up again...stop dreaming I say...get back into it !
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is not a good day, me and my dad came close to dying in a car crash, but I will go back a bit more, first I put all my college work aside so I can spend some time with my Carly, (precious as always) and more time for some casual work that I do for Film and Tv as an extra, So anyway Im out Friday night I come home at around 4am I rest for a bit, without much sleep at all I just pack my bag and leave for work, the time now is a little over 5:AM, So my dad decides to wake up before the sun is out and give me a lift, what a great guy, I was going to drive, but two things 1: I have my Learner's licence =( ( I know it's sick for a 20year old ) and 2: I was still a little drunk :/ ...so we are coming close to our destination, and I have my head resting on the passenger's side and all of the sudden I tilt my head back up and I notice my dad is doing about 80 k's an hour, going through a RED light and a giant Petrol truck comes from the left road turning into the main road and I scream "DAD, RED LIGHT" and he breaks, the car swerves and leaves a nice big burnout mark on the road, we are only a couple of metres away from the truck with the car smelling of burnt rubber, then we realise that we have got to stay awake, at 5am..DAMMM I was a little freaked out, but stranger things have happened, anyhow I get there and I slowly sip back about 4 coffes over 2 to 3 hours while Im watching the sunrise and waiting for the film crew to get everyone ready to do their shit, then the rest is details just Cut...Go..blah blah you know how it works, for about 6 to 7 hours, So im having a hangover, havent slept and still tired from working on my college work all freakin week and what happens?...I get lost, I never been in this area before, so it only takes me about 35 minutes to find a near by train station, So I practicly fall asleep, and all of the sudden I start to feel like crying, I was feeling odd, It wasn't like normal crying I was just having a little panic attack or something, lucky for me the train came and I made it through the way home, by now all the caffeine I had during the day starts to kick in and I decide to do my work for college and have a chat to Carly online, It is now 10:30pm as I am writing this, I have only slept an hour and a half today, and im feeling very depressed, but in a small mellow way, any bad feeling is an ok feeling when your at home, I think so, The next 3 weeks are going to be alot busier then this, I hope I can survive till the holidays, It would also help If I was doing ok at college :/, I just haven't been able, to put enough time and effort into it lately, I have been focusing my time on people around me, and earning money, as I am broke. Someone in my street saw me running to the train station at 7am a few days ago and screamed out "Stop trying to please everyone" and I have been thinking about that since, and I guess that is the reason I am home now instead of being at another 21st birthday party of a college friend, So after I finish publishing this, Im probably going to hit the bed, I have so many thoughts, so many new views, another time for change is coming and I can feel it, so let's see how I feel tomorrow, and If I am up for another full day of last minute college assigments, by for now people. 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Im going to regret this Are'nt I? 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      There are things in life, that noone wants to let go, by things I mean people, emotions and a certain atmosphere that sorounds us, Is there a breaking point, limit on how much you can take? I know the feeling of pakcing your bags and leaving and running and dreaming and beginning is always there, but how close have you gone? just a though...
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       darkness should have told me that the daylight was coming before I said goodbye
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      What a feeling, here goes an attempt at describing it, I have been listening to alot of Creed, Blink182, Faithless, Coldplay and so forth...and today I found my old mp3 albums CD with Portishead, Dummy in it and Whoa what rush, now am I hypersensitive? or is this normal I just felt like I do when I miss Carly =) It was weird I put it on and the music came on and I put it louder, It's on now, helping me to work, write, and think clearer, this I why I like them so damm much, they bring balance to my mind when I listen to it......arghhh back down I go, give me a minute and I just might write something more =)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know what to say, It hurts to find out someone you know tried to commit suicide, it hurts for them and everyone around them, I just wanted to say, if you ever think of doing it..or you are right now, ACCEPT the fact that no matter what I say, your family or your friends will say no one in this god dammed world will know what your thinking no matter if we relate or not, now doesnt that give you some kind of power over doubt? the fact that your hold something so personal, Ok so you feel like shit but think about it for a second, if your mind is capable of letting you go through this shit, why not let it go right through and make it ..make it out of of there, No one including you knows what happens when you die, and dont let that be the reason to go, just stay here, I say kill yourself only in one circumstance or two, if you fulfilled your life, and or have passed your thoughts and history on to someone else, Who are we to say  STOP dont doit?, its all your desicion, We can only offer our soft or hard morals you have to be the judge, dont run away too soon, live your life, go through the shit and come out alive...good bye for now
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I like to explain things and make everything sound clear, but today Im just not in the mood, Im trying so hard to get used to being a happy person, because I am, geting closer to finishing my degree, family still together (barely), got a beautiful girlfriend, that Im crazy over... I guess thats pretty much it, its funny how the fact that im in debt, poor and cant drive feels like a little grain of rice right now, I want a job in Design part time right now really, really bad, It would solve so many gaps and help out alot, Im tired of peole telling me I have skill and talent, balh blah, I am aware that I have been doing design and art for a while blah blah fuking blah, but theres more then one person in the world, lets not be selfish now =), Im just waiting for that big break..the opening, come to think of it, i aint really waiting, Im expecting it, but I guess We just hav to work harder then hard on these things, now taking away the jobless lifestyle, Im feeling pretty god dam good, I never in my wildest dreams thought I would be ok this year or infact ever. But no matter what theres always more, we always want more dont we?...yes we do..so until then I will  just stay clean, and drink only once a week hahah ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,June,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      one word for the past 7 weeks "HAPPY"!...another word, "Carly", and one more, "Missing"
     
    
</post>

<date>09,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been ok...kind of... the last couple of days I have just been enjoying the holidays a bit more without work and such, got me a  urlLink Henna tattoo  thingy, and just worked on  urlLink TransAquariums.com , I'm leaving soon to see my friend Rupert, from  urlLink Visions Of Them  he is Hospital and having a hard time, so I'm going to dance around for his entertainment =) two more things, I just got a new Host and URL all thanks to Michael Tussey from  urlLink Shodown.net , so from now on its -   luis.shodown.net   - and the last bit for this afternoon is that I'm leaving tomorrow, going camping for a few days, I should be back by Friday and ready to start kicking it again after taking a break from home and city life. That's it for now... more deep and meaningful's later ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>06,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to another filming this morning, took about a hour to get there =/ it was for a show on  urlLink SBS  called  urlLink Going Home  and I must say it was very boring, but well worth it when you watch the show, it took about 6 hours to shoot, it's an odd show, a mix of today's news and drama with a group of regular Characters on a Train carriage everyday. I was surprised to see that the whole train was a Set. Anyhow other things happening either then work, hmmm just fighting with my parents, the older we get the further apart we become it seems =(... I miss Carly this is the longest I have gone without seeing her I think, hopefully I will see her tomorrow, and next week I am going to be away for 3 or 4 days on a camp with some college buddies, just to get away from the dreaded city life and family life for a while, and on that same week, another fancy dress party, and this time I will try not to drink so much, I end up wearing a ballerina wig, like last time. Well I also updated my Design Folio, so you can look at that, but there's more stuff I need to scan so keep a watch if that interests you ;), bye for now.
     
    
</post>

<date>05,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to work today again, as an extra for film and TV, I was in the background pretending to be an Orderly at the Hospital, It was fun, also finished my new site design, third one this week, I actually put more time and effort into this one, so It will stay up for longer then a week, heh. That's pretty much all for now, I'm not in a very descriptive and inquisitive mood at the moment, give me a few more hours at home being alone and I will probably come back to the usual weird mood.
     
    
</post>

<date>04,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      when an angel sings, let it finish it's song
     
    
</post>

<date>02,July,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      desktop, Right click, new, Text document... a breath, a thought, a nod, and feeling  That's all It takes for me to start pumping my emotions onto words, hardly I ever show anyone, because It becomes to personal, so personal that I just delete 2 pages sometimes, and smile for the fact that I got it all out of my system, about 2 or more months ago, I used to write so much, and It was short little useless words and lines to just In a way try to motivate readers, but proverbs are well ignored by the people that need them the most  I'm feeling odd today, yet again, but strangely enough everything expect for the No-Work thing seems to be going so good its scaring me, I been so hooked on unhappiness, I don't know what to do at the moment, Is it Carly? is it time? age...? or just the air and the atmosphere changing? Who knows, maybe its better not to, just take it all in, open your arms and scream, and laugh, then scream some more...
     
    
</post>

<date>29,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I was gonna post something like " aww, me and my brother went driving around looking for an fish'n'chips place, to eat tonight" but fuckin hell do you seriously give a rats ass about things that I do that everyone else does? go watch some Big Brother if you do, my thought for today though is that sometimes you can say too much to certain people, there is such as thing as too much information, that later on can be used agaisnt you...by that you will be or can be condtradicting yourself, God I hope that makes sence, heh, now for the "how-im-feeling" part, Im feeling pretty darn good, saw my close friends finished my work, avoided an argument with Lecturer heh, and I will see my g/f tomorw night ! whahooo, she will be here for a few days, you know with most of my family gone overseas, and me bein a shit cook and bein lonely heh, ok I guess thats enough for now, Il be back later, it's stil early and there's plenty more drinks to go.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Amongst the anguish, amongst the pain.....ahh fuck it Im not going to use big ass words to say something simple as hell, we have pain, Me and you, yes you and automaticly we compare witch is deeper or witch is worse, for what? a simple grant of pity ??, yes...normal human nature I would say, everyone does it, but Wouldnt it be nice if we all accepted that every invidual has his/her struggle wether it be mentally or physycally or both, whatever hapens in life, it hapens to one person, one lifetime, dont let anyone determine how mentally stable you are. I know I havent recently, My eyes have been opened in the last week, by listening and viewing other people in their environment,and in general just growing out of my usual attitude, it happens, some things are going on with my best friend and it's pretty serious stuff, thats going to make him feel alot less in the coming weeks, I really wont mention what it is out of respect, and another one of my close friends Kim has had his struggle, and damm it He will write his love story one of these days for you all to see, It will make you cry ! (He knows what im talking about) and then there's Carly my girlfriend, she puts on a brave face most of the time, but her like everyone else in their own life is going through a rought time and Although I always knew about these things, Once you go deeper and look in their eyes and see further then the fine line itself, and discover how they feel, rather then the story, it becomes a much more stronger effect, and that's what hit me. Of all the words and actions you could take to support someone, sometimes you jsut cant say anything, like Forrest Gump said  "Sometimes theres just not enough rocks" , While im tryin hard to adjust my attitude back being a "Nice" guy all over again, I would like for you to think about someone near you, and whatever you think you have been thorugh no matter how bad, try for one day to imagine the feelings or at least watch that person, and accept that they have a right to curse life, no matter the scale of the situation. This may sound like a line from Fight Club, but Selfishness is just masturbation, I declare this this, "think about someone else day" heh im out of here for now, bahbye.  urlLink One link for u =D 
     
    
</post>

<date>24,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      No, I didnt go to the  urlLink gathering  last night =( , I thought Id' stay home and try and finish a few weeks worth of work in one day, just so I can spend more time with sweet ol'  urlLink Carly , and I will be away for a day from my working space and computer, I guess I just want to miss it all over again heh, and also I have been getting some coments on my Journal, more then usual, It's nice to know there are people out there that do listen when I babble. It's been a strange day yesterday and today I only left my room about 4 times to go toilet, dinner, n such crap. as for deep and meaningfull's, I dont think I can pull one out of my head right now, as I am feeling pretty normal, for once! But I will say one thing that I said a few times before I click Post and Publish and walk out the door =  "Everything you see fits in a frame, you just have to capture the right image!"   One more thing ! check out this cover  urlLink  018   ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>23,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I might go to the  urlLink DiK  /  urlLink AusINfront  get-together tonight, who knows, Im trying hard to finish all my college projects today, because tomorw is good old "Spend time with girlfriend" day, Things have been ok...maybe not that good but decent, yesterday was one of those days where everyone close to you turns on you, and you realise their right, I was trying to speak to one of my close friends and I said some bad shit now he turned agaisnt me, then was my family, seech I wont even go into that, now that im geting way too personal, I think it's time I say "Enough" and talk about the site, yes I have redesigned, and within the next few days I will updating it alot more, and moderating, some old bad shitty designs in my Folio.
     
    
</post>

<date>19,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Is there a time to live your life compressed in one year?, it seems that's we try to do, when we are in that inspirational state of mind, I mean does the "life is too short" concept work anymore? but then again, is it worth sitting around your couch doing things one by one, or maybe even just contemplating it? I think not, something happens to us from the moment we sit and ponder to the moment we get up and take action, It's like an action movie in your mind your in the plot and your thinking about what will happen before the ending, well metaphor after metaphor I sit here typing away, in my "state-of-mind" trying to reach the people that visit my website/journal to my thoughts, I guess that's my motive here, because I havent quiet figured it out just as yet.
     
    
</post>

<date>13,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Here I stand, pondering yet another day lonely miserable night, thinking about what I have done and what I am Doing, holy crap, look another writing from a young depressed person! Well that’s for you to judge not me, You know, if there is one thing about me that I do know is that I am open and I can be sensitive, sometimes a Real hard ass too, and one thing I have always believed in and craved for was love and romance, not in the Pathetic old lady novel way, just a certain passion for someone that returns it or a certain passion for Something you do, I have put these wanted feelings and emotions so far hight up my list it drove me insane, As I grew and as the years went past, with all the people I met, the drinks I have drunk, the food I have eaten, some things changed and some haven’t, but One thing that has changed to this point in time, Is that romance for life or someone is finally here in my arms, and as hard as it is to say it, I am fucking it up, I don’t know wether I play emotional games with myself or the people around me but, the more they keep getting closer to me the more I keep shutting them out and at the same time slowly begging them for more attention, Is this a normal human reaction?  I don’t know... Some things in my family have happened in the last few weeks that have spun me out a little, I don’t know wether it's the ugly weather, the atmosphere of Sydney in winter, the air, the time or god knows what, something has happened and im loosing my head, yet again, it's so much harder now, that I have someone, that someone is what I have always thought would cure me from this insane, pathetic negative lifestyle. What is the cure for happiness for you? Is it love, money, power or success? Witch one of these things makes you happy, none of them seem to make me happy for a full working week, something is wrong, and yes I am Ashamed to say this, and it may or may not seem like a total load of mind games-bull crap to leech guilt and pity in and out of you, But it's not, I simply speak my mind, and to me that is a very, very complex mind, I cannot understand why I do the things I do.  Of all the deadlines and work I have to do, as I had been rotting away in this room for days, I cannot seem to push any ideas for the work, all I can seem to do Is express myself through art, from very hard drawings to some digital photography, to writing babbled words. I speak direct from my mind, and from the heart I don’t know I have not looked far enough into there to see what comes out, but whatever happens, whatever words I say, I know that at the end of the week, on that bright sunny Sunday I alway know that I will be what I want, because I have not spent all these years dreaming of things to come, only to wake up all over again, so wether I manage to get over this mental and emotional barrier alone or together alone, I will do it, because I see myself being there, every time, and this second I decide to take it bit by bit, by saying what has been said before by many people before me " I will not Die Today"
     
    
</post>

<date>12,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Been a while since I last posted something "straight from the heart" here, Lately I have been geting a few hits from numerous websites, witch is always good, but anyhow, Im feeling like shit again, WAHOO what a big fucking surprise hey? Youd think being in love with someone would make everything seem good, well no I cant seem to get rid of my depression, I had another little freakin panic attack yesterday, Carly seemed so happy today, so I didnt even bring it up, to top it off I was sick for some reason, I hate throwing up, but then again who the hell loves it? my throat is sore, that should keep my mouth shut... and working on some lame website design for my college. What else? hmm yup,  I finnaly updated the digital art section with all the recent artworks I have done, including "Mind Games 9", witch I know some ppl have been asking for, Ok I think after going to bed at 4am everyday this week I will make a change go now while I still feel normal, til next time good night, or something along those lines.
     
    
</post>

<date>07,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been slowly adding alot of content to this site, and doing alot of photography,  urlLink Chek out the section , and also added a Guestbook in the Info section, and a new cover and in FLASH ! yes I have been playing with flash, hmm what else, it's my girlfriend Carly's birthday this Friday and until then I will simply be working on my brand spankin new college assigments, Its beena few days without me dad, he left to work overseas and Me and my mum have to take care of the Vending Machine buisness. hmm thats going to be a bit hard, but hell if my dad did that and kept his job..im sure I can do it, and I got the Car too Weeeeeeeeee
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, Well well...yet another design, and with another design, comes a new attitude a new anti-style look and new content..kind of =/. and It's been a while since I last wrote a decent entry on this thing, It's beena hectic few weeks and it's not about to get any better soon, but everything will be ok, or half ok, Im off back to working on my stuff, I will update this darn journal tonight...
     
    
</post>

<date>22,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      im running out of time to do my college work before I leave sydney, and what do I do...go out !..it was a friends 21'st I got really, badly drunk, ended up trying to calm down some boxer, lost my mobile phone, embarrassed myself and did all that shit everybody loves to do, Then I came home had a breakdown and told my mother everything thats been happneing with me for the last 5 years, from girls, to drugs, to drinking..to everything, I just woke up about 30 minutes ago, I cant face people right now, im suposse to meet Carly for lunch to say goodbye, before I leave...I doubt that will be happening, I feel like total and absolute shit, to top it off, I have never been this broke before, my credit will go to literaly zero in the next week or so, I probably wont write here anymore, maybe Things will be better who knows, who cares, I have no tolerance or time for this site or the internet right now, Im out.
     
    
</post>

<date>21,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      an email from some guy  "Oh, apologies, I was thrown aloft by your absolute inability to form a sentence and use proper grammar."  and  "You called someone (of much higher intelligence) a total idiot yet, in that sentence, you couldn't even properly spell "total".  Pathetic"  Well I dont get you people if you rather act like a freakin english teacher then pay attention to the message then do that, please keep em coming.
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Another long awaited...post, my journal, my home to my thoughts...to often have I taken advantage of it. and raped it with useless words of philosophy, hatred, guilt, negativity and in some cases, sheer happiness, today this is either one of them or all of them, My hair is starting to look afro and growing into my ears, I haven’t shaved for almost 2 weeks, I just don’t care...all over again I repeat these words...I’m starting to realise every journal entry here sounds as if I’m narrating my life story.. Oh well I jump online to type here because I hit rock bottom of depression, and I use it as a replacement for sleeping pills or alcohol, So many time I explained the feelings of atmosphere. And fuck all that, I cant seem to find a good one that lasts for more then a few hours, I don’t want to blame my dad for leaving Australia or blame my girlfriend or even my friends for feeling like shit, but sometimes I do...although I guess that’s normal to react this way...I guess the people I rely on...are just. Well so focused on my life...when they go away or show a little frustration towards me...i react very sensitve or depressive. Is it selfish of me to think negative about life, because I never get my way? Hopefully there’s someone out there who is so addicted to unhappiness...as me.  so many times we hear about depression, different names, different cures...different ages and reasons...well I’m tired of coming up with reason. I simply cannot have the energy to create or smile about anything. Thrown in a family.. Nope still not happy...throw in a beautiful girl that loves you...nope still not happy...throw in a shit load of friends who constantly support you. Nothing...how bout some skill...no we don’t want that.  That’s right. Lost confused...how much longer can I say "Im young and stupid" is 15 young, 21?..or maybe 30?..Tell me, id like to know what is the age...i grow out of this negativity...and why oh why wont it go away. I want to be 15 again.. As usual. Good night. 
     
    
</post>

<date>20,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      it's bad enough some idiot took my old domain name ( urlLink dekonstrukted.com ) but did he have to  urlLink RIP my work ? and also riped another old  urlLink dekon cover done by   .  urlLink Eric Carl , this guy is a tottal IDIOT !
     
    
</post>

<date>18,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink ONE   for you and  urlLink TWO  for us.  urlLink She   knows what I mean by this action ;)..thinkin of ya babe
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      look I dont know how long this has been up but  urlLink my college has a new website , the design is kinda crap..but the content is all there !
     
    
</post>

<date>17,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      the feeling you get just before you go to bed... the one that rushes through your body..and makes you frown as if that frown was made to be there, the feeling that your legs are abotu to colapse and your body will give up, when your think..and think..and you automaticly look for the next closest thing that makes you happy or that you remember from childhood, you go to your computer, because it's your life...you live on the internet, the poeple you know, the people you met, the work you do, the thoughts you write..it's all in the computer...it just doesnt happen..these feelings of hoplesness come down on you as if a ghost just entered your body, how many times do I have to go thruogh this? im almost 21, I should be over this by now, 15 no more...18 never again Grow Up Luis !... Shut down, is the next step...the wuiet sound of nothing is the next big part...after hearing the PC fan...and Mp3 playing for the last 12 hours..It seems weird..the tears stop for one second...you look around, the posters, the artwork, half my life around this room, half my thoughts in front of me. After I get over the quiet sound of Air.. I colapse in my bed..one more time..we go through the process of being like hell is in my head, one more sleepless night, perhaps not, because at least these days I dont need to wonder and pray for the love and freedom I have now. This at least allows me to sleep, This week I was looked down form some people I know because through their eyes i have everythign they dont, the girl, the family, the roof...but fair enough, It's not a matter of "look at the things you have and not what you dont have" I cannot help the way I am..nor change it in the snap, I Am addicted to unhappiness, I admit, more people have suffred alot more...but doesnt mean I cannot open my mouth..and let my feelings out, and have my own rants abotu life and people and society and what not, I have just as much right to do that as you, whoever you are. So yes This crazy depression stil pop's up these days, I cannot get the motivation I had in the past years, no more swimming, no more capoeira, I cant even get myself to draw or make any form of art or nothing,..just eat, sleep and do college work. So Hopefully this crazy summer the sun might put me back into square one..until then Il just do what im doing, and be there for the people that need me..as they they are there for me..good night
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      a quote from Justin Fox of AustralianINfront.com.au    "15.9.01- This is a note to say: PLEASE stop sending us emails which are asking us to plug URL's which point to funky, glorified flash splash pages of the NYC event. Personally I think the designers doing this are being disrespectful and sick in the head.- posted by Justin Fox 15.9.01"   I agree, almost every site I have been to lately has had some kind of graphic related to this, a tribute is ok but some people are going overboard with dedications simply so they can get attention, Some ppl... I know just take advantage of the "emotion" thats going on, but remember its not in your house it's in the center of NYC so some respect would be nice, but hey who am I to talk, im one of you, im not a new yorker, I simply agree with that statement Justin said, not that anyone has sent me anything =D.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      I dont know whats going on...SHIT the world sux, its that time to drop your confidence and so forth..blah blah...i might take this site down.. the shit jsut aint doing it for me right now....GoodBye
     
    
</post>

<date>13,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      New content, I added a new addition to the Photography section, the model is my friend Alex Baker. He is going through some bad shit and havinga rought break up, and I had an attempt at capturing the diffrent emotions he had with my shitty little Digital Camera, with some help from Mr Photoshop.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      This is crazy, there have been so many discussions all over the world, about, how it's not right to blame the middle east, and I agree, but dont tottaly think that will be a NO, I mean there have been people singing in the street and burning american flags and shooting bullets of joy, so wether they did it or not, dont say there are saints floating around there. Anyway, im not here to take sides, be racist or defend good old american freedom, I am a Portugese/Australian and proud of it, I cannot belive Grown men, ADULT's will create a war in this time, in this year, so we have heard all the NOSTRADAMUS shit and seen al lthe videos of the buildings burning, but, damm, there has got to be more to this then meets the eye, im sure they could have foun some info about those planes... Aw well My brains are fried thinking about it, if your my age, you may feel like you missed out on revolutions like your fathers have in their time...and makes you think this time SUX, well, I remember watching the gulf war, wen i arrived to australia, I went through watching the East Timor massacre's and al lthose good old american high school shootings, so, let's not say this is has been a booring time without revolution and big headlines, cause this is big, now it's time to take out hats down and bow down our necks in thought of all those people, and get through this time...I say this, because I have a feeling that there is alot more to come, this Attack seems huge, but very unfinished, I dont know....back to Instant messenger to chat..and siping my coffe.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
        "In the City of God there will be a great thunder, two brothers torn apart by Chaos, while the fortress endures, the great leader will succumb"  "The third big war will begin when the big city is burning"    - Nostradamus 1654!   Today I realised why there's so much suicide in people's minds, this is SHOCK, and HORROR, there's not one person right now who does not know anything about what hapend, in the last 30 hours or so, I was online late night when this happned, and it was morning over in NY, and half the internet was overloaded, when I got visoins of what hapned and stayed up til 2am watching the news, I ran out of words to say... maybe in a little while.
     
    
</post>

<date>09,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      im not trying to sound corny by any means, but if I close my eyes take a spin on my desk chair, and stop, I can still smell her, internally, im feeling chaotic all over again, externally my body has given up, so very tired, a nap would be good now, I come back later, I have one big ass rant and discussion to write and post soon, maybe tonight or tomrow, ...Way too tired to do it now.
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      thanks Cutie for updating my journal...and the kind words ;), that was posted last night, before we left to a fancy dress party, it was fun..kinda strange and i didnt really like it, simply because i felt like I was ina singles party with my girlfriend, it seems to me, in this world wen your a couple you have to only hang out with couples...it's like two worlds clash...maybe im paranoid, maybe..who cares, i havent slept much in 2 days, Cutie's in bed, im here doing my college work, and scratching my eyes, ready to scream... I feel hungover, good afternoon, bye
     
    
</post>

<date>08,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was one of the first days that had physical effects to show that summer is really comin soon.....it's about time. This is Carly, an I'm taking it upon myself to update Luis's journal today. Still thinking of what needs to be said....or what just feels like being. Luis is making his bed. The Beatles are playing somewhere in my ear. Takes you back. Even if you didn't exist. I can't really update anything as such from the week...because I don't really know what's been going on, so I'll just stay off that....and keep to something I know. Get back to where we wanna go. I feel weird in this room. I haven't worked out yet whether good or bad. But i think i've spent more time in here than my own room....so it feels a little more natural to be in here. I know you...you know me....one thing i can tell you is you got to be free.....come together....right now. Too many wandering thoughts. I apoligise for the lack of style that Luis usually contructs through his own journal entries, can't say my mind is actually that organised to think...let alone write like that. And when the night is cloudy, there is still a light that shines on me. I wonder when these nights are going to hurry up and get longer. Summer is an odd feeling. But so is darkness. Whisper words of wisdom. I feel like Hershey's. Maybe I could sit here and plug Luis' artwork, heh. But it's not here for that. Trend setter. Fashion Star. Commersialised ego-mania. Nah. The thing I love most about his work, is that most (if not all of it), is created apon pure emotion. Not one from a thing of the era. Every piece from his heart or a feeling in his head.... Hello Goodbye....time is passing and so am I......must flee. This be it all for today....I be on my way....farewell...
     
    
</post>

<date>02,September,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      Miss me? I’m back, after a couple of day's at C's house, my brother had a dam party and I had planned a good few days over here, but dang was it still fun, whilst I’m going to be here sipping back on my Crownie beer, and doing some small work for college and talking to my bud Kim, I thought I'd post something, the good "atmosphere" is changing, If you read my journal often "god forbid" you’ll know that I often talk about "atmosphere" and what I mean by that, is the certain mood or weather or feeling you get from the current time, its the odour in the air, the time the sun comes down, the content on TV, every little details that makes you describe in the back of your mind what kind of day or time it is, and to me i notice this once in a while, today is one of those days, I’m kind of scared, don’t know if its a good feeling, but all I can right now is  I MISS SUMMER !,  the Australian summer, where I go to  urlLink Bondi   urlLink Beach  a few times a week in the holidays, play and/or watch some  urlLink Capoeira , have an ice cream and go out on the town, without worrying about taking a jacket, the day's will be longer, the nights will be allot stickier ;) the short skirts will be a coming and the singlets will be arriving, summer in Sydney is the only thing I really adore about Sydney at the moment, and dam it we are getting close !!, hmm, I’m off to eat my 3rd dinner today, later peeps. ooh one more thing, I missed  urlLink Fathers'Day  yesterday, he is working in NZ right now =// so until I get a chance to call him, I'l just post something here to make up for it, he's a great man, that has lived a great life, and has been a good father during all of it, congrats =D
     
    
</post>

<date>05,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      if theres one thing i keep learning is...that you cant please everyone...
     
    
</post>

<date>03,October,2001</date>
<post>

	 
      as the raging pain of feeling my shoulder blade practicly falling off from days of unconfortable sleep keep pinning at me, so do the thoughts of all things gone wrong, we allways expect the worst from life, with the expectation a miricale will happen and the opposite will rise. as your sitting there complaining about how I cant type (spell) to save me, I sit here with a frown, and baggy eye bags, doing nothing but pondering on what could have been, and what should have been, for the past week I have been away from the internet, from practicly all my life, even away from the state, I was in a whole new place, with some friends, and I wont go into the exact holiday right now, but It was a pretty harsh experience, one that I havent had in a while anyway, I noticed how much of an attached lifestyle I have had created here in sydney, from girlfriend to college life, It's all good I missed everything as much as the next, It's not like it was one of them life changing holidays, because it wasnt, but spending some time away from things right now, was a good idea..and helped me put things into perspective a little more, im trying so hard to help and support the people around me at the moment rather then focus onn my idiotic worries, but it's becoming a strain when people refuse to accept your help as shut you out, how many times do you keep on knoking on that door until that person leaves it open long enough to see you smile at them?
     
    
</post>

<date>31,January,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I am back. It's been Awhile.
     
    
</post>

<date>29,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I have decided ...that i will stop sucking up for now.. I realised i dont really want a full time graphic design position that bad.. the industry does suck.. but i wont accuse everyone of being an idiot... I just feel like I have alot to do..working on posters and selling them online.. getting my magazine out on the streets from concept to reality.. things have to happen the way i dream them to be .. i want them to..and they will.. i have many things to do and projects to start on. So get stuffed all your arrogant employers.. and shove your '5 years or more experience' up where the sun dont shine.. im gona take over and be your competitor.  btw... one external link for today..  urlLink Bill Gates !!  you would think that his guy being so fucking rich..he could afford a decent designer to work on this official biography site.. unbeleivable. The corporate world is so pathetic. Back to youth culture..and honest work I go.. im tired of this.. dont ask me to do a logo again.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to my new folio website.. here I will showcase most of my recent work, plus older college work. Reason = to get more work, and show off. the Multimedia, Illustration and Profile sections are still to come in the next couple of days.
     
    
</post>

<date>28,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.sun.com/950801/columns/MaryMorris.col9508.html  Now thats an article! im going to hold this baby for a while !! anyone that considers themselves to be a web designer  (possibly 95% of the freakin world population) *do not hold me to that sarcastic percentage ;)  should read this.  Also I would formely like to apologize for the logo system and small-type kind of design, I was running very low on inpiration and became very driven and motivated by other websites, I dont usually do this, but it happnes to the best of us designer-types, anyhow this site will soon be called LAD Media, I am currently enrolled in a small business managment course and at the same time trying to edit a magazine, so you wont hear or see much of my stuff besides the new LAD Media site im working on, and I really am trying to finish it and put it up ASAP, I plan to post more news and dicuss more issues via this journal slash news box thingamibob.  
     
    
</post>

<date>05,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "We're all Christ and we're all Hitler. We are trying to make Christ's message contemporary. We want Christ to win. What would he have done if he had advertisements, T.V., records, films and newspapers? The miracle today is communication. So let's use it." -John Lennon '69
     
    
</post>

<date>28,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I was part of a cool exhibition last night i got some photos, Knot galelry is one hell of a cool place  urlLink chek them out 
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      its that time again.. , finished my course.. i been having good days.. starting to make art again, be expecting more stuff very soon.
     
    
</post>

<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      if your looking for my other crazier non-corporate-kind-of stuff go to  urlLink EMPTYROOM  
     
    
</post>

<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      only an hour before sunrise, what do you do?
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      when your a sad french song away from tears, remember your past not your present, smile and go to sleep, you need it... for tomorrow is another day.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      pain is something we want in secret to create a big opening for our hapiness, a big entrance for that big fucking grin of sucess.
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      we need not look in the mirror ..but rather close our eyes and look inside our mind
     
    
</post>

<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      nice, blunt and simple...new site ! ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a big weekend, and I usually would come around and complain and analyze it, but those were the old days, I promised a public site for TINT would come soon and it will. alot more things coming to this site, thanks for all the support from you the visitors and chronic emailers heh.
     
    
</post>

<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      A few things have hapened, I had one of my entries made it to the Australian INfront Visual Response comp, witch was displayed in the recent DIGIT expo and confrence held in sydney (pics soon)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      hey all, Im currently working TINT its a magazine for creative people, becomeing a lengthy task, probably wont be ready to distribute til late november or dec. Im also working with my friend Keith to release the next installed of  urlLink RASTER  and tomorrow morning im heading off to  urlLink DIGIT  , should be a good expo, i will take pics and write more on it later.
     
    
</post>

<date>22,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      new print titled 'breathe' with a cheaper price that wont last long. New shoping cart system, more to come.
     
    
</post>

<date>16,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://cgi.ebay.com.au/ws/eBayISAPI.dll?ViewItem&item=922655067   Also i put up 2 new artworks of the same caliber "Coporate Pig" up for sale. cheaper price ordering from eBay if your in Australia
     
    
</post>

<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ok people if you havent already noticed on the new main page, that im selling prints of some of my work, the Silence² peice is something i did especially for this website, i will only be printing a few of them, all will be numbered in order and signed, for authenticity, I will have more prints soon and if you wish to have any of my other work printed feel free to make a request, by dropping me an email, if you support me, my site and or like my art please help buy purchasing this print, its a good quality print and will look nicely on your wall ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
           Disorder      Rating        urlLink Paranoid :    Very High       urlLink Schizoid :    Moderate       urlLink Schizotypal :    Very High       urlLink Antisocial :    Moderate       urlLink Borderline :    Moderate       urlLink Histrionic :    High       urlLink Narcissistic :    High       urlLink Avoidant :    Very High       urlLink Dependent :    High       urlLink Obsessive-Compulsive :    High       --  urlLink Click Here To Take The Test  --      
     
    
</post>

<date>17,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink www.sarakula.com  has been launched be sure to purchase the album and/or listen tot he sample tracks on the website.
     
    
</post>

<date>12,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      for the last few weeks I have been working on a cd cover for a fantastic local band called Sarakula if your in sydney, drop down to Bar Broadway for the launch, also keep an eye out for the website, and if you go to the Online store on this website, you can purchase a Sarakula poster for only $10USD! I am also making the prints a little special, if you buy 2 or more I will send you another free one of your choice, I should also mention that if you would like any of my art or designs on this website, you may request it, just send me an  urlLink email   And now for the venue details...  'Mystery Morning' Album Launch! 8.00pm, Thursday the 19th of December Bar Broadway - cnr Regent st and Broadway, Central $5 door charge   urlLink www.sarakula.com   
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I really love designers who can make work like this...  urlLink 'In Design We Trust' 
     
    
</post>

<date>11,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      something external today, im announcing my favourite websites, or websites of favourtive people or places *drum roll*  urlLink Graphic Havoc - A Visual Agency  /  urlLink Neasden Control Centre  /  urlLink Fthr productions  /  urlLink Test Pilot Collective  /  urlLink Ra's page 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Been a while, i had a huge bloody day today for the past few days.. firstly I been doing driving lessons to finally get my dam licence (6years late) and on Friday I went to my old college exhibition, I was happy with the print work, talked to some old lecturers, bad night tho after my old lecturer/owner-of-the-college got really pissed as hell and i was talking to him he said" you wanna be a fucking magazine guy.. Be a fucking magazine.. Don’t be a wimp...etc..etc" u get the picture shouted in front of all my friends and students and teachers as if to be preaching to me and telling me I’m a looser, embarrassed the crap out of me.. so i will actually take his advice and get the mag done and deliver it to his door personally with a big "HOWSYA GOIN". Support IS a little hard to find these days, people are become very selfish and absorbed by the almighty $   I been staying with my girlfriend rehearsing for a abstract play, a small theatre in Cronulla beach, Sydney, i was filling in for someone, i couldn’t remember my lines it was horrible but we managed to do it, i met some really cool people and im also thinking of doing this a weekend hobby, its so nerve-racking but it helps to rid of fears and makes me happy and its so dam fun, anyhow i was playing Kenikie from Grease, we just did a small section of it to end the show that was put on by the regular students of this theatre anyhow i can go home happy tonight. And let the wine and sugar sit in my stomach for a while.  In other news i got  urlLink www.tintmagazine.com  up, but you need to have a login to view the temp page, i will be publishing a public page soon, so keep it bookmarked YAL, TINT magazine is getting done. 
     
    
</post>

<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Current projects + BFS Illustration and website + Drifted, Products and Merchendise + Parktrent Concept website 
     
    
</post>

<date>19,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Current projects + Abnormis - Hosting Solutions + Raster V4 + Drifted, Products and Merchendise + Katrien, the band (Art Direction) + Parktrent Hurstville website and promos. + Tint Magazine (Editor, Art Director)
     
    
</post>

<date>07,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      new URL, new DESIGN, new TIME, new WORK..just go here   urlLink www.luisaraujo.com   
     
    
</post>

<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahh, 1 hour left to home time at work, servers are all down, I've done my ebaying, emailing, chatting, napping, eating, and every other freakkin ING you can possibly do while stuck in an office.  Feels good coming towards the end of it. However I have something else on my mind this afternoon. Its just that moment when you get a burst of confidence for no reason, you think back to your hopes, dreams and all other bullshit you have wanted to do throughout life, and you think hey maybe I could do it, its never too late, Now before I begin to sound like Anthony Robbins (god help us all, the fucking asshole makes people tell the world they cannot live without a set of his CD's..Give me a break!)..So back to it. It's never too late!  I had dreams of publishing a magazine, of owning that sentimental slash materialistic item like a 1991 Celica or X-men Issue 1..Whatever suits you best friends! And, yeah I kind of lost my chain of thought.. Ah well I was going to go on about being confident, and getting what you want..blah blah, I have been thinking of making next year the "big" change year, although I have said it in that respect thousands of times, such as many other people have as well, I have never thought about my life this far ahead, next year is months and months away..And IM sitting here thinking something like "ok, I've fucked up enough times, I've procrastinated enough times, I've done too much enough times to not go for gold!, how do I do this right?" then I find myself walking around or driving around..Subconsciously thinking and planning on what IM going to do in the longterm,... Something not many 23 year olds do I gather!.  and it makes me feel good, because I can actually imagine myself doing certain things I want or wanted to do, whereas before it was just me trying to convince myself I could.. When you grow up your parents give you encouragement to keep playing that electric guitar..Its like that.. You don't know you can do it..You just hope you can...A fools hope.  But is this confident feeling real? Is it true? I hope so..But in my short experience nothing is definate.. Only close to it.  IT brings me to my main point.. Its a midi-life crisis, before being middle aged..And after becoming a teenager..It could happen between 25 and 35.. and its actually more like a hangover from the pre-midi-life-crisis (boy that will get a laugh), Its a hangover from what? Responsibility, after you finish partying, spending money, sleeping around, doing all the crazy post-teenager shit, you get to a point where you start get used to working, and you realize that there is a tone of responsibilities in the world, from bills, to family to health. Things in life you were only vaguely aware of become more visible! And this causes young people to perhaps get burned out and just freak out, they perhaps go overseas to see if the feeling fades or just sit there and rot until they begin to develop a beer gut.  so after you get fed up of having this hangover and realize you have to do something, you tend to see things in a different light..And that's where the midi-life crisis comes about, jokes between friends and loved ones start to become rare, you find yourself spending more time thinking ahead or perhaps just sleeping..So the day can go quicker (it generates a feeling that all payments and problems might be gone sooner..Or before you Die)  now that might just be me with too much caffeine or maybe IM just a freakin nutcase, however it is written and sense is to be made out of at least 5% of that..So until next time.. Goodbye
     
    
</post>

<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have found a new comfort, it's taken me a few weeks to work up the energy to start making art, this is no masterpiece, but considering I used, wet used tissues with spit, old whiteboard markers and crusty old color pencils, its not so bad, originally I had just a few words and that big blue strip of paint, in recent months/years basquiat has been a major inspiration, so that might be slightly noticeable, hence me showcasing my guilt by calling myself "copycat" this is only a sign of perhaps a new start in artmaking from me, I don't know.. nuff talk.   
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IM trying to get used to blogging again, I need to just write and let it all out, I have been living in my head for far too long and I suppose this is a start, I don't care how many people come here, I don't have a site tracker, this isn't even public yet, it just feels good to talk and imagine people reading your thoughts, it's almost like selling yourself to the world and saying "HEY WHAT DO U THINK?!! U LIKE ME AM I AN ORIGINAL MEMBER OF SOCIETY OR WHAT?" but only on some fucked up levels I guess.  I am home from work and feeling so tired, for no good reason really, my life is mostly work and projects around design and artmaking, so I will be talking a lot about that, and there will be the occasional "Oh I FEEL SO SAD, PITY ME" attitude, we all cant avoid those at certain times, depending on the weather.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         one of many unfinished paintings from the last 12 months.. im struggling to find what kind of direction i want..techincally, in order to show what i want to create in terms of visual impact.
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A lot of the older posts, you might find seem somewhat immature, and well stupid! But that's the progression we go through I guess. IM not ashamed to show them, there are many I posted while being slightly under the influence ;)
     
    
</post>

<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have dragged this blogg, through over 10 websites, from corporate portfolios, personal webpages to just simple news updates notifications, over 100 posts of random and just plain crap, im back for more!!  I have missed blogging, after judging the culture as i do when everything becomes popular, i decided i like it, i cant read too many bloggs , because im lazy and busy, but i like to talk and jsut type what i feel and what i think, it makes me feel good, so this is a rusty first post/introduction, but eventually i will begin again. so listen if you will, if not dont come back..simple rule.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>