<Blog>

<date>30,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Another day another post. Anyone else really want to get gmail? 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Welcome to ropadope. 
    
    
</post>

<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       3 nights in a hotel room with the kids. More on Tuesday -- if I make it. 
    
    
</post>

<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Played hockey on the Olympic-sized rink at Bloomingotn Ice Gardens last night until about 12:40AM this morning. That's a big ice sheet -- the same one the 1980 Olympic Team practiced on. It was cool, especially with the storm outside lighting up the sky.  I'm going to play every Wednesday night with these guys. Two times a week is perfect.  P.S. My gloves are so stinky.  
    
    
</post>

<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Am I supposed to be worried about the latest terrorism threat? They issue it, but they do nothing to the threat level (that assinine color code system). What the hell is going on up at the ol' White House? It just keeps getting more and more absurd. 
    
    
</post>

<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Asher better start sleeping soon or both Ang and I are going to perish. 
    
    
</post>

<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://johnkerryisadouchebagbutimvotingforhimanyway.com  
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Must sleep. Asher still is not sleeping through the night... not even close. I'm not getting up with him but the screaming is a pain in the ass. 
    
    
</post>

<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Poker today. Lost $8.15. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Rain, rain, rain... playing open hockey this morning and then Poker with the Kid, Misgen and Scott this afternoon. After almost no sleep, I'll be hitting the sack early. 
    
    
</post>

<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Spent the day in the yard planting and doing a few patches in the driveway. Tired as hell.  OH! And Ang and I decided that taking all three kids to Shrek 2 was a dandy idea. HELL. I ended up taking kids #2 & #3 home after about 20 minutes. NEVER AGAIN. New rule -- none of our kids goes to a movie until they're 3 years old. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Not a great game last night. Oh well. Maybe Sunday will be better.  I think we'll all go and see Shrek 2 today. 
    
    
</post>

<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Timberwolves against the Lakers at the Target Center tonight. I went to games 7 against the Kings and it was amazing. I think the Wolves have a chance if Cassell can make it through the series. Back spasms are no fun.  Asher is screaming. Argh. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Two Words: Who gives a shit?   LOS ANGELES (AP) - "As Good As It Gets" actress Helen Hunt has something that makes life even better: a new baby girl.  Hunt, who won an Oscar for that movie, gave birth to the child in Beverly Hills, publicist Stephen Huvane told The Associated Press Friday.  Makena' lei Gordon Carnahan, born May 13, and her mom are both healthy, Huvane said. The father is Hunt's companion, Matthew Carnahan, who produced the TV series "Fastlane."  The baby's first name comes from a town in Maui, Hawaii, and her middle name is from Hunt's father, TV director Gordon Hunt. She arrived several weeks early, weighing about 6 pounds.  This is the second child for Carnahan and the first for the 40-year-old Hunt, who previously was married to Hank Azaria, who voices several characters on "The Simpsons."  Hunt, former co-star of the sitcom "Mad About You," hasn't appeared in a movie since 2001's "The Curse of the Jade Scorpion." She'll be in two upcoming films: the Oscar Wilde adaptation "A Good Woman" with Scarlett Johansson, and the HBO movie "Empire Falls," based on the Pulitzer Prize-winning novel by Richard Russo, which co-stars Ed Harris and Paul Newman.    
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       What does everyone think about this  urlLink Andy Kaufmann deal?  
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So this expanded child-tax credit... This pretty much just reduces what I get back in April right? Not sure whether I like it or not. 
    
    
</post>

<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Been staying up waaaaaay too late lately. Must sleep. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Keanu and Alan Cumming married? Wackiness. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       orkut is pretty cool. lemme know if you want in. 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The keyboard shortcuts on gmail are extraordinary. Very nice work guys! 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I need a new cell phone plan in the Twin Cities. Who should I use? 
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Stewart is a genius.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (via TechTV Screesavers)									  									Had  Ponce de Leon  actually found the fountain of youth, I know how he would have felt.   Vindicated! Rejuvenated! All-powerful! Which is exactly how I felt after I upgraded my 40-hour ReplayTV unit to a 250-hour ReplayTV unit.  Now you may be saying, "Opening my ReplayTV sounds difficult and a bit intimidating." Or maybe, "I'm not sure I'm up to the task."    Put those thoughts out of your head! If you took a shower this morning, you've done something more difficult than upgrading your ReplayTV's hard drive. If you know how to walk, you have the skills to upgrade your ReplayTV hard drive. It's so easy that if breathing wasn't involuntary, upgrading your ReplayTV HD would be easier.   OK, so I'm engaging in a bit of  hyperbole  for dramatic effect. But it did only take me 20 minutes.   DIY savings  Let's take a look at how much moolah and/or cashola you can save by buying the smallest capacity ReplayTV unit and upgrading it to a 160-hour unit by yourself.     A 160-hour ReplayTV unit  costs about $450. A 40-hour ReplayTV unit costs about $117. A 160GB hard drive (1GB = 1 hour at standard quality) costs about $150. The total cost of a DIY 160-hour ReplayTV unit is about $267.   The difference between the retail and upgraded ReplayTV units is about $184. In other words, that's what you can save!   Choosing a hard drive  Obviously, the first step is to buy a new hard drive. People have upgraded their single-drive ReplayTV units to dual-drive units, but I don't recommend it.     Drive capacity   Below are the approximate ratios of recording-time to file-size.  Keep them in mind when you're selecting the size of your hard drive.     Standard quality: This is the recording time advertised on the box and in stores, and one hour translates to about 1GB. Medium quality: This is the quality setting I use. One hour translates to 2GB, so a 160GB drive equals 80 hours of recording time. High quality: This is the most storage-consuming setting, as 1 hour takes up 3GB of drive space. A 160GB drive will hold 53 hours of recording time.    Drive speed   ReplayTV units act  really  funky if they get too hot. 7,200 rpm drives run hotter than 5,400 rpm drives, and the standard drive in a ReplayTV unit is 5,400 rpm.    While many people have had luck using 7,200 rpm drives and some have reported performance increases, unless your ReplayTV unit is in a well-ventilated area (and you're brave), I recommend sticking with 5,400 rpm drives.   Drive brands   People use many brands to upgrade their ReplayTV hard drive, but most have success with  Maxtor  drives. After all, Maxtor manufactures the hard drives for your ReplayTV unit.   When I asked for a 250GB HD, Maxtor sent me one from its  Quickview  line, which is designed for audio/video streaming. According to Maxtor, these drives employ a 2MB modified-caching scheme, specialized seek profiles, and large block-transfers that are optimized for streaming media. In other words, these drives are custom-designed for PVRs, so they're the best bet for your upgrading needs.  I've only found one place that sells Quickview drives online, and that's  WeaKnees.com .  If you want to skip the fun of doing it yourself, you can also buy a  readymade drive kit  for a few dollars more.     Beefing up your unit      System Requirements   You must be running Windows XP/2000/NT, Linux, a Win9x boot disk, or a Linux boot disk.   Software   You'll need a program called RTVPatch, which you can  download here    The How-To   I could tell you how to do it, but the  perfect  tutorial already exists on  the RTVPatch site  Follow the page's detailed instructions to the letter!  If you run into problems, refer to  this FAQ page  as needed.   There isn't much else to say -- except this again: Follow the eight steps on the RTVPatch site, and don't stray!       That's all folks!   You now have many more hours of precious recording time available! I've never felt so powerful in all my life! I could bench-press a freight train! I could rule the world! (OK, I am again engaging in hyperbole for dramatic effect.)   Enjoy your bigger, badder ReplayTV!    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Your trainwreck is showing.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    LyndiLyndiLyndiLou.&nbsp; urlLink    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       NEW YORK (AP) - Photos of two American soldiers posing with thumbs up near a body packed in ice at Iraq's Abu Ghraib prison were shown on ABC-TV.  The photos showed Army Sgt. Charles A. Graner Jr. and Spc. Sabrina Harman, both of whom have already been charged in the prisoner abuse scandal.  They also were shown Thursday on the Arabic TV station Al-Arabiya.  The detainee, whose badly bruised corpse was in a body bag packed with ice, died in the prison's showers while being interrogurated by the CIA or other civilian agents, ABC reported Wednesday. It said the Justice Department is investigating the death.  In an account published Monday, the Los Angeles Times reported that the victim had been brought to the prison with his head covered by an empty sandbag. It said he died in the midst of intensive questioning in the shower by military intelligence officials. After he collapsed, the interrogators removed the bag and then saw severe head wounds that had not been treated.  Calls by The Associated Press Thursday to Graner's lawyer, Guy Womack of Houston, and to Harman's attorney, Frank Spinner of Colorado Springs, Colo., were not immediately returned.  Womack told ABC News the photo of his client represented inappropriate "gallows humor."    
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       BAGHDAD, Iraq (AP) - A U.S. air strike near the Syrian border killed more than 40 people, Iraqi officials said, and while the U.S. military said the target was a suspected safehouse for foreign fighters from Syria, Iraqis said a helicopter had attacked a wedding party.  The attack Wednesday happened about 2:45 a.m. in a desert region near the border with Syria and Jordan, according to Lt. Col. Ziyad al-Jbouri, deputy police chief of Ramadi, the provincial capital about 250 miles to the east. He said 42 to 45 people died, including 15 children and 10 women. Dr. Salah al-Ani, who works at a hospital in Ramadi, put the death toll at 45.  The strike came before American soldiers clashed Wednesday with Shiite militiamen in two cities south of the capital, killing at least eight of them, U.S. officials said. Mortars and rockets fell on widely scattered areas of the Iraqi capital.  U.S. officials reported no American casualties during engagements in the Shiite holy cities of Karbala and Najaf. But assailants with hand grenades killed a U.S. soldier and wounded three in central Baghdad early Thursday, the military said.   
    
    
</post>

<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Another post. Another post. Another post. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Blogger rules. 've tred emulatng t... Stupd "ii" ey. and "k". 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       just finished mowing the lawn... right before the rain hits. Nice out. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Busting my ass here fighting fires at work. I need to mow the lawn. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The google mail swap site is going nuts. I think we have a winner. 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm going to game 7 of the Timberwolves/Kings series tonight. A nice surprise indeed! 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yea! I got a gmail account. You can reach me at ropadopeNOSPAM@Evergmail.com (you'll need to de-spam that address to avoid bouncebacks). 
    
    
</post>

<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Think I'll get some dinner on the patio of W.A. Frost tonight.  Yum. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yet another post. Whis one has a few more words in it. Likey? 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm posting more now than before. We'll see how long this lasts. 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Congratulations are in order for one of our users. Film deal for 'Baghdad blogger': "The Baghdad Blog, a book based on an online diary written by an Iraqi man about life during the conflict there, is to be made into a film." First a book, then a movie and it all started at Blogger. Nice!  
    
    
</post>

<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I finished burning some cd's today and dealt with a screaming kid all night. Fun times.  I really want a gmail account. 
    
    
</post>

<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm reading Jeffrey Eugenides' "Middlesex". Excellent book -- an epic. I can't put it down. It's like when I read his "The Virgin Suicides" only better.  I can't wait to see what happens next -- and for his next book. 
    
    
</post>

<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The ear is still screwed up. I'm going to make an appointment today if possible. Ang and I are going on a date tonight - yea! 
    
    
</post>

<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Seems the GMail invites have stopped. I've never gotten one to give out. Bummer. Anyway, the service is really great. I'm trying to come up with a plan to have all of my non-work mail forwarded to the GMail account. I've already moved over 7 years of saved messages to the system and am still under 100MB.  Very very cool. I'm going to start automating backups of sensitive info in encrypted compressed files and have them automgically emailed to the GMail account. Perpetual backups! 
    
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So after a weekend of kids and swimming in the hotel pool, I have swimmer's ear. Making it very difficult to live. 
    
    
</post>


</Blog>