<Blog>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GLORP! You will be able to view the old site updates that i was doing by hand  urlLink here  once i get this blogger working they way i want it to.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I updated  urlLink www.dmbirc.org  Its getting close to finished and it needs a lot of tweaks. I  thank everyone for my support in making that site and helping me still with errors that need to be fixed.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The blogger is now online. yay. giddy yup!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey this is much faster. yay.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink This  freaked me out when I was in 6th grade so much. I remember rewinding it over and over. Still spooks me.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      eep why is the  urlLink GURT CAM  broken? stupid gurtcam. People are bugging me to update my website. :Þ I'm just too busy with  urlLink other things . And the other things I am busy with I am lazy about. I'm sorry. I guess I am just lazy. I'll try to keep more up to date in the journal. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I took  urlLink www.dmbirc.org  offline for a bit untill it is absolutley finished. I keep finding little things that I want to change on it. Everyone that signs my guestbook rocks [except one or two but i wont name names :Þ] Thank you for taking the time to say you stoped by and what-not. Later..
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi. its February! one week till my birthday.  urlLink buy me stuff  please. :)
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       bacbad:  gurt: will you link to  urlLink dream-networks.net  on your sites?  GURT:  sure. hang on  GET HOSTED.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I won't be on  urlLink IRC  or  urlLink AIM  or any chat stuff much lately. I need to get away from my cyber palz™ for a little while. You can  urlLink e-mail  me or call me and I'll be happy to talk.   things i plan on doing while im not chating... [in no kind of order] -get a steady job. -work with Mike on the songs we've written so far. -save money. -finish filling out the financial aid stuff. -finish  urlLink dmbirc.org  so that I can pass it off to someone who can update it regularly. -work on artwork. -find out who I am.    I talked to my boss, Rob at  urlLink Saratoga Web  and he said he's got a lot of work for me to do now so hopefully this will turn into something steady.  I'm excited about that and it couldn't have happened at a better time.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a fax number now.  urlLink 707.982.1760 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The DNS stuff is finally all fixed now.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  DUSTIN DIAMOND who portrayed “SCREECH” from T.V.’s “ urlLink SAVED BY THE BELL ” has just completed his first instructional chess video. - urlLink http://www.thegamester.com/   Saved By The Bell rules.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Jim Gallagher  rules. He let me play with  urlLink glass . it was beyond fun! Thank you!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went and saw  urlLink Skrape  tonight in Albany. It was an excellent show and the band was really nice. They signed a  urlLink poster  for me. whoop.  urlLink Buy  thier CD " urlLink New Killer America ".
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I went to  urlLink Best Buy  and bought  urlLink 13 Ways To Bleed On Stage  by  urlLink Cold . It's a decent cd and only  urlLink 10 bucks . Yeah.. I know.. Scooter  urlLink sounds  like the guy from  urlLink Bush .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I went out today. I went to get my hair cut and then to work. I was not needed at work. Anyhow.. Mike and I went to the mall. I bought a  urlLink FOX  hat and matching sticker for my bass.. some  urlLink jeans  and a new small  urlLink aerobie . Hooray.    "Mary sits down by the shoreline.. she wants the ducks to be her friends.."     "I know. This time. I know this time she's gonna come around"  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi. Do not forget that tonight is the first episode of  urlLink That's My Bush!  on Comedy Central. It's on at 10:30pm EST. Check your  urlLink local listings .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know  urlLink this  is kinda old, but  urlLink Letterman  rocks. And I need an update. Thanks to  urlLink Star  and her blog for reminding me about that  urlLink top ten list .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        April Fools. Yeah.. I had messed with the site as a joke. No one got it. Oh well. I have  urlLink new shoes , and you don't. The woman that sold them to me was nice and cute.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink "DADAT DADAT DADAT!" 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What the ass?
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi. im bored. im sick. i have to work tonight. i couldn't make it in last night, i was sick. :( Laura should visit me at work tonight. you should also  urlLink e-mail me , Laura.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Jessica Simpson   shit   urlLink split her pants . I guess this isn't the first time according to  urlLink this site . I'll tell you more about it at  urlLink Nick's Things  dot com.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The host for  urlLink the guestbook  shit the bed and I lost like 4 entries. Bastards! Also, I updated the  urlLink contacts  page so that you can add me to the appropriate account by clicking on the icon and also to include my  urlLink Yahoo! Messenger  account as well as my  urlLink Jabber  account. Jabber is great. sorta. It has its ups and downs, but the interface is way better than  urlLink Trillian  in my opinion.  I need to get a hold of  urlLink Flash .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know for a fact that people visit my webpage. But the fact that is unknown is why people that visit do not sign  urlLink the guestbook . I know who you are, I have my ways of keeping track of stats. But just  urlLink sign  the fucking thing. damn it!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Sad Guys Wish    My pal  urlLink Omar  wrote and illustrated a short story titled  urlLink The Sad Guys Wish . It's a really neat short story about a sad guy and his wish. It also has some very cool cameos in it. Omar is 16 and lives in Irvine, California. For more information about him, visit  urlLink www.omargazi.com . As far as I know, Omar is still alive dispite what his web site might lead you to believe.  Also I wou'd like to take this time to say that  urlLink blogger  is a piece of crap and that I fucking hate when I got to post and it says something like "You're not cool enough to type fast enough to post in your friends web log." Fuck you Mr. Blogger.   urlLink LJ 4EVA
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am really tired of my web page. But I don't have the nuggets to mess it up like Nick does to  urlLink his . I'm even tired of the internet. As well as writing in my jounral. I need a internet enema or something. A swift Kick in the arse. Not to mention my car back on the road.  Oh yeah, I bet that  urlLink Bella Knox  will Knox Your Sox Off.  Visit her site because she's a great pal and you know you want her.  I was gonna plug some other web sites too but I forgot which.   urlLink www.leatherface.net  - This is Mikes now.  urlLink starleigh.net  - This is Mikes now too. huhuh.  Yeah.. that about does it for now.  Sleep.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I just ordered this  urlLink RioVolt SP250  from  urlLink buy.com . It's  urlLink Nick s fault!   It sure beats the pants off of any dumb  urlLink non-cd mp3 player . you know, those crap SONY ones that only hold a full album if you encode the mp3s to sound like shit. I have a ton of mp3s on CDRs. No need for Memory Stick bull shit. What a waste of money that crap is. For pennies I can store 8 or 9 albums on a cd, and I have. At least 50 times. Too bad it is on back order. Now I just have to wait for the thing to arrive..  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           urlLink This  here is reasons I decided I needed to own  urlLink Quake 3 .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am adddicted to  urlLink Freze Tag  for the  urlLink Quake 3 Arena . It's a lot fun. [On the server that I use] everyone runs around with the same weapons [The Railgun or the Gauntlet]. One hit "freezes". You have to unfreeze your team members by standing next to them for a few seconds while dodging and freezing the other color team. You also have a gappler hook thing so you can attach yourself to walls or high ceilings to snipe or pull yourself up out of bad situations [think Spider-Man] . Sure that is camping, but this is  urlLink freeze tag , not "run around and kill everyone in sight" so you' better becareful where you're running to to unfreeze a team members. I might just be hiding in the rafters waiting for your ass. ;)  I find that it's, fun, fast paced, and very addicting.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Yesterday I bought  urlLink Jack Johnson - Brushfire Fairytails . I thought it was a good purchase. It's kinda rare for me to buy a CD and enjoy every song on it. It's great mellow acoustic tunes. Ben Harper is on the CD too. I know lot's of people have been listening to this guy for a while, but how come no one told me about him untill a month ago!? d'oh! Get more info on Johnson from the  urlLink All Music Guide .  Thanks you Jill for the recomendation 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hi. I purchased this nifty poster here today. I got it from  urlLink www.obeygiant.com . It's by that  urlLink Shepard Fairey  guy. He was the origonal creator of those Andre the Giant has a posse stickers.  Some times buying things makes me feel a little bit more better. Today I also purchased a digital camera.  urlLink The Fuji FinePix 2600 Zoom Digital Camera . It will be great for taking it to shows and what not. I wish I had it Thursday night. I went to go see the band that was my favorite when I was in 8th grade.  urlLink The Spin Doctors . Go ahead and laugh. But they're such a good band that got a pretty bad rap. They got together for a "reunion" tour of 8 shows. These guys are really talented and were plagued with that rush your second album thing. The bass player, Mark is really funky. I was talking to him for a while but I was drunk so I don't remember what we talked about. Female bass players I think briefly. The guitars are really bluesy. The drummer rocks and vocals are good. They might not have done anyhting too special. But you know you like them. You know you do. I got ahold of thier  urlLink set list  and also had them sign my CD. The camera would have been great to have that night. Oh well.   So there you have it.  Another update.  See you next month. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        My guestbook died. I'm pretty pissed about that. A lot of those comments were great. A lot of people signed it. Some people from High School and other random people. And Jill. I would have never found Jill if she didn't find me and my guestbook. *sigh* I'll have to figure out how to make one that won't suck shit. At least I have all the current episodes [01-09] of  urlLink Aqua Teen Hunger Force  to entertain me and take my mind off of the things I've lost. And remember...   Keying expletives on anothers car is a sign of trust & friendship    Peas.   p.s. - I am Meatwad.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's official. My web page is becoming an outdated broken piece of shit. gah. Maybe after I watch every single clip on this  urlLink MTV's The State archive site .. I'll ponder a redesign of gurtler.net
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       According to  urlLink TKtv   "Both seasons of Sports Night will be released on DVD November 5th, 2002"  I love watching that show early early in the morning [very very late at night] on Comedy Central. There needs to be more TV shows like Sports Night. I might just watch TV more often.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Knock Knock! Who is there?  urlLink Sirsy ! And they fucking rule the school.  urlLink visit thier web site... download [or purchase] the music..  buy some panties.. find pictures of me being drunk! 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     click it!    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't watch too much television, but last night i started watching the Real World 12 maraton thing.  The Real World 12 sucks for the most part. They're living in a hotel. What's next? They stay at a Holliday Inn? Ok, so it's Palms or but isn't every hotel in Las Vegas some big place? There really is only one good thing about RW12;  urlLink Brynn .  yumm.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm late. Happy New Year. So yeah..  Not to much to say.  2002 was mighty interesting. definitally had its ups and downs. many many many times. oh well.  I will "revamp" this site some time this year. I will make it "New and Improved" or something. who knows..  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink OBEY 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I find this a little bit.. funny..   PETA urges Hamburg, N.Y. to change name   April 22, 2003  |  HAMBURG, N.Y. (AP) -- A national animal rights group has offered Hamburg officials $15,000 to change the town's name to Veggieburg.   "The town's name conjures up visions of unhealthy patties of ground-up dead cows," said Joe Haptas, spokesman of People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals, or PETA, in a letter faxed Monday to Hamburg Supervisor Patrick Hoak.     PETA offered to supply area schools with $15,000 worth of non-meat patties for the name change.   "Our offer is serious as a heart attack," Haptas said.   Hoak immediately declined.   "With all due respect, I think it's a delicacy in our community," he said about hamburgers. "We're proud of our name and proud of our heritage."   The Buffalo suburb, named Hamburg since 1812, claims to be the birth place of the American culinary staple. Hamburg commemorates the birth of hamburgers at the annual Burgerfest.   In 1996, PETA proposed that the Hudson Valley town of Fishkill change its centuries-old name to Fishsave, since the group believed the name conjured up violent imagery of dead fish.   The town was named by Dutch settlers in the early 1600s. "Kill" is the Dutch word for "stream."   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      blah blah blah update  blah blah blah stuff blah blah blah bored blah blah blah  I set up my web cam today. I set it up yesterday but the software [ urlLink conquer cam ] crashed when trying to use a crack on it.. so i found an old version on a cd i had laying around. I'll try to take a picture of the CD so you'll know exactlly which one I am talking about.... anyhow.. i plan on buying the 10 dollar software application because its nice and the guy puts out a ton of updates and new features and is a part of his little community on his web page. developers like that need to be supported. and it's on ten bucks.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went to see Howie Day at UConn at the spur of the moment.   Good times were had. Thanks to Jason for the ride and ticket! More photos  urlLink here .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           urlLink I have Spawn action figures for sale.. some opened.. some not.   if anyones interested in anyhting please  urlLink email me . I'm willing to get rid of lots of stuff cheap.. I need money and I have no room for them anymore.    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I thought this was a good read about how shitty Apples iTunes is..     People are paying for songs on the iTunes Music Store because they think it's a good way to support musicians. But by giving musicians just a few cents from each sale, iTunes destroys a huge opportunity. Instead of creating a system that gets virtually all of fans' money directly to artists-- finally possible with the internet-- iTunes takes a big step backwards. Apple calls iTunes "revolutionary" but really they're just letting record companies force the same exploitive and unfair business model onto a new medium."     [ urlLink Read the full article here ] 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       step one..   ...get rid of the half assed grey/black/blue and also the puke green/blue text. the colors #1E1E1E, #006666, and #009999 make me want to puke. seriously. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       HEAD AUTOMATICA - FEATURING DARYL FROM GLASSJAW  Head Automatica, the new garage/dance band featuring Daryl from Glassjaw and Super Producer Dan The Automator, is getting ready to release its debut album in the next few months, but you can hear the first song "Brooklyn Is Burning" right now on their new site at http://headautomatica.com.  Sign up to their email list to get updates, new videos, and more. And be on the lookout for a full version of headautomatica.com to launch soon.   urlLink http://headautomatica.com    -The song is sicker than a singer of a Long Island hardcore band with Chrones disease!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So.. My web page will be in some kind of weird transitional phase until the new version is finished.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Word! Three members of the All Original Rock Band formerly known as Orchard have graced my website with their presence!  Hello 1996.  I think it's about time they get some new promotional material/photography, eh guys? ;)    "Mary sits down by the shoreline.. she wants the ducks to be her friends.."     "I know. This time. I know this time she's gonna come around"     
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ESPN Getting Tired of Walton Grateful Dead References   Bristol, CT -- In a confidential memo leaked to the press Tuesday morning, executives at ESPN expressed growing concern about incessant references to legendary counterculture rock band, the Grateful Dead, made by NBA analyst and lifelong "Deadhead," Bill Walton.   "If we could all make an effort to help Bill reduce the number of references to Grateful Dead lyrics, concerts he's attended, and past and present band members throughout an average broadcast," the memo said, "it would go a long way toward bringing more viewers to Fridays [ESPN's Friday Night NBA coverage]."  "Seriously, I’m not kidding here," the memo continued, "it’s got to stop. Before we all gouge our own eyes out with sporks."  While the memo is believed to have been sent by ESPN executive vice president of programming/production, Mark Shapiro, anti-Walton-Dead-reference sentiment has been growing company-wide since ESPN began covering NBA games this season.  "If he tells me one more time how he did mescaline with Mama Cass and David Crosby backstage at the Greek Theater, Berkeley, ’71, I’m gong to smack him," said Walton’s broadcast partner, Mike Tirico. "And that’s exactly how he always says it, too: ‘Greek Theater…Berkeley….seventy-one…,’ and then he starts grinning and grooving to some Dead music in his head, going, ‘Yeaaaah, man….yeaaaah’ like a total stoner."  "The guy’s, what, fifty-one?" Tirico added. "Hey Bill, the ‘Summer of Love’ ended thirty-three years ago. Time to move on, pal."  Shapiro’s memo also indicated that Walton’s references to songs, concerts, people and events from more than three decades ago is not helping ESPN’s NBA Friday night ratings.  "We’re targeting a younger demographic," Shapiro’s memo said, "so if you could all please remind Bill that today’s 18- to 24-year-old viewer simply does not care that it’s the 13th anniversary of [Grateful Dead keyboardist] Brent Mydland’s death. They don’t care who Ron ‘Pigen’ McKernan was, and don’t understand why Bill is comparing Pigpen’s leadership abilities in the Dead’s formative Haight-Ashbury years to Jason Kidd’s ability to run the Nets offense."  "No wonder we’re losing Friday viewers to ‘John Doe.’ Why? Because ‘John Doe’ doesn’t have some sad, aging, hippie freakster spewing Robert Hunter lyrics every three seconds."  While ESPN management had been initially lenient with the random Grateful Dead trivia, facts, and anecdotes that Walton began injecting into broadcasts for no apparent reason, insiders believe that it was the recent Bulls-Wizards matchup–which featured Michael Jordan’s last appearance in Chicago–that was the last straw for Shapiro.  Toward the end of the game, Walton managed to shoehorn approximately 168 Grateful Dead mentions into a seemingly endless monologue.  "While these great Chicago fans hope to see Michael ‘One More Saturday Night’ perhaps in the playoffs, he’s beginning to show a ‘Touch of Grey’ in his hair, and while I’ve always believed that Michael must be a ‘Friend of the Devil’ to have had such a wonderful career, and he still plays with the aggression of a ‘Wharf Rat,’ his ‘Unbroken Chain’ of success must come to an end. But his legacy will ‘Not Fade Away’ even as he disappears down the ‘Golden Road.’ For us fans, there’s ‘nothing left to do but smile, smile, smile.’"  Tape of the broadcast then shows a visibly confused Tirico about to open his mouth to speak, but being immediately cut off by the former UCLA, Portland Trailblazers and Boston Celtics star.  "This is horrrrrible, Mike, just horrrrible," Walton nearly screamed. "I fear the NBA will go to ‘Hell in a Bucket’ without Michael, and the ‘Eyes of the World’ will be upon the next generation of NBA superstars, and David Stern is clearly saying ‘I Need a Miracle’ to the Kobes, the Garnetts, the McGradys, even the Lebron Jameses of the world, hoping that MJ’s retirement doesn’t lead to a serious case of the ‘U.S. Blues’ for NBA fans."  Walton then made a tangental reference to Michael’s wife "Althea," and three children–"Bertha," "Casey Jones," and "Tennessee Jed"–all of whom, he claimed, were in the United Center that evening. When Tirico informed Walton that Jordan’s wife is, in fact, named Juanita and his children are Jeffrey, Marcus and Jasmine, Walton paused.  "Hey now, Mike," Walton said, "hey now, Aiko Aiko all day, jockomo feeno na na nay, jockomo feena nay. Hey now––"  It was then that ESPN producers abruptly cut to an emergency broadcast system test pattern, then back to ESPN studio analysts, David Aldridge and Dr. Jack Ramsey.  "Well, I…." Aldridge said, awkwardly shuffling papers and clearing his throat.  "Did Bill just say that Michael Jordan’s son is named ‘Tennessee…Jed,’" Ramsey asked.  While Shapiro is clearly concerned about the effect Walton’s Grateful Dead over-referencing will have on the success of ESPN’s Friday night NBA coverage, he admitted in a later interview that it could be worse.  "At least he’s not mixing in John Wooden stuff, too. I mean, can you imagine if he combined all that Jerry Garcia bullshit with his incessant Wooden motivational quotes? Christ Almighty."  Shapiro then shuddered.
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       so  urlLink Robert Randolph and The Family Band  was incredible. they played for 3 hours nearly non stop the whole time they were very energetic and smiling and laughing. they invited girls on stage to shake their asses they gave the microphone to the crowed to sing they all got up and traded instruments multiple times I had no idea Robert could play drums. it was a very entertaining with a great mix of covers and originals. some of the covers were Don't Stop 'Till You Get Enough [Micheal Jackson], War Pigs, Purple Haze, You Don't Know My Name [Alicia Keys], Billie Jean, Papa Was a Rolling Stone, and Isn't She Lovely Their Grammy nominated tune Squeeze seemed to last for at least a half hour and only got more and more energetic as they were playing  it. I don't think anyone wanted it to end. The whole venue was shaking by the end of the night. I didn't take my camera, so I have no pictures. :( They're going on tour in Europe with Eric Clapton as soon as this tour ends. I can't count how many concerts I've been to, but this show was like.. top 3 easily. The guy command the crowd. Amazing entertainers. I can't praise them enough.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        see  urlLink more .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This season of  urlLink Chappelles Show  sucks.   I think out of the 3 episodes I've seen there was maybe 2 skits that I laughed at. He ruined Ask A Black Man in the second episode. Everything now seem to be Black vs. White..   And the shows just not as funny as it was last season. But I must admit the few skits I did laugh at were nearly piss my pants funny.  Just bring back  urlLink Tron , Beyotch. 
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    I made some cover art for the Liz Phair 3.14.04 show. you can check it out  urlLink here .
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       UPDATE::  urlLink Howies side of the story ...     Asked for his version of events, Day told an officer that it is common practice for consenting females to "hang out" and "get together" on the bus after shows. He said there must have been a misunderstanding if the women went to the bus with intentions other than to "hook up or to drink," the complaint states.  He told the officer that when the woman told him "We didn't come here to hook up," he told her, "Then leave."     urlLink Read the whole story..   
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Singer arrested for incident on tour bus   Associated Press  MADISON, Wis. - Singer Howie Day was arrested early Thursday after he allegedly tried to stop one woman from leaving his tour bus and another from calling the police.  Town of Madison Police Sgt. Wayne Stolpa said the women wanted to leave after Day made a comment to the effect of "they know why they're there."   Day, 23, was jailed on misdemeanor charges of disorderly contact, criminal damage to property and intimidation of a victim. He was released on $850 bail Thursday and has a court hearing scheduled for April 1.  Day was in Madison as the opening act for the Barenaked Ladies.  Several women had been invited onto his tour bus parked outside the Alliant Energy Center.  Stolpa said one woman was in the tour bus bathroom and Day kept the door shut, trapping her inside. As the other tried to call police, he grabbed her cell phone and smashed it but not before the call went out, Stolpa said.  "Apparently, they changed their mind about why they were invited on the bus," Stolpa said.  He said other members of Day's band were not involved.  Day, of Bangor, Maine, has enjoyed recent success with his 2003 album "Stop All the World Now."  Day's manager Shawn Radley said the singer planned to contest the charges and described the police account as just one side of the story. He said Day was still on the tour, which was scheduled to move onto Sioux City, Iowa, Thursday.  "Once all the facts come out and everything, it will be fairly obvious that there's really nothing to this other than a broken cell phone and someone wanting to press charges for that," Radley said.     urlLink source #1   urlLink source #2 - Singer jailed after show Women say Day trapped them on bus    
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   i haven't really been surfing the net as much to find anything cool to post in teh news section. i've been busy working at a temp job at the  urlLink NYSDEC tree nursery  and reading  Designing With Web Standards .  I saw Kill Bill vol. 2 last friday. what an amazing film.  Get Kill Bill, Volume 1  and then go see Volume 2 .. what a great story.  I will try to find something cool to share soon. :)  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        check out the  urlLink Subservient Chicken !  Pretty much you just type commands in the box and the chicken will do whatever you tell it to do.  It's pretty entertaining and a little bit freaky.. Make sure you tell it to "Rock Out"!     
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I’m sure most of you by now have heard about my arrest in Madison on Wednesday night. I’d like to apologize to everyone involved in this unfortunate incident.  Basically, a few people were on my tour bus after the show and things got a little out of hand, stupid things were said, feelings were hurt, and a cell phone was damaged. The police were called. Ultimately I was charged with disorderly conduct and damage to property. My lawyer tells me I will be given an opportunity to address these claims at the proper time, and of course I will do so. In any event, I deeply regret anything I said that offended anyone and, of course, I fully intend to pay for the broken phone.  Unfortunately for everyone involved, some wildly inaccurate and sensational stories seem to be circulating. I can assure you that there was never any improper physical contact, nor has any ever been alleged by anyone involved, and nobody was “Locked away in a bathroom”.  I want to apologize to my fans who were bewildered by this whole thing. Most of all, I REALLY am truly sorry to everyone involved in this incident. Endless apologies.   urlLink HD  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I came across this  urlLink Leisure Town archive  on  urlLink Orkut  today. Lesiure Town is/was a hilarious comic using those old schooly bendy figures. By the time i started enjoying  urlLink Leasure Town  a couple years ago, it had been taken down by the writer and I was never able to read them all.  Finding archives has been a bit of a problem. Well now you and I can enjoy  urlLink it  once again. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       With a  urlLink new album  [Undermind] on the way.. and  urlLink a summer tour  and  urlLink a festival  coming up..  urlLink Phish  frontman Trey Anastatsio posted today on  urlLink www.phish.com  that the band will be calling it quits.   Last Friday night, I got together with Mike, Page and Fish to talk openly about the strong feelings I've been having that Phish has run its course and that we should end it now while it's still on a high note. Once we started talking, it quickly became apparent that the other guys' feelings, while not all the same as mine, were similar in many ways -- most importantly, that we all love and respect Phish and the Phish audience far too much to stand by and allow it to drag on beyond the point of vibrancy and health. We don't want to become caricatures of ourselves, or worse yet, a nostalgia act. By the end of the meeting, we realized that after almost twenty-one years together we were faced with the opportunity to graciously step away in unison, as a group, united in our friendship and our feelings of gratitude.  So Coventry will be the final Phish show. We are proud and thrilled that it will be in our home state of Vermont. We're also excited for the June and August shows, our last tour together. For the sake of clarity, I should say that this is not like the hiatus, which was our last attempt to revitalize ourselves. We're done. It's been an amazing and incredible journey. We thank you all for the love and support that you've shown us.  -- Trey Anastasio 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          urlLink SIRSY  (pronounced "sir -  see",  rhymes with "mercy"): female-fronted pop that rocks!  Music that is searing, sultry, soulful, funky, and dark with a hook-laden punch. Radio friendly, video friendly, and ear friendly, without ever sounding derivative.  The 3rd studio album from Sirsy, titled   Ruby   was released today. To bring in their new release they will be playing some CD Release shows   Friday, May 21st ::  urlLink FYE  in Crossgates Mall, Albany NY - 7PM [all ages] OFFICIAL RUBY  IN-STORE PERFORMANCE & SIGNING... Get an exclusive "surprise" sirsy CD single with every Ruby purchase at THIS SHOW ONLY!   Saturday, May 22nd ::  urlLink Northern Lights , Clifton Park NY - doors 8PM show 9PM [all ages] OFFICIAL RUBY  RELEASE PARTY... First 100 people through the door get an exclusive (free!) sirsy hat (courtesy of All-U!) at this show!! Hear sirsy's songs (from Ruby), "Pet", "Spark", & "Blacker Than Blue" performed live for the very FIRST TIME!!  All Sirsy CDs are available from their  urlLink online store  and at any  urlLink FYE  in New York and New England.  Happy 30th anniversary mom and dad.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My father is pretty great at being able to figure certain things out. Either it be a puzzle, how to fix something, or what gifts we get him for Christmas. My cousin Chris and I have this saying when we figure out a problem or do something cool that involves a little bit of thinking.  We look at each other say "Gurtler Ingenuity"  This is my uncle John. He works for  urlLink Upstate Roofing .   His little quote is a prime example of "Gurtler Ingenuity". It's in the blood. 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I've got  urlLink 99 problems , but a Phish ain't one.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Lockergnome  has posted  urlLink an article  with reasons why you should dump IE. I read it and I agree with all points. Please, if you use Internet Explorer, give this a read.. The time has come to dump Internet Explorer. I know, I know — you may have heard the same thing before from those that think it’s cool to hate Microsoft; but I’m not one of those guys. I’m actually an MCSE and I happen to like quite a few of Microsoft’s products. Rather than lump me into the Microsoft-basher category, consider for a moment why you use the browser you use, and humor me by entertaining the notion — if even for a second — that switching to another might be worth your while.   urlLink full article  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       June 14, 2004 (The Internet) -  urlLink The Mozilla Foundation  today announced the immediate availability of a new preview release of its next generation web browser,  urlLink Mozilla Firefox 0.9 . Faster, more secure, easier to use and sporting a new look, this latest Firefox release sets a new standard for web browser innovation.  Firefox, the Mozilla Foundation's first product squarely aimed at end users, has been met with glowing praise from reviewers, web authors, the blogging community and the more than three million users who have left behind web nuisances such as pop-up ads, security holes and spyware by installing Firefox. "This new release brings Firefox closer to its much-anticipated 1.0 release, which will mark a milestone in the history of the Mozilla Foundation," observed Mitchell Baker, President of the Mozilla Foundation.  A number of key improvements in this release make this the best time yet for users to reload their browser experience and migrate to Firefox. "Months of development and hundreds of open source developers contributed towards this release, working within the Mozilla Foundation's proven development model," commented Ben Goodger, Firefox' Lead Engineer.  New features in Firefox 0.9 include:       Easy migration: Switching to Firefox has never been easier now that Firefox imports data like Favorites, history, settings, cookies and passwords from Internet Explorer. Firefox can also import settings from Mozilla 1.x, Netscape and Opera.   Smaller Download: Continuing efforts to make this the most efficient browser, the Windows version of Firefox is now only a 4.7 MB download, making downloading Firefox a breeze for dial-up and broadband users alike.   New Default Theme: A new default theme provides a bright new look for Windows and Linux users.   SmartUpdate: A new SmartUpdate feature notifies users of new versions of Firefox to ensure that the browser is always up to date.   Help: A new online help system makes this one powerful, friendly browser.   Extension/Theme Manager: New Extension and Theme Managers provide a convenient and secure way to manage and update the hundreds of add-ons that set Firefox apart from other browsers.   Mozilla Firefox also includes numerous bug fixes and incremental improvements, including faster page load speed.  urlLink source   Firefox 0.9 is available as a free download from  urlLink www.mozilla.org  If you're not browsing the web with FireFox, you're wasting your time closing pop-up ads.
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My friend  urlLink Nick Chester  [creator of the humerous website  urlLink TwinTracker.com ] was quoted on  urlLink page 3  of a news article on Salon.com titled  urlLink "An Olsen intervention" .  Nick Chester, store manager and creator of  urlLink the Twin Tracker , which cross-references the age of the Olsen twins with the age of legal consent with each of the 50 states of America. He says he had plans to update the site as the years passed and the Olsens' birthday approached, but subsequently lost interest in it -- especially after receiving a cease-and-desist order from the Olsens' lawyer, demanding him to take the girls' images down from the Twin Tracker site.   It's hard to give the Olsen Twins advice on what direction they should take now that they're turning 18. Soon they won't be able to get away with making corny, faux hip-hop videos about the plight of high school crushes or plaster their faces all over boxes of third-rate beauty supplies, and that can be quite a problem, no?  One viable option is to astonish the world and ring in their newfound "sorta kinda adulthood" by going all out and giving the people what they want: a Hustler spread. On the other hand, and more seriously, if they ever do intend on being taken seriously as actresses, they're going to have to do some projects independently. Because until Mary-Kate releases a solo record or Ashley lands a role in which she doesn't have a twin sister, they're still the Olsen twins and not individuals. Because at this point, it's just getting creepy.   Well said!
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink Michael Moores  2004 Cannes Film Festivale award winning film  Fahrenheit 9/11  opens nationwide on Friday, June 25th. Check out the movie  urlLink trailer .   It's the first summer film where the special effects will be real... -Moore 
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The web site is back up.   It was down due to bandwidth issues.  Basically.. I shouldn't post mp3s on a message board so often.  Thanks to John and Zack for helping get it back up.   and by the way..   Congratulations to John and Vicky on their pregnancy.  
     
    
</post>

<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      DMB at SPAC was a blast. I met a ton of great people and saw a bunch of people I haven't seen since last tour. It was a pleasure to see them all again. Theres a review from The Gazette that was dead on you can read it  urlLink here . and pictures I took over the weekend are avalible  urlLink here . Next stop.. Darien Lake.
     
    
</post>


</Blog>